-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O walking/O through/O the/O crypts/O beneath/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O as/O he/O had/O walked/O a/O thousand/O times/O before/O ./O 
The/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O watched/O him/O pass/O with/O eyes/O of/O ice/O ,/O and/O the/O direwolves/O at/O their/O feet/O turned/O their/O great/O stone/O heads/O and/O snarled/O ./O 
Last/O of/O all/O ,/O he/O came/O to/O the/O tomb/O where/O his/O father/O slept/O ,/O with/O Brandon/PERSON and/O Lyanna/PERSON beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Lyanna/PERSON 's/O statue/O whispered/O ./O 
She/O wore/O a/O garland/O of/O pale/O blue/O roses/O ,/O and/O her/O eyes/O wept/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O jerked/O upright/O ,/O his/O heart/O racing/O ,/O the/O blankets/O tangled/O around/O him/O ./O 
The/O room/O was/O black/O as/O pitch/O ,/O and/O someone/O was/O hammering/O on/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O called/O loudly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Groggy/O and/O naked/O ,/O he/O stumbled/O his/O way/O across/O the/O darkened/O chamber/O ./O 
When/O he/O opened/O the/O door/O ,/O he/O found/O Tomard/PERSON with/O an/O upraised/O fist/O ,/O and/O Cayn/PERSON with/O a/O taper/O in/O hand/O ./O 
Between/O them/O stood/O the/O king/O 's/O own/O steward/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O man/O 's/O face/O might/O have/O been/O carved/O of/O stone/O ,/O so/O little/O did/O it/O show/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O Hand/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O intoned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O Grace/O the/O King/O commands/O your/O presence/O ./O 
At/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O So/O Robert/PERSON had/O returned/O from/O his/O hunt/O ./O 
It/O was/O long/O past/O time/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O need/O a/O few/O moments/O to/O dress/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON left/O the/O man/O waiting/O without/O ./O 
Cayn/PERSON helped/O him/O with/O his/O clothes/O ;/O white/O linen/O tunic/O and/O grey/O cloak/O ,/O trousers/O cut/O open/O down/O his/O plaster-sheathed/O leg/O ,/O his/O badge/O of/O office/O ,/O and/O last/O of/O all/O a/O belt/O of/O heavy/O silver/O links/O ./O 
He/O sheathed/O the/O Valyrian/O dagger/O at/O his/O waist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Red/O Keep/O was/O dark/O and/O still/O as/O Cayn/PERSON and/O Tomard/PERSON escorted/O him/O across/O the/O inner/O bailey/O ./O 
The/O moon/O hung/O low/O over/O the/O walls/O ,/O ripening/O toward/O full/O ./O 
On/O the/O ramparts/O ,/O a/O guardsman/O in/O a/O gold/O cloak/O walked/O his/O rounds/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O royal/O apartments/O were/O in/O Maegor/LOCATION 's/O Holdfast/LOCATION ,/O a/O massive/O square/O fortress/O that/O nestled/O in/O the/O heart/O of/O the/O Red/O Keep/O behind/O walls/O twelve/O feet/O thick/O and/O a/O dry/O moat/O lined/O with/O iron/O spikes/O ,/O a/O castle-within-acastle/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON Blount/PERSON guarded/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O bridge/O ,/O white/O steel/O armor/O ghostly/O in/O the/O moonlight/O ./O 
Within/O ,/O Ned/PERSON passed/O two/O other/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Preston/PERSON Greenfield/PERSON stood/O at/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O steps/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON waited/O at/O the/O door/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O bedchamber/O ./O 
Three/O men/O in/O white/O cloaks/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O remembering/O ,/O and/O a/O strange/O chill/O went/O through/O him/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON '/O s/O face/O was/O as/O pale/O as/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O only/O to/O look/O at/O him/O to/O know/O that/O something/O was/O dreadfully/O wrong/O ./O 
The/O royal/O steward/O opened/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bring/O him/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON 's/O voice/O called/O ,/O strangely/O thick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Fires/O blazed/O in/O the/O twin/O hearths/O at/O either/O end/O of/O the/O bedchamber/O ,/O filling/O the/O room/O with/O a/O sullen/O red/O glare/O ./O 
The/O heat/O within/O was/O suffocating/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON lay/O across/O the/O canopied/O bed/O ./O 
At/O the/O bedside/O hovered/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O ,/O while/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON paced/O restlessly/O before/O the/O shuttered/O windows/O ./O 
Servants/O moved/O back/O and/O forth/O ,/O feeding/O logs/O to/O the/O fire/O and/O boiling/O wine/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON sat/O on/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O bed/O beside/O her/O husband/O ./O 
Her/O hair/O was/O tousled/O ,/O as/O if/O from/O sleep/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O nothing/O sleepy/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
They/O followed/O Ned/PERSON as/O Tomard/PERSON and/O Cayn/PERSON helped/O him/O cross/O the/O room/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O move/O very/O slowly/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O were/O still/O dreaming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O king/O still/O wore/O his/O boots/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON could/O see/O dried/O mud/O and/O blades/O of/O grass/O clinging/O to/O the/O leather/O where/O Robert/PERSON 's/O feet/O stuck/O out/O beneath/O the/O blanket/O that/O covered/O him/O ,/O A/O green/O doublet/O lay/O ''/O ,/O ``/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O slashed/O open/O and/O discarded/O ,/O the/O cloth/O crusted/O with/O red-brown/O stains/O ./O 
The/O room/O smelled/O of/O smoke/O and/O blood/O and/O death/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ned/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O whispered/O when/O he/O saw/O him/O ./O 
His/O face/O was/O pale/O as/O milk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O .../O closer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O men/O brought/O him/O close/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON steadied/O himself/O with/O a/O hand/O on/O the/O bedpost/O ./O 
He/O had/O only/O to/O look/O down/O at/O Robert/PERSON to/O know/O how/O bad/O it/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O .../O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O began/O ,/O his/O throat/O clenched/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O boar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON was/O still/O in/O his/O hunting/O greens/O ,/O his/O cloak/O spattered/O with/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O devil/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O husked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O own/O fault/O ./O 
Too/O much/O wine/O ,/O damn/O me/O to/O hell/O ./O 
Missed/O my/O thrust/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O where/O were/O the/O rest/O of/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON demanded/O of/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O was/O Ser/O Barristan/O and/O the/O Kingsguard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Renly/O 's/O mouth/O twitched/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O commanded/O us/O to/O stand/O aside/O and/O let/O him/O take/O the/O boar/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O lifted/O the/O blanket/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O done/O what/O they/O could/O to/O close/O him/O up/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O nowhere/O near/O enough/O ./O 
The/O boar/O must/O have/O been/O a/O fearsome/O thing/O ./O 
It/O had/O ripped/O the/O king/O from/O groin/O to/O nipple/O with/O its/O tusks/O ./O 
The/O wine/O -/O soaked/O bandages/O that/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION Pycelle/LOCATION had/O applied/O were/O already/O black/O with/O blood/O ,/O and/O the/O smell/O off/O the/O wound/O was/O hideous/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON 's/O stomach/O turned/O ./O 
He/O let/O the/O blanket/O fall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stinks/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stink/O of/O death/O ,/O do/O n't/O think/O I/O ca/O n't/O smell/O it/O ./O 
Bastard/O did/O me/O good/O ,/O eh/O ?/O 
But/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O paid/O him/O back/O in/O kind/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O 's/O smile/O was/O as/O terrible/O as/O his/O wound/O ,/O his/O teeth/O red/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drove/O a/O knife/O right/O through/O his/O eye/O ./O 
Ask/O them/O if/O I/O did/O n't/O ./O 
Ask/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Truly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON murmured/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O brought/O the/O carcass/O back/O with/O us/O ,/O at/O my/O brother/O 's/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O the/O feast/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O leave/O us/O ./O 
The/O lot/O of/O you/O ./O 
I/O need/O to/O speak/O with/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON ,/O my/O sweet/O lord/O Cersei/PERSON began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O said/O leave/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON insisted/O with/O a/O hint/O of/O his/O old/O fierceness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O part/O of/O that/O do/O n't/O you/O understand/O ,/O woman/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON gathered/O up/O her/O skirts/O and/O her/O dignity/O and/O led/O the/O way/O to/O the/O door/O ./O 
Lord/O Renly/PERSON and/O the/O others/O followed/O ./O 
Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON lingered/O ,/O his/O hands/O shaking/O as/O he/O offered/O the/O king/O a/O cup/O of/O thick/O white/O liquid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ./O 
For/O your/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON knocked/O the/O cup/O away/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Away/O with/O you/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O sleep/O soon/O enough/O ,/O old/O fool/O ./O 
Get/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O gave/O Ned/PERSON a/O stricken/O look/O as/O he/O shuffled/O from/O the/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Damn/O you/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O when/O they/O were/O alone/O ./O 
His/O leg/O was/O throbbing/O so/O badly/O he/O was/O almost/O blind/O with/O pain/O ./O 
Or/O perhaps/O it/O was/O grief/O that/O fogged/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O lowered/O himself/O to/O the/O bed/O ,/O beside/O his/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O do/O you/O always/O have/O to/O be/O so/O headstrong/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O fuck/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O hoarsely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O killed/O the/O bastard/O ,/O did/O n't/O I/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O A/O lock/O of/O matted/O black/O hair/O fell/O across/O his/O eyes/O as/O he/O glared/O up/O at/O Ned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ought/O to/O do/O the/O same/O for/O you/O ./O 
Ca/O n't/O leave/O a/O man/O to/O hunt/O in/O peace/O ./O 
Ser/O Robar/O found/O me/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON 's/O head/O ./O 
Ugly/O thought/O ./O 
Never/O told/O the/O Hound/O ./O 
Let/O Cersei/PERSON surprise/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O laugh/O turned/O into/O a/O grunt/O as/O a/O spasm/O of/O pain/O hit/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O ,/O swallowing/O his/O agony/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O girl/O ./O 
Daenerys/O ./O 
Only/O a/O child/O ,/O you/O were/O ''/O ,/O ``/O right/O .../O that/O 's/O why/O ,/O the/O girl/O .../O the/O gods/O sent/O the/O boar/O .../O sent/O to/O punish/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O The/O king/O coughed/O ,/O bringing/O up/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wrong/O ,/O it/O was/O wrong/O ,/O I./O ./O 
./O 
only/O a/O girl/O .../O Varys/O ,/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O even/O my/O brother/O .../O worthless/O .../O no/O one/O to/O tell/O me/O no/O but/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON .../O only/O you/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O lifted/O his/O hand/O ,/O the/O gesture/O pained/O and/O feeble/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Paper/O and/O ink/O ./O 
There/O ,/O on/O the/O table/O ./O 
Write/O what/O I/O tell/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON smoothed/O the/O paper/O out/O across/O his/O knee/O and/O took/O up/O the/O quill/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O your/O command/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O will/O and/O word/O of/O Robert/PERSON of/O House/O Baratheon/O ,/O the/O First/O of/O his/O Name/O ,/O King/O of/O the/O Andals/O and/O all/O the/O rest-put/O in/O the/O damn/O titles/O ,/O you/O know/O how/O it/O goes/O ./O 
I/O do/O hereby/O command/O Eddard/O of/O House/O Stark/O ,/O Lord/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Winterfell/ORGANIZATION and/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O to/O serve/O as/O Lord/O Regent/O and/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O upon/O my/O .../O upon/O my/O death/O .../O to/O rule/O in/O my/O .../O in/O my/O stead/O ,/O until/O my/O son/O Joffrey/PERSON does/O come/O of/O age/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON is/O not/O your/O son/O ,/O he/O wanted/O to/O say/O ,/O but/O the/O words/O would/O not/O come/O ./O 
The/O agony/O was/O written/O too/O plainly/O across/O Robert/PERSON 's/O face/O ;/O he/O could/O not/O hurt/O him/O more/O ./O 
So/O Ned/PERSON bent/O his/O head/O and/O wrote/O ,/O but/O where/O the/O king/O had/O said/O \/O ``/O my/O son/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O scrawled/O \/O ``/O my/O heir/O \/O ''/O instead/O ./O 
The/O deceit/O made/O him/O feel/O soiled/O ./O 
The/O lies/O we/O tellfor/O love/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
May/O the/O gods/O forgive/O me/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O else/O would/O you/O have/O me/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Say/O .../O whatever/O you/O need/O to/O ./O 
Protect/O and/O defend/O ,/O gods/O old/O and/O new/O ,/O you/O have/O the/O words/O ./O 
Write/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O sign/O it/O ./O 
You/O give/O it/O to/O the/O council/O when/O I/O 'm/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O in/O a/O voice/O thick/O with/O grief/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O must/O not/O do/O this/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O die/O on/O me/O ./O 
The/O realm/O needs/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON took/O his/O hand/O ,/O fingers/O squeezing/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O .../O such/O a/O bad/O liar/O ,/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O through/O his/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O realm/O .../O the/O realm/O knows/O .../O what/O a/O wretched/O king/O I/O 've/O been/O ./O 
Bad/O as/O Aerys/O ,/O the/O gods/O spare/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O his/O dying/O friend/O ,/O \/O ``/O not/O so/O bad/O as/O Aerys/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
Not/O near/O so/O bad/O as/O Aerys/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON managed/O a/O weak/O red/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O the/O least/O ,/O they/O will/O say/O .../O this/O last/O thing/O .../O this/O I/O did/O right/O ./O 
You/O wo/O n't/O fail/O me/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O rule/O now/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O hate/O it/O ,/O worse/O than/O I/O did/O .../O but/O you/O 'll/O do/O well/O ./O 
Are/O you/O done/O with/O the/O scribbling/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON offered/O Robert/PERSON the/O paper/O ./O 
The/O king/O scrawled/O his/O signature/O blindly/O ,/O leaving/O a/O smear/O of/O blood/O across/O the/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O seal/O should/O be/O witnessed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Serve/O the/O boar/O at/O my/O funeral/O feast/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON rasped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Apple/ORGANIZATION in/O its/O mouth/O ,/O skin/O seared/O crisp/O ./O 
Eat/O the/O bastard/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O care/O if/O you/O choke/O on/O him/O ./O 
Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O Lyanna/PERSON 's/O voice/O echoed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Daenerys/O ./O 
Let/O her/O live/O ./O 
If/O you/O can/O ,/O if/O it/O .../O not/O too/O late/O .../O talk/O to/O them/O .../O Varys/O ,/O Littlefinger/PERSON .../O do/O n't/O let/O them/O kill/O her/O ./O 
And/O help/O my/O son/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Make/O him/O be/O .../O better/O than/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O winced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O will/O ,/O my/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O closed/O his/O eyes/O and/O seemed/O to/O relax/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Killed/O by/O a/O pig/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ought/O to/O laugh/O ,/O but/O it/O hurts/O too/O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O was/O not/O laughing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shall/O I/O call/O them/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON gave/O a/O weak/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ./O 
Gods/O ,/O why/O is/O it/O so/O cold/O in/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O servants/O rushed/O back/O in/O and/O hurried/O to/O feed/O the/O fires/O ./O 
The/O queen/O had/O gone/O ;/O that/O was/O some/O small/O relief/O ,/O at/O least/O ./O 
If/O she/O had/O any/O sense/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON would/O take/O her/O children/O and/O fly/O before/O the/O break/O of/O day/O ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O ./O 
She/O had/O lingered/O too/O long/O already/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O King/O Robert/PERSON did/O not/O seem/O to/O miss/O her/O ./O 
He/O bid/O his/O brother/O Renly/PERSON and/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION Pycelle/LOCATION to/O stand/O in/O witness/O as/O he/O pressed/O his/O seal/O into/O the/O hot/O yellow/O wax/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O dripped/O upon/O his/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O give/O me/O something/O for/O the/O pain/O and/O let/O me/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Hurriedly/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O mixed/O him/O another/O draught/O of/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ./O 
This/O time/O the/O king/O drank/O deeply/O ./O 
His/O black/O beard/O was/O beaded/O with/O thick/O white/O droplets/O when/O he/O threw/O the/O empty/O cup/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O I/O dream/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON gave/O him/O his/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O give/O Lyanna/PERSON your/O love/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Take/O care/O of/O my/O children/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O words/O twisted/O in/O Ned/PERSON 's/O belly/O like/O a/O knife/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O he/O was/O at/O a/O loss/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O bring/O himself/O to/O lie/O ./O 
Then/O he/O remembered/O the/O bastards/O :/O little/O Barra/PERSON at/O her/O mother/O 's/O breast/O ,/O Mya/PERSON in/O the/O Vale/LOCATION ,/O Gendry/PERSON at/O his/O forge/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O .../O guard/O your/O children/O as/O if/O they/O were/O my/O own/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O slowly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON nodded/O and/O closed/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON watched/O his/O old/O friend/O sag/O softly/O into/O the/O pillows/O as/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O washed/O the/O pain/O from/O his/O face/O ./O 
Sleep/O took/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Heavy/O chains/O jangled/O softly/O as/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O came/O up/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O do/O all/O in/O my/O power/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O the/O wound/O has/O mortified/O ./O 
It/O took/O them/O two/O days/O to/O get/O him/O back/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O I/O saw/O him/O ,/O it/O was/O too/O late/O ./O 
I/O can/O lessen/O His/O Grace/O 's/O suffering/O ,/O but/O only/O the/O gods/O can/O heal/O him/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O long/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O By/O rights/O ,/O he/O should/O be/O dead/O already/O ./O 
I/O have/O never/O seen/O a/O man/O cling/O to/O life/O so/O fiercely/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O was/O always/O strong/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O wise/O ,/O perhaps/O ,/O but/O strong/O ./O 
\/O ''/O In/O the/O sweltering/O heat/O of/O the/O bedchamber/O ,/O his/O brow/O was/O slick/O with/O sweat/O ./O 
He/O might/O have/O been/O Robert/PERSON 's/O ghost/O as/O he/O stood/O there/O ,/O young/O and/O dark/O and/O handsome/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O slew/O the/O boar/O ./O 
His/O entrails/O were/O sliding/O from/O his/O belly/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O he/O slew/O the/O boar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O was/O full/O of/O wonder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON was/O never/O a/O man/O to/O leave/O the/O battleground/O so/O long/O as/O a/O foe/O remained/O standing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O the/O door/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON still/O guarded/O the/O tower/O stairs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON has/O given/O Robert/PERSON the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O that/O no/O one/O disturbs/O his/O rest/O without/O leave/O from/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O shall/O be/O as/O you/O command/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON seemed/O old/O beyond/O his/O years/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O failed/O my/O sacred/O trust/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Even/O the/O truest/O knight/O can/O not/O protect/O a/O king/O against/O himself/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON loved/O to/O hunt/O boar/O ./O 
I/O have/O seen/O him/O take/O a/O thousand/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O would/O stand/O his/O ground/O without/O flinching/O ,/O his/O legs/O braced/O ,/O the/O great/O spear/O in/O his/O hands/O ,/O and/O as/O often/O as/O not/O he/O would/O curse/O the/O boar/O as/O it/O charged/O ,/O and/O wait/O until/O the/O last/O possible/O second/O ,/O until/O it/O was/O almost/O on/O him/O ,/O before/O he/O killed/O it/O with/O a/O single/O sure/O and/O savage/O thrust/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O could/O know/O this/O one/O would/O be/O his/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O kind/O to/O say/O so/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O himself/O said/O as/O much/O ./O 
He/O blamed/O the/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O white-haired/O knight/O gave/O a/O weary/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O Grace/PERSON was/O reeling/O in/O his/O saddle/O by/O the/O time/O we/O flushed/O the/O boar/O from/O his/O lair/O ,/O yet/O he/O commanded/O us/O all/O to/O stand/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wonder/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O asked/O Varys/PERSON ,/O so/O quietly/O ,/O \/O ``/O who/O gave/O the/O king/O this/O wine/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O not/O heard/O the/O eunuch/O approach/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O looked/O around/O ,/O there/O he/O stood/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O black/O velvet/O robe/O that/O brushed/O the/O floor/O ,/O and/O his/O face/O was/O freshly/O powdered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O wine/O was/O from/O the/O king/O 's/O own/O skin/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O one/O skin/O ?/O 
Hunting/O is/O such/O thirsty/O work/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O not/O keep/O count/O ./O 
More/O than/O one/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
His/O squire/O would/O fetch/O him/O a/O fresh/O skin/O whenever/O he/O required/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Such/O a/O dutiful/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O to/O make/O certain/O His/O Grace/O did/O not/O lack/O for/O refreshment/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O a/O bitter/O taste/O in/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
He/O recalled/O the/O two/O fair-haired/O boys/O Robert/PERSON had/O sent/O chasing/O after/O a/O breastplate/O stretcher/O ./O 
The/O king/O had/O told/O everyone/O the/O tale/O that/O night/O at/O the/O feast/O ,/O laughing/O until/O he/O shook/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Which/O squire/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O elder/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Lancel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O the/O lad/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O stalwart/O boy/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O nephew/O to/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON and/O cousin/O to/O the/O queen/O ./O 
I/O hope/O the/O dear/O sweet/O lad/O does/O not/O blame/O himself/O ./O 
Children/O are/O so/O vulnerable/O in/O the/O innocence/O of/O their/O youth/O ,/O how/O well/O do/O I/O remember/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Certainly/O Varys/O had/O once/O been/O young/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON doubted/O that/O he/O had/O ever/O been/O innocent/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O mention/O children/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON had/O a/O change/O of/O heart/O concerning/O Daenerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
Whatever/O arrangements/O you/O made/O ,/O I/O want/O unmade/O ./O 
At/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Alas/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O once/O may/O be/O too/O late/O ./O 
I/O fear/O those/O birds/O have/O flown/O ./O 
But/O I/O shall/O do/O what/O I/O can/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
With/O your/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O bowed/O and/O vanished/O down/O the/O steps/O ,/O his/O soft-soled/O slippers/O whispering/O against/O the/O stone/O as/O he/O made/O his/O descent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cayn/O and/O Tomard/O were/O helping/O Ned/PERSON across/O the/O bridge/O when/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON emerged/O from/O Maegor/LOCATION 's/O Holdfast/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O after/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O a/O moment/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON stopped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Renly/O walked/O to/O his/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O your/O men/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O met/O in/O the/O center/O of/O the/O bridge/O ,/O the/O dry/O moat/O beneath/O them/O ./O 
Moonlight/O silvered/O the/O cruel/O edges/O of/O the/O spikes/O that/O lined/O its/O bed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON gestured/O ./O 
Tomard/PERSON and/O Cayn/PERSON bowed/O their/O heads/O and/O backed/O away/O respectfully/O ./O 
Lord/O Renly/PERSON glanced/O warily/O at/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON on/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O span/O ,/O at/O Ser/LOCATION Preston/LOCATION in/O the/O doorway/O behind/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Was/O it/O the/O regency/O ?/O 
Has/O my/O brother/O named/O you/O Protector/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O did/O not/O wait/O for/O a/O reply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O I/O have/O thirty/O men/O in/O my/O personal/O guard/O ,/O and/O other/O friends/O beside/O ,/O knights/O and/O lords/O ./O 
Give/O me/O an/O hour/O ,/O and/O I/O can/O put/O a/O hundred/O swords/O in/O your/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O should/O I/O do/O with/O a/O hundred/O swords/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Strike/O !/O 
Now/O ,/O while/O the/O castle/O sleeps/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Renly/O looked/O back/O at/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON again/O and/O dropped/O his/O voice/O to/O an/O urgent/O whisper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O get/O Joffrey/PERSON away/O from/O his/O mother/O and/O take/O him/O in/O hand/O ./O 
Protector/O or/O no/O ,/O the/O man/O who/O holds/O the/O king/O holds/O the/O kingdom/O ./O 
We/O should/O seize/O Myrcella/PERSON and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tommen/O as/O well/O ./O 
Once/O we/O have/O her/O children/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON will/O not/O dare/O oppose/O us/O ./O 
The/O council/O will/O confirm/O you/O as/O Lord/O Protector/O and/O make/O Joffrey/PERSON your/O ward/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O regarded/O him/O coldly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON is/O not/O dead/O yet/O ./O 
The/O gods/O may/O spare/O him/O ./O 
If/O not/O ,/O I/O shall/O convene/O the/O council/O to/O hear/O his/O final/O words/O and/O consider/O the/O matter/O of/O the/O succession/O ,/O but/O I/O will/O not/O dishonor/O his/O last/O hours/O on/O earth/O by/O shedding/O blood/O in/O his/O halls/O and/O dragging/O frightened/O children/O from/O their/O beds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON took/O a/O step/O back/O ,/O taut/O as/O a/O bowstring/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Every/O moment/O you/O delay/O gives/O Cersei/PERSON another/O moment/O to/O prepare/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O Robert/PERSON dies/O ,/O it/O may/O be/O too/O late/O .../O for/O both/O of/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O we/O should/O pray/O that/O Robert/PERSON does/O not/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Small/O chance/O of/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Renly/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sometimes/O the/O gods/O are/O merciful/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O are/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON turned/O away/O and/O went/O back/O across/O the/O moat/O ,/O to/O the/O tower/O where/O his/O brother/O lay/O dying/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O Ned/PERSON returned/O to/O his/O chambers/O ,/O he/O felt/O weary/O and/O heartsick/O ,/O yet/O there/O was/O no/O question/O of/O his/O going/O back/O to/O sleep/O ,/O not/O now/O ./O 
When/O you/O play/O the/O game/O of/O thrones/O ,/O you/O win/O or/O you/O die/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O told/O him/O in/O the/O godswood/O ./O 
He/O found/O himself/O wondering/O if/O he/O had/O done/O the/O right/O thing/O by/O refusing/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON '/O s/O offer/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O taste/O for/O these/O intrigues/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O no/O honor/O in/O threatening/O children/O ,/O and/O yet/O .../O if/O Cersei/PERSON elected/O to/O fight/O rather/O than/O flee/O ,/O he/O might/O well/O have/O need/O of/O Renly/O '/O s/O hundred/O swords/O ,/O and/O more/O besides/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O Cayn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O he/O 's/O not/O in/O his/O chambers/O ,/O take/O as/O many/O men/O as/O you/O need/O and/O search/O every/O winesink/O and/O whorehouse/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O until/O you/O find/O him/O ./O 
Bring/O him/O to/O me/O before/O break/O of/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Cayn/PERSON bowed/O and/O took/O his/O leave/O ,/O and/O Ned/PERSON turned/O to/O Tomard/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Wind/O Witch/O sails/O on/O the/O evening/O tide/O ./O 
Have/O you/O chosen/O the/O escort/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ten/O men/O ,/O with/O Porther/O in/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Twenty/O ,/O and/O you/O will/O command/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
Porther/PERSON was/O a/O brave/O man/O ,/O but/O headstrong/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O someone/O more/O solid/O and/O sensible/O to/O keep/O watch/O over/O his/O daughters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tom/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ca/O n't/O say/O I/O 'll/O be/O sad/O to/O see/O the/O back/O of/O this/O place/O ./O 
I/O miss/O the/O wife/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O pass/O near/O Dragonstone/LOCATION when/O you/O turn/O north/O ./O 
I/O need/O you/O to/O deliver/O a/O letter/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tom/PERSON looked/O apprehensive/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O Dragonstone/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O island/O fortress/O of/O House/O Targaryen/PERSON had/O a/O sinister/O repute/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O Captain/O Qos/PERSON to/O hoist/O my/O banner/O as/O soon/O as/O he/O comes/O in/O sight/O of/O the/O island/O ./O 
They/O may/O be/O wary/O of/O unexpected/O visitors/O ./O 
If/O he/O is/O reluctant/O ,/O offer/O him/O whatever/O it/O takes/O ./O 
I/O will/O give/O you/O a/O letter/O to/O place/O into/O the/O hand/O of/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ./O 
No/O one/O else/O ./O 
Not/O his/O steward/O ,/O nor/O the/O captain/O of/O his/O guard/O ,/O nor/O his/O lady/O wife/O ,/O but/O only/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON himself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O Tomard/PERSON had/O left/O him/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON sat/O staring/O at/O the/O flame/O of/O the/O candle/O that/O burned/O beside/O him/O on/O the/O table/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O his/O grief/O overwhelmed/O him/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O nothing/O so/O much/O as/O to/O seek/O out/O the/O godswood/O ,/O to/O kneel/O before/O the/O heart/O tree/O and/O pray/O for/O the/O life/O of/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O been/O more/O than/O a/O brother/O to/O him/O ./O 
Men/O would/O whisper/O afterward/O that/O Eddard/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Stark/O had/O betrayed/O his/O king/O 's/O friendship/O and/O disinherited/O his/O sons/O ;/O he/O could/O only/O hope/O that/O the/O gods/O would/O know/O better/O ,/O and/O that/O Robert/PERSON would/O learn/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O in/O the/O land/O beyond/O the/O grave/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON took/O out/O the/O king/O 's/O last/O letter/O ./O 
A/O roll/O of/O crisp/O white/O parchment/O sealed/O with/O golden/O wax/O ,/O a/O few/O short/O words/O and/O a/O smear/O of/O blood/O ./O 
How/O small/O the/O difference/O between/O victory/O and/O defeat/O ,/O between/O life/O and/O death/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O drew/O out/O a/O fresh/O sheet/O of/O paper/O and/O dipped/O his/O quill/O in/O the/O inkpot/O ./O 
To/O His/O Grace/O ,/O Stannis/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON House/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O he/O wrote/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O you/O receive/O this/O letter/O ,/O your/O brother/O Robert/PERSON ,/O our/O King/O these/O past/O fifteen/O years/O ,/O will/O be/O dead/O ./O 
He/O was/O savaged/O by/O a/O boar/O whilst/O hunting/O in/O the/O kingswood/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O letters/O seemed/O to/O writhe/O and/O twist/O on/O the/O paper/O as/O his/O hand/O trailed/O to/O a/O stop/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON were/O not/O men/O to/O suffer/O disgrace/O meekly/O ;/O they/O would/O fight/O rather/O than/O flee/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON was/O wary/O ,/O after/O the/O murder/O of/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O but/O it/O was/O imperative/O that/O he/O sail/O for/O King/O 's/O Landing/O at/O once/O with/O all/O his/O power/O ,/O before/O the/O Lannisters/O could/O march/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O chose/O each/O word/O with/O care/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O done/O ,/O he/O signed/O the/O letter/O Eddard/O Stark/O ,/O Lord/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Winterfell/ORGANIZATION ,/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O and/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O ,/O blotted/O the/O paper/O ,/O folded/O it/O twice/O ,/O and/O melted/O the/O sealing/O wax/O over/O the/O candle/O flame/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O regency/O would/O be/O a/O short/O one/O ,/O he/O reflected/O as/O the/O wax/O softened/O ./O 
The/O new/O king/O would/O choose/O his/O own/O Hand/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON would/O be/O free/O to/O go/O home/O ./O 
The/O thought/O of/O Winterfell/O brought/O a/O wan/O smile/O to/O his/O face/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O hear/O Bran/O 's/O laughter/O once/O more/O ,/O to/O go/O hawking/O with/O Robb/PERSON ,/O to/O watch/O Rickon/PERSON at/O play/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O drift/O off/O to/O a/O dreamless/O sleep/O in/O his/O own/O bed/O with/O his/O arms/O wrapped/O tight/O around/O his/O lady/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cayn/PERSON returned/O as/O he/O was/O pressing/O the/O direwolf/O seal/O down/O into/O the/O soft/O white/O wax/O ./O 
Desmond/PERSON was/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O between/O them/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
Ned/PERSON thanked/O his/O guards/O and/O sent/O them/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON was/O clad/O in/O a/O blue/O velvet/O tunic/O with/O puffed/O sleeves/O ,/O his/O silvery/O cape/O patterned/O with/O mockingbirds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O congratulations/O are/O in/O order/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O seated/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON scowled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O lies/O wounded/O and/O near/O to/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O also/O know/O that/O Robert/PERSON has/O named/O you/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O eyes/O flicked/O to/O the/O king/O 's/O letter/O on/O the/O table/O beside/O him/O ,/O its/O seal/O unbroken/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O how/O is/O it/O you/O know/O that/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Varys/O hinted/O as/O much/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O you/O have/O just/O confirmed/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O mouth/O twisted/O in/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O Varys/O and/O his/O little/O birds/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON spoke/O truly/O ,/O the/O man/O has/O some/O black/O art/O ./O 
I/O do/O not/O trust/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Excellent/O ./O 
You/O 're/O learning/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON leaned/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O I/O 'll/O wager/O you/O did/O not/O drag/O me/O here/O in/O the/O black/O of/O night/O to/O discuss/O the/O eunuch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O the/O secret/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON was/O murdered/O to/O protect/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON will/O leave/O no/O trueborn/O son/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON and/O Tommen/PERSON are/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O bastards/O ,/O born/O of/O his/O incestuous/O union/O with/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON lifted/O an/O eyebrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shocking/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O tone/O that/O suggested/O he/O was/O not/O shocked/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O girl/O as/O well/O ?/O 
No/O doubt/O ./O 
So/O when/O the/O king/O dies/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O throne/O by/O rights/O passes/O to/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O the/O elder/O of/O Robert/PERSON 's/O two/O brothers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON stroked/O his/O pointed/O beard/O as/O he/O considered/O the/O matter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O it/O would/O seem/O ./O 
Unless/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unless/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
There/O is/O no/O seeming/O to/O this/O ./O 
Stannis/O is/O the/O heir/O ./O 
Nothing/O can/O change/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stannis/O can/O not/O take/O the/O throne/O without/O your/O help/O ./O 
If/O you/O 're/O wise/O ,/O you/O 'll/O make/O certain/O Joffrey/PERSON succeeds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON gave/O him/O a/O stony/O stare/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O no/O shred/O of/O honor/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O a/O shred/O ,/O surely/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON replied/O negligently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hear/O me/O out/O ./O 
Stannis/O is/O no/O friend/O of/O yours/O ,/O nor/O of/O mine/O ./O 
Even/O his/O brothers/O can/O scarcely/O stomach/O him/O ./O 
The/O man/O is/O iron/O ,/O hard/O and/O unyielding/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O give/O us/O a/O new/O Hand/O and/O a/O new/O council/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O he/O 'll/O thank/O you/O for/O handing/O him/O the/O crown/O ,/O but/O he/O wo/O n't/O love/O you/O for/O it/O ./O 
And/O his/O ascent/O will/O mean/O war/O ./O 
Stannis/O can/O not/O rest/O easy/O on/O the/O throne/O until/O Cersei/PERSON and/O her/O bastards/O are/O dead/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON will/O sit/O idly/O while/O his/O daughter/O 's/O head/O is/O measured/O for/O a/O spike/O ?/O 
Casterly/O Rock/O will/O rise/O ,/O and/O not/O alone/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON found/O it/O in/O him/O to/O pardon/O men/O who/O served/O King/O Aerys/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O did/O him/O fealty/O ./O 
Stannis/O is/O less/O forgiving/O ./O 
He/O will/O not/O have/O forgotten/O the/O siege/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ,/O and/O the/O Lords/O Tyrell/PERSON and/O Redwyne/O dare/O not/O ./O 
Every/O man/O who/O fought/O beneath/O the/O dragon/O banner/O or/O rose/O with/O Balon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON will/O have/O good/O cause/O to/O fear/O ./O 
Seat/O Stannis/O on/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O and/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O the/O realm/O will/O bleed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O look/O at/O the/O other/O side/O of/O the/O coin/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON is/O but/O twelve/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON gave/O you/O the/O regency/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
You/O are/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O and/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O ./O 
The/O power/O is/O yours/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
All/O you/O need/O do/O is/O reach/O out/O and/O take/O it/O ./O 
Make/O your/O peace/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Release/O the/O Imp/O ./O 
Wed/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON to/O your/O Sansa/O ./O 
Wed/O your/O younger/O girl/O to/O Prince/PERSON Tommen/PERSON ,/O and/O your/O heir/O to/O Myrcella/PERSON ./O 
It/O will/O be/O four/O years/O before/O Joffrey/PERSON comes/O of/O age/O ./O 
By/O then/O he/O will/O look/O to/O you/O as/O a/O second/O father/O ,/O and/O if/O not/O ,/O well/O .../O four/O years/O is/O a/O good/O long/O while/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Long/O enough/O to/O dispose/O of/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ./O 
Then/O ,/O should/O Joffrey/PERSON prove/O troublesome/O ,/O we/O can/O reveal/O his/O little/O secret/O and/O put/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON on/O the/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON repeated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON gave/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O need/O someone/O to/O share/O your/O burdens/O ./O 
I/O assure/O you/O ,/O my/O price/O would/O be/O modest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O price/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON 's/O voice/O was/O ice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O what/O you/O suggest/O is/O treason/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O if/O we/O lose/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O forget/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O forget/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O 
You/O forget/O Jory/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ./O 
And/O you/O forget/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O the/O dagger/O and/O laid/O it/O on/O the/O table/O between/O them/O ;/O a/O length/O of/O dragonbone/O and/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O as/O sharp/O as/O the/O difference/O between/O right/O and/O wrong/O ,/O between/O true/O and/O false/O ,/O between/O life/O and/O death/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O sent/O a/O man/O to/O cut/O my/O son/O 's/O throat/O ,/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O I/O did/O forget/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Pray/O forgive/O me/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O I/O did/O not/O remember/O that/O I/O was/O talking/O to/O a/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O mouth/O quirked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O it/O will/O be/O Stannis/O ,/O and/O war/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O a/O choice/O ./O 
Stannis/O is/O the/O heir/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Far/O be/O it/O from/O me/O to/O dispute/O the/O Lord/O Protector/O ./O 
What/O would/O you/O have/O of/O me/O ,/O then/O ?/O 
Not/O my/O wisdom/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O do/O my/O best/O to/O forget/O your/O .../O wisdom/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O with/O distaste/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O called/O you/O here/O to/O ask/O for/O the/O help/O you/O promised/O Catelyn/PERSON ./O 
This/O is/O a/O perilous/O hour/O for/O all/O of/O us/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON has/O named/O me/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Protector/O ,/O true/O enough/O ,/O but/O in/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O world/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON is/O still/O his/O son/O and/O heir/O ./O 
The/O queen/O has/O a/O dozen/O knights/O and/O a/O hundred/O men-at-arms/O who/O will/O do/O whatever/O she/O commands/O .../O enough/O to/O overwhelm/O what/O remains/O of/O my/O own/O household/O guard/O ./O 
And/O for/O all/O I/O know/O ,/O her/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON may/O be/O riding/O for/O King/O 's/O Landing/O even/O as/O we/O speak/O ,/O with/O a/O Lannister/O host/O at/O his/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O without/O an/O army/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Little/O finger/O toyed/O with/O the/O dagger/O on/O the/O table/O ,/O turning/O it/O slowly/O with/O a/O finger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O small/O love/O lost/O between/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON and/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Bronze/PERSON Yohn/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ,/O Lady/PERSON Tanda/PERSON ,/O the/O Redwyne/O twins/O .../O each/O of/O them/O has/O a/O retinue/O of/O knights/O and/O sworn/O swords/O here/O at/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Renly/O has/O thirty/O men/O in/O his/O personal/O guard/O ,/O the/O rest/O even/O fewer/O ./O 
It/O is/O not/O enough/O ,/O even/O if/O I/O could/O be/O certain/O that/O all/O of/O them/O will/O choose/O to/O give/O me/O their/O allegiance/O ./O 
I/O must/O have/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O ./O 
The/O City/O Watch/O is/O two/O thousand/O strong/O ,/O sworn/O to/O defend/O the/O castle/O ,/O the/O city/O ,/O and/O the/O king/O 's/O peace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O but/O when/O the/O queen/O proclaims/O one/O king/O and/O the/O Hand/O another/O ,/O whose/O peace/O do/O they/O protect/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON flicked/O at/O the/O dagger/O with/O his/O finger/O ,/O setting/O it/O spinning/O in/O place/O ./O 
Round/O and/O round/O it/O went/O ,/O wobbling/O as/O it/O turned/O ./O 
When/O at/O last/O it/O slowed/O to/O a/O stop/O ,/O the/O blade/O pointed/O at/O Littlefinger/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O there/O 's/O your/O answer/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O follow/O the/O man/O who/O pays/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O back/O and/O looked/O Ned/PERSON full/O in/O the/O face/O ,/O his/O grey-green/O eyes/O bright/O with/O mockery/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O wear/O your/O honor/O like/O a/O suit/O of/O armor/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
You/O think/O it/O keeps/O you/O safe/O ,/O but/O all/O it/O does/O is/O weigh/O you/O down/O and/O make/O it/O hard/O for/O you/O to/O move/O ./O 
Look/O at/O you/O now/O ./O 
You/O know/O why/O you/O summoned/O me/O here/O ./O 
You/O know/O what/O you/O want/O to/O ask/O me/O to/O do/O ./O 
You/O know/O it/O has/O to/O be/O done/O .../O but/O it/O 's/O not/O honorable/O ,/O so/O the/O words/O stick/O in/O your/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O neck/O was/O rigid/O with/O tension/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O he/O was/O so/O angry/O that/O he/O did/O not/O trust/O himself/O to/O speak/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ought/O to/O make/O you/O say/O it/O ,/O but/O that/O would/O be/O cruel/O .../O so/O have/O no/O fear/O ,/O my/O good/O lord/O ./O 
For/O the/O sake/O of/O the/O love/O I/O bear/O for/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O I/O will/O go/O to/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON this/O very/O hour/O and/O make/O certain/O that/O the/O City/O Watch/O is/O yours/O ./O 
Six/O thousand/O gold/O pieces/O should/O do/O it/O ./O 
A/O third/O for/O the/O Commander/O ,/O a/O third/O for/O the/O officers/O ,/O a/O third/O for/O the/O men/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O able/O to/O buy/O them/O for/O half/O that/O much/O ,/O but/O I/O prefer/O not/O to/O take/O chances/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Smiling/O ,/O he/O plucked/O up/O the/O dagger/O and/O offered/O it/O to/O Ned/PERSON ,/O hilt/O first/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
