-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O You/O are/O as/O hopeless/O as/O any/O boys/O I/O have/O ever/O trained/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON announced/O when/O they/O had/O all/O assembled/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O hands/O were/O made/O for/O manure/O shovels/O ,/O not/O for/O swords/O ,/O and/O if/O it/O were/O up/O to/O me/O ,/O the/O lot/O of/O you/O would/O be/O set/O to/O herding/O swine/O ./O 
But/O last/O night/O I/O was/O told/O that/O Gueren/PERSON is/O marching/O five/O new/O boys/O up/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
One/O or/O two/O may/O even/O be/O worth/O the/O price/O of/O piss/O ./O 
To/O make/O room/O for/O them/O ,/O I/O have/O decided/O to/O pass/O eight/O of/O you/O on/O to/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O to/O do/O with/O as/O he/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O called/O out/O the/O names/O one/O by/O one/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Toad/O ./O 
Stone/O Head/O ./O 
Aurochs/O ./O 
Lover/O ./O 
Pimple/O ./O 
Monkey/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Loon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Last/O ,/O he/O looked/O at/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O the/O Bastard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pyp/O let/O fly/O a/O whoop/O and/O thrust/O his/O sword/O into/O the/O air/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON fixed/O him/O with/O a/O reptile/O stare/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O will/O call/O you/O men/O of/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O now/O ,/O but/O you/O are/O bigger/O fools/O than/O the/O Mummer/O 's/O Monkey/O here/O if/O you/O believe/O that/O ./O 
You/O are/O boys/O still/O ,/O green/O and/O stinking/O of/O summer/O ,/O and/O when/O the/O winter/O comes/O you/O will/O die/O like/O flies/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O with/O that/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON took/O his/O leave/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O other/O boys/O gathered/O round/O the/O eight/O who/O had/O been/O named/O ,/O laughing/O and/O cursing/O and/O offering/O congratulations/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON smacked/O Toad/PERSON on/O the/O butt/O with/O the/O flat/O of/O his/O sword/O and/O shouted/O ,/O \/O ``/O Toad/O ,/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Yelling/O that/O a/O black/O brother/O needed/O a/O horse/O ,/O Pyp/PERSON leapt/O onto/O Grenn/PERSON 's/O shoulders/O ,/O and/O they/O tumbled/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O rolling/O and/O punching/O and/O hooting/O ./O 
Dareon/PERSON dashed/O inside/O the/O armory/O and/O returned/O with/O a/O skin/O of/O sour/O red/O ./O 
As/O they/O passed/O the/O wine/O from/O hand/O to/O hand/O ,/O grinning/O like/O fools/O ,/O Jon/PERSON noticed/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON standing/O by/O himself/O beneath/O a/O bare/O dead/O tree/O in/O the/O corner/O of/O the/O yard/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON offered/O him/O the/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O swallow/O of/O wine/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O thank/O you/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O you/O well/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O well/O ,/O truly/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O fat/O boy/O lied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O so/O happy/O for/O you/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O round/O face/O quivered/O as/O he/O forced/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O be/O First/O Ranger/O someday/O ,/O just/O as/O your/O uncle/O was/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON corrected/O ./O 
He/O would/O not/O accept/O that/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O dead/O ./O 
Before/O he/O could/O say/O more/O ,/O Haider/PERSON cried/O ,/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O you/O planning/O to/O drink/O that/O all/O yourself/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON snatched/O the/O skin/O from/O his/O hand/O and/O danced/O away/O ,/O laughing/O ./O 
While/O Grenn/PERSON seized/O his/O arm/O ,/O Pyp/PERSON gave/O the/O skin/O a/O squeeze/O ,/O and/O a/O thin/O stream/O of/O red/O squirted/O Jon/PERSON in/O the/O face/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON howled/O in/O protest/O at/O the/O waste/O of/O good/O wine/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON sputtered/O and/O struggled/O ./O 
Matthar/PERSON and/O Jeren/PERSON climbed/O the/O wall/O and/O began/O pelting/O them/O all/O with/O snowballs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O he/O wrenched/O free/O ,/O with/O snow/O in/O his/O hair/O and/O wine/O stains/O on/O his/O surcoat/O ,/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON had/O gone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O night/O ,/O Three-Finger/O Hobb/PERSON cooked/O the/O boys/O a/O special/O meal/O to/O mark/O the/O occasion/O ./O 
When/O Jon/PERSON arrived/O at/O the/O common/O hall/O ,/O the/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON himself/O led/O him/O to/O the/O bench/O near/O the/O fire/O ./O 
The/O older/O men/O clapped/O him/O on/O the/O arm/O in/O passing/O ./O 
The/O eight/O soon-to-be/O brothers/O feasted/O on/O rack/O of/O lamb/O baked/O in/O a/O crust/O of/O garlic/O and/O herbs/O ,/O garnished/O with/O sprigs/O of/O mint/O ,/O and/O surrounded/O by/O mashed/O yellow/O turnips/O swimming/O in/O butter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O From/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O own/O table/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON told/O them/O ./O 
There/O were/O salads/O of/O spinach/O and/O chickpeas/O and/O turnip/O greens/O ,/O and/O afterward/O bowls/O of/O iced/O blueberries/O and/O sweet/O cream/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O they/O 'll/O keep/O us/O together/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON wondered/O as/O they/O gorged/O themselves/O happily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Toad/PERSON made/O a/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O not/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sick/O of/O looking/O at/O those/O ears/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ho/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Pyp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Listen/O to/O the/O crow/O call/O the/O raven/O black/O ./O 
You/O 're/O certain/O to/O be/O a/O ranger/O ,/O Toad/O ./O 
They/O 'll/O want/O you/O as/O far/O from/O the/O castle/O as/O they/O can/O ./O 
If/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON attacks/O ,/O lift/O your/O visor/O and/O show/O your/O face/O ,/O and/O he/O 'll/O run/O off/O screaming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Everyone/O laughed/O but/O Grenn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O I/O 'm/O a/O ranger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O and/O everyone/O else/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Matthar/PERSON ./O 
Every/O man/O who/O wore/O the/O black/O walked/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O every/O man/O was/O expected/O to/O take/O up/O steel/O in/O its/O defense/O ,/O but/O the/O rangers/O were/O the/O true/O fighting/O heart/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
It/O was/O they/O who/O dared/O ride/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O sweeping/O through/O the/O haunted/O forest/O and/O the/O icy/O mountain/O heights/O west/O of/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O fighting/O wildlings/O and/O giants/O and/O monstrous/O snow/O bears/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O everyone/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Haider/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O the/O builders/O for/O me/O ./O 
What/O use/O would/O rangers/O be/O if/O the/O Wall/O fell/O down/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O order/O of/O builders/O provided/O the/O masons/O and/O carpenters/O to/O repair/O keeps/O and/O towers/O ,/O the/O miners/O to/O dig/O tunnels/O and/O crush/O stone/O for/O roads/O and/O footpaths/O ,/O the/O woodsmen/O to/O clear/O away/O new/O growth/O wherever/O the/O forest/O pressed/O too/O close/O to/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Once/O ,/O it/O was/O said/O ,/O they/O had/O quarried/O immense/O blocks/O of/O ice/O from/O frozen/O lakes/O deep/O in/O the/O haunted/O forest/O ,/O dragging/O them/O south/O on/O sledges/O so/O the/O Wall/O might/O be/O raised/O ever/O higher/O ./O 
Those/O days/O were/O centuries/O gone/O ,/O however/O ;/O now/O ,/O it/O was/O all/O they/O could/O do/O to/O ride/O the/O Wall/O from/O Eastwatch/LOCATION to/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O watching/O for/O cracks/O or/O signs/O of/O melt/O and/O making/O what/O repairs/O they/O could/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O no/O fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dareon/PERSON observed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O certain/O to/O be/O a/O builder/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON 's/O certain/O to/O be/O a/O ranger/O ./O 
He/O 's/O the/O best/O sword/O and/O the/O best/O rider/O among/O us/O ,/O and/O his/O uncle/O was/O the/O First/O before/O he/O .../O \/O ''/O His/O voice/O trailed/O off/O awkwardly/O as/O he/O realized/O what/O he/O had/O almost/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Benjen/O Stark/O is/O still/O First/O Ranger/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O toying/O with/O his/O bowl/O of/O blueberries/O ./O 
The/O rest/O might/O have/O given/O up/O all/O hope/O of/O his/O uncle/O 's/O safe/O return/O ,/O but/O not/O him/O ./O 
He/O pushed/O away/O the/O berries/O ,/O scarcely/O touched/O ,/O and/O rose/O from/O the/O bench/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O n't/O you/O going/O to/O eat/O those/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Toad/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON had/O hardly/O tasted/O Hobb/PERSON 's/O great/O feast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O could/O not/O eat/O another/O bite/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O his/O cloak/O from/O its/O hook/O near/O the/O door/O and/O shouldered/O his/O way/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pyp/O followed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O what/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sam/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O not/O at/O table/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O not/O like/O him/O to/O miss/O a/O meal/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O suppose/O he/O 's/O taken/O ill/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O frightened/O ./O 
We/O 're/O leaving/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O remembered/O the/O day/O he/O had/O left/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O all/O the/O bittersweet/O farewells/O ;/O Bran/O lying/O broken/O ,/O Robb/PERSON with/O snow/O in/O his/O hair/O ,/O Arya/PERSON raining/O kisses/O on/O him/O after/O he/O 'd/O given/O her/O Needle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Once/O we/O say/O our/O words/O ,/O we/O 'll/O all/O have/O duties/O to/O attend/O to/O ./O 
Some/O of/O us/O may/O be/O sent/O away/O ,/O to/O Eastwatch/LOCATION or/O the/O Shadow/O Tower/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON will/O remain/O in/O training/O ,/O with/O the/O likes/O of/O Rast/PERSON and/O Cuger/PERSON and/O these/O new/O boys/O who/O are/O coming/O up/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
Gods/O only/O know/O what/O they/O 'll/O be/O like/O ,/O but/O you/O can/O bet/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON will/O send/O them/O against/O him/O ,/O first/O chance/O he/O gets/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pyp/O made/O a/O grimace/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O did/O all/O you/O could/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O we/O could/O was/O n't/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O deep/O restlessness/O was/O on/O him/O as/O he/O went/O back/O to/O Hardin/PERSON 's/O Tower/O for/O Ghost/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O walked/O beside/O him/O to/O the/O stables/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O more/O skittish/O horses/O kicked/O at/O their/O stalls/O and/O laid/O back/O their/O ears/O as/O they/O entered/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON saddled/O his/O mare/O ,/O mounted/O ,/O and/O rode/O out/O from/O Castle/O Black/O ,/O south/O across/O the/O moonlit/O night/O ./O 
Ghost/O raced/O ahead/O of/O him/O ,/O flying/O over/O the/O ground/O ,/O gone/O in/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON let/O him/O go/O ./O 
A/O wolf/O needed/O to/O hunt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O no/O destination/O in/O mind/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O only/O to/O ride/O ./O 
He/O followed/O the/O creek/O for/O a/O time/O ,/O listening/O to/O the/O icy/O trickle/O of/O water/O over/O rock/O ,/O then/O cut/O across/O the/O fields/O to/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
It/O stretched/O out/O before/O him/O ,/O narrow/O and/O stony/O and/O pocked/O with/O weeds/O ,/O a/O road/O of/O no/O particular/O promise/O ,/O yet/O the/O sight/O of/O it/O filled/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON with/O a/O vast/O longing/O ./O 
Winterfell/PERSON was/O down/O that/O road/O ,/O and/O beyond/O it/O Riverrun/O and/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O so/O many/O other/O places/O ;/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O the/O Isles/O of/O Faces/O ,/O the/O red/O mountains/O of/O Dome/LOCATION ,/O the/O hundred/O islands/O of/O Braavos/LOCATION in/O the/O sea/O ,/O the/O smoking/O ruins/O of/O old/O Valyria/LOCATION ./O 
All/O the/O places/O that/O Jon/PERSON would/O never/O see/O ./O 
The/O world/O was/O down/O that/O road/O .../O and/O he/O was/O here/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Once/O he/O swore/O his/O vow/O ,/O the/O Wall/O would/O be/O his/O home/O until/O he/O was/O old/O as/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O sworn/O yet/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O ./O 
He/O was/O no/O outlaw/O ,/O bound/O to/O take/O the/O black/O or/O pay/O the/O penalty/O for/O his/O crimes/O ./O 
He/O had/O come/O here/O freely/O ,/O and/O he/O might/O leave/O freely/O .../O until/O he/O said/O the/O words/O ./O 
He/O need/O only/O ride/O on/O ,/O and/O he/O could/O leave/O it/O all/O behind/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O the/O moon/O was/O full/O again/O ,/O he/O would/O be/O back/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O his/O brothers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Your/O half/O brothers/O ,/O a/O voice/O inside/O reminded/O him/O ./O 
And/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O who/O will/O not/O welcome/O you/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O place/O for/O him/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O no/O place/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O either/O ./O 
Even/O his/O own/O mother/O had/O not/O had/O a/O place/O for/O him/O ./O 
The/O thought/O of/O her/O made/O him/O sad/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O who/O she/O had/O been/O ,/O what/O she/O had/O looked/O like/O ,/O why/O his/O father/O had/O left/O her/O ./O 
Because/O she/O was/O a/O whore/O or/O an/O adulteress/O ,/O fool/O ./O 
Something/O dark/O and/O dishonorable/O ,/O or/O else/O why/O was/O Lord/O Eddard/O too/O ashamed/O to/O speak/O of/O her/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON turned/O away/O from/O the/O kingsroad/O to/O look/O behind/O him/O ./O 
The/O fires/O of/O Castle/O Black/O were/O hidden/O behind/O a/O hill/O ,/O but/O the/O Wall/O was/O there/O ,/O pale/O beneath/O the/O moon/O ,/O vast/O and/O cold/O ,/O running/O from/O horizon/O to/O horizon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wheeled/O his/O horse/O around/O and/O started/O for/O home/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O returned/O as/O he/O crested/O a/O rise/O and/O saw/O the/O distant/O glow/O of/O lamplight/O from/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O Tower/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O s/O muzzle/O was/O red/O with/O blood/O as/O he/O trotted/O beside/O the/O horse/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON found/O himself/O thinking/O of/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON again/O on/O the/O ride/O back/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O he/O reached/O the/O stables/O ,/O he/O knew/O what/O he/O must/O do/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/O Aemon/O '/O s/O apartments/O were/O in/O a/O stout/O wooden/O keep/O below/O the/O rookery/O ./O 
Aged/O and/O frail/O ,/O the/O maester/O shared/O his/O chambers/O with/O two/O of/O the/O younger/O stewards/O ,/O who/O tended/O to/O his/O needs/O and/O helped/O him/O in/O his/O duties/O ./O 
The/O brothers/O joked/O that/O he/O had/O been/O given/O the/O two/O ugliest/O men/O in/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ;/O being/O blind/O ,/O he/O was/O spared/O having/O to/O look/O at/O them/O ./O 
Clydas/PERSON was/O short/O ,/O bald/O ,/O and/O chinless/O ,/O with/O small/O pink/O eyes/O like/O a/O mole/O ./O 
Chett/PERSON had/O a/O wen/O on/O his/O neck/O the/O size/O of/O a/O pigeon/O 's/O egg/O ,/O and/O a/O face/O red/O with/O boils/O and/O pimples/O ./O 
Perhaps/O that/O was/O why/O he/O always/O seemed/O so/O angry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O Chett/PERSON who/O answered/O Jon/PERSON 's/O knock/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O need/O to/O speak/O to/O Maester/O Aemon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O maester/O is/O abed/O ,/O as/O you/O should/O be/O ./O 
Come/O back/O on/O the/O morrow/O and/O maybe/O he/O 'll/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O began/O to/O shut/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON jammed/O it/O open/O with/O his/O boot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O need/O to/O speak/O to/O him/O now/O ./O 
The/O morning/O will/O be/O too/O late/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chett/PERSON scowled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O maester/O is/O not/O accustomed/O to/O being/O woken/O in/O the/O night/O ./O 
Do/O you/O know/O how/O old/O he/O is/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Old/O enough/O to/O treat/O visitors/O with/O more/O courtesy/O than/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O him/O my/O pardons/O ./O 
I/O would/O not/O disturb/O his/O rest/O if/O it/O were/O not/O important/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O if/O I/O refuse/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O his/O boot/O wedged/O solidly/O in/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O stand/O here/O all/O night/O if/O I/O must/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O black/O brother/O made/O a/O disgusted/O noise/O and/O opened/O the/O door/O to/O admit/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wait/O in/O the/O library/O ./O 
There/O 's/O wood/O ./O 
Start/O a/O fire/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O have/O the/O maester/O catching/O a/O chill/O on/O account/O of/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/O had/O the/O logs/O crackling/O merrily/O by/O the/O time/O Chett/PERSON led/O in/O Maester/O Aemon/O ./O 
The/O old/O man/O was/O clad/O in/O his/O bed/O robe/O ,/O but/O around/O his/O throat/O was/O the/O chain/O collar/O of/O his/O order/O ./O 
A/O maester/O did/O not/O remove/O it/O even/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O chair/O beside/O the/O fire/O would/O be/O pleasant/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O when/O he/O felt/O the/O warmth/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O settled/O comfortably/O ,/O Chett/PERSON covered/O his/O legs/O with/O a/O fur/O and/O went/O to/O stand/O by/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O sorry/O to/O have/O woken/O you/O ,/O Maester/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O did/O not/O wake/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O find/O I/O need/O less/O sleep/O as/O I/O grow/O older/O ,/O and/O I/O am/O grown/O very/O old/O ./O 
I/O often/O spend/O half/O the/O night/O with/O ghosts/O ,/O remembering/O times/O fifty/O years/O past/O as/O if/O they/O were/O yesterday/O ./O 
The/O mystery/O of/O a/O midnight/O visitor/O is/O a/O welcome/O diversion/O ./O 
So/O tell/O me/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O why/O have/O you/O come/O calling/O at/O this/O strange/O hour/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O ask/O that/O Samwell/O Tarly/O be/O taken/O from/O training/O and/O accepted/O as/O a/O brother/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O concern/O of/O Maester/LOCATION Aemon/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Chett/PERSON complained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Our/O Lord/O Commander/O has/O given/O the/O training/O of/O recruits/O into/O the/O hands/O of/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O he/O may/O say/O when/O a/O boy/O is/O ready/O to/O swear/O his/O vow/O ,/O as/O you/O surely/O know/O ./O 
Why/O then/O come/O to/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O listens/O to/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O the/O wounded/O and/O the/O sick/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O are/O in/O your/O charge/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O is/O your/O friend/O Samwell/PERSON wounded/O or/O sick/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON promised/O ,/O \/O ``/O unless/O you/O help/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O told/O them/O all/O of/O it/O ,/O even/O the/O part/O where/O he/O 'd/O set/O Ghost/O at/O Rast/PERSON 's/O throat/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON listened/O silently/O ,/O blind/O eyes/O fixed/O on/O the/O fire/O ,/O but/O Chett/PERSON 's/O face/O darkened/O with/O each/O word/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Without/O us/O to/O keep/O him/O safe/O ,/O Sam/PERSON will/O have/O no/O chance/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON finished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O hopeless/O with/O a/O sword/O ./O 
My/O sister/O Arya/PERSON could/O tear/O him/O apart/O ,/O and/O she/O 's/O not/O yet/O ten/O ./O 
If/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON makes/O him/O fight/O ,/O it/O 's/O only/O a/O matter/O of/O time/O before/O he/O 's/O hurt/O or/O killed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chett/O could/O stand/O no/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O seen/O this/O fat/O boy/O in/O the/O common/O hall/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O a/O pig/O ,/O and/O a/O hopeless/O craven/O as/O well/O ,/O if/O what/O you/O say/O is/O true/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O it/O is/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O Chett/PERSON ,/O what/O would/O you/O have/O us/O do/O with/O such/O a/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Leave/O him/O where/O he/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Chett/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Wall/O is/O no/O place/O for/O the/O weak/O ./O 
Let/O him/O train/O until/O he/O is/O ready/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O many/O years/O that/O takes/O ./O 
Ser/O Alliser/O shall/O make/O a/O man/O of/O him/O or/O kill/O him/O ,/O as/O the/O gods/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O stupid/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O deep/O breath/O to/O gather/O his/O thoughts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O remember/O once/O I/O asked/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON why/O he/O wore/O a/O chain/O around/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON touched/O his/O own/O collar/O lightly/O ,/O his/O bony/O ,/O wrinkled/O finger/O stroking/O the/O heavy/O metal/O links/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O told/O me/O that/O a/O maester/O 's/O collar/O is/O made/O of/O chain/O to/O remind/O him/O that/O he/O is/O sworn/O to/O serve/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ,/O remembering/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O asked/O why/O each/O link/O was/O a/O different/O metal/O ./O 
A/O silver/O chain/O would/O look/O much/O finer/O with/O his/O grey/O robes/O ,/O I/O said/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
A/O maester/O forges/O his/O chain/O with/O study/O ,/O he/O told/O me/O ./O 
The/O different/O metals/O are/O each/O a/O different/O kind/O of/O learning/O ,/O gold/O for/O the/O study/O of/O money/O and/O accounts/O ,/O silver/O for/O healing/O ,/O iron/O for/O warcraft/O ./O 
And/O he/O said/O there/O were/O other/O meanings/O as/O well/O ./O 
The/O collar/O is/O supposed/O to/O remind/O a/O maester/O of/O the/O realm/O he/O serves/O ,/O is/O n't/O that/O so/O ?/O 
Lords/O are/O gold/O and/O knights/O steel/O ,/O but/O two/O links/O ca/O n't/O make/O a/O chain/O ./O 
You/O also/O need/O silver/O and/O iron/O and/O lead/O ,/O tin/O and/O copper/O and/O bronze/O and/O all/O the/O rest/O ,/O and/O those/O are/O farmers/O and/O smiths/O and/O merchants/O and/O the/O like/O ./O 
A/O chain/O needs/O all/O sorts/O of/O metals/O ,/O and/O a/O land/O needs/O all/O sorts/O of/O people/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O so/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O needs/O all/O sorts/O too/O ./O 
Why/O else/O have/O rangers/O and/O stewards/O and/O builders/O ?/O 
Lord/O Randyll/PERSON could/O n't/O make/O Sam/PERSON a/O warrior/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON wo/O n't/O either/O ./O 
You/O ca/O n't/O hammer/O tin/O into/O iron/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O hard/O you/O beat/O it/O ,/O but/O that/O does/O n't/O mean/O tin/O is/O useless/O ./O 
Why/O should/O n't/O Sam/PERSON be/O a/O steward/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chett/O gave/O an/O angry/O scowl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O a/O steward/O ./O 
You/O think/O it/O 's/O easy/O work/O ,/O fit/O for/O cowards/O ?/O 
The/O order/O of/O stewards/O keeps/O the/O Watch/O alive/O ./O 
We/O hunt/O and/O farm/O ,/O tend/O the/O horses/O ,/O milk/O the/O cows/O ,/O gather/O firewood/O ,/O cook/O the/O meals/O ./O 
Who/O do/O you/O think/O makes/O your/O clothing/O ?/O 
Who/O brings/O up/O supplies/O from/O the/O south/O ?/O 
The/O stewards/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON was/O gentler/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O your/O friend/O a/O hunter/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O hates/O hunting/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON had/O to/O admit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O he/O plow/O a/O field/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O maester/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O he/O drive/O a/O wagon/O or/O sail/O a/O ship/O ?/O 
Could/O he/O butcher/O a/O cow/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chett/O gave/O a/O nasty/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O seen/O what/O happens/O to/O soft/O lordlings/O when/O they/O 're/O put/O to/O work/O ./O 
Set/O them/O to/O churning/O butter/O and/O their/O hands/O blister/O and/O bleed/O ./O 
Give/O them/O an/O axe/O to/O split/O logs/O ,/O and/O they/O cut/O off/O their/O own/O foot/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O one/O thing/O Sam/PERSON could/O do/O better/O than/O anyone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Maester/O Aemon/O prompted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON glanced/O warily/O at/O Chett/LOCATION ,/O standing/O beside/O the/O door/O ,/O his/O boils/O red/O and/O angry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O could/O help/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O quickly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O can/O do/O sums/O ,/O and/O he/O knows/O how/O to/O read/O and/O write/O ./O 
I/O know/O Chett/PERSON ca/O n't/O read/O ,/O and/O Clydas/PERSON has/O weak/O eyes/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON read/O every/O book/O in/O his/O father/O 's/O library/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O be/O good/O with/O the/O ravens/O too/O ./O 
Animals/O seem/O to/O like/O him/O ./O 
Ghost/O took/O to/O him/O straight/O off/O ./O 
There/O 's/O a/O lot/O he/O could/O ''/O ,/O ``/O do/O ,/O besides/O fighting/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O needs/O every/O man/O ./O 
Why/O kill/O one/O ,/O to/O no/O end/O ?/O 
Make/O use/O of/O him/O instead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON closed/O his/O eyes/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O brief/O moment/O Jon/PERSON was/O afraid/O that/O he/O had/O gone/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON taught/O you/O well/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ./O 
Your/O mind/O is/O as/O deft/O as/O your/O blade/O ,/O it/O would/O seem/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Does/O that/O mean/O ./O 
./O 
?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O means/O I/O shall/O think/O on/O what/O you/O have/O said/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O told/O him/O firmly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O now/O ,/O I/O believe/O I/O am/O ready/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
Chett/PERSON ,/O show/O our/O young/O brother/O to/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
