-LSB-/O ``/O ARYA/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O High/O ,/O \/O ''/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON called/O out/O ,/O slashing/O at/O her/O head/O ./O 
The/O stick/O swords/O clacked/O as/O Arya/PERSON parried/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Left/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ,/O and/O his/O blade/O came/O whistling/O ./O 
Hers/O darted/O to/O meet/O it/O ./O 
The/O clack/O made/O him/O click/O his/O teeth/O together/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Right/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O and/O \/O ``/O Low/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O \/O ``/O Left/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O \/O ``/O Left/O \/O ''/O again/O ,/O faster/O and/O faster/O ,/O moving/O forward/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON retreated/O before/O him/O ,/O checking/O each/O blow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lunge/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O warned/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O thrust/O she/O sidestepped/O ,/O swept/O his/O blade/O away/O ,/O and/O slashed/O at/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
She/O almost/O touched/O him/O ,/O almost/O ,/O so/O close/O it/O made/O her/O grin/O ./O 
A/O strand/O of/O hair/O dangled/O in/O her/O eyes/O ,/O limp/O with/O sweat/O ./O 
She/O pushed/O it/O away/O with/O the/O back/O of/O her/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Left/O ,/O \/O ''/O Syrio/PERSON sang/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Low/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O sword/O was/O a/O blur/O ,/O and/O the/O Small/ORGANIZATION Hall/ORGANIZATION echoed/O to/O the/O clack/O clack/O clack/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Left/O ./O 
Left/O ./O 
High/O ./O 
Left/O ./O 
Right/O ./O 
Left/O ./O 
Low/O ./O 
Left/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wooden/O blade/O caught/O her/O high/O in/O the/O breast/O ,/O a/O sudden/O stinging/O blow/O that/O hurt/O all/O the/O more/O because/O it/O came/O from/O the/O wrong/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ow/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O cried/O out/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O a/O fresh/O bruise/O there/O by/O the/O time/O she/O went/O to/O sleep/O ,/O somewhere/O out/O at/O sea/O ./O 
A/O bruise/O is/O a/O lesson/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O and/O each/O lesson/O makes/O us/O better/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/O stepped/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O dead/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON made/O a/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O cheated/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O hotly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O said/O left/O and/O you/O went/O right/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ./O 
And/O now/O you/O are/O a/O dead/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O you/O lied/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O words/O lied/O ./O 
My/O eyes/O and/O my/O arm/O shouted/O out/O the/O truth/O ,/O but/O you/O were/O not/O seeing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O watched/O you/O every/O second/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Watching/O is/O not/O seeing/O ,/O dead/O girl/O ./O 
The/O water/O dancer/O sees/O ./O 
Come/O ,/O put/O down/O the/O sword/O ,/O it/O is/O time/O for/O listening/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O followed/O him/O over/O to/O the/O wall/O ,/O where/O he/O settled/O onto/O a/O bench/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Syrio/O Forel/O was/O first/O sword/O to/O the/O Sealord/O of/O Braavos/LOCATION ,/O and/O are/O you/O knowing/O how/O that/O came/O to/O pass/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O were/O the/O finest/O swordsman/O in/O the/O city/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ,/O but/O why/O ?/O 
Other/O men/O were/O stronger/O ,/O faster/O ,/O younger/O ,/O why/O was/O Syrio/O Forel/O the/O best/O ?/O 
I/O will/O tell/O you/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O touched/O the/O tip/O of/O his/O little/O finger/O lightly/O to/O his/O eyelid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O seeing/O ,/O the/O true/O seeing/O ,/O that/O is/O the/O heart/O of/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hear/O me/O ./O 
The/O ships/O of/O Braavos/LOCATION sail/O as/O far/O as/O the/O winds/O blow/O ,/O to/O lands/O strange/O and/O wonderful/O ,/O and/O when/O they/O return/O their/O captains/O fetch/O queer/O animals/O to/O the/O Sealord/ORGANIZATION 's/O menagerie/O ./O 
Such/O animals/O as/O you/O have/O never/O seen/O ,/O striped/O horses/O ,/O great/O spotted/O things/O with/O necks/O as/O long/O as/O stilts/O ,/O hairy/O mouse-pigs/O as/O big/O as/O cows/O ,/O stinging/O manticores/O ,/O tigers/O that/O carry/O their/O cubs/O in/O a/O pouch/O ,/O terrible/O walking/O lizards/O with/O scythes/O for/O claws/O ./O 
Syrio/O Forel/O has/O seen/O these/O things/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O On/O the/O day/O I/O am/O speaking/O of/O ,/O the/O first/O sword/O was/O newly/O dead/O ,/O and/O the/O Sealord/ORGANIZATION sent/O for/O me/O ./O 
Many/O bravos/O had/O come/O to/O him/O ,/O and/O as/O many/O had/O been/O sent/O away/O ,/O none/O could/O say/O why/O ./O 
When/O I/O came/O into/O his/O presence/O ,/O he/O was/O seated/O ,/O and/O in/O his/O lap/O was/O a/O fat/O yellow/O cat/O ./O 
He/O told/O me/O that/O one/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O his/O captains/O had/O brought/O the/O beast/O to/O him/O ,/O from/O an/O island/O beyond/O the/O sunrise/O ./O 
`/O Have/O you/O ever/O seen/O her/O like/O she/O asked/O of/O me/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O to/O him/O I/O said/O ,/O `/O Each/O night/O in/O the/O alleys/O of/O Braavos/O I/O see/O a/O thousand/O like/O him/O ,/O '/O and/O the/O Sealord/ORGANIZATION laughed/O ,/O and/O that/O day/O I/O was/O named/O the/O first/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON screwed/O up/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Syrio/PERSON clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O cat/O was/O an/O ordinary/O cat/O ,/O no/O more/O ./O 
The/O others/O expected/O a/O fabulous/O beast/O ,/O so/O that/O is/O what/O they/O saw/O ./O 
How/O large/O it/O was/O ,/O they/O said/O ./O 
It/O was/O no/O larger/O than/O any/O other/O cat/O ,/O only/O fat/O from/O indolence/O ,/O for/O the/O Sealord/ORGANIZATION fed/O it/O from/O his/O own/O table/O ./O 
What/O curious/O small/O ears/O ,/O they/O said/O ./O 
Its/O ears/O had/O been/O chewed/O away/O in/O kitten/O fights/O ./O 
And/O it/O was/O plainly/O a/O tomcat/O ,/O yet/O the/O Sealord/ORGANIZATION said/O `/O her/O ,/O '/O and/O that/O is/O what/O the/O others/O saw/O ./O 
Are/O you/O hearing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON thought/O about/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O saw/O what/O was/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ./O 
Opening/O your/O eyes/O is/O all/O that/O is/O needing/O ./O 
The/O heart/O lies/O and/O the/O head/O plays/O tricks/O with/O us/O ,/O but/O the/O eyes/O see/O true/O ./O 
Look/O with/O your/O eyes/O ./O 
Hear/O with/O your/O ears/O ./O 
Taste/O with/O your/O mouth/O ./O 
Smell/O with/O your/O nose/O ./O 
Feel/O with/O your/O skin/O ./O 
Then/O comes/O the/O thinking/O ,/O afterward/O ,/O and/O in/O that/O way/O knowing/O the/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Arya/PERSON ,/O grinning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON allowed/O himself/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O thinking/O that/O when/O we/O are/O reaching/O this/O Winterfell/O of/O yours/O ,/O it/O will/O be/O time/O to/O put/O this/O needle/O in/O your/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O eagerly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wait/O till/O I/O show/O Jon/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Behind/O her/O the/O great/O wooden/O doors/O of/O the/O Small/O Hall/O flew/O open/O with/O a/O resounding/O crash/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON whirled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O knight/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O stood/O beneath/O the/O arch/O of/O the/O door/O with/O five/O Lannister/O guardsmen/O arrayed/O behind/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O in/O full/O armor/O ,/O but/O his/O visor/O was/O up/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON remembered/O his/O droopy/O eyes/O and/O rustcolored/O whiskers/O from/O when/O he/O had/O come/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O the/O king/O :/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON ./O 
The/O red/O cloaks/O wore/O mail/O shirts/O over/O boiled/O leather/O and/O steel/O caps/O with/O lion/O crests/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O knight/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O come/O with/O us/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON chewed/O her/O lip/O uncertainly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O want/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O wants/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON took/O a/O step/O forward/O ,/O but/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON held/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O why/O is/O it/O that/O Lord/O Eddard/O is/O sending/O Lannister/O men/O in/O the/O place/O of/O his/O own/O ?/O 
I/O am/O wondering/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mind/O your/O place/O ,/O dancing/O master/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O concern/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O father/O would/O n't/O send/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
She/O snatched/O up/O her/O stick/O sword/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Put/O down/O the/O stick/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O a/O Sworn/O Brother/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON Kingsguard/PERSON ,/O the/O White/LOCATION Swords/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O was/O the/O Kingslayer/O when/O he/O killed/O the/O old/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O go/O with/O you/O if/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON ran/O out/O of/O patience/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O his/O men/O ./O 
He/O lowered/O the/O visor/O of/O his/O helm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Three/O of/O them/O started/O forward/O ,/O chainmail/O clinking/O softly/O with/O each/O step/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O suddenly/O afraid/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O to/O slow/O the/O racing/O of/O her/O heart/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/O Forel/O stepped/O between/O them/O ,/O tapping/O his/O wooden/O sword/O lightly/O against/O his/O boot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O be/O stopping/O there/O ./O 
Are/O you/O men/O or/O dogs/O that/O you/O would/O threaten/O a/O child/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Out/O of/O the/O way/O ,/O old/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O the/O red/O cloaks/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/O 's/O stick/O came/O whistling/O up/O and/O rang/O against/O his/O helm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O will/O now/O be/O speaking/O to/O me/O with/O more/O respect/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bald/O bastard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O yanked/O free/O his/O longsword/O ./O 
The/O stick/O moved/O again/O ,/O blindingly/O fast/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON heard/O a/O loud/O crack/O as/O the/O sword/O went/O clattering/O to/O the/O stone/O floor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O hand/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O guardsman/O yelped/O ,/O cradling/O his/O broken/O fingers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O quick/O ,/O for/O a/O dancing/O master/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O slow/O ,/O for/O a/O knight/O ,/O \/O ''/O Syrio/PERSON replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Kill/O the/O Braavosi/O and/O bring/O me/O the/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O knight/O in/O the/O white/O armor/O commanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Four/O Lannister/O guardsmen/O unsheathed/O their/O swords/O ./O 
The/O fifth/O ,/O with/O the/O broken/O fingers/O ,/O spat/O and/O pulled/O free/O a/O dagger/O with/O his/O left/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O ,/O sliding/O into/O his/O water/O dancer/O 's/O stance/O ,/O presenting/O only/O his/O side/O to/O the/O foe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON child/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ,/O never/O looking/O ,/O never/O taking/O his/O eyes/O off/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O are/O done/O with/O dancing/O for/O the/O day/O ./O 
Best/O you/O are/O going/O now/O ./O 
Run/O to/O your/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON did/O not/O want/O to/O leave/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O taught/O her/O to/O do/O as/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Swift/PERSON as/O a/O deer/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON as/O the/O Lannisters/O closed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON retreated/O ,/O her/O own/O sword/O stick/O clutched/O tightly/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O 
Watching/O him/O now/O ,/O she/O realized/O that/O Syrio/PERSON had/O only/O been/O toying/O with/O her/O when/O they/O dueled/O ./O 
The/O red/O cloaks/O came/O at/O him/O from/O three/O sides/O with/O steel/O in/O their/O hands/O ./O 
They/O had/O chainmail/O over/O their/O chest/O and/O arms/O ,/O and/O steel/O codpieces/O sewn/O into/O their/O pants/O ,/O but/O only/O leather/O on/O their/O legs/O ./O 
Their/O hands/O were/O bare/O ,/O and/O the/O caps/O they/O wore/O had/O noseguards/O ,/O but/O no/O visor/O over/O the/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/O did/O not/O wait/O for/O them/O to/O reach/O him/O ,/O but/O spun/O to/O his/O left/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O never/O seen/O a/O man/O move/O as/O fast/O ./O 
He/O checked/O one/O sword/O with/O his/O stick/O and/O whirled/O away/O from/O a/O second/O ./O 
Off/O balance/O ,/O the/O second/O man/O lurched/O into/O the/O first/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON put/O a/O boot/O to/O his/O back/O and/O the/O red/O cloaks/O went/O down/O together/O ./O 
The/O third/O guard/O came/O leaping/O over/O them/O ,/O slashing/O at/O the/O water/O dancer/O 's/O head/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON ducked/O under/O his/O blade/O and/O thrust/O upward/O ./O 
The/O guardsman/O fell/O screaming/O as/O blood/O welled/O from/O the/O wet/O red/O hole/O where/O his/O left/O eye/O had/O been/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O fallen/O men/O were/O getting/O up/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON kicked/O one/O in/O the/O face/O and/O snatched/O the/O steel/O cap/O off/O the/O other/O 's/O head/O ./O 
The/O dagger/O man/O stabbed/O at/O him/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON caught/O the/O thrust/O in/O the/O helmet/O and/O shattered/O the/O man/O 's/O kneecap/O with/O his/O stick/O ./O 
The/O last/O red/O cloak/O shouted/O a/O curse/O and/O charged/O ,/O hacking/O down/O with/O both/O hands/O on/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Syrio/O rolled/O right/O ,/O and/O the/O butcher/O 's/O cut/O caught/O the/O helmetless/O man/O between/O neck/O and/O shoulder/O as/O he/O struggled/O to/O his/O knees/O ./O 
The/O longsword/O crunched/O through/O mail/O and/O leather/O and/O flesh/O ./O 
The/O man/O on/O his/O knees/O shrieked/O ./O 
Before/O his/O killer/O could/O wrench/O free/O his/O blade/O ,/O Syrio/PERSON jabbed/O him/O in/O the/O apple/O of/O his/O throat/O ./O 
The/O guardsman/O gave/O a/O choked/O cry/O and/O staggered/O back/O ,/O clutching/O at/O his/O neck/O ,/O his/O face/O blackening/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Five/O men/O were/O down/O ,/O dead/O ,/O or/O dying/O by/O the/O time/O Arya/PERSON reached/O the/O back/O door/O that/O opened/O on/O the/O kitchen/O ./O 
She/O heard/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON curse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bloody/O oafs/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O ,/O drawing/O his/O longsword/O from/O its/O scabbard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Syrio/O Forel/O resumed/O his/O stance/O and/O clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON child/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ,/O never/O looking/O at/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O be/O gone/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Look/O with/O your/O eyes/O ,/O he/O had/O said/O ./O 
She/O saw/O :/O the/O knight/O in/O his/O pale/O armor/O head/O to/O foot/O ,/O legs/O ,/O throat/O ,/O and/O hands/O sheathed/O in/O metal/O ,/O eyes/O hidden/O behind/O his/O high/O white/O helm/O ,/O and/O in/O his/O hand/O cruel/O steel/O ./O 
Against/O that/O :/O Syrio/PERSON ,/O in/O a/O leather/O vest/O ,/O with/O a/O wooden/O sword/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Syrio/O ,/O run/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O screamed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O first/O sword/O of/O Braavos/O does/O not/O run/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sang/O as/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON slashed/O at/O him/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON danced/O away/O from/O his/O cut/O ,/O his/O stick/O a/O blur/O ./O 
In/O a/O heartbeat/O ,/O he/O had/O bounced/O blows/O off/O the/O knight/O 's/O temple/O ,/O elbow/O ,/O and/O throat/O ,/O the/O wood/O ringing/O against/O the/O metal/O of/O helm/O ,/O gauntlet/O ,/O and/O gorget/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON stood/O frozen/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON advanced/O ;/O Syrio/PERSON backed/O away/O ./O 
He/O checked/O the/O next/O blow/O ,/O spun/O away/O from/O the/O second/O ,/O deflected/O the/O third/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O fourth/O sliced/O his/O stick/O in/O two/O ,/O splintering/O the/O wood/O and/O shearing/O through/O the/O lead/O core/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sobbing/O ,/O Arya/PERSON spun/O and/O ran/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O plunged/O through/O the/O kitchens/O and/O buttery/O ,/O blind/O with/O panic/O ,/O weaving/O between/O cooks/O and/O potboys/O ./O 
A/O baker/O 's/O helper/O stepped/O in/O front/O of/O her/O ,/O holding/O a/O wooden/O tray/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON bowled/O her/O over/O ,/O scattering/O fragrant/O loaves/O of/O fresh-baked/O bread/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
She/O heard/O shouting/O behind/O her/O as/O she/O spun/O around/O a/O portly/O butcher/O who/O stood/O gaping/O at/O her/O with/O a/O cleaver/O in/O his/O hands/O ./O 
His/O arms/O were/O red/O to/O the/O elbow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O All/O that/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O went/O racing/O through/O her/O head/O ./O 
Swift/PERSON as/O a/O deer/O ./O 
Quiet/O as/O a/O shadow/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
Quick/O as/O a/O snake/O ./O 
Calm/O as/O still/O water/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
Strong/O as/O a/O bear/O ./O 
Fierce/O as/O a/O wolverine/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
The/O man/O who/O fears/O losing/O has/O already/O lost/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ./O 
The/O grip/O of/O her/O wooden/O sword/O was/O slick/O with/O sweat/O ,/O and/O Arya/PERSON was/O breathing/O hard/O when/O she/O reached/O the/O turret/O stair/O ./O 
For/O an/O instant/O she/O froze/O ./O 
Up/O or/O down/O ?/O 
Up/O would/O take/O her/O to/O the/O covered/O bridge/O that/O spanned/O the/O small/O court/O to/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O but/O that/O would/O be/O the/O way/O they/O 'd/O expect/O her/O to/O go/O ,/O for/O certain/O ./O 
Never/O do/O what/O they/O expect/O ,/O Syrio/PERSON once/O said/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON went/O down/O ,/O around/O and/O around/O ,/O leaping/O over/O the/O narrow/O stone/O steps/O two/O and/O three/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
She/O emerged/O in/O a/O cavernous/O vaulted/O cellar/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O casks/O of/O ale/O stacked/O twenty/O feet/O tall/O ./O 
The/O only/O light/O came/O through/O narrow/O slanting/O windows/O high/O in/O the/O wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O cellar/O was/O a/O dead/O end/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O way/O out/O but/O the/O way/O she/O had/O come/O in/O ./O 
She/O dare/O not/O go/O back/O up/O those/O steps/O ,/O but/O she/O could/O n't/O stay/O here/O ,/O either/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O find/O her/O father/O and/O tell/O him/O what/O had/O happened/O ./O 
Her/O father/O would/O protect/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON thrust/O her/O wooden/O sword/O through/O her/O belt/O and/O began/O to/O climb/O ,/O leaping/O from/O cask/O to/O cask/O until/O she/O could/O reach/O the/O window/O ./O 
Grasping/O the/O stone/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O she/O pulled/O herself/O up/O ./O 
The/O wall/O was/O three/O feet/O thick/O ,/O the/O window/O a/O tunnel/O slanting/O up/O and/O out/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON wriggled/O toward/O daylight/O ./O 
When/O her/O head/O reached/O ground/O level/O ,/O she/O peered/O across/O the/O bailey/O to/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O stout/O wooden/O door/O hung/O splintered/O and/O broken/O ,/O as/O if/O by/O axes/O ./O 
A/O dead/O man/O sprawled/O facedown/O on/O the/O steps/O ,/O his/O cloak/O tangled/O beneath/O him/O ,/O the/O back/O of/O his/O mailed/O shirt/O soaked/O red/O ./O 
The/O corpse/O 's/O cloak/O was/O grey/O wool/O trimmed/O with/O white/O satin/O ,/O she/O saw/O with/O sudden/O terror/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O tell/O who/O he/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
What/O was/O happening/O ?/O 
Where/O was/O her/O father/O ?/O 
Why/O had/O the/O red/O cloaks/O come/O for/O her/O ?/O 
She/O remembered/O what/O the/O man/O with/O the/O yellow/O beard/O had/O said/O ,/O the/O day/O she/O had/O found/O the/O monsters/O ./O 
If/O one/O Hand/O can/O die/O ,/O why/O not/O a/O second/O ?/O 
Arya/PERSON felt/O tears/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O held/O her/O breath/O to/O listen/O ./O 
She/O heard/O the/O sounds/O of/O fighting/O ,/O shouts/O ,/O screams/O ,/O the/O clang/O of/O steel/O on/O steel/O ,/O coming/O through/O the/O windows/O of/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O could/O not/O go/O back/O ./O 
Her/O father/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON closed/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O she/O was/O too/O frightened/O to/O move/O ./O 
They/O had/O killed/O Jory/PERSON and/O Wyl/O and/O Heward/PERSON ,/O and/O that/O guardsman/O on/O the/O step/O ,/O whoever/O he/O had/O been/O ./O 
They/O could/O kill/O her/O father/O too/O ,/O and/O her/O if/O they/O caught/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O aloud/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O no/O good/O pretending/O to/O be/O a/O water/O dancer/O ,/O Syrio/PERSON had/O been/O a/O water/O dancer/O and/O the/O white/O knight/O had/O probably/O killed/O him/O ,/O and/O anyhow/O she/O was/O only/O a/O little/O girl/O with/O a/O wooden/O stick/O ,/O alone/O and/O afraid/O ./O 
She/O squirmed/O out/O into/O the/O yard/O ,/O glancing/O around/O warily/O as/O she/O climbed/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
The/O castle/O seemed/O deserted/O ./O 
The/O Red/O Keep/O was/O never/O deserted/O ./O 
All/O the/O people/O must/O be/O hiding/O inside/O ,/O their/O doors/O barred/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON glanced/O up/O longingly/O at/O her/O bedchamber/O ,/O then/O moved/O away/O from/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O keeping/O close/O to/O the/O wall/O as/O she/O slid/O from/O shadow/O to/O shadow/O ./O 
She/O pretended/O she/O was/O chasing/O cats/O .../O except/O she/O was/O the/O cat/O now/O ,/O and/O if/O they/O caught/O her/O ,/O they/O would/O kill/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Moving/O between/O buildings/O and/O over/O walls/O ,/O keeping/O stone/O to/O her/O back/O wherever/O possible/O so/O no/O one/O could/O surprise/O her/O ,/O Arya/PERSON reached/O the/O stables/O almost/O without/O incident/O ./O 
A/O dozen/O gold/O cloaks/O in/O mail/O and/O plate/O ran/O past/O as/O she/O was/O edging/O across/O the/O inner/O bailey/O ,/O but/O without/O knowing/O whose/O side/O they/O were/O on/O ,/O she/O hunched/O down/O low/O in/O the/O shadows/O and/O let/O them/O pass/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hullen/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O been/O master/O of/O horse/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION as/O long/O as/O Arya/PERSON could/O remember/O ,/O was/O slumped/O on/O the/O ground/O by/O the/O stable/O door/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O stabbed/O so/O many/O times/O it/O looked/O as/O if/O his/O tunic/O was/O patterned/O with/O scarlet/O flowers/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O certain/O he/O was/O dead/O ,/O but/O when/O she/O crept/O closer/O ,/O his/O eyes/O opened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON Underfoot/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O .../O warn/O your/O .../O your/O lord/O father/O .../O \/O ''/O Frothy/O red/O spittle/O bubbled/O from/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
The/O master/O of/O horse/O closed/O his/O eyes/O again/O and/O said/O no/O more/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O were/O more/O bodies/O ;/O a/O groom/O she/O had/O played/O with/O ,/O and/O three/O of/O her/O father/O 's/O household/O guard/O ./O 
A/O wagon/O ,/O laden/O with/O crates/O and/O chests/O ,/O stood/O abandoned/O near/O the/O door/O of/O the/O stable/O ./O 
The/O dead/O men/O must/O have/O been/O loading/O it/O for/O the/O trip/O to/O the/O docks/O when/O they/O were/O attacked/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON snuck/O closer/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O corpses/O was/O Desmond/PERSON ,/O who/O 'd/O shown/O her/O his/O longsword/O and/O promised/O to/O protect/O her/O father/O ./O 
He/O lay/O on/O his/O back/O ,/O staring/O blindly/O at/O the/O ceiling/O as/O flies/O crawled/O across/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Close/O to/O him/O was/O a/O dead/O man/O in/O the/O red/O cloak/O and/O lion-crest/O helm/O of/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Only/O one/O ,/O though/O ./O 
Every/O northerner/O is/O worth/O ten/O of/O these/O southron/O swords/O ,/O Desmond/PERSON had/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O liar/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O kicking/O his/O body/O in/O a/O sudden/O fury/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O animals/O were/O restless/O in/O their/O stalls/O ,/O whickering/O and/O snorting/O at/O the/O scent/O of/O blood/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON 's/O only/O plan/O was/O to/O saddle/O a/O horse/O and/O flee/O ,/O away/O from/O the/O castle/O and/O the/O city/O ./O 
All/O she/O had/O to/O do/O was/O ''/O ,/O ``/O stay/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O it/O would/O take/O her/O back/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
She/O took/O a/O bridle/O and/O harness/O off/O the/O wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O she/O crossed/O in/O back/O of/O the/O wagon/O ,/O a/O fallen/O chest/O caught/O her/O eye/O ./O 
It/O must/O have/O been/O knocked/O down/O in/O the/O fight/O or/O dropped/O as/O it/O was/O being/O loaded/O ./O 
The/O wood/O had/O split/O ,/O the/O lid/O opening/O to/O spill/O the/O chest/O 's/O contents/O across/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON recognized/O silks/O and/O satins/O and/O velvets/O she/O never/O wore/O ./O 
She/O might/O need/O warm/O clothes/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O though/O .../O and/O besides/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON knelt/O in/O the/O dirt/O among/O the/O scattered/O clothes/O ./O 
She/O found/O a/O heavy/O woolen/O cloak/O ,/O a/O velvet/O skirt/O and/O a/O silk/O tunic/O and/O some/O smallclothes/O ,/O a/O dress/O her/O mother/O had/O embroidered/O for/O her/O ,/O a/O silver/O baby/O bracelet/O she/O might/O sell/O ./O 
Shoving/O the/O broken/O lid/O out/O of/O the/O way/O ,/O she/O groped/O inside/O the/O chest/O for/O Needle/O ./O 
She/O had/O hidden/O it/O way/O down/O at/O the/O bottom/O ,/O under/O everything/O ,/O but/O her/O stuff/O had/O all/O been/O jumbled/O around/O when/O the/O chest/O was/O dropped/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O Arya/PERSON was/O afraid/O someone/O had/O found/O the/O sword/O and/O stolen/O it/O ./O 
Then/O her/O fingers/O felt/O the/O hardness/O of/O metal/O under/O a/O satin/O gown/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O she/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O hissed/O close/O behind/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Startled/O ,/O Arya/PERSON whirled/O ./O 
A/O stableboy/O stood/O behind/O her/O ,/O a/O smirk/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O his/O filthy/O white/O undertunic/O peeking/O out/O from/O beneath/O a/O soiled/O jerkin/O ./O 
His/O boots/O were/O covered/O with/O manure/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O a/O pitchfork/O in/O one/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O do/O n't/O know/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O knows/O her/O ,/O oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Help/O me/O saddle/O a/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON pleaded/O ,/O reaching/O back/O into/O the/O chest/O ,/O groping/O for/O Needle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O 's/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O he/O 'll/O reward/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Father/O 's/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O ./O 
He/O shuffled/O toward/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O the/O queen/O who/O 'll/O be/O rewarding/O me/O ./O 
Come/O here/O ,/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stay/O away/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O fingers/O closed/O around/O Needle/O 's/O hilt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O says/O ,/O come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O grabbed/O her/O arm/O ,/O hard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Everything/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON had/O ever/O taught/O her/O vanished/O in/O a/O heartbeat/O ./O 
In/O that/O instant/O of/O sudden/O terror/O ,/O the/O only/O lesson/O Arya/PERSON could/O remember/O was/O the/O one/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON had/O given/O her/O ,/O the/O very/O first/O ./O 
She/O stuck/O him/O with/O the/O pointy/O end/O ,/O driving/O the/O blade/O upward/O with/O a/O wild/O ,/O hysterical/O strength/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Needle/O went/O through/O his/O leather/O jerkin/O and/O the/O white/O flesh/O of/O his/O belly/O and/O came/O out/O between/O his/O shoulder/O blades/O ./O 
The/O boy/O dropped/O the/O pitchfork/O and/O made/O a/O soft/O noise/O ,/O something/O between/O a/O gasp/O and/O a/O sigh/O ./O 
His/O hands/O closed/O around/O the/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O moaned/O ,/O as/O his/O undertunic/O began/O to/O redden/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O it/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O she/O took/O it/O out/O ,/O he/O died/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O horses/O were/O screaming/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON stood/O over/O the/O body/O ,/O still/O and/O frightened/O in/O the/O face/O of/O death/O ./O 
Blood/O had/O gushed/O from/O the/O boy/O 's/O mouth/O as/O he/O collapsed/O ,/O and/O more/O was/O seeping/O from/O the/O slit/O in/O his/O belly/O ,/O pooling/O beneath/O his/O body/O ./O 
His/O palms/O were/O cut/O where/O he/O 'd/O grabbed/O at/O the/O blade/O ./O 
She/O backed/O away/O slowly/O ,/O Needle/O red/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O get/O away/O ,/O someplace/O far/O from/O here/O ,/O someplace/O safe/O away/O from/O the/O stableboy/O 's/O accusing/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O snatched/O up/O the/O bridle/O and/O harness/O again/O and/O ran/O to/O her/O mare/O ,/O but/O as/O she/O lifted/O the/O saddle/O to/O the/O horse/O 's/O back/O ,/O Arya/PERSON realized/O with/O a/O sudden/O sick/O dread/O that/O the/O castle/O gates/O would/O be/O closed/O ./O 
Even/O the/O postern/O doors/O would/O likely/O be/O guarded/O ./O 
Maybe/O the/O guards/O would/O n't/O recognize/O her/O ./O 
If/O ''/O ,/O ``/O they/O thought/O she/O was/O a/O boy/O ,/O perhaps/O they/O 'd/O let/O her/O .../O no/O ,/O they/O 'd/O have/O orders/O not/O to/O let/O anyone/O out/O ,/O it/O would/O n't/O matter/O whether/O they/O knew/O her/O or/O not/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O there/O was/O another/O way/O out/O of/O the/O castle/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O saddle/O slipped/O from/O Arya/PERSON 's/O fingers/O and/O fell/O to/O the/O dirt/O with/O a/O thump/O and/O a/O puff/O of/O dust/O ./O 
Could/O she/O find/O the/O room/O with/O the/O monsters/O again/O ?/O 
She/O was/O n't/O certain/O ,/O yet/O she/O knew/O she/O had/O to/O try/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O found/O the/O clothing/O she/O 'd/O gathered/O and/O slipped/O into/O the/O cloak/O ,/O concealing/O Needle/O beneath/O its/O folds/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O her/O things/O she/O tied/O in/O a/O roll/O ./O 
With/O the/O bundle/O under/O her/O arm/O ,/O she/O crept/O to/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O stable/O ./O 
Unlatching/O the/O back/O door/O ,/O she/O peeked/O out/O anxiously/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O the/O distant/O sound/O of/O swordplay/O ,/O and/O the/O shivery/O wail/O of/O a/O man/O screaming/O in/O pain/O across/O the/O bailey/O ./O 
She/O would/O need/O to/O go/O down/O the/O serpentine/O steps/O ,/O past/O the/O small/O kitchen/O and/O the/O pig/O yard/O ,/O that/O was/O how/O she/O 'd/O gone/O last/O time/O ,/O chasing/O the/O black/O tomcat/O .../O only/O that/O would/O take/O her/O right/O past/O the/O barracks/O of/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O ./O 
She/O could/O n't/O go/O that/O way/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON tried/O to/O think/O of/O another/O way/O ./O 
If/O she/O crossed/O to/O the/O other/O side/O of/O the/O castle/O ,/O she/O could/O creep/O along/O the/O river/O wall/O and/O through/O the/O little/O godswood/O .../O but/O first/O she/O 'd/O have/O to/O cross/O the/O yard/O ,/O in/O the/O plain/O view/O of/O the/O guards/O on/O the/O walls/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O never/O seen/O so/O many/O men/O on/O the/O walls/O ./O 
Gold/O cloaks/O ,/O most/O of/O them/O ,/O armed/O with/O spears/O ./O 
Some/O of/O them/O knew/O her/O by/O sight/O ./O 
What/O would/O they/O do/O if/O they/O saw/O her/O running/O across/O the/O yard/O ?/O 
She/O 'd/O look/O so/O small/O from/O up/O there/O ,/O would/O they/O be/O able/O to/O tell/O who/O she/O was/O ?/O 
Would/O they/O care/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O to/O leave/O now/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O but/O when/O the/O moment/O came/O ,/O she/O was/O too/O frightened/O to/O move/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Calm/O as/O still/O water/O ,/O a/O small/O voice/O whispered/O in/O her/O ear/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O so/O startled/O she/O almost/O dropped/O her/O bundle/O ./O 
She/O looked/O around/O wildly/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O one/O in/O the/O stable/O but/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O horses/O ,/O and/O the/O dead/O men/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Quiet/O as/O a/O shadow/O ,/O she/O heard/O ./O 
Was/O it/O her/O own/O voice/O ,/O or/O Syrio/PERSON 's/O ?/O 
She/O could/O not/O tell/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O it/O calmed/O her/O fears/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O stepped/O out/O of/O the/O stable/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O scariest/O thing/O she/O 'd/O ever/O done/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O run/O and/O hide/O ,/O but/O she/O made/O herself/O walk/O across/O the/O yard/O ,/O slowly/O ,/O putting/O one/O foot/O in/O front/O of/O the/O other/O as/O if/O she/O had/O all/O the/O time/O in/O the/O world/O and/O no/O reason/O to/O be/O afraid/O of/O anyone/O ./O 
She/O thought/O she/O could/O feel/O their/O eyes/O ,/O like/O bugs/O crawling/O on/O her/O skin/O under/O her/O clothes/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON never/O looked/O up/O ./O 
If/O she/O saw/O them/O watching/O ,/O all/O her/O courage/O would/O desert/O her/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O drop/O the/O bundle/O of/O clothes/O and/O run/O and/O cry/O like/O a/O baby/O ,/O and/O then/O they/O would/O have/O her/O ./O 
She/O kept/O her/O gaze/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O she/O reached/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O royal/O sept/O on/O the/O far/O side/O of/O the/O yard/O ,/O Arya/PERSON was/O cold/O with/O sweat/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O had/O raised/O the/O hue/O and/O cry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sept/O was/O open/O and/O empty/O ./O 
Inside/O ,/O half/O a/O hundred/O prayer/O candles/O burned/O in/O a/O fragrant/O silence/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON figured/O the/O gods/O would/O never/O miss/O two/O ./O 
She/O stuffed/O them/O up/O her/O sleeves/O ,/O and/O left/O by/O a/O back/O window/O ./O 
Sneaking/O back/O to/O the/O alley/O where/O she/O had/O cornered/O the/O one-eared/O torn/O was/O easy/O ,/O but/O after/O that/O she/O got/O lost/O ./O 
She/O crawled/O in/O and/O out/O of/O windows/O ,/O hopped/O over/O walls/O ,/O and/O felt/O her/O way/O through/O dark/O cellars/O ,/O quiet/O as/O a/O shadow/O ./O 
Once/O she/O heard/O a/O woman/O weeping/O ./O 
It/O took/O her/O ''/O ,/O ``/O more/O than/O an/O hour/O to/O find/O the/O low/O narrow/O window/O that/O slanted/O down/O to/O the/O dungeon/O where/O the/O monsters/O waited/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O tossed/O her/O bundle/O through/O and/O doubled/O back/O to/O light/O her/O candle/O ./O 
That/O was/O chancy/O ;/O the/O fire/O she/O 'd/O remembered/O seeing/O had/O burnt/O down/O to/O embers/O ,/O and/O she/O heard/O voices/O as/O she/O was/O blowing/O on/O the/O coals/O ./O 
Cupping/O her/O fingers/O around/O the/O flickering/O candle/O ,/O she/O went/O out/O the/O window/O as/O they/O were/O coming/O in/O the/O door/O ,/O without/O ever/O getting/O a/O glimpse/O of/O who/O it/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O This/O time/O the/O monsters/O did/O not/O frighten/O her/O ./O 
They/O seemed/O almost/O old/O friends/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON held/O the/O candle/O over/O her/O head/O ./O 
With/O each/O step/O she/O took/O ,/O the/O shadows/O moved/O against/O the/O walls/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O were/O turning/O to/O watch/O her/O pass/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dragons/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
She/O slid/O Needle/O out/O from/O under/O her/O cloak/O ./O 
The/O slender/O blade/O seemed/O very/O small/O and/O the/O dragons/O very/O big/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O Arya/PERSON felt/O better/O with/O steel/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O long/O windowless/O hall/O beyond/O the/O door/O was/O as/O black/O as/O she/O remembered/O ./O 
She/O held/O Needle/O in/O her/O left/O hand/O ,/O her/O sword/O hand/O ,/O the/O candle/O in/O her/O right/O fist/O ./O 
Hot/O wax/O ran/O down/O across/O her/O knuckles/O ./O 
The/O entrance/O to/O the/O well/O had/O been/O to/O the/O left/O ,/O so/O Arya/PERSON went/O right/O ./O 
Part/O of/O her/O wanted/O to/O run/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O afraid/O of/O snuffing/O out/O her/O candle/O ./O 
She/O heard/O the/O faint/O squeaking/O of/O rats/O and/O glimpsed/O a/O pair/O of/O tiny/O glowing/O eyes/O on/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O light/O ,/O but/O rats/O did/O not/O scare/O her/O ./O 
Other/O things/O did/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O so/O easy/O to/O hide/O here/O ,/O as/O she/O had/O hidden/O from/O the/O wizard/O and/O the/O man/O with/O the/O forked/O beard/O ./O 
She/O could/O almost/O see/O the/O stableboy/O standing/O against/O the/O wall/O ,/O his/O hands/O curled/O into/O claws/O with/O the/O blood/O still/O dripping/O from/O the/O deep/O gashes/O in/O his/O palms/O where/O Needle/O had/O cut/O him/O ./O 
He/O might/O be/O waiting/O to/O grab/O her/O as/O she/O passed/O ./O 
He/O would/O see/O her/O candle/O coming/O a/O long/O way/O off/O ./O 
Maybe/O she/O would/O be/O better/O off/O without/O the/O light/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Fear/O cuts/O deeper/O than/O swords/O ,/O the/O quiet/O voice/O inside/O her/O whispered/O ./O 
Suddenly/O Arya/PERSON remembered/O the/O crypts/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
They/O were/O a/O lot/O scarier/O than/O this/O place/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O been/O just/O a/O little/O girl/O the/O first/O time/O she/O saw/O them/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O Robb/PERSON had/O taken/O them/O down/O ,/O her/O and/O Sansa/PERSON and/O baby/O Bran/O ,/O who/O 'd/O been/O no/O bigger/O than/O Rickon/PERSON was/O now/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O only/O had/O one/O candle/O between/O them/O ,/O and/O Bran/O 's/O eyes/O had/O gotten/O as/O big/O as/O saucers/O as/O he/O stared/O at/O the/O stone/O faces/O of/O the/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O ,/O with/O their/O wolves/O at/O their/O feet/O and/O their/O iron/O swords/O across/O their/O laps/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON took/O them/O all/O the/O way/O down/O to/O the/O end/O ,/O past/O Grandfather/O and/O Brandon/PERSON and/O Lyanna/PERSON ,/O to/O show/O them/O their/O own/O tombs/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON kept/O looking/O at/O the/O stubby/O little/O candle/O ,/O anxious/O that/O it/O might/O go/O out/O ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON had/O told/O her/O there/O were/O spiders/O down/O here/O ,/O and/O rats/O as/O big/O as/O dogs/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON smiled/O when/O she/O said/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O are/O worse/O things/O than/O spiders/O and/O rats/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O where/O the/O dead/O walk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O That/O was/O when/O they/O heard/O the/O sound/O ,/O low/O and/O deep/O and/O shivery/O ./O 
Baby/ORGANIZATION Bran/ORGANIZATION had/O clutched/O at/O Arya/PERSON 's/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O spirit/O stepped/O out/O of/O the/O open/O tomb/O ,/O pale/O white/O and/O moaning/O for/O blood/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ran/O shrieking/O for/O the/O stairs/O ,/O and/O Bran/O wrapped/O himself/O around/O Robb/PERSON 's/O leg/O ,/O sobbing/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON stood/O her/O ground/O and/O gave/O the/O spirit/O a/O punch/O ./O 
It/O was/O only/O Jon/PERSON ,/O covered/O with/O flour/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O stupid/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O scared/O the/O baby/O ,/O \/O ''/O but/O Jon/PERSON and/O Robb/PERSON just/O laughed/O and/O laughed/O ,/O and/O pretty/O soon/O Bran/O and/O Arya/PERSON were/O laughing/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O memory/O made/O Arya/PERSON smile/O ,/O and/O after/O that/O the/O darkness/O held/O no/O more/O terrors/O for/O her/O ./O 
The/O stableboy/O was/O dead/O ,/O she/O 'd/O killed/O him/O ,/O and/O if/O he/O jumped/O out/O at/O her/O she/O 'd/O kill/O him/O again/O ./O 
She/O was/O ''/O ,/O ``/O going/O home/O ./O 
Everything/O would/O be/O better/O once/O she/O was/O home/O again/O ,/O safe/O behind/O Winterfell/ORGANIZATION 's/O grey/O granite/O walls/O ./O 
Her/O footsteps/O sent/O soft/O echoes/O hurrying/O ahead/O of/O her/O as/O Arya/PERSON plunged/O deeper/O into/O the/O darkness/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
