-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O he/O had/O taken/O his/O pleasure/O ,/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON rose/O from/O their/O sleeping/O mats/O to/O tower/O above/O her/O ./O 
His/O skin/O shone/O dark/O as/O bronze/O in/O the/O ruddy/O light/O from/O the/O brazier/O ,/O the/O faint/O lines/O of/O old/O scars/O visible/O on/O his/O broad/O chest/O ./O 
Ink-black/O hair/O ,/O loose/O and/O unbound/O ,/O cascaded/O over/O his/O shoulders/O and/O down/O his/O back/O ,/O well/O past/O his/O waist/O ./O 
His/O manhood/O glistened/O wetly/O ./O 
The/O khal/O 's/O mouth/O twisted/O in/O a/O frown/O beneath/O the/O droop/O of/O his/O long/O mustachio/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O has/O no/O need/O of/O iron/O chairs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON propped/O herself/O on/O an/O elbow/O to/O look/O up/O at/O him/O ,/O so/O tall/O and/O magnificent/O ./O 
She/O loved/O his/O hair/O especially/O ./O 
It/O had/O never/O been/O cut/O ;/O he/O had/O never/O known/O defeat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O prophesied/O that/O the/O stallion/O will/O ride/O to/O the/O ends/O of/O the/O earth/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O earth/O ends/O at/O the/O black/O salt/O sea/O ,/O \/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON answered/O at/O once/O ./O 
He/O wet/O a/O cloth/O in/O a/O basin/O of/O warm/O water/O to/O wipe/O the/O sweat/O and/O oil/O from/O his/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O horse/O can/O cross/O the/O poison/O water/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O there/O are/O ships/O by/O the/O thousand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O as/O she/O had/O told/O him/O before/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wooden/O horses/O with/O a/O hundred/O legs/O ,/O that/O fly/O across/O the/O sea/O on/O wings/O full/O of/O wind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON did/O not/O want/O to/O hear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O will/O speak/O no/O more/O of/O wooden/O horses/O and/O iron/O chairs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O dropped/O the/O cloth/O and/O began/O to/O dress/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O day/O I/O will/O go/O to/O the/O grass/O and/O hunt/O ,/O woman/O wife/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O as/O he/O shrugged/O into/O a/O painted/O vest/O and/O buckled/O on/O a/O wide/O belt/O with/O heavy/O medallions/O of/O silver/O ,/O gold/O ,/O and/O bronze/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O sun-and-stars/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON would/O take/O his/O bloodriders/O and/O ride/O in/O search/O of/O hrakkar/O ,/O the/O great/O white/O lion/O of/O the/O plains/O ./O 
If/O they/O returned/O triumphant/O ,/O her/O lord/O husband/O 's/O joy/O would/O be/O fierce/O ,/O and/O he/O might/O be/O willing/O to/O hear/O her/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Savage/O beasts/O he/O did/O not/O fear/O ,/O nor/O any/O man/O who/O had/O ever/O drawn/O breath/O ,/O but/O the/O sea/O was/O a/O different/O matter/O ./O 
To/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O water/O that/O a/O horse/O could/O not/O drink/O was/O something/O foul/O ;/O the/O heaving/O grey-green/O plains/O of/O the/O ocean/O filled/O them/O with/O superstitious/O loathing/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON was/O a/O bolder/O man/O than/O the/O other/O horselords/O in/O half/O a/O hundred/O ways/O ,/O she/O had/O found/O .../O but/O not/O in/O this/O ./O 
If/O only/O she/O could/O get/O him/O onto/O a/O ship/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O After/O the/O khal/O and/O his/O bloodriders/O had/O ridden/O off/O with/O their/O bows/O ,/O Dany/PERSON summoned/O her/O handmaids/O ./O 
Her/O body/O felt/O so/O fat/O and/O ungainly/O now/O that/O she/O welcomed/O the/O help/O of/O their/O strong/O arms/O and/O deft/O hands/O ,/O whereas/O before/O she/O had/O often/O been/O uncomfortable/O with/O the/O way/O they/O fussed/O and/O fluttered/O about/O her/O ./O 
They/O scrubbed/O her/O clean/O and/O dressed/O her/O in/O sandsilk/O ,/O loose/O and/O flowing/O ./O 
As/O Doreah/PERSON combed/O out/O her/O hair/O ,/O she/O sent/O Jhiqui/PERSON to/O find/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O knight/O came/O at/O once/O ./O 
He/O wore/O horsehair/O leggings/O and/O painted/O vest/O ,/O like/O a/O rider/O ./O 
Coarse/O black/O hair/O covered/O his/O thick/O chest/O and/O muscular/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O princess/O ./O 
How/O may/O I/O serve/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O must/O talk/O to/O my/O lord/O husband/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON says/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O will/O have/O all/O the/O lands/O of/O the/O earth/O to/O rule/O ,/O and/O no/O need/O to/O cross/O the/O poison/O water/O ./O 
He/O talks/O of/O leading/O his/O khalasar/O east/O after/O Rhaego/PERSON is/O born/O ,/O to/O plunder/O the/O lands/O around/O the/O Jade/O Sea/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O knight/O looked/O thoughtful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O khal/O has/O never/O seen/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O are/O nothing/O to/O him/O ./O 
If/O he/O thinks/O of/O them/O at/O all/O ,/O no/O doubt/O he/O thinks/O of/O islands/O ,/O a/O few/O small/O cities/O ''/O ,/O ``/O clinging/O to/O rocks/O in/O the/O manner/O of/O Lorath/O or/O Lys/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O stormy/O seas/O ./O 
The/O riches/O of/O the/O east/O must/O seem/O a/O more/O tempting/O prospect/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O he/O must/O ride/O west/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O despairing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O help/O me/O make/O him/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O never/O seen/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O either/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O yet/O she/O felt/O as/O though/O she/O knew/O them/O from/O all/O the/O tales/O her/O brother/O had/O told/O her/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON had/O promised/O her/O a/O thousand/O times/O that/O he/O would/O take/O her/O back/O one/O day/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O dead/O now/O and/O his/O promises/O had/O died/O with/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O do/O things/O in/O their/O own/O time/O ,/O for/O their/O own/O reasons/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O knight/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O patience/O ,/O Princess/O ./O 
Do/O not/O make/O your/O brother/O 's/O mistake/O ./O 
We/O will/O go/O home/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Home/O ?/O 
The/O word/O made/O her/O feel/O sad/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O his/O Bear/LOCATION Island/LOCATION ,/O but/O what/O was/O home/O to/O her/O ?/O 
A/O few/O tales/O ,/O names/O recited/O as/O solemnly/O as/O the/O words/O of/O a/O prayer/O ,/O the/O fading/O memory/O of/O a/O red/O door/O .../O was/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON to/O be/O her/O home/O forever/O ?/O 
When/O she/O looked/O at/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O ,/O was/O she/O looking/O at/O her/O future/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O must/O have/O seen/O the/O sadness/O on/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O great/O caravan/O arrived/O during/O the/O night/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ./O 
Four/O hundred/O horses/O ,/O from/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION by/O way/O of/O Norvos/LOCATION and/O Qohor/PERSON ,/O under/O the/O command/O of/O Merchant/O Captain/O Byan/PERSON Votyris/PERSON ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON may/O have/O sent/O a/O letter/O ./O 
Would/O you/O care/O to/O visit/O the/O Western/O Market/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON stirred/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O markets/O came/O alive/O when/O a/O caravan/O had/O come/O in/O ./O 
You/O could/O never/O tell/O what/O treasures/O the/O traders/O might/O bring/O this/O time/O ,/O and/O it/O would/O be/O good/O to/O hear/O men/O speaking/O Valyrian/O again/O ,/O as/O they/O did/O in/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Irri/O ,/O have/O them/O prepare/O a/O litter/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O tell/O your/O khas/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O withdrawing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON had/O been/O with/O her/O ,/O Dany/PERSON would/O have/O ridden/O her/O silver/O ./O 
Among/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O mothers/O stayed/O on/O horseback/O almost/O up/O to/O the/O moment/O of/O birth/O ,/O and/O she/O did/O not/O want/O to/O seem/O weak/O in/O her/O husband/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
But/O with/O the/O khal/O off/O hunting/O ,/O it/O was/O pleasant/O to/O lie/O back/O on/O soft/O cushions/O and/O be/O carried/O across/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O with/O red/O silk/O curtains/O to/O shield/O her/O from/O the/O sun/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON saddled/O up/O and/O rode/O beside/O her/O ,/O with/O the/O four/O young/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O and/O her/O handmaids/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O day/O was/O warm/O and/O cloudless/O ,/O the/O sky/O a/O deep/O blue/O ./O 
When/O the/O wind/O blew/O ,/O she/O could/O smell/O the/O rich/O scents/O of/O grass/O and/O earth/O ./O 
As/O her/O litter/O passed/O beneath/O the/O stolen/O monuments/O ,/O she/O went/O from/O sunlight/O to/O shadow/O and/O back/O again/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON swayed/O along/O ,/O studying/O the/O faces/O of/O dead/O heroes/O and/O forgotten/O kings/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O if/O the/O gods/O of/O burned/O cities/O could/O still/O answer/O prayers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O I/O were/O not/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O she/O thought/O wistfully/O ,/O this/O could/O be/O my/O home/O ./O 
She/O was/O khaleesi/O ,/O she/O had/O a/O strong/O man/O and/O a/O swift/O horse/O ,/O handmaids/O to/O serve/O her/O ,/O warriors/O to/O keep/O her/O safe/O ,/O an/O honored/O place/O in/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O awaiting/O her/O when/O she/O grew/O old/O .../O and/O in/O her/O womb/O grew/O a/O son/O who/O would/O one/O day/O bestride/O the/O world/O ./O 
That/O should/O be/O enough/O for/O any/O woman/O .../O but/O not/O for/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
With/O Viserys/O gone/O ,/O Daenerys/PERSON was/O the/O last/O ,/O the/O very/O last/O ./O 
She/O was/O the/O seed/O of/O kings/O and/O conquerors/O ,/O and/O so/O too/O the/O child/O inside/O her/O ./O 
She/O must/O not/O forget/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Western/O Market/O was/O a/O great/O square/O of/O beaten/O earth/O surrounded/O by/O warrens/O of/O mud-baked/O brick/O ,/O animal/O pens/O ,/O whitewashed/O drinking/O halls/O ./O 
Hummocks/O rose/O from/O the/O ground/O like/O the/O backs/O of/O great/O subterranean/O beasts/O breaking/O the/O surface/O ,/O yawning/O black/O mouths/O leading/O down/O to/O cool/O ''/O ,/O ``/O and/O cavernous/O storerooms/O below/O ./O 
The/O interior/O of/O the/O square/O was/O a/O maze/O of/O stalls/O and/O crookback/O aisles/O ,/O shaded/O by/O awnings/O of/O woven/O grass/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O hundred/O merchants/O and/O traders/O were/O unloading/O their/O goods/O and/O setting/O up/O in/O stalls/O when/O they/O arrived/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O the/O great/O market/O seemed/O hushed/O and/O deserted/O compared/O to/O the/O teeming/O bazaars/O that/O Dany/PERSON remembered/O from/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O other/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
The/O caravans/O made/O their/O way/O to/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON from/O east/O and/O west/O not/O so/O much/O to/O sell/O to/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON as/O to/O trade/O with/O each/O other/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O explained/O ./O 
The/O riders/O let/O them/O come/O and/O go/O unmolested/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O observed/O the/O peace/O of/O the/O sacred/O city/O ,/O did/O not/O profane/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION or/O the/O Womb/O of/O the/O World/O ,/O and/O honored/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O with/O the/O traditional/O gifts/O of/O salt/O ,/O silver/O ,/O and/O seed/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON did/O not/O truly/O comprehend/O this/O business/O of/O buying/O and/O selling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON liked/O the/O strangeness/O of/O the/O Eastern/O Market/O too/O ,/O with/O all/O its/O queer/O sights/O and/O sounds/O and/O smells/O ./O 
She/O often/O spent/O her/O mornings/O there/O ,/O nibbling/O tree/O eggs/O ,/O locust/O pie/O ,/O and/O green/O noodles/O ,/O listening/O to/O the/O high/O ululating/O voices/O of/O the/O spellsingers/O ,/O gaping/O at/O manticores/O in/O silver/O cages/O and/O immense/O grey/O elephants/O and/O the/O striped/O black-and-white/O horses/O of/O the/O Jogos/ORGANIZATION Nhai/ORGANIZATION ./O 
She/O enjoyed/O watching/O all/O the/O people/O too/O :/O dark/O solemn/O Asshai'i/O and/O tall/O pale/O Qartheen/O ,/O the/O bright-eyed/O men/O of/O Yi/PERSON Ti/PERSON in/O monkey-tail/O hats/O ,/O warrior/O maids/O from/O Bayasabhad/LOCATION ,/O Shamyriana/LOCATION ,/O and/O Kayakayanaya/LOCATION with/O iron/O rings/O in/O their/O nipples/O and/O rubies/O in/O their/O cheeks/O ,/O even/O the/O dour/O and/O frightening/O Shadow/O Men/O ,/O who/O covered/O their/O arms/O and/O legs/O and/O chests/O with/O tattoos/O and/O hid/O their/O faces/O behind/O masks/O ./O 
The/O Eastern/O Market/O was/O a/O place/O of/O wonder/O and/O magic/O for/O Dany/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O the/O Western/O Market/O smelled/O of/O home/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O Irri/PERSON and/O Jhiqui/PERSON helped/O her/O from/O her/O litter/O ,/O she/O sniffed/O ,/O and/O recognized/O the/O sharp/O odors/O of/O garlic/O and/O pepper/O ,/O scents/O that/O reminded/O Dany/PERSON of/O days/O long/O gone/O in/O the/O alleys/O of/O Tyrosh/LOCATION and/O Myr/ORGANIZATION and/O brought/O a/O fond/O smile/O to/O her/O face/O ./O 
Under/O that/O she/O smelled/O the/O heady/O sweet/O perfumes/O of/O Lys/O ./O 
She/O saw/O slaves/O carrying/O bolts/O of/O intricate/O Myrish/O lace/O and/O fine/O wools/O in/O a/O dozen/O rich/O colors/O ./O 
Caravan/O guards/O wandered/O among/O the/O aisles/O in/O copper/O helmets/O and/O knee-length/O tunics/O of/O quilted/O yellow/O cotton/O ,/O empty/O scabbards/O swinging/O from/O their/O woven/O leather/O belts/O ./O 
Behind/O one/O stall/O an/O armorer/O displayed/O steel/O breastplates/O worked/O with/O gold/O and/O silver/O in/O ornate/O patterns/O ,/O and/O helms/O hammered/O in/O the/O shapes/O of/O fanciful/O beasts/O ./O 
Next/O to/O him/O was/O a/O pretty/O young/O woman/O selling/O Lannisport/O goldwork/O ,/O rings/O and/O brooches/O and/O tores/O and/O exquisitely/O wrought/O medallions/O suitable/O for/O belting/O ./O 
A/O huge/O eunuch/O guarded/O her/O stall/O ,/O mute/O and/O hairless/O ,/O dressed/O in/O sweat-stained/O velvets/O and/O scowling/O at/O anyone/O who/O came/O close/O ./O 
Across/O the/O aisle/O ,/O a/O fat/O cloth/O trader/O from/O Yi/PERSON Ti/PERSON was/O haggling/O with/O a/O Pentoshi/LOCATION over/O the/O price/O of/O some/O green/O dye/O ,/O the/O monkey/O tail/O on/O his/O hat/O swaying/O back/O and/O forth/O as/O he/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O was/O a/O little/O girl/O ,/O I/O loved/O to/O play/O in/O the/O bazaar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON as/O they/O wandered/O down/O the/O shady/O aisle/O between/O the/O stalls/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O so/O alive/O there/O ,/O all/O the/O people/O shouting/O and/O laughing/O ,/O so/O many/O wonderful/O things/O to/O look/O at/O .../O though/O we/O seldom/O had/O enough/O coin/O to/O buy/O anything/O .../O well/O ,/O except/O for/O a/O sausage/O now/O and/O again/O ,/O or/O honeyfingers/O .../O do/O they/O have/O honeyfingers/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O the/O kind/O they/O bake/O in/O Tyrosh/LOCATION ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cakes/O ,/O are/O they/O ?/O 
I/O could/O not/O say/O ,/O Princess/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O bowed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O would/O pardon/O me/O for/O a/O time/O ,/O I/O will/O seek/O out/O the/O captain/O and/O see/O if/O he/O has/O letters/O for/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O well/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O help/O you/O find/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O need/O for/O you/O to/O trouble/O yourself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON glanced/O away/O impatiently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Enjoy/O the/O market/O ./O 
I/O will/O rejoin/O you/O when/O my/O business/O is/O concluded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Curious/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O as/O she/O watched/O him/O stride/O off/O through/O the/O throngs/O ./O 
She/O did/O n't/O see/O why/O she/O should/O not/O go/O with/O him/O ./O 
Perhaps/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON meant/O to/O find/O a/O woman/O after/O he/O met/O with/O the/O merchant/O captain/O ./O 
Whores/O frequently/O traveled/O with/O the/O caravans/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O and/O some/O men/O were/O queerly/O shy/O about/O their/O couplings/O ./O 
She/O gave/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O the/O others/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O handmaids/O trailed/O along/O as/O Dany/PERSON resumed/O her/O stroll/O through/O the/O market/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O look/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O exclaimed/O to/O Doreah/LOCATION ,/O \/O ``/O those/O are/O the/O kind/O of/O sausages/O I/O meant/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O pointed/O to/O a/O stall/O where/O a/O wizened/O little/O woman/O was/O grilling/O meat/O and/O onions/O on/O a/O hot/O firestone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O make/O them/O with/O lots/O of/O garlic/O and/O hot/O peppers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Delighted/O with/O her/O discovery/O ,/O Dany/PERSON insisted/O the/O others/O join/O her/O for/O a/O sausage/O ./O 
Her/O handmaids/O wolfed/O theirs/O down/O giggling/O and/O grinning/O ,/O though/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O sniffed/O at/O the/O grilled/O meat/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O taste/O different/O than/O I/O remember/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O after/O her/O first/O few/O bites/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O I/O make/O them/O with/O pork/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O woman/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O all/O my/O pigs/O died/O on/O the/O Dothraki/O sea/O ./O 
These/O are/O made/O of/O horsemeat/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O but/O I/O spice/O them/O the/O same/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON felt/O disappointed/O ,/O but/O Quaro/PERSON liked/O his/O sausage/O so/O well/O he/O decided/O to/O have/O another/O one/O ,/O and/O Rakharo/PERSON had/O to/O outdo/O him/O and/O eat/O three/O more/O ,/O belching/O loudly/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON giggled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O not/O laughed/O since/O your/O brother/O the/O Khal/PERSON Rhaggat/PERSON was/O crowned/O by/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Irri/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O good/O to/O see/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON smiled/O shyly/O ./O 
It/O was/O sweet/O to/O laugh/O ./O 
She/O felt/O half/O a/O girl/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O wandered/O for/O half/O the/O morning/O ./O 
She/O saw/O a/O beautiful/O feathered/O cloak/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION ,/O and/O took/O it/O for/O a/O gift/O ./O 
In/O return/O ,/O she/O gave/O the/O merchant/O a/O silver/O medallion/O from/O her/O belt/O ./O 
That/O was/O how/O it/O was/O done/O among/O the/O Dothraki/O ./O 
A/O birdseller/O taught/O a/O green-and-red/O parrot/O to/O say/O her/O name/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON laughed/O again/O ,/O yet/O still/O refused/O to/O take/O him/O ./O 
What/O would/O she/O do/O with/O a/O green/O -/O and-red/O parrot/O in/O a/O khalasar/O ?/O 
She/O did/O take/O a/O dozen/O flasks/O of/O scented/O oils/O ,/O the/O perfumes/O of/O her/O childhood/O ;/O she/O had/O only/O to/O close/O her/O eyes/O and/O sniff/O them/O and/O she/O could/O see/O the/O big/O house/O with/O the/O red/O door/O once/O more/O ./O 
When/O Doreah/PERSON looked/O longingly/O at/O a/O fertility/O charm/O at/O a/O magician/O 's/O booth/O ,/O Dany/PERSON took/O that/O too/O and/O gave/O it/O to/O the/O handmaid/O ,/O thinking/O that/O now/O she/O should/O find/O something/O for/O Irri/ORGANIZATION and/O Jhiqui/PERSON as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Turning/O a/O corner/O ,/O they/O came/O upon/O a/O wine/O merchant/O offering/O thimble-sized/O cups/O of/O his/O wares/O to/O the/O passersby/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O reds/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O cried/O in/O fluent/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O sweet/O reds/O ,/O from/O Lys/PERSON and/O Volantis/PERSON and/O the/O Arbor/PERSON ./O 
Whites/O from/O Lys/O ,/O Tyroshi/PERSON pear/O brandy/O ,/O firewine/O ,/O pepperwine/O ,/O the/O pale/O green/O nectars/O of/O Myr/O ./O 
Smokeberry/O browns/O and/O Andalish/O sours/O ,/O I/O have/O them/O ,/O I/O have/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O a/O small/O man/O ,/O slender/O and/O handsome/O ,/O his/O flaxen/O hair/O curled/O and/O perfumed/O after/O the/O fashion/O of/O Lys/O ./O 
When/O Dany/PERSON paused/O before/O his/O stall/O ,/O he/O bowed/O low/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O taste/O for/O the/O khaleesi/O ?/O 
I/O have/O a/O sweet/O red/O from/O Dome/LOCATION ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O it/O sings/O of/O plums/O and/O cherries/O and/O rich/O dark/O oak/O ./O 
A/O cask/O ,/O a/O cup/O ,/O a/O swallow/O ?/O 
One/O taste/O ,/O and/O you/O will/O name/O your/O child/O after/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O son/O has/O his/O name/O ,/O but/O I/O will/O try/O your/O summerwine/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O in/O Valyrian/LOCATION ,/O Valyrian/PERSON as/O they/O spoke/O it/O in/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
The/O words/O felt/O strange/O on/O her/O tongue/O ,/O after/O so/O long/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O a/O taste/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O merchant/O must/O have/O taken/O her/O for/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O with/O her/O clothes/O and/O her/O oiled/O hair/O and/O sun/O -/O browned/O skin/O ./O 
When/O she/O spoke/O ,/O he/O gaped/O at/O her/O in/O astonishment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O you/O are/O .../O Tyroshi/O ?/O 
Can/O it/O be/O so/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O speech/O may/O be/O Tyroshi/LOCATION ,/O and/O my/O garb/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O but/O I/O am/O of/O Westeros/PERSON ,/O of/O the/O Sunset/O Kingdoms/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Doreah/PERSON stepped/O up/O beside/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O the/O honor/O to/O address/O Daenerys/O of/O the/O House/O Targaryen/O ,/O Daenerys/PERSON Stormborn/PERSON ,/O khaleesi/O of/O the/O riding/O men/O and/O princess/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wine/O merchant/O dropped/O to/O his/O knees/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O bowing/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rise/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON commanded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O still/O like/O to/O taste/O that/O summerwine/O you/O spoke/O of/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O man/O bounded/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O ?/O 
Dornish/O swill/O ./O 
It/O is/O not/O worthy/O of/O a/O princess/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O dry/O red/O from/O the/O Arbor/PERSON ,/O crisp/O and/O delectable/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O let/O me/O give/O you/O a/O cask/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O visits/O to/O the/O Free/O Cities/O had/O given/O him/O a/O taste/O for/O good/O wine/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON knew/O that/O such/O a/O noble/O vintage/O would/O please/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O honor/O me/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O murmured/O sweetly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O honor/O is/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O merchant/O rummaged/O about/O in/O the/O back/O of/O his/O stall/O and/O produced/O a/O small/O oaken/O cask/O ./O 
Burned/O into/O the/O wood/O was/O a/O cluster/O of/O grapes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Redwyne/O sigil/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O pointing/O ,/O \/O ``/O for/O the/O Arbor/PERSON ./O 
There/O is/O no/O finer/O drink/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON and/O I/O will/O share/O it/O together/O ./O 
Aggo/O ,/O take/O this/O back/O to/O my/O litter/O ,/O if/O you/O 'd/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O wineseller/O beamed/O as/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON hefted/O the/O cask/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O did/O not/O realize/O that/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O returned/O until/O she/O heard/O the/O knight/O say/O ,/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O was/O strange/O ,/O brusque/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Aggo/O ,/O put/O down/O that/O cask/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Aggo/O looked/O at/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
She/O gave/O a/O hesitant/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O is/O something/O wrong/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O a/O thirst/O ./O 
Open/O it/O ,/O wineseller/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O merchant/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wine/O is/O for/O the/O khaleesi/O ,/O not/O for/O the/O likes/O of/O you/O ,/O ser/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/PERSON moved/O closer/O to/O the/O stall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O do/O n't/O open/O it/O ,/O I/O 'll/O crack/O it/O open/O with/O your/O head/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O carried/O no/O weapons/O here/O in/O the/O sacred/O city/O ,/O save/O his/O hands-yet/O his/O hands/O were/O enough/O ,/O big/O ,/O hard/O ,/O dangerous/O ,/O his/O knuckles/O covered/O with/O coarse/O dark/O hairs/O ./O 
The/O wineseller/O hesitated/O a/O moment/O ,/O then/O took/O up/O his/O hammer/O and/O knocked/O the/O plug/O from/O the/O cask/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pour/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON commanded/O ./O 
The/O four/O young/O warriors/O of/O Dany/PERSON '/O s/O khas/O arrayed/O themselves/O behind/O him/O ,/O frowning/O ,/O watching/O with/O their/O dark/O ,/O almond-shaped/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O be/O a/O crime/O to/O drink/O this/O rich/O a/O wine/O without/O letting/O it/O breathe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O wineseller/O had/O not/O put/O his/O hammer/O down/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON reached/O for/O the/O whip/O coiled/O at/O his/O belt/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON stopped/O him/O with/O a/O light/O touch/O on/O the/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O as/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON says/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
People/O were/O stopping/O to/O watch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O man/O gave/O her/O a/O quick/O ,/O sullen/O glance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O the/O princess/O commands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O to/O set/O aside/O his/O hammer/O to/O lift/O the/O cask/O ./O 
He/O filled/O two/O thimble-sized/O tasting/O cups/O ,/O pouring/O so/O deftly/O he/O did/O not/O spill/O a/O drop/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/PERSON lifted/O a/O cup/O and/O sniffed/O at/O the/O wine/O ,/O frowning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sweet/O ,/O is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O wineseller/O said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O you/O smell/O the/O fruit/O ,/O ser/O ?/O 
The/O perfume/O of/O the/O Arbor/PERSON ./O 
Taste/O it/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O and/O tell/O me/O it/O is/O n't/O the/O finest/O ,/O richest/O wine/O that/O 's/O ever/O touched/O your/O tongue/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON offered/O him/O the/O cup/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O taste/O it/O first/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O worthy/O of/O this/O vintage/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O a/O poor/O wine/O merchant/O who/O drinks/O up/O his/O own/O wares/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O smile/O was/O amiable/O ,/O yet/O she/O could/O see/O the/O sheen/O of/O sweat/O on/O his/O brow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O drink/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O cold/O as/O ice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Empty/O the/O cup/O ,/O or/O I/O will/O tell/O them/O to/O hold/O you/O down/O while/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON pours/O the/O whole/O cask/O down/O your/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wineseller/O shrugged/O ,/O reached/O for/O the/O cup/O .../O and/O grabbed/O the/O cask/O instead/O ,/O flinging/O it/O at/O her/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON bulled/O into/O her/O ,/O knocking/O her/O out/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
The/O cask/O bounced/O off/O his/O shoulder/O and/O smashed/O open/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON stumbled/O and/O lost/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O screamed/O ,/O thrusting/O her/O hands/O out/O to/O break/O her/O fall/O .../O and/O Doreah/PERSON caught/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O and/O wrenched/O her/O backward/O ,/O so/O she/O landed/O on/O her/O legs/O and/O not/O her/O belly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O trader/O vaulted/O over/O the/O stall/O ,/O darting/O between/O Aggo/LOCATION and/O Rakharo/LOCATION ./O 
Quaro/PERSON reached/O for/O an/O arakh/O that/O was/O not/O there/O as/O the/O blond/O man/O slammed/O him/O aside/O ./O 
He/O raced/O down/O the/O aisle/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON heard/O the/O snap/O of/O Jhogo/PERSON 's/O whip/O ,/O saw/O the/O leather/O lick/O out/O and/O coil/O around/O the/O wineseller/O 's/O leg/O ./O 
The/O man/O sprawled/O face/O first/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O dozen/O caravan/O guards/O had/O come/O running/O ./O 
With/O them/O was/O the/O master/O himself/O ,/O Merchant/O Captain/O Byan/PERSON Votyris/PERSON ,/O a/O diminutive/O Norvoshi/O with/O skin/O like/O old/O leather/O and/O a/O bristling/O blue/O mustachio/O that/O swept/O up/O to/O his/O ears/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O know/O what/O had/O happened/O without/O a/O word/O being/O spoken/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O this/O one/O away/O to/O await/O the/O pleasure/O of/O the/O khal/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O commanded/O ,/O gesturing/O at/O the/O man/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Two/O guards/O hauled/O the/O wineseller/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O goods/O I/O gift/O to/O you/O as/O well/O ,/O Princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O merchant/O captain/O went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Small/O token/O of/O regret/O ,/O that/O one/O of/O mine/O would/O do/O this/O thing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Doreah/O and/O Jhiqui/PERSON helped/O Dany/PERSON back/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
The/O poisoned/O wine/O was/O leaking/O from/O the/O broken/O cask/O into/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O did/O you/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O trembling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O not/O know/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O not/O until/O the/O man/O refused/O to/O drink/O ,/O but/O once/O I/O read/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON 's/O letter/O ,/O I/O feared/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O dark/O eyes/O swept/O over/O the/O faces/O of/O the/O strangers/O in/O the/O market/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ./O 
Best/O not/O to/O talk/O of/O it/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON was/O near/O tears/O as/O they/O carried/O her/O back/O ./O 
The/O taste/O in/O her/O mouth/O was/O one/O she/O had/O known/O before/O :/O fear/O ./O 
For/O years/O she/O had/O lived/O in/O terror/O of/O Viserys/LOCATION ,/O afraid/O of/O waking/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
This/O was/O even/O worse/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O just/O for/O herself/O that/O she/O feared/O now/O ,/O but/O for/O her/O baby/O ./O 
He/O must/O have/O sensed/O her/O fright/O ,/O for/O he/O moved/O restlessly/O inside/O her/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON stroked/O the/O swell/O of/O her/O belly/O gently/O ,/O wishing/O she/O could/O reach/O him/O ,/O touch/O him/O ,/O soothe/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O little/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O as/O her/O litter/O swayed/O along/O ,/O curtains/O drawn/O tight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O and/O the/O dragon/O does/O not/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Under/O the/O hollow/O hummock/O of/O earth/O that/O was/O her/O home/O in/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O Dany/PERSON ordered/O them/O to/O leave/O her-all/O but/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O as/O she/O lowered/O herself/O onto/O her/O cushions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Was/O it/O the/O Usurper/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O drew/O out/O a/O folded/O parchment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O letter/O to/O Viserys/O ,/O from/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON ./O 
Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON offers/O lands/O and/O lordships/O for/O your/O death/O ,/O or/O your/O brother/O 's/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O sob/O was/O half/O a/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O does/O not/O know/O yet/O ,/O does/O he/O ?/O 
The/O Usurper/O owes/O Drogo/PERSON a/O lordship/O ./O 
\/O ''/O This/O time/O her/O laugh/O was/O half/O a/O sob/O ./O 
She/O hugged/O herself/O protectively/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O me/O ,/O you/O said/O ./O 
Only/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O and/O the/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O grim/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
He/O can/O not/O have/O my/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O would/O not/O weep/O ,/O she/O decided/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O shiver/O with/O fear/O ./O 
The/O Usurper/O has/O woken/O the/O dragon/O now/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O .../O and/O her/O eyes/O went/O to/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O resting/O in/O their/O nest/O of/O dark/O velvet/O ./O 
The/O shifting/O lamplight/O linmed/O their/O stony/O scales/O ,/O and/O shimmering/O motes/O of/O jade/O and/O scarlet/O and/O gold/O swam/O in/O the/O air/O around/O them/O ,/O like/O courtiers/O around/O a/O king/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Was/O it/O madness/O that/O seized/O her/O then/O ,/O born/O of/O fear/O ?/O 
Or/O some/O strange/O wisdom/O buried/O in/O her/O blood/O ?/O 
Dany/PERSON could/O not/O have/O said/O ./O 
She/O heard/O her/O own/O voice/O saying/O ,/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O light/O the/O brazier/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O looked/O at/O her/O strangely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O so/O hot/O ./O 
Are/O you/O certain/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O had/O never/O been/O so/O certain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O have/O a/O chill/O ./O 
Light/O the/O brazier/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O bowed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O the/O coals/O were/O afire/O ,/O Dany/PERSON sent/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON from/O her/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O be/O alone/O to/O do/O what/O she/O must/O do/O ./O 
This/O is/O madness/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O as/O she/O lifted/O the/O black-and-scarlet/O egg/O from/O the/O velvet/O ./O 
It/O will/O only/O crack/O and/O Burn/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O so/O beautiful/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON will/O call/O me/O a/O fool/O if/O I/O ruin/O it/O ,/O and/O yet/O ,/O and/O yet/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cradling/O the/O egg/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O she/O carried/O it/O to/O the/O fire/O and/O pushed/O it/O down/O amongst/O the/O burning/O coals/O ./O 
The/O black/O scales/O seemed/O to/O glow/O as/O they/O drank/O the/O heat/O ./O 
Flames/O licked/O against/O the/O stone/O with/O small/O red/O tongues/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON placed/O the/O other/O two/O eggs/O beside/O the/O black/O one/O in/O the/O fire/O ./O 
As/O she/O stepped/O back/O from/O the/O brazier/O ,/O the/O breath/O trembled/O in/O her/O throat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O watched/O until/O the/O coals/O had/O turned/O to/O ashes/O ./O 
Drifting/O sparks/O floated/O up/O and/O out/O of/O the/O smokehole/O ./O 
Heat/O shimmered/O in/O waves/O around/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O ./O 
And/O that/O was/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Your/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON was/O the/O last/O dragon/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O said/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON gazed/O at/O her/O eggs/O sadly/O ./O 
What/O had/O she/O expected/O ?/O 
A/O thousand/O thousand/O years/O ago/O they/O had/O been/O alive/O ,/O but/O now/O they/O were/O only/O pretty/O rocks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O could/O not/O make/O a/O dragon/O ./O 
A/O dragon/O was/O air/O and/O fire/O ./O 
Living/O flesh/O ,/O not/O dead/O stone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O brazier/O was/O cold/O again/O by/O the/O time/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON returned/O ./O 
Cohollo/PERSON was/O leading/O a/O packhorse/O behind/O him/O ,/O with/O the/O carcass/O of/O a/O great/O white/O lion/O slung/O across/O its/O back/O ./O 
Above/O ,/O the/O stars/O were/O coming/O out/O ./O 
The/O khal/O laughed/O as/O he/O swung/O down/O off/O his/O stallion/O and/O showed/O her/O the/O scars/O on/O his/O leg/O where/O the/O hrakkar/O had/O raked/O him/O through/O his/O leggings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O make/O you/O a/O cloak/O of/O its/O skin/O ,/O moon/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O what/O had/O happened/O at/O the/O market/O ,/O all/O laughter/O stopped/O ,/O and/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON grew/O very/O quiet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O poisoner/O was/O the/O first/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON warned/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O he/O will/O not/O be/O the/O last/O ./O 
Men/O will/O risk/O much/O for/O a/O lordship/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON was/O silent/O for/O a/O time/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O This/O seller/O of/O poisons/O ran/O from/O the/O moon/O of/O my/O life/O ./O 
Better/O he/O should/O run/O after/O her/O ./O 
So/O he/O will/O ./O 
Jhogo/PERSON ,/O Jorah/PERSON the/PERSON Andal/PERSON ,/O to/O each/O of/O you/O I/O say/O ,/O choose/O any/O horse/O you/O wish/O from/O my/O herds/O ,/O and/O it/O is/O yours/O ./O 
Any/O horse/O save/O my/O red/O and/O the/O silver/O that/O was/O my/O bride/O gift/O to/O the/O moon/O of/O my/O life/O ./O 
I/O make/O this/O gift/O to/O you/O for/O what/O you/O did/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O to/O Rhaego/O son/O of/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O the/O stallion/O who/O will/O mount/O the/O world/O ,/O to/O him/O I/O also/O pledge/O a/O gift/O ./O 
To/O him/O I/O will/O give/O this/O iron/O chair/O his/O mother/O 's/O father/O sat/O in/O ./O 
I/O will/O give/O him/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
I/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O khal/O ,/O will/O do/O this/O thing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O rose/O ,/O and/O he/O lifted/O his/O fist/O to/O the/O sky/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O take/O my/O khalasar/O west/O to/O where/O the/O world/O ends/O ,/O and/O ride/O the/O wooden/O horses/O across/O the/O black/O salt/O water/O as/O no/O khal/O has/O done/O before/O ./O 
I/O will/O kill/O the/O men/O in/O the/O iron/O suits/O and/O tear/O down/O their/O stone/O houses/O ./O 
I/O will/O rape/O their/O women/O ,/O take/O their/O children/O as/O slaves/O ,/O and/O bring/O their/O broken/O gods/O back/O to/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON to/O bow/O down/O beneath/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION ./O 
This/O I/O vow/O ,/O I/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON son/PERSON of/PERSON Bharbo/PERSON ./O 
This/O I/O swear/O before/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION ,/O as/O the/O stars/O look/O down/O in/O witness/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O khalasar/O left/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON two/O days/O later/O ,/O striking/O south/O and/O west/O across/O the/O plains/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON led/O them/O on/O his/O great/O red/O stallion/O ,/O with/O Daenerys/PERSON beside/O him/O on/O her/O silver/O ./O 
The/O wineseller/O hurried/O behind/O them/O ,/O naked/O ,/O on/O foot/O ,/O chained/O at/O throat/O and/O wrists/O ./O 
His/O chains/O were/O fastened/O to/O the/O halter/O of/O Dany/PERSON 's/O silver/O ./O 
As/O she/O rode/O ,/O he/O ran/O after/O her/O ,/O barefoot/O and/O stumbling/O ./O 
No/O harm/O would/O come/O to/O him/O .../O so/O long/O as/O he/O kept/O up/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
