-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O and/O the/O girls/O were/O eight/O days/O gone/O when/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON came/O to/O her/O one/O night/O in/O Bran/O 's/O sickroom/O ,/O carrying/O a/O reading/O lamp/O and/O the/O books/O of/O account/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O past/O time/O that/O we/O reviewed/O the/O figures/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O want/O to/O know/O how/O much/O this/O royal/O visit/O cost/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O looked/O at/O Bran/O in/O his/O sickbed/O and/O brushed/O his/O hair/O back/O off/O his/O forehead/O ./O 
It/O had/O grown/O very/O long/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O to/O cut/O it/O soon/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O no/O need/O to/O look/O at/O figures/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O never/O taking/O her/O eyes/O from/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O what/O the/O visit/O cost/O us/O ./O 
Take/O the/O books/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O the/O king/O 's/O party/O had/O healthy/O appetites/O ./O 
We/O must/O replenish/O our/O stores/O before/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O cut/O him/O off/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O said/O ,/O take/O the/O books/O away/O ./O 
The/O steward/O will/O attend/O to/O our/O needs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O have/O no/O steward/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON reminded/O her/O ./O 
Like/O a/O little/O grey/O rat/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O he/O would/O not/O let/O go/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Poole/PERSON went/O south/O to/O establish/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O household/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O absently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
I/O remember/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O looked/O so/O pale/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O whether/O they/O might/O move/O his/O bed/O under/O the/O window/O ,/O so/O he/O could/O get/O the/O morning/O sun/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON set/O the/O lamp/O in/O a/O niche/O by/O the/O door/O and/O fiddled/O with/O its/O wick/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O are/O several/O appointments/O that/O require/O your/O immediate/O attention/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Besides/O the/O steward/O ,/O we/O need/O a/O captain/O of/O the/O guards/O to/O fill/O Jory/PERSON 's/O place/O ,/O a/O new/O master/O of/O horse/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O eyes/O snapped/O around/O and/O found/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O master/O of/O horse/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O voice/O was/O a/O whip/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O maester/O was/O shaken/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Hullen/PERSON rode/O south/O with/O Lord/PERSON Eddard/PERSON ,/O so/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O son/O lies/O here/O broken/O and/O dying/O ,/O Luwin/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O wish/O to/O discuss/O a/O new/O master/O of/O horse/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O think/O I/O care/O what/O happens/O in/O the/O stables/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O think/O it/O matters/O to/O me/O one/O whit/O ?/O 
I/O would/O gladly/O butcher/O every/O horse/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O my/O own/O hands/O if/O it/O would/O open/O Bran/O 's/O eyes/O ,/O do/O you/O understand/O that/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O bowed/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O but/O the/O appointments/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O make/O the/O appointments/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O not/O heard/O him/O enter/O ,/O but/O there/O he/O stood/O in/O the/O doorway/O ,/O looking/O at/O her/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O shouting/O ,/O she/O realized/O with/O a/O sudden/O flush/O of/O shame/O ./O 
What/O was/O happening/O to/O her/O ?/O 
She/O was/O so/O tired/O ,/O and/O her/O head/O hurt/O all/O the/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON looked/O from/O Catelyn/LOCATION to/O her/O son/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O prepared/O a/O list/O of/O those/O we/O might/O wish/O to/O consider/O for/O the/O vacant/O offices/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O offering/O Robb/PERSON a/O paper/O plucked/O from/O his/O sleeve/O ./O 
Her/O son/O glanced/O at/O the/O names/O ./O 
He/O had/O come/O from/O outside/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O ;/O his/O cheeks/O were/O red/O from/O the/O cold/O ,/O his/O hair/O shaggy/O and/O windblown/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Good/O men/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 'll/O talk/O about/O them/O tomorrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O handed/O back/O the/O list/O of/O names/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O good/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O paper/O vanished/O into/O his/O sleeve/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Leave/O us/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON bowed/O and/O departed/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON closed/O the/O door/O behind/O him/O and/O turned/O to/O her/O ./O 
He/O was/O wearing/O a/O sword/O ,/O she/O saw/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O what/O are/O you/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O had/O always/O thought/O Robb/PERSON looked/O like/O her/O ;/O like/O Bran/O and/O Rickon/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O he/O had/O the/O Tully/O coloring/O ,/O the/O auburn/O hair/O ,/O the/O blue/O eyes/O ./O 
Yet/O now/O for/O the/O first/O time/O she/O saw/O something/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O in/O his/O face/O ,/O something/O as/O stern/O and/O hard/O as/O the/O north/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O am/O I/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O echoed/O ,/O puzzled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O can/O you/O ask/O that/O ?/O 
What/O do/O you/O imagine/O I/O 'm/O doing/O ?/O 
I/O am/O taking/O care/O of/O your/O brother/O ./O 
I/O am/O taking/O care/O of/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O what/O you/O call/O it/O ?/O 
You/O have/O n't/O left/O this/O room/O since/O Bran/O was/O hurt/O ./O 
You/O did/O n't/O even/O come/O to/O the/O gate/O when/O Father/O and/O the/O girls/O went/O south/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O said/O my/O farewells/O to/O them/O here/O ,/O and/O watched/O them/O ride/O out/O from/O that/O window/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O begged/O Ned/PERSON not/O to/O go/O ,/O not/O now/O ,/O not/O after/O what/O had/O happened/O ;/O everything/O had/O changed/O now/O ,/O could/O n't/O he/O see/O that/O ?/O 
It/O was/O no/O use/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O choice/O ,/O he/O had/O told/O her/O ,/O and/O then/O he/O left/O ,/O choosing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O leave/O him/O ,/O even/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O not/O when/O any/O moment/O could/O be/O his/O last/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O be/O with/O him/O ,/O if/O .../O if/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O took/O her/O son/O 's/O limp/O hand/O ,/O sliding/O his/O fingers/O through/O her/O own/O ./O 
He/O was/O so/O frail/O and/O thin/O ,/O with/O no/O strength/O left/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O but/O she/O could/O still/O feel/O the/O warmth/O of/O life/O through/O his/O skin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON 's/O voice/O softened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O not/O going/O to/O die/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ./O 
Maester/O Luwin/PERSON says/O the/O time/O of/O greatest/O danger/O has/O passed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O if/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON is/O wrong/O ?/O 
What/O if/O Bran/PERSON needs/O me/O and/O I/O 'm/O not/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/O needs/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O only/O three/O ,/O he/O does/O n't/O understand/O what/O 's/O happening/O ./O 
He/O thinks/O everyone/O has/O deserted/O him/O ,/O so/O he/O follows/O me/O around/O all/O day/O ,/O clutching/O my/O leg/O and/O crying/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O to/O do/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O paused/O a/O moment/O ,/O chewing/O on/O his/O lower/O lip/O the/O way/O he/O 'd/O done/O when/O he/O was/O little/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/PERSON ,/O I/O need/O you/O too/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O trying/O but/O I/O ca/O n't/O .../O I/O ca/O n't/O do/O it/O all/O by/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O broke/O with/O sudden/O emotion/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON remembered/O that/O he/O was/O only/O fourteen/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O get/O up/O and/O go/O to/O him/O ,/O but/O Bran/O was/O still/O holding/O her/O hand/O and/O she/O could/O not/O move/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O the/O tower/O ,/O a/O wolf/O began/O to/O howl/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON trembled/O ,/O just/O for/O a/O second/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bran/O 's/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON opened/O the/O window/O and/O let/O the/O night/O air/O into/O the/O stuffy/O tower/O room/O ./O 
The/O howling/O grew/O louder/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O cold/O and/O lonely/O sound/O ,/O full/O of/O melancholy/O and/O despair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O needs/O to/O stay/O warm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O needs/O to/O hear/O them/O sing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
Somewhere/O out/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O a/O second/O wolf/O began/O to/O howl/O in/O chorus/O with/O the/O first/O ./O 
Then/O a/O third/O ,/O closer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shaggydog/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O as/O their/O voices/O rose/O and/O fell/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O can/O tell/O them/O apart/O if/O you/O listen/O close/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O shaking/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O grief/O ,/O the/O cold/O ,/O the/O howling/O of/O the/O direwolves/O ./O 
Night/O after/O night/O ,/O the/O howling/O and/O the/O cold/O wind/O and/O the/O grey/O empty/O castle/O ,/O on/O and/O on/O they/O went/O ,/O never/O changing/O ,/O and/O her/O boy/O lying/O there/O broken/O ,/O the/O sweetest/O of/O her/O children/O ,/O the/O gentlest/O ,/O Bran/O who/O loved/O to/O laugh/O and/O climb/O and/O dreamt/O of/O knighthood/O ,/O all/O gone/O now/O ,/O she/O would/O never/O hear/O him/O laugh/O again/O ./O 
Sobbing/O ,/O she/O pulled/O her/O hand/O free/O of/O his/O and/O covered/O her/O ears/O against/O those/O terrible/O howls/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Make/O them/O stop/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O cried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O stand/O it/O ,/O make/O them/O stop/O ,/O make/O them/O stop/O ,/O kill/O them/O all/O if/O you/O must/O ,/O just/O make/O them/O stop/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O did/O n't/O remember/O falling/O to/O the/O floor/O ,/O but/O there/O she/O was/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON was/O lifting/O her/O ,/O holding/O her/O in/O strong/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ./O 
They/O would/O never/O hurt/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O helped/O her/O to/O her/O narrow/O bed/O in/O the/O corner/O of/O the/O sickroom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Close/O your/O eyes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rest/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON tells/O me/O you/O 've/O hardly/O slept/O since/O Bran/O 's/O fall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O wept/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O forgive/O me/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O I/O ca/O n't/O ,/O what/O if/O he/O dies/O while/O I/O 'm/O asleep/O ,/O what/O if/O he/O dies/O ,/O what/O if/O he/O dies/O .../O \/O ''/O The/O wolves/O were/O still/O howling/O ./O 
She/O screamed/O and/O held/O her/O ears/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O gods/O ,/O close/O the/O window/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O swear/O to/O me/O you/O 'll/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON went/O to/O the/O window/O ,/O but/O as/O he/O reached/O for/O the/O shutters/O another/O sound/O was/O added/O to/O the/O mournful/O howling/O of/O the/O direwolves/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dogs/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O listening/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O the/O dogs/O are/O barking/O ./O 
They/O 've/O never/O done/O that/O before/O .../O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON heard/O his/O breath/O catch/O in/O his/O throat/O ./O 
When/O she/O looked/O up/O ,/O his/O face/O was/O pale/O in/O the/O lamplight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fire/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Fire/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O and/O then/O ,/O Bran/O !/O 
\/O ``/O Help/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O urgently/O ,/O sitting/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Help/O me/O with/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON did/O not/O seem/O to/O hear/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O library/O tower/O 's/O on/O fire/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O could/O see/O the/O flickering/O reddish/O light/O through/O the/O open/O window/O now/O ./O 
She/O sagged/O with/O relief/O ./O 
Bran/O was/O safe/O ./O 
The/O library/O was/O across/O the/O bailey/O ,/O there/O was/O no/O way/O the/O fire/O would/O reach/O them/O here/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O the/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON looked/O at/O her/O as/O if/O she/O 'd/O gone/O mad/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O stay/O here/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O come/O back/O as/O soon/O as/O the/O fire/O 's/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O ran/O then/O ./O 
She/O heard/O him/O shout/O to/O the/O guards/O outside/O the/O room/O ,/O heard/O them/O descending/O together/O in/O a/O wild/O rush/O ,/O taking/O the/O stairs/O two/O and/O three/O at/O a/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O ,/O there/O were/O shouts/O of/O \/O ``/O Fire/O !/O 
\/O ''/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O screams/O ,/O running/O footsteps/O ,/O the/O whinny/O of/O frightened/O horses/O ,/O and/O the/O frantic/O barking/O of/O the/O castle/O dogs/O ./O 
The/O howling/O was/O gone/O ,/O she/O realized/O as/O she/O listened/O to/O the/O cacophony/O ./O 
The/O direwolves/O had/O fallen/O silent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O a/O silent/O prayer/O of/O thanks/O to/O the/O seven/O faces/O of/O god/O as/O she/O went/O to/O the/O window/O ./O 
Across/O the/O bailey/O ,/O long/O tongues/O of/O flame/O shot/O from/O the/O windows/O of/O the/O library/O ./O 
She/O watched/O the/O smoke/O rise/O into/O the/O sky/O and/O thought/O sadly/O of/O all/O the/O books/O the/O Starks/PERSON had/O gathered/O over/O the/O centuries/O ./O 
Then/O she/O closed/O the/O shutters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O turned/O away/O from/O the/O window/O ,/O the/O man/O was/O in/O the/O room/O with/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O were/O n't/O s/O `/O posed/O to/O be/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O sourly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O was/O s/O `/O posed/O to/O be/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O a/O small/O ,/O dirty/O man/O in/O filthy/O brown/O clothing/O ,/O and/O he/O stank/O of/O horses/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON knew/O all/O the/O men/O who/O worked/O in/O their/O stables/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O none/O of/O them/O ./O 
He/O was/O gaunt/O ,/O with/O limp/O blond/O hair/O and/O pale/O eyes/O deep-sunk/O in/O a/O bony/O face/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O a/O dagger/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O looked/O at/O the/O knife/O ,/O then/O at/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
The/O word/O stuck/O in/O her/O throat/O ,/O the/O merest/O whisper/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O must/O have/O heard/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O a/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O dead/O already/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O louder/O now/O as/O she/O found/O her/O voice/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O spun/O back/O toward/O the/O window/O to/O scream/O for/O help/O ,/O but/O the/O man/O moved/O faster/O than/O she/O would/O have/O believed/O ./O 
One/O hand/O clamped/O down/O over/O her/O mouth/O and/O yanked/O back/O her/O head/O ,/O the/O other/O brought/O the/O dagger/O up/O to/O her/O windpipe/O ./O 
The/O stench/O of/O him/O was/O overwhelming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O reached/O up/O with/O both/O hands/O and/O grabbed/O the/O blade/O with/O all/O her/O strength/O ,/O pulling/O it/O away/O from/O her/O throat/O ./O 
She/O heard/O him/O cursing/O into/O her/O ear/O ./O 
Her/O fingers/O were/O slippery/O with/O blood/O ,/O but/O she/O would/O not/O let/O go/O of/O the/O dagger/O ./O 
The/O hand/O over/O her/O mouth/O clenched/O more/O tightly/O ,/O shutting/O off/O her/O air/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON twisted/O her/O head/O to/O the/O side/O and/O managed/O to/O get/O a/O piece/O of/O his/O flesh/O between/O her/O teeth/O ./O 
She/O bit/O down/O hard/O into/O his/O palm/O ./O 
The/O man/O grunted/O in/O pain/O ./O 
She/O ground/O her/O teeth/O together/O ''/O ,/O ``/O and/O tore/O at/O him/O ,/O and/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O he/O let/O go/O ./O 
The/O taste/O of/O his/O blood/O filled/O her/O mouth/O ./O 
She/O sucked/O in/O air/O and/O screamed/O ,/O and/O he/O grabbed/O her/O hair/O and/O pulled/O her/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O and/O she/O stumbled/O and/O went/O down/O ,/O and/O then/O he/O was/O standing/O over/O her/O ,/O breathing/O hard/O ,/O shaking/O ./O 
The/O dagger/O was/O still/O clutched/O tightly/O in/O his/O right/O hand/O ,/O slick/O with/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O were/O n't/O s/O `/O posed/O to/O be/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O repeated/O stupidly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O the/O shadow/O slip/O through/O the/O open/O door/O behind/O him/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O low/O rumble/O ,/O less/O than/O a/O snarl/O ,/O the/O merest/O whisper/O of/O a/O threat/O ,/O but/O he/O must/O have/O heard/O something/O ,/O because/O he/O started/O to/O turn/O just/O as/O the/O wolf/O made/O its/O leap/O ./O 
They/O went/O down/O together/O ,/O half/O sprawled/O over/O Catelyn/ORGANIZATION where/O she/O 'd/O fallen/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O had/O him/O under/O the/O jaw/O ./O 
The/O man/O 's/O shriek/O lasted/O less/O than/O a/O second/O before/O the/O beast/O wrenched/O back/O its/O head/O ,/O taking/O out/O half/O his/O throat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O blood/O felt/O like/O warm/O rain/O as/O it/O sprayed/O across/O her/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O wolf/O was/O looking/O at/O her/O ./O 
Its/O jaws/O were/O red/O and/O wet/O and/O its/O eyes/O glowed/O golden/O in/O the/O dark/O room/O ./O 
It/O was/O Bran/O 's/O wolf/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
Of/O course/O it/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON whispered/O ,/O her/O voice/O faint/O and/O tiny/O ./O 
She/O lifted/O her/O hand/O ,/O trembling/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O padded/O closer/O ,/O sniffed/O at/O her/O fingers/O ,/O then/O licked/O at/O the/O blood/O with/O a/O wet/O rough/O tongue/O ./O 
When/O it/O had/O cleaned/O all/O the/O blood/O off/O her/O hand/O ,/O it/O turned/O away/O silently/O and/O jumped/O up/O on/O Bran/O 's/O bed/O and/O lay/O down/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON began/O to/O laugh/O hysterically/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O way/O they/O found/O them/O ,/O when/O Robb/PERSON and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON burst/O in/O with/O half/O the/O guards/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
When/O the/O laughter/O finally/O died/O in/O her/O throat/O ,/O they/O wrapped/O her/O in/O warm/O blankets/O and/O led/O her/O back/O to/O the/O Great/O Keep/O ,/O to/O her/O own/O chambers/O ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON undressed/O her/O and/O helped/O her/O into/O a/O scalding/O hot/O bath/O and/O washed/O the/O blood/O off/O her/O with/O a/O soft/O cloth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O Maester/O Luwin/PERSON arrived/O to/O dress/O her/O wounds/O ./O 
The/O cuts/O in/O her/O fingers/O went/O deep/O ,/O almost/O to/O the/O bone/O ,/O and/O her/O scalp/O was/O raw/O and/O bleeding/O where/O he/O 'd/O pulled/O out/O a/O handful/O of/O hair/O ./O 
The/O maester/O told/O her/O the/O pain/O was/O just/O starting/O now/O ,/O and/O gave/O her/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O to/O help/O her/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Finally/O she/O closed/O her/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O opened/O them/O again/O ,/O they/O told/O her/O that/O she/O had/O slept/O four/O days/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O and/O sat/O up/O in/O bed/O ./O 
It/O all/O seemed/O like/O a/O nightmare/O to/O her/O now/O ,/O everything/O since/O Bran/O 's/O fall/O ,/O a/O terrible/O dream/O of/O blood/O and/O grief/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O the/O pain/O in/O her/O hands/O to/O remind/O her/O that/O it/O was/O real/O ./O 
She/O felt/O weak/O and/O light-headed/O ,/O yet/O strangely/O resolute/O ,/O as/O if/O a/O great/O weight/O had/O lifted/O from/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bring/O me/O some/O bread/O and/O honey/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O her/O servants/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O take/O word/O to/O Maester/O Luwin/O that/O my/O bandages/O want/O changing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O looked/O at/O her/O in/O surprise/O and/O ran/O to/O do/O her/O bidding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON remembered/O the/O way/O she/O had/O been/O before/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O ashamed/O ./O 
She/O had/O let/O them/O all/O down/O ,/O her/O children/O ,/O her/O husband/O ,/O her/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
It/O would/O not/O happen/O again/O ./O 
She/O would/O show/O these/O northerners/O how/O strong/O a/O Tully/O of/O Riverrun/O could/O be/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON arrived/O before/O her/O food/O ./O 
Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON came/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O her/O husband/O 's/O ward/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O and/O lastly/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON ,/O a/O muscular/O guardsman/O with/O a/O square/O brown/O beard/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O new/O captain/O of/O the/O guard/O ,/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
Her/O son/O was/O dressed/O in/O boiled/O leather/O and/O ringmail/O ,/O she/O saw/O ,/O and/O a/O sword/O hung/O at/O his/O waist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O was/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON asked/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O knows/O his/O name/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O no/O man/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ,/O but/O some/O says/O they/O seen/O him/O here/O and/O about/O the/O castle/O these/O past/O few/O weeks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O men/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O or/O one/O of/O the/O Lannisters/O '/O ./O 
He/O could/O have/O waited/O behind/O when/O the/O others/O left/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hal/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O all/O these/O strangers/O filling/O up/O Winterfell/PERSON of/O late/O ,/O there/O 's/O no/O way/O of/O saying/O who/O he/O belonged/O to/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 'd/O been/O biding/O in/O your/O stables/O ,/O \/O ''/O Greyjoy/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O could/O smell/O it/O on/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O how/O could/O he/O go/O unnoticed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O sharply/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hallis/O Mollen/O looked/O abashed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Between/O the/O horses/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON took/O south/O and/O them/O we/O sent/O north/O to/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O the/O stalls/O were/O half-empty/O ./O 
It/O were/O no/O great/O trick/O to/O hide/O from/O the/O stableboys/O ./O 
Could/O be/O Hodor/PERSON saw/O him/O ,/O the/O talk/O is/O that/O boy/O 's/O been/O acting/O queer/O ,/O but/O simple/O as/O he/O is/O .../O \/O ''/O Hal/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O found/O where/O he/O 'd/O been/O sleeping/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON put/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O had/O ninety/O silver/O stags/O in/O a/O leather/O bag/O buried/O beneath/O the/O straw/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O good/O to/O know/O my/O son/O 's/O life/O was/O not/O sold/O cheaply/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O bitterly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hallis/O Mollen/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O confused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Begging/O your/O grace/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ,/O you/O saying/O he/O was/O out/O to/O kill/O your/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Greyjoy/PERSON was/O doubtful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O madness/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O came/O for/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O kept/O muttering/O how/O I/O was/O n't/O supposed/O to/O be/O there/O ./O 
He/O set/O the/O library/O fire/O thinking/O I/O would/O rush/O to/O put/O it/O out/O ,/O taking/O any/O guards/O with/O me/O ./O 
If/O I/O had/O n't/O been/O half/O -/O mad/O with/O grief/O ,/O it/O would/O have/O worked/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O anyone/O want/O to/O kill/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O he/O 's/O only/O a/O little/O boy/O ,/O helpless/O ,/O sleeping/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON gave/O her/O firstborn/O a/O challenging/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O are/O to/O rule/O in/O the/O north/O ,/O you/O must/O think/O these/O things/O through/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
Answer/O your/O own/O question/O ./O 
Why/O would/O anyone/O want/O to/O kill/O a/O sleeping/O child/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Before/O he/O could/O answer/O ,/O the/O servants/O returned/O with/O a/O plate/O of/O food/O fresh/O from/O the/O kitchen/O ./O 
There/O was/O much/O more/O than/O she/O 'd/O asked/O for/O :/O hot/O bread/O ,/O butter/O and/O honey/O and/O blackberry/O preserves/O ,/O a/O rasher/O of/O bacon/O and/O a/O soft-boiled/O egg/O ,/O a/O wedge/O of/O cheese/O ,/O a/O pot/O of/O mint/O tea/O ./O 
And/O with/O it/O came/O Maester/O Luwin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O is/O my/O son/O ,/O Maester/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON looked/O at/O all/O the/O food/O and/O found/O she/O had/O no/O appetite/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON lowered/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Unchanged/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O reply/O she/O had/O expected/O ,/O no/O more/O and/O no/O less/O ./O 
Her/O hands/O throbbed/O with/O pain/O ,/O as/O if/O the/O blade/O were/O still/O in/O her/O ,/O cutting/O deep/O ./O 
She/O sent/O the/O servants/O away/O and/O looked/O back/O to/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O the/O answer/O yet/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Someone/O is/O afraid/O Bran/O might/O wake/O up/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O afraid/O of/O what/O he/O might/O say/O or/O do/O ,/O afraid/O of/O something/O he/O knows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O proud/O of/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Very/O good/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O turned/O to/O the/O new/O captain/O of/O the/O guard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O keep/O Bran/O safe/O ./O 
If/O there/O was/O one/O killer/O ,/O there/O could/O be/O others/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O many/O guards/O do/O you/O want/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Hal/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O long/O as/O Lord/O Eddard/O is/O away/O ,/O my/O son/O is/O the/O master/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON stood/O a/O little/O taller/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Put/O one/O man/O in/O the/O sickroom/O ,/O night/O and/O day/O ,/O one/O outside/O the/O door/O ,/O two/O at/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O stairs/O ./O 
No/O one/O sees/O Bran/O without/O my/O warrant/O or/O my/O mother/O 's/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O it/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON suggested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O let/O his/O wolf/O stay/O in/O the/O room/O with/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON added/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
And/O then/O again/O :/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Hallis/O Mollen/O bowed/O and/O left/O the/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O when/O the/O guardsman/O had/O gone/O ,/O \/O ``/O did/O you/O chance/O to/O notice/O the/O dagger/O the/O killer/O used/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O circumstances/O did/O not/O allow/O me/O to/O examine/O it/O closely/O ,/O but/O I/O can/O vouch/O for/O its/O edge/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O dry/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O do/O you/O ask/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O found/O the/O knife/O still/O in/O the/O villain/O 's/O grasp/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O to/O me/O that/O it/O was/O altogether/O too/O fine/O a/O weapon/O for/O such/O a/O man/O ,/O so/O I/O looked/O at/O it/O long/O and/O hard/O ./O 
The/O blade/O is/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O the/O hilt/O dragonbone/O ./O 
A/O weapon/O like/O that/O has/O no/O business/O being/O in/O the/O hands/O of/O such/O as/O him/O ./O 
Someone/O gave/O it/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O ,/O thoughtful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O close/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O looked/O at/O her/O strangely/O ,/O but/O did/O as/O she/O told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O I/O am/O about/O to/O tell/O you/O must/O not/O leave/O this/O room/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O your/O oaths/O on/O that/O ./O 
If/O even/O part/O of/O what/O I/O suspect/O is/O true/O ,/O Ned/PERSON and/O my/O girls/O have/O ridden/O into/O deadly/O danger/O ,/O and/O a/O word/O in/O the/O wrong/O ears/O could/O mean/O their/O lives/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON is/O a/O second/O father/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O so/O swear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O my/O oath/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O mine/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O echoed/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O looked/O at/O her/O son/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O you/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O nodded/O his/O consent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O sister/O Lysa/PERSON believes/O the/O Lannisters/O murdered/O her/O husband/O ,/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON ,/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O comes/O to/O me/O that/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON did/O not/O join/O the/O hunt/O the/O day/O Bran/O fell/O ./O 
He/O remained/O here/O in/O the/O castle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O room/O was/O deathly/O quiet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O think/O Bran/O fell/O from/O that/O tower/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O into/O the/O stillness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O he/O was/O thrown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O shock/O was/O plain/O on/O their/O faces/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O that/O is/O a/O monstrous/O suggestion/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O the/O Kingslayer/PERSON would/O flinch/O at/O the/O murder/O of/O an/O innocent/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O would/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O limit/O to/O Lannister/O pride/O or/O Lannister/O ambition/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O boy/O had/O always/O been/O surehanded/O in/O the/O past/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O knew/O every/O stone/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON swore/O ,/O his/O young/O face/O dark/O with/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O this/O is/O true/O ,/O he/O will/O pay/O for/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O his/O sword/O and/O waved/O it/O in/O the/O air/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O kill/O him/O myself/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON bristled/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Put/O that/O away/O !/O 
The/O Lannisters/O are/O a/O hundred/O leagues/O away/O ./O 
Never/O draw/O your/O sword/O unless/O you/O mean/O to/O use/O it/O ./O 
How/O many/O times/O must/O I/O tell/O you/O ,/O foolish/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Abashed/O ,/O Robb/PERSON sheathed/O his/O sword/O ,/O suddenly/O a/O child/O again/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON said/O to/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O my/O son/O is/O wearing/O steel/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O old/O master-at-arms/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O thought/O it/O was/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON was/O looking/O at/O her/O anxiously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Past/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Winterfell/O may/O have/O need/O of/O all/O its/O swords/O soon/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O best/O not/O be/O made/O of/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O on/O the/O hilt/O of/O his/O blade/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O if/O it/O comes/O to/O that/O ,/O my/O House/ORGANIZATION owes/O yours/O a/O great/O debt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON pulled/O at/O his/O chain/O collar/O where/O it/O chafed/O against/O his/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O we/O have/O is/O conjecture/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O queen/O 's/O beloved/O brother/O we/O mean/O to/O accuse/O ./O 
She/O will/O not/O take/O it/O kindly/O ./O 
We/O must/O have/O proof/O ,/O or/O forever/O keep/O silent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O proof/O is/O in/O the/O dagger/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O fine/O blade/O like/O that/O will/O not/O have/O gone/O unnoticed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O only/O one/O place/O to/O find/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON realized/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Someone/O must/O go/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O go/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O place/O is/O here/O ./O 
There/O must/O always/O be/O a/O Stark/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O looked/O at/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON with/O his/O great/O white/O whiskers/O ,/O at/O Maester/LOCATION Luwin/LOCATION in/O his/O grey/O robes/O ,/O at/O young/O Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O lean/O and/O dark/O and/O impetuous/O ./O 
Who/O to/O send/O ?/O 
Who/O would/O be/O believed/O ?/O 
Then/O she/O knew/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON struggled/O to/O push/O back/O the/O blankets/O ,/O her/O bandaged/O fingers/O as/O stiff/O and/O unyielding/O as/O stone/O ./O 
She/O climbed/O out/O of/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O must/O go/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O is/O that/O wise/O ?/O 
Surely/O the/O Lannisters/O would/O greet/O your/O arrival/O with/O suspicion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O about/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O ./O 
The/O poor/O boy/O looked/O utterly/O confused/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O mean/O to/O leave/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O done/O everything/O I/O can/O for/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O laying/O a/O wounded/O hand/O on/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O life/O is/O in/O the/O hands/O of/O the/O gods/O and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O 
As/O you/O reminded/O me/O yourself/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O I/O have/O other/O children/O to/O think/O of/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O need/O a/O strong/O escort/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O send/O Hal/PERSON with/O a/O squad/O of/O guardsmen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O large/O party/O attracts/O unwelcome/O attention/O ./O 
I/O would/O not/O have/O the/O Lannisters/O know/O I/O am/O coming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON protested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O let/O me/O accompany/O you/O at/O least/O ./O 
The/O kingsroad/O can/O be/O perilous/O for/O a/O woman/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O be/O taking/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ./O 
She/O thought/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O then/O nodded/O her/O consent/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Two/O riders/O can/O move/O as/O fast/O as/O one/O ,/O and/O a/O good/O deal/O faster/O than/O a/O long/O column/O burdened/O by/O wagons/O and/O wheelhouses/O ./O 
I/O will/O welcome/O your/O company/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
We/O will/O follow/O the/O White/O Knife/O down/O to/O the/O sea/O ,/O and/O hire/O a/O ship/O at/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ./O 
Strong/O horses/O and/O brisk/O winds/O should/O bring/O us/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O well/O ahead/O of/O Ned/PERSON and/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O then/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O we/O shall/O see/O what/O we/O shall/O see/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
