-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O death/O was/O a/O great/O sadness/O for/O all/O of/O us/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O be/O more/O than/O happy/O to/O tell/O you/O what/O I/O can/O of/O the/O manner/O of/O his/O passing/O ./O 
Do/O be/O seated/O ./O 
Would/O you/O care/O for/O refreshments/O ?/O 
Some/O dates/O ,/O perhaps/O ?/O 
I/O have/O some/O very/O fine/O persimmons/O as/O well/O ./O 
Wine/O no/O longer/O agrees/O with/O my/O digestion/O ,/O I/O fear/O ,/O but/O I/O can/O offer/O you/O a/O cup/O of/O iced/O milk/O ,/O sweetened/O with/O honey/O ./O 
I/O find/O it/O most/O refreshing/O in/O this/O heat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O denying/O the/O heat/O ;/O Ned/PERSON could/O feel/O the/O silk/O tunic/O clinging/O to/O his/O chest/O ./O 
Thick/O ,/O moist/O air/O covered/O the/O city/O like/O a/O damp/O woolen/O blanket/O ,/O and/O the/O riverside/O had/O grown/O unruly/O as/O the/O poor/O fled/O their/O hot/O ,/O airless/O warrens/O to/O jostle/O for/O sleeping/O places/O near/O the/O water/O ,/O where/O the/O only/O breath/O of/O wind/O was/O to/O be/O found/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O would/O be/O most/O kind/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O seating/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pycelle/PERSON lifted/O a/O tiny/O silver/O bell/O with/O thumb/O and/O forefinger/O and/O tinkled/O it/O gently/O ./O 
A/O slender/O young/O serving/O girl/O hurried/O into/O the/O solar/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Iced/O milk/O for/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O and/O myself/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ,/O child/O ./O 
Well/O sweetened/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O the/O girl/O went/O to/O fetch/O their/O drinks/O ,/O the/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION knotted/O his/O fingers/O together/O and/O rested/O his/O hands/O on/O his/O stomach/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O smallfolk/O say/O that/O the/O last/O year/O of/O summer/O is/O always/O the/O hottest/O ./O 
It/O is/O not/O so/O ,/O yet/O ofttimes/O it/O feels/O that/O way/O ,/O does/O it/O not/O ?/O 
On/O days/O like/O this/O ,/O I/O envy/O you/O northerners/O your/O summer/O snows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O heavy/O jeweled/O chain/O around/O the/O old/O man/O 's/O neck/O chinked/O softly/O as/O he/O shifted/O in/O his/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O be/O sure/O ,/O King/O Maekar/PERSON 's/O summer/O was/O hotter/O than/O this/O one/O ,/O and/O near/O as/O long/O ./O 
There/O were/O fools/O ,/O even/O in/O the/O Citadel/LOCATION ,/O who/O took/O that/O to/O mean/O that/O the/O Great/O Summer/O had/O come/O at/O last/O ,/O the/O summer/O that/O never/O ends/O ,/O but/O in/O the/O seventh/O year/O it/O broke/O suddenly/O ,/O and/O we/O had/O a/O short/O autumn/O and/O a/O terrible/O long/O winter/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O the/O heat/O was/O fierce/O while/O it/O lasted/O ./O 
Oldtown/O steamed/O and/O sweltered/O by/O day/O and/O came/O alive/O only/O by/O night/O ./O 
We/O would/O walk/O in/O the/O gardens/O by/O the/O river/O and/O argue/O about/O the/O gods/O ./O 
I/O remember/O the/O smells/O of/O those/O nights/O ,/O my/O lord-perfume/O and/O sweat/O ,/O melons/O ripe/O to/O bursting/O ,/O peaches/O and/O pomegranates/O ,/O nightshade/O and/O moonbloom/O ./O 
I/O was/O a/O young/O man/O then/O ,/O still/O forging/O my/O chain/O ./O 
The/O heat/O did/O not/O exhaust/O me/O as/O it/O does/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON 's/O eyes/O were/O so/O heavily/O lidded/O he/O looked/O half-asleep/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O pardons/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
You/O did/O not/O come/O to/O hear/O foolish/O meanderings/O of/O a/O summer/O forgotten/O before/O your/O father/O was/O born/O ./O 
Forgive/O an/O old/O man/O his/O wanderings/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O ./O 
Minds/O are/O like/O swords/O ,/O I/O do/O fear/O ./O 
The/O old/O ones/O go/O to/O rust/O ./O 
Ah/O ,/O and/O here/O is/O our/O milk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O serving/O girl/O placed/O the/O tray/O between/O them/O ,/O and/O Pycelle/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O lifted/O a/O cup/O ,/O tasted/O ,/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ./O 
You/O may/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O the/O girl/O had/O taken/O her/O leave/O ,/O Pycelle/PERSON peered/O at/O Ned/PERSON through/O pale/O ,/O rheumy/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O where/O were/O we/O ?/O 
Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
You/O asked/O about/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON sipped/O politely/O at/O the/O iced/O milk/O ./O 
It/O was/O pleasantly/O cold/O ,/O but/O oversweet/O to/O his/O taste/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O the/O Hand/O had/O not/O seemed/O quite/O himself/O for/O some/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O had/O sat/O together/O on/O council/O many/O a/O year/O ,/O he/O and/O I/O ,/O and/O the/O signs/O were/O there/O to/O read/O ,/O but/O I/O put/O them/O down/O to/O the/O great/O burdens/O he/O had/O borne/O so/O faithfully/O for/O so/O long/O ./O 
Those/O broad/O shoulders/O were/O weighed/O down/O by/O all/O the/O cares/O of/O the/O realm/O ,/O and/O more/O besides/O ./O 
His/O son/O was/O ever/O sickly/O ,/O and/O his/O lady/O wife/O so/O anxious/O that/O she/O would/O scarcely/O let/O the/O boy/O out/O of/O her/O sight/O ./O 
It/O was/O enough/O to/O weary/O even/O a/O strong/O man/O ,/O and/O the/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON was/O not/O young/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O if/O he/O seemed/O melancholy/O and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O tired/O ./O 
Or/O so/O I/O thought/O at/O the/O time/O ./O 
Yet/O now/O I/O am/O less/O certain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O a/O ponderous/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O can/O you/O tell/O me/O of/O his/O final/O illness/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Grand/O Maester/O spread/O his/O hands/O in/O a/O gesture/O of/O helpless/O sorrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O came/O to/O me/O one/O day/O asking/O after/O a/O certain/O book/O ,/O as/O hale/O and/O healthy/O as/O ever/O ,/O though/O it/O did/O seem/O to/O me/O that/O something/O was/O troubling/O him/O deeply/O ./O 
The/O next/O morning/O he/O was/O twisted/O over/O in/O pain/O ,/O too/O sick/O to/O rise/O from/O bed/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON thought/O it/O was/O a/O chill/O on/O the/O stomach/O ./O 
The/O weather/O had/O been/O hot/O ,/O and/O the/O Hand/O often/O iced/O his/O wine/O ,/O which/O can/O upset/O the/O digestion/O ./O 
When/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON continued/O to/O weaken/O ,/O I/O went/O to/O him/O myself/O ,/O but/O the/O gods/O did/O not/O grant/O me/O the/O power/O to/O save/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O heard/O that/O you/O sent/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Grand/O Maester/O 's/O nod/O was/O as/O slow/O and/O deliberate/O as/O a/O glacier/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O ,/O and/O I/O fear/O the/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON will/O never/O forgive/O me/O that/O ./O 
Maybe/O I/O was/O wrong/O ,/O but/O at/O the/O time/O I/O thought/O it/O best/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON is/O like/O a/O son/O to/O me/O ,/O and/O I/O yield/O to/O none/O in/O my/O esteem/O for/O his/O abilities/O ,/O but/O he/O is/O young/O ,/O and/O the/O young/O ofttimes/O do/O not/O comprehend/O the/O frailty/O of/O an/O older/O body/O ./O 
He/O was/O purging/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON with/O wasting/O potions/O and/O pepper/O juice/O ,/O and/O I/O feared/O he/O might/O kill/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON say/O anything/O to/O you/O during/O his/O final/O hours/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pycelle/O wrinkled/O his/O brow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O the/O last/O stage/O of/O his/O fever/O ,/O the/O Hand/O called/O out/O the/O name/O Robert/PERSON several/O times/O ,/O but/O whether/O he/O was/O asking/O for/O his/O son/O or/O for/O the/O king/O I/O could/O not/O say/O ./O 
Lady/O Lysa/PERSON would/O not/O permit/O the/O boy/O to/O enter/O the/O sickroom/O ,/O for/O fear/O that/O he/O too/O might/O be/O taken/O ill/O ./O 
The/O king/O did/O come/O ,/O and/O he/O sat/O beside/O the/O bed/O for/O hours/O ,/O talking/O and/O joking/O of/O times/O long/O past/O in/O hopes/O of/O raising/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON 's/O spirits/O ./O 
His/O love/O was/O fierce/O to/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Was/O there/O nothing/O else/O ?/O 
No/O final/O words/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O saw/O that/O all/O hope/O had/O fled/O ,/O I/O gave/O the/O Hand/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O so/O he/O should/O not/O suffer/O ./O 
Just/O before/O he/O closed/O his/O eyes/O for/O the/O last/O time/O ,/O he/O whispered/O something/O to/O the/O king/O and/O his/O lady/O wife/O ,/O a/O blessing/O for/O his/O son/O ./O 
The/O seed/O is/O strong/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
At/O the/O end/O ,/O his/O speech/O was/O too/O slurred/O to/O comprehend/O ./O 
Death/O did/O not/O come/O until/O the/O next/O morning/O ,/O but/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON was/O at/O peace/O after/O that/O ./O 
He/O never/O spoke/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON took/O another/O swallow/O of/O milk/O ,/O trying/O not/O to/O gag/O on/O the/O sweetness/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O it/O seem/O to/O you/O that/O there/O was/O anything/O unnatural/O about/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON '/O s/O death/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unnatural/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O aged/O maester/O 's/O voice/O was/O thin/O as/O a/O whisper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O I/O could/O not/O say/O so/O ./O 
Sad/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
Yet/O in/O its/O own/O way/O ,/O death/O is/O the/O most/O natural/O thing/O of/O all/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON rests/O easy/O now/O ,/O his/O burdens/O lifted/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O illness/O that/O took/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Had/O you/O ever/O seen/O its/O like/O before/O ,/O in/O other/O men/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Near/O forty/O years/O I/O have/O been/O Grand/O Maester/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Under/O our/O good/O King/O Robert/PERSON ,/O and/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON before/O him/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O Jaehaerys/PERSON the/O Second/O before/O him/O ,/O and/O even/O for/O a/O few/O short/O months/O under/O Jaehaerys/PERSON 's/O father/O ,/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Fortunate/O ,/O the/O Fifth/O of/O His/O Name/O ./O 
I/O have/O seen/O more/O of/O illness/O than/O I/O care/O to/O remember/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
I/O will/O tell/O you/O this/O :/O Every/O case/O is/O different/O ,/O and/O every/O case/O is/O alike/O ./O 
Lord/O Jon/PERSON 's/O death/O was/O no/O stranger/O than/O any/O other/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O wife/O thought/O otherwise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Grand/O Maester/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O recall/O now/O ,/O the/O widow/O is/O sister/O to/O your/O own/O noble/O wife/O ./O 
If/O an/O old/O man/O may/O be/O forgiven/O his/O blunt/O speech/O ,/O let/O me/O say/O that/O grief/O can/O derange/O even/O the/O strongest/O and/O most/O disciplined/O of/O minds/O ,/O and/O the/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON was/O never/O that/O ./O 
Since/O her/O last/O stillbirth/O ,/O she/O has/O seen/O enemies/O in/O every/O shadow/O ,/O and/O the/O death/O of/O her/O lord/O husband/O left/O her/O shattered/O and/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O you/O are/O quite/O certain/O that/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON died/O of/O a/O sudden/O illness/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON replied/O gravely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O not/O illness/O ,/O my/O good/O lord/O ,/O what/O else/O could/O it/O be/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Poison/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON suggested/O quietly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pycelle/O 's/O sleepy/O eyes/O flicked/O open/O ./O 
The/O aged/O maester/O shifted/O uncomfortably/O in/O his/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O disturbing/O thought/O ./O 
We/O are/O not/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O where/O such/O things/O are/O common/O ./O 
Grand/O Maester/PERSON Aethelmure/PERSON wrote/O that/O all/O men/O carry/O murder/O in/O their/O hearts/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O ,/O the/O poisoner/O is/O beneath/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O fell/O silent/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O his/O eyes/O lost/O in/O thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O you/O suggest/O is/O possible/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O yet/O I/O do/O not/O think/O it/O likely/O ./O 
Every/O hedge/O maester/O knows/O the/O common/O poisons/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON displayed/O none/O of/O the/O signs/O ./O 
And/O the/O Hand/O was/O loved/O by/O all/O ./O 
What/O sort/O of/O monster/O in/O man/O 's/O flesh/O would/O dare/O to/O murder/O such/O a/O noble/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O heard/O it/O said/O that/O poison/O is/O a/O woman/O 's/O weapon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pycelle/PERSON stroked/O his/O beard/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O said/O ./O 
Women/O ,/O cravens/O .../O and/O eunuchs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O cleared/O his/O throat/O and/O spat/O a/O thick/O glob/O of/O phlegm/O onto/O the/O rushes/O ./O 
Above/O them/O ,/O a/O raven/O cawed/O loudly/O in/O the/O rookery/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON was/O born/O a/O slave/O in/O Lys/O ,/O did/O you/O know/O ?/O 
Put/O not/O your/O trust/O in/O spiders/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O was/O scarcely/O anything/O Ned/PERSON needed/O to/O be/O told/O ;/O there/O was/O something/O about/O Varys/PERSON that/O made/O his/O flesh/O crawl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O remember/O that/O ,/O Maester/O ./O 
And/O I/O thank/O you/O for/O your/O help/O ./O 
I/O have/O taken/O enough/O of/O your/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/PERSON pushed/O himself/O up/O from/O his/O chair/O slowly/O and/O escorted/O Ned/PERSON to/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O I/O have/O helped/O in/O some/O small/O way/O to/O put/O your/O mind/O at/O ease/O ./O 
If/O there/O is/O any/O other/O service/O I/O might/O perform/O ,/O you/O need/O only/O ask/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O One/O thing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O be/O curious/O to/O examine/O the/O book/O that/O you/O lent/O Jon/PERSON the/O day/O before/O he/O fell/O ill/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O fear/O you/O would/O find/O it/O of/O little/O interest/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O a/O ponderous/O tome/O by/O Grand/O Maester/O Malleon/O on/O the/O lineages/O of/O the/O great/O houses/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Still/O ,/O I/O should/O like/O to/O see/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O opened/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ./O 
I/O have/O it/O here/O somewhere/O ./O 
When/O I/O find/O it/O ,/O I/O shall/O have/O it/O sent/O to/O your/O chambers/O straightaway/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O been/O most/O courteous/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
Then/O ,/O almost/O as/O an/O afterthought/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O One/O last/O question/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
You/O mentioned/O that/O the/O king/O was/O at/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O bedside/O when/O he/O died/O ./O 
I/O wonder/O ,/O was/O the/O queen/O with/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ,/O no/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O and/O the/O children/O were/O making/O the/O journey/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O in/O company/O with/O her/O father/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON had/O brought/O a/O retinue/O to/O the/O city/O for/O the/O tourney/O on/O Prince/LOCATION Joffrey/LOCATION 's/O name/O day/O ,/O no/O doubt/O hoping/O to/O see/O his/O son/O Jaime/PERSON win/O the/O champion/O 's/O crown/O ./O 
In/O that/O he/O was/O sadly/O disappointed/O ./O 
It/O fell/O to/O me/O to/O send/O the/O queen/O word/O of/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O sudden/O death/O ./O 
Never/O have/O I/O sent/O off/O a/O bird/O with/O a/O heavier/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dark/O wings/O ,/O dark/O words/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON murmured/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O proverb/O Old/O Nan/PERSON had/O taught/O him/O as/O a/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O the/O fishwives/O say/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O agreed/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O we/O know/O it/O is/O not/O always/O so/O ./O 
When/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON 's/O bird/O brought/O the/O word/O about/O your/O Bran/O ,/O the/O message/O lifted/O every/O true/O heart/O in/O the/O castle/O ,/O did/O it/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Maester/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gods/O are/O merciful/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON bowed/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O to/O me/O as/O often/O as/O you/O like/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
I/O am/O here/O to/O serve/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O as/O the/O door/O swung/O shut/O ,/O but/O whom/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O On/O the/O way/O back/O to/O his/O chambers/O ,/O he/O came/O upon/O his/O daughter/O Arya/PERSON on/O the/O winding/O steps/O of/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O windmilling/O her/O arms/O as/O she/O struggled/O to/O balance/O on/O one/O leg/O ./O 
The/O rough/O stone/O had/O scuffed/O her/O bare/O feet/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON stopped/O and/O looked/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O what/O are/O you/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Syrio/O says/O a/O water/O dancer/O can/O stand/O on/O one/O toe/O for/O hours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O hands/O flailed/O at/O the/O air/O to/O steady/O herself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O to/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Which/O toe/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O teased/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Any/O toe/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ,/O exasperated/O with/O the/O question/O ./O 
She/O hopped/O from/O her/O right/O leg/O to/O her/O left/O ,/O swaying/O dangerously/O before/O she/O regained/O her/O balance/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Must/O you/O do/O your/O standing/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O a/O long/O hard/O fall/O down/O these/O steps/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Syrio/O says/O a/O water/O dancer/O never/O falls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O lowered/O her/O leg/O to/O stand/O on/O two/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ,/O will/O Bran/O come/O and/O live/O with/O us/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O sweet/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O needs/O to/O win/O his/O strength/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON bit/O her/O lip/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O will/O Bran/O do/O when/O he/O 's/O of/O age/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON knelt/O beside/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O years/O to/O find/O that/O answer/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
For/O now/O ,/O it/O is/O enough/O to/O know/O that/O he/O will/O live/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O night/O the/O bird/O had/O come/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O taken/O the/O girls/O to/O the/O castle/O godswood/O ,/O an/O acre/O of/O elm/O and/O alder/O and/O black/O cottonwood/O overlooking/O the/O river/O ./O 
The/O heart/O tree/O there/O was/O a/O great/O oak/O ,/O its/O ancient/O limbs/O overgrown/O with/O smokeberry/O vines/O ;/O they/O knelt/O before/O it/O to/O offer/O their/O thanksgiving/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O had/O been/O a/O weirwood/O ./O 
Sansa/O drifted/O to/O sleep/O as/O the/O moon/O rose/O ,/O Arya/PERSON several/O hours/O later/O ,/O curling/O up/O in/O the/O grass/O under/O Ned/PERSON 's/O cloak/O ./O 
All/O through/O the/O dark/O hours/O he/O kept/O his/O vigil/O alone/O ./O 
When/O dawn/O broke/O over/O the/O city/O ,/O the/O dark/O red/O blooms/O of/O dragon/O 's/O breath/O surrounded/O the/O girls/O where/O they/O lay/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O dreamed/O of/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON had/O whispered/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O him/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O going/O to/O be/O a/O knight/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON was/O saying/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O knight/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
Can/O he/O still/O be/O a/O knight/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O saw/O no/O use/O in/O lying/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O someday/O he/O may/O be/O the/O lord/O of/O a/O great/O holdfast/O and/O sit/O on/O the/O king/O 's/O council/O ./O 
He/O might/O raise/O castles/O like/O Brandon/PERSON the/O Builder/O ,/O or/O sail/O a/O ship/O across/O the/O Sunset/LOCATION Sea/LOCATION ,/O or/O enter/O your/O mother/O 's/O Faith/O and/O become/O the/O High/O Septon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O But/O he/O will/O never/O run/O beside/O his/O wolf/O again/O ,/O he/O thought/O with/O a/O sadness/O too/O deep/O for/O words/O ,/O or/O lie/O with/O a/O woman/O ,/O or/O hold/O his/O own/O son/O in/O his/O arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON cocked/O her/O head/O to/O one/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O I/O be/O a/O king/O 's/O councillor/O and/O build/O castles/O and/O become/O the/O High/O Septon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O kissing/O her/O lightly/O on/O the/O brow/O ,/O \/O ``/O will/O marry/O a/O king/O and/O rule/O his/O castle/O ,/O and/O your/O sons/O will/O be/O knights/O and/O princes/O and/O lords/O and/O ,/O yes/O ,/O perhaps/O even/O a/O High/O Septon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON screwed/O up/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O that/O 's/O Sansa/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O folded/O up/O her/O right/O leg/O and/O resumed/O her/O balancing/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON sighed/O and/O left/O her/O there/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O his/O chambers/O ,/O he/O stripped/O off/O his/O sweat-stained/O silks/O and/O sluiced/O cold/O water/O over/O his/O head/O from/O the/O basin/O beside/O the/O bed/O ./O 
Alyn/PERSON entered/O as/O he/O was/O drying/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON is/O without/O and/O begs/O audience/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Escort/O him/O to/O my/O solar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O reaching/O for/O a/O fresh/O tunic/O ,/O the/O lightest/O linen/O he/O could/O find/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O see/O him/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Little/O finger/O was/O perched/O on/O the/O window/O seat/O when/O Ned/PERSON entered/O ,/O watching/O the/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O practice/O at/O swords/O in/O the/O yard/O below/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O only/O old/O Selmy/PERSON 's/O mind/O were/O as/O nimble/O as/O his/O blade/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O wistfully/O ,/O \/O ``/O our/O council/O meetings/O would/O be/O a/O good/O deal/O livelier/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O is/O as/O valiant/O and/O honorable/O as/O any/O man/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON had/O come/O to/O have/O a/O deep/O respect/O for/O the/O aged/O ,/O whitehaired/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O as/O tiresome/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON added/O ,/O \/O ``/O though/O I/O daresay/O he/O should/O do/O well/O in/O the/O tourney/O ./O 
Last/O year/O he/O unhorsed/O the/O Hound/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O only/O four/O years/O ago/O that/O he/O was/O champion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O question/O of/O who/O might/O win/O the/O tourney/O interested/O Eddard/O Stark/O not/O in/O the/O least/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O there/O a/O reason/O for/O this/O visit/O ,/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON ,/O or/O are/O you/O here/O simply/O to/O enjoy/O the/O view/O from/O my/O window/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O promised/O Cat/O I/O would/O help/O you/O in/O your/O inquiries/O ,/O and/O so/O I/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O took/O Ned/PERSON aback/O ./O 
Promise/O or/O no/O promise/O ,/O he/O could/O not/O find/O it/O in/O him/O to/O trust/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON ,/O who/O struck/O him/O as/O too/O clever/O by/O half/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O something/O for/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Someone/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON corrected/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Four/O someones/O ,/O if/O truth/O be/O told/O ./O 
Had/O you/O thought/O to/O question/O the/O Hand/O 's/O servants/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O could/O ./O 
Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON took/O her/O household/O back/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON had/O done/O him/O no/O favor/O in/O that/O regard/O ./O 
All/O those/O who/O had/O stood/O closest/O to/O her/O husband/O had/O gone/O with/O her/O when/O she/O fled/O :/O Jon/PERSON 's/O maester/O ,/O his/O steward/O ,/O the/O captain/O of/O his/O guard/O ,/O his/O knights/O and/O retainers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Most/O of/O her/O household/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O not/O all/O ./O 
A/O few/O remain/O ./O 
A/O pregnant/O kitchen/O girl/O hastily/O wed/O to/O one/O of/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON 's/O grooms/O ,/O a/O stablehand/O who/O joined/O the/O City/O Watch/O ,/O a/O potboy/O discharged/O from/O service/O for/O theft/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON '/O s/O squire/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O squire/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON was/O pleasantly/O surprised/O ./O 
A/O man/O 's/O squire/O often/O knew/O a/O great/O deal/O of/O his/O comings/O and/O goings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Hugh/PERSON of/O the/O Vale/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON named/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O knighted/O the/O boy/O after/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON '/O s/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O send/O for/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON winced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O step/O over/O here/O to/O the/O window/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Come/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O show/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Frowning/O ,/O Ned/PERSON crossed/O to/O the/O window/O ./O 
Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON made/O a/O casual/O gesture/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ,/O across/O the/O yard/O ,/O at/O the/O door/O of/O the/O armory/O ,/O do/O you/O see/O the/O boy/O squatting/O by/O the/O steps/O honing/O a/O sword/O with/O an/O oilstone/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O of/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O reports/O to/O Varys/O ./O 
The/O Spider/O has/O taken/O a/O great/O interest/O in/O you/O and/O all/O your/O doings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O shifted/O in/O the/O window/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O glance/O at/O the/O wall/O ./O 
Farther/O west/O ,/O above/O the/O stables/O ./O 
The/O guardsman/O leaning/O on/O the/O ramparts/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O saw/O the/O man/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Another/O of/O the/O eunuch/O 's/O whisperers/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O this/O one/O belongs/O to/O the/O queen/O ./O 
Notice/O that/O he/O enjoys/O a/O fine/O view/O of/O the/O door/O to/O this/O tower/O ,/O the/O better/O to/O note/O who/O calls/O on/O you/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O are/O others/O ,/O many/O unknown/O even/O to/O me/O ./O 
The/O Red/O Keep/O is/O full/O of/O eyes/O ./O 
Why/O do/O you/O think/O I/O hid/O Cat/O in/O a/O brothel/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O had/O no/O taste/O for/O these/O intrigues/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O ./O 
It/O did/O seem/O as/O though/O the/O man/O on/O the/O walls/O was/O watching/O him/O ./O 
Suddenly/O uncomfortable/O ,/O Ned/PERSON moved/O away/O from/O the/O window/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O everyone/O someone/O 's/O informer/O in/O this/O cursed/O city/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Scarcely/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
He/O counted/O on/O the/O fingers/O on/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O there/O 's/O me/O ,/O you/O ,/O the/O king/O .../O although/O ,/O come/O to/O think/O on/O it/O ,/O the/O king/O tells/O the/O queen/O much/O too/O much/O ,/O and/O I/O 'm/O less/O than/O certain/O about/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stood/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O there/O a/O man/O in/O your/O service/O that/O you/O trust/O utterly/O and/O completely/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ned/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O that/O case/O ,/O I/O have/O a/O delightful/O palace/O in/O Valyria/LOCATION that/O I/O would/O dearly/O love/O to/O sell/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O with/O a/O mocking/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wiser/O answer/O was/O no/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O be/O that/O as/O it/O may/O ./O 
Send/O this/O paragon/O of/O yours/O to/O Ser/PERSON Hugh/PERSON and/O the/O others/O ./O 
Your/O own/O comings/O and/O goings/O will/O be/O noted/O ,/O but/O even/O Varys/O the/O Spider/O can/O not/O watch/O every/O man/O in/O your/O service/O every/O hour/O of/O the/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O started/O for/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON called/O after/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
am/O grateful/O for/O your/O help/O ./O 
Perhaps/O I/O was/O wrong/O to/O distrust/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON fingered/O his/O small/O pointed/O beard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O slow/O to/O learn/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
Distrusting/O me/O was/O the/O wisest/O thing/O you/O 've/O done/O since/O you/O climbed/O down/O off/O your/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
