-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O had/O taken/O shelter/O beneath/O a/O copse/O of/O aspens/O just/O off/O the/O high/O road/O ./O 
Tyrion/O was/O gathering/O deadwood/O while/O their/O horses/O took/O water/O from/O a/O mountain/O stream/O ./O 
He/O stooped/O to/O pick/O up/O a/O splintered/O branch/O and/O examined/O it/O critically/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O this/O do/O ?/O 
I/O am/O not/O practiced/O at/O starting/O fires/O ./O 
Morrec/PERSON did/O that/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O fire/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ,/O spitting/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O so/O hungry/O to/O die/O ,/O dwarf/O ?/O 
Or/O have/O you/O taken/O leave/O of/O your/O senses/O ?/O 
A/O fire/O will/O bring/O the/O clansmen/O down/O on/O us/O from/O miles/O around/O ./O 
I/O mean/O to/O survive/O this/O journey/O ,/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O how/O do/O you/O hope/O to/O do/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O ./O 
He/O tucked/O the/O branch/O under/O his/O arm/O and/O poked/O around/O through/O the/O sparse/O undergrowth/O ,/O looking/O for/O more/O ./O 
His/O back/O ached/O from/O the/O effort/O of/O bending/O ;/O they/O had/O been/O riding/O since/O daybreak/O ,/O when/O a/O stone-faced/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON had/O ushered/O them/O through/O the/O Bloody/O Gate/O and/O commanded/O them/O never/O to/O return/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O have/O no/O chance/O of/O fighting/O our/O way/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O two/O can/O cover/O more/O ground/O than/O ten/O ,/O and/O attract/O less/O notice/O ./O 
The/O fewer/O days/O we/O spend/O in/O these/O mountains/O ,/O the/O more/O like/O we/O are/O to/O reach/O the/O riverlands/O ./O 
Ride/O hard/O and/O fast/O ,/O I/O say/O ./O 
Travel/O by/O night/O and/O hole/O up/O by/O day/O ,/O avoid/O the/O road/O where/O we/O can/O ,/O make/O no/O noise/O and/O light/O no/O fires/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O splendid/O plan/O ,/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
Try/O it/O ,/O as/O you/O like/O .../O and/O forgive/O me/O if/O I/O do/O not/O linger/O to/O bury/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O think/O to/O outlive/O me/O ,/O dwarf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O sellsword/O grinned/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O dark/O gap/O in/O his/O smile/O where/O the/O edge/O of/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON 's/O shield/O had/O cracked/O a/O tooth/O in/O half/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Riding/O hard/O and/O fast/O by/O night/O is/O a/O sure/O way/O to/O tumble/O down/O a/O mountain/O and/O crack/O your/O skull/O ./O 
I/O prefer/O to/O make/O my/O crossing/O slow/O and/O easy/O ./O 
I/O know/O you/O love/O the/O taste/O of/O horse/O ,/O Bronn/LOCATION ,/O but/O if/O our/O mounts/O die/O under/O us/O this/O time/O ,/O we/O 'll/O be/O trying/O to/O saddle/O shadowcats/O .../O and/O if/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O I/O think/O the/O clans/O will/O find/O us/O no/O matter/O what/O we/O do/O ./O 
Their/O eyes/O are/O all/O around/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O swept/O a/O gloved/O hand/O over/O the/O high/O ,/O wind-carved/O crags/O that/O surrounded/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON grimaced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O we/O 're/O dead/O men/O ,/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O so/O ,/O I/O prefer/O to/O die/O comfortable/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O need/O a/O fire/O ./O 
The/O nights/O are/O cold/O up/O here/O ,/O and/O hot/O food/O will/O warm/O our/O bellies/O and/O lift/O our/O spirits/O ./O 
Do/O you/O suppose/O there/O 's/O any/O game/O to/O be/O had/O ?/O 
Lady/O Lysa/PERSON has/O kindly/O provided/O us/O with/O a/O veritable/O feast/O of/O salt/O beef/O ,/O hard/O cheese/O ,/O and/O stale/O bread/O ,/O but/O I/O would/O hate/O to/O break/O a/O tooth/O so/O far/O from/O the/O nearest/O maester/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O find/O meat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Beneath/O a/O fall/O of/O black/O hair/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON 's/O dark/O eyes/O regarded/O Tyrion/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O leave/O you/O here/O with/O your/O fool/O 's/O fire/O ./O 
If/O I/O took/O your/O horse/O ,/O I/O 'd/O have/O twice/O the/O chance/O to/O make/O it/O through/O ./O 
What/O would/O you/O do/O then/O ,/O dwarf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Die/O ,/O most/O like/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O stooped/O to/O get/O another/O stick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O think/O I/O 'd/O do/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 'd/O do/O it/O in/O an/O instant/O ,/O if/O it/O meant/O your/O life/O ./O 
You/O were/O quick/O enough/O to/O silence/O your/O friend/O Chiggen/PERSON when/O he/O caught/O that/O arrow/O in/O his/O belly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON had/O yanked/O back/O the/O man/O 's/O head/O by/O the/O hair/O and/O driven/O the/O point/O of/O his/O dirk/O in/O under/O the/O ear/O ,/O and/O afterward/O told/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON that/O the/O other/O sellsword/O had/O died/O of/O his/O wound/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O good/O as/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O his/O moaning/O was/O bringing/O them/O down/O on/O us/O ./O 
Chiggen/PERSON would/O have/O done/O the/O same/O for/O me/O .../O and/O he/O was/O no/O friend/O ,/O only/O a/O man/O I/O rode/O with/O ./O 
Make/O no/O mistake/O ,/O dwarf/O ./O 
I/O fought/O for/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O not/O love/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O your/O blade/O I/O needed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O not/O your/O love/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O dumped/O his/O armful/O of/O wood/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O bold/O as/O any/O sellsword/O ,/O I/O 'll/O give/O you/O that/O ./O 
How/O did/O you/O know/O I/O 'd/O take/O your/O part/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON squatted/O awkwardly/O on/O his/O stunted/O legs/O to/O build/O the/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O tossed/O the/O dice/O ./O 
Back/O at/O the/O inn/O ,/O you/O and/O Chiggen/PERSON helped/O take/O me/O captive/O ./O 
Why/O ?/O 
The/O others/O saw/O it/O as/O their/O duty/O ,/O for/O the/O honor/O of/O the/O lords/O they/O served/O ,/O but/O not/O you/O two/O ./O 
You/O had/O no/O lord/O ,/O no/O duty/O ,/O and/O precious/O little/O honor/O ,/O so/O why/O trouble/O to/O involve/O yourselves/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O out/O his/O knife/O and/O whittled/O some/O thin/O strips/O of/O bark/O off/O one/O of/O the/O sticks/O he/O 'd/O gathered/O ,/O to/O serve/O as/O kindling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O why/O do/O sellswords/O do/O anything/O ?/O 
For/O gold/O ./O 
You/O were/O thinking/O Lady/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O reward/O you/O for/O your/O help/O ,/O perhaps/O even/O take/O you/O into/O her/O service/O ./O 
Here/O ,/O that/O should/O do/O ,/O I/O hope/O ./O 
Do/O you/O have/O a/O flint/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/O slid/O two/O fingers/O into/O the/O pouch/O at/O his/O belt/O and/O tossed/O down/O a/O flint/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON caught/O it/O in/O the/O air/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O thanks/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O thing/O is/O ,/O you/O did/O not/O know/O the/O Starks/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Eddard/PERSON is/O a/O proud/O ,/O honorable/O ,/O and/O honest/O man/O ,/O and/O his/O lady/O wife/O is/O worse/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O no/O doubt/O she/O would/O have/O found/O a/O coin/O or/O two/O for/O you/O when/O this/O was/O all/O over/O ,/O and/O pressed/O it/O in/O your/O hand/O with/O a/O polite/O word/O and/O a/O look/O of/O distaste/O ,/O but/O that/O 's/O the/O most/O you/O could/O have/O hoped/O for/O ./O 
The/O Starks/PERSON look/O for/O courage/O and/O loyalty/O and/O honor/O in/O the/O men/O they/O choose/O to/O serve/O them/O ,/O and/O if/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O you/O and/O Chiggen/PERSON were/O lowborn/O scum/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O struck/O the/O flint/O against/O his/O dagger/O ,/O trying/O for/O a/O spark/O ./O 
Nothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O a/O bold/O tongue/O ,/O little/O man/O ./O 
One/O day/O someone/O is/O like/O to/O cut/O it/O out/O and/O make/O you/O eat/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Everyone/O tells/O me/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON glanced/O up/O at/O the/O sellsword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O I/O offend/O you/O ?/O 
My/O pardons/O .../O but/O you/O are/O scum/O ,/O Bronn/LOCATION ,/O make/O no/O mistake/O ./O 
Duty/O ,/O honor/O ,/O friendship/O ,/O what/O 's/O that/O to/O you/O ?/O 
No/O ,/O do/O n't/O trouble/O yourself/O ,/O we/O both/O know/O the/O answer/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O you/O 're/O not/O stupid/O ./O 
Once/O we/O reached/O the/O Vale/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O no/O more/O need/O of/O you/O .../O but/O I/O did/O ,/O and/O the/O one/O thing/O the/O Lannisters/O have/O never/O lacked/O for/O is/O gold/O ./O 
When/O the/O moment/O came/O to/O toss/O the/O dice/O ,/O I/O was/O counting/O on/O your/O being/O smart/O enough/O to/O know/O where/O your/O best/O interest/O lay/O ./O 
Happily/O for/O me/O ,/O you/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slammed/O stone/O and/O steel/O together/O again/O ,/O fruitlessly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Bronn/PERSON ,/O squatting/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O do/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O the/O knife/O and/O flint/O from/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O hands/O and/O struck/O sparks/O on/O his/O first/O try/O ./O 
A/O curl/O of/O bark/O began/O to/O smolder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Scum/O you/O may/O be/O ,/O but/O you/O 're/O undeniably/O useful/O ,/O and/O with/O a/O sword/O in/O your/O hand/O you/O 're/O almost/O as/O good/O as/O my/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON ./O 
What/O do/O you/O want/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON ?/O 
Gold/O ?/O 
Land/O ?/O 
Women/O ?/O 
Keep/O me/O alive/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O have/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/O blew/O gently/O on/O the/O fire/O ,/O and/O the/O flames/O leapt/O up/O higher/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O you/O die/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O then/O ,/O I/O 'll/O have/O one/O mourner/O whose/O grief/O is/O sincere/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O grinning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gold/O ends/O when/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O fire/O was/O blazing/O up/O nicely/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON stood/O ,/O tucked/O the/O flint/O back/O into/O his/O pouch/O ,/O and/O tossed/O Tyrion/O his/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fair/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sword/O 's/O yours/O ,/O then/O .../O but/O do/O n't/O go/O looking/O for/O me/O to/O bend/O the/O knee/O and/O mlord/O you/O every/O time/O you/O take/O a/O shit/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O no/O man/O 's/O toady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O any/O man/O 's/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O no/O doubt/O you/O 'd/O betray/O me/O as/O quick/O as/O you/O did/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O if/O you/O saw/O a/O profit/O in/O it/O ./O 
If/O the/O day/O ever/O comes/O when/O you/O 're/O tempted/O to/O sell/O me/O out/O ,/O remember/O this/O ,/O Bronn-ITl/O match/O their/O price/O ,/O whatever/O it/O is/O ./O 
I/O like/O living/O ./O 
And/O now/O ,/O do/O you/O think/O you/O could/O do/O something/O about/O finding/O us/O some/O supper/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O care/O of/O the/O horses/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ,/O unsheathing/O the/O long/O dirk/O he/O wore/O at/O his/O hip/O ./O 
He/O strode/O into/O the/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O An/O hour/O later/O the/O horses/O had/O been/O rubbed/O down/O and/O fed/O ,/O the/O fire/O was/O crackling/O away/O merrily/O ,/O and/O a/O haunch/O of/O a/O young/O goat/O was/O turning/O above/O the/O flames/O ,/O spitting/O and/O hissing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O we/O lack/O now/O is/O some/O good/O wine/O to/O wash/O down/O our/O kid/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O ,/O a/O woman/O ,/O and/O another/O dozen/O swords/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O sat/O cross-legged/O beside/O the/O fire/O ,/O honing/O the/O edge/O of/O his/O longsword/O with/O an/O oilstone/O ./O 
There/O was/O something/O strangely/O reassuring/O about/O the/O rasping/O sound/O it/O made/O when/O he/O drew/O it/O down/O the/O steel/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O full/O dark/O soon/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O sellsword/O pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O take/O first/O watch/O .../O for/O all/O the/O good/O it/O will/O do/O us/O ./O 
It/O might/O be/O kinder/O to/O let/O them/O kill/O us/O in/O our/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O imagine/O they/O 'll/O be/O here/O long/O before/O it/O comes/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O smell/O of/O the/O roasting/O meat/O made/O Tyrion/PERSON '/O s/O mouth/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON watched/O him/O across/O the/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O a/O plan/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O flatly/O ,/O with/O a/O scrape/O of/O steel/O on/O stone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O hope/O ,/O call/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Another/O toss/O of/O the/O dice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O With/O our/O lives/O as/O the/O stake/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O choice/O do/O we/O have/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O over/O the/O fire/O and/O sawed/O a/O thin/O slice/O of/O meat/O from/O the/O kid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ahhhh/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sighed/O happily/O as/O he/O chewed/O ./O 
Grease/O ran/O down/O his/O chin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O bit/O tougher/O than/O I/O 'd/O like/O ,/O and/O in/O want/O of/O spicing/O ,/O but/O I/O 'll/O not/O complain/O too/O loudly/O ./O 
If/O I/O were/O back/O at/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O I/O 'd/O be/O dancing/O on/O a/O precipice/O in/O hopes/O of/O a/O boiled/O bean/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O yet/O you/O gave/O the/O turnkey/O a/O purse/O of/O gold/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O Lannister/O always/O pays/O his/O debts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Even/O Mord/PERSON had/O scarcely/O believed/O it/O when/O Tyrion/PERSON tossed/O him/O the/O leather/O purse/O ./O 
The/O gaoler/O 's/O eyes/O had/O gone/O big/O as/O boiled/O eggs/O as/O he/O yanked/O open/O -/O the/O drawstring/O and/O beheld/O the/O glint/O of/O gold/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O kept/O the/O silver/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O told/O him/O with/O a/O crooked/O smile/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O you/O were/O promised/O the/O gold/O ,/O and/O there/O it/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O more/O than/O a/O man/O like/O Mord/PERSON could/O hope/O to/O earn/O in/O a/O lifetime/O of/O abusing/O prisoners/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O remember/O what/O I/O said/O ,/O this/O is/O only/O a/O taste/O ./O 
If/O you/O ever/O grow/O tired/O of/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O service/O ,/O present/O yourself/O at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O pay/O you/O the/O rest/O of/O what/O I/O owe/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O With/O golden/O dragons/O spilling/O out/O of/O both/O hands/O ,/O Mord/PERSON had/O fallen/O to/O his/O knees/O and/O promised/O that/O he/O would/O do/O just/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON yanked/O out/O his/O dirk/O and/O pulled/O the/O meat/O from/O the/O fire/O ./O 
He/O began/O to/O carve/O thick/O chunks/O of/O charred/O meat/O off/O the/O bone/O as/O Tyrion/PERSON hollowed/O out/O two/O heels/O of/O stale/O bread/O to/O serve/O as/O trenchers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O do/O reach/O the/O river/O ,/O what/O will/O you/O do/O then/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O sellsword/O asked/O as/O he/O cut/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O a/O whore/O and/O a/O featherbed/O and/O a/O flagon/O of/O wine/O ,/O for/O a/O start/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON held/O out/O his/O trencher/O ,/O and/O Bronn/LOCATION filled/O it/O with/O meat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O then/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION or/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O I/O think/O ./O 
I/O have/O some/O questions/O that/O want/O answering/O ,/O concerning/O a/O certain/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O sellsword/O chewed/O and/O swallowed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O you/O were/O telling/O it/O true/O ?/O 
It/O was/O not/O your/O knife/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O smiled/O thinly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O I/O look/O a/O liar/O to/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O their/O bellies/O were/O full/O ,/O the/O stars/O had/O come/O out/O and/O a/O halfmoon/O was/O rising/O over/O the/O mountains/O ./O 
Tyrion/O spread/O his/O shadowskin/O cloak/O on/O the/O ground/O and/O stretched/O out/O with/O his/O saddle/O for/O a/O pillow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Our/O friends/O are/O taking/O their/O sweet/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O I/O were/O them/O ,/O I/O 'd/O fear/O a/O trap/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O else/O would/O we/O be/O so/O open/O ,/O if/O not/O to/O lure/O them/O in/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O we/O ought/O to/O sing/O and/O send/O them/O fleeing/O in/O terror/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O began/O to/O whistle/O a/O tune/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O mad/O ,/O dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O as/O he/O cleaned/O the/O grease/O out/O from/O under/O his/O nails/O with/O his/O dirk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O 's/O your/O love/O of/O music/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O it/O was/O music/O you/O wanted/O ,/O you/O should/O have/O gotten/O the/O singer/O to/O champion/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O would/O have/O been/O amusing/O ./O 
I/O can/O just/O see/O him/O fending/O off/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON with/O his/O woodharp/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O resumed/O his/O whistling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O know/O this/O song/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O hear/O it/O here/O and/O there/O ,/O in/O inns/O and/O whorehouses/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Myrish/O ./O 
`/O The/O Seasons/O of/O My/O Love/O ./O '/O 
Sweet/O and/O sad/O ,/O if/O you/O understand/O the/O words/O ./O 
The/O first/O girl/O I/O ever/O bedded/O used/O to/O sing/O it/O ,/O and/O I/O 've/O never/O been/O able/O to/O put/O it/O out/O of/O my/O head/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON gazed/O up/O at/O the/O sky/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O clear/O cold/O night/O and/O the/O stars/O shone/O down/O upon/O the/O mountains/O as/O bright/O and/O merciless/O as/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O met/O her/O on/O a/O night/O like/O this/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O heard/O himself/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON and/O I/O were/O riding/O back/O from/O Lannisport/LOCATION when/O we/O heard/O a/O scream/O ,/O and/O she/O came/O running/O out/O into/O the/O road/O with/O two/O men/O dogging/O her/O heels/O ,/O shouting/O threats/O ./O 
My/O brother/O unsheathed/O his/O sword/O and/O went/O after/O them/O ,/O while/O I/O dismounted/O to/O protect/O the/O girl/O ./O 
She/O was/O scarcely/O a/O year/O older/O than/O I/O was/O ,/O dark/O -/O haired/O ,/O slender/O ,/O with/O a/O face/O that/O would/O break/O your/O heart/O ./O 
It/O certainly/O broke/O mine/O ./O 
Lowborn/O ,/O halfstarved/O ,/O unwashed/O .../O yet/O lovely/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O torn/O the/O rags/O she/O was/O wearing/O half/O off/O her/O back/O ,/O so/O I/O wrapped/O her/O in/O my/O cloak/O while/O Jaime/PERSON chased/O the/O men/O into/O the/O woods/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O he/O came/O trotting/O back/O ,/O I/O 'd/O gotten/O a/O name/O out/O of/O her/O ,/O and/O a/O story/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O crofter/O 's/O child/O ,/O orphaned/O when/O her/O father/O died/O of/O fever/O ,/O on/O her/O way/O to/O .../O well/O ,/O nowhere/O ,/O really/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON was/O all/O in/O a/O lather/O to/O hunt/O down/O the/O men/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O often/O outlaws/O dared/O prey/O on/O travelers/O so/O near/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O he/O took/O it/O as/O an/O insult/O ./O 
The/O girl/O was/O too/O frightened/O to/O send/O off/O by/O herself/O ,/O though/O ,/O so/O I/O offered/O to/O take/O her/O to/O the/O closest/O inn/O and/O feed/O her/O while/O my/O brother/O rode/O back/O to/O the/O Rock/O for/O help/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O hungrier/O than/O I/O would/O have/O believed/O ./O 
We/O finished/O two/O whole/O chickens/O and/O part/O of/O a/O third/O ,/O and/O drank/O a/O flagon/O of/O wine/O ,/O talking/O ./O 
I/O was/O only/O thirteen/O ,/O and/O the/O wine/O went/O to/O my/O head/O ,/O I/O fear/O ./O 
The/O next/O thing/O I/O knew/O ,/O I/O was/O sharing/O her/O bed/O ./O 
If/O she/O was/O shy/O ,/O I/O was/O shyer/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O never/O know/O where/O I/O found/O the/O courage/O ./O 
When/O I/O broke/O her/O maidenhead/O ,/O she/O wept/O ,/O but/O afterward/O she/O kissed/O me/O and/O sang/O her/O little/O song/O ,/O and/O by/O morning/O I/O was/O in/O love/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON 's/O voice/O was/O amused/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Absurd/O ,/O is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O began/O to/O whistle/O the/O song/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O married/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O finally/O admitted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O Lannister/O of/O Casterly/O Rock/O wed/O to/O a/O crofter/O 's/O daughter/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O did/O you/O manage/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O you/O 'd/O be/O astonished/O at/O what/O a/O boy/O can/O make/O of/O a/O few/O lies/O ,/O fifty/O pieces/O of/O silver/O ,/O and/O a/O drunken/O septon/O ./O 
I/O dared/O not/O bring/O my/O bride/O home/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O so/O I/O set/O her/O up/O in/O a/O cottage/O of/O her/O own/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O fortnight/O we/O played/O at/O being/O man/O and/O wife/O ./O 
And/O then/O the/O septon/O sobered/O and/O confessed/O all/O to/O my/O lord/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O surprised/O at/O how/O desolate/O it/O made/O him/O feel/O to/O say/O it/O ,/O even/O after/O all/O these/O years/O ./O 
Perhaps/O he/O was/O just/O tired/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O end/O of/O my/O marriage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sat/O up/O and/O stared/O at/O the/O dying/O fire/O ,/O blinking/O at/O the/O light/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O sent/O the/O girl/O away/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O did/O better/O than/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O First/O he/O made/O my/O brother/O tell/O me/O the/O truth/O ./O 
The/O girl/O was/O a/O whore/O ,/O you/O see/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON arranged/O the/O whole/O affair/O ,/O the/O road/O ,/O the/O outlaws/O ,/O all/O of/O it/O ./O 
He/O thought/O it/O was/O time/O I/O had/O a/O woman/O ./O 
He/O paid/O double/O for/O a/O maiden/O ,/O knowing/O it/O would/O be/O my/O first/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O After/O Jaime/PERSON had/O made/O his/O confession/O ,/O to/O drive/O home/O the/O lesson/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON brought/O my/O wife/O in/O and/O gave/O her/O to/O his/O guards/O ./O 
They/O paid/O her/O fair/O enough/O ./O 
A/O silver/O for/O each/O man/O ,/O how/O many/O whores/O command/O that/O high/O a/O price/O ?/O 
He/O sat/O me/O down/O in/O the/O corner/O of/O the/O barracks/O and/O bade/O me/O watch/O ,/O and/O at/O the/O end/O she/O had/O so/O many/O silvers/O the/O coins/O were/O slipping/O through/O her/O fingers/O and/O rolling/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O she/O .../O \/O ''/O The/O smoke/O was/O stinging/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON cleared/O his/O throat/O and/O turned/O away/O from/O the/O fire/O ,/O to/O gaze/O out/O into/O darkness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON had/O me/O go/O last/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O quiet/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O he/O gave/O me/O a/O gold/O coin/O to/O pay/O her/O ,/O because/O I/O was/O a/O Lannister/O ,/O and/O worth/O more/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O After/O a/O time/O he/O heard/O the/O noise/O again/O ,/O the/O rasp/O of/O steel/O on/O stone/O as/O Bronn/PERSON sharpened/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thirteen/O or/O thirty/O or/O three/O ,/O I/O would/O have/O killed/O the/O man/O who/O did/O that/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O swung/O around/O to/O face/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O may/O get/O that/O chance/O one/O day/O ./O 
Remember/O what/O I/O told/O you/O ./O 
A/O Lannister/O always/O pays/O his/O debts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O yawned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O I/O will/O try/O and/O sleep/O ./O 
Wake/O me/O if/O we/O 're/O about/O to/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O rolled/O himself/O up/O in/O the/O shadowskin/O and/O shut/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O ground/O was/O stony/O and/O cold/O ,/O but/O after/O a/O time/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON did/O sleep/O ./O 
He/O dreamt/O of/O the/O sky/O cell/O ./O 
This/O time/O he/O was/O the/O gaoler/O ,/O not/O the/O prisoner/O ,/O big/O ,/O with/O a/O strap/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O hitting/O his/O father/O ,/O driving/O him/O back/O ,/O toward/O the/O abyss/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tyrion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON 's/O warning/O was/O low/O and/O urgent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O was/O awake/O in/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O ./O 
The/O fire/O had/O burned/O down/O to/O embers/O ,/O and/O the/O shadows/O were/O creeping/O in/O all/O around/O them/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON had/O raised/O himself/O to/O one/O knee/O ,/O his/O sword/O in/O one/O hand/O and/O his/O dirk/O in/O the/O other/O ./O 
Tyrion/O held/O up/O a/O hand/O :/O stay/O still/O ,/O it/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O share/O our/O fire/O ,/O the/O night/O is/O cold/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O to/O the/O creeping/O shadows/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O we/O 've/O no/O wine/O to/O offer/O you/O ,/O but/O you/O 're/O welcome/O to/O some/O of/O our/O goat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O All/O movement/O stopped/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON saw/O the/O glint/O of/O moonlight/O on/O metal/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Our/O mountain/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O called/O out/O from/O the/O trees/O ,/O deep/O and/O hard/O and/O unfriendly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Our/O goat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O goat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O you/O meet/O your/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O different/O voice/O replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O say/O it/O was/O Gunthor/O son/O of/O Gurn/PERSON of/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O who/O sent/O you/O to/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O branch/O cracked/O underfoot/O as/O he/O stepped/O into/O the/O light/O ;/O a/O thin/O man/O in/O a/O horned/O helmet/O ,/O armed/O with/O a/O long/O knife/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O Shagga/O son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON \/O ''/O That/O was/O the/O first/O voice/O ,/O deep/O and/O deadly/O ./O 
A/O boulder/O shifted/O to/O their/O left/O ,/O and/O stood/O ,/O and/O became/O a/O man/O ./O 
Massive/O and/O slow/O and/O strong/O he/O seemed/O ,/O dressed/O all/O in/O skins/O ,/O with/O a/O club/O in/O his/O right/O hand/O and/O an/O axe/O in/O his/O left/O ./O 
He/O smashed/O them/O together/O as/O he/O lumbered/O closer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Other/O voices/O called/O other/O names/O ,/O Conn/LOCATION and/O Torrek/LOCATION and/O Jaggot/PERSON and/O more/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON forgot/O the/O instant/O he/O heard/O them/O ;/O ten/O at/O least/O ./O 
A/O few/O had/O swords/O and/O knives/O ;/O others/O brandished/O pitchforks/O and/O scythes/O and/O wooden/O spears/O ./O 
He/O waited/O until/O they/O were/O done/O shouting/O out/O their/O names/O before/O he/O gave/O them/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O Tyrion/O son/O of/O Tywin/LOCATION ,/O of/O the/O Clan/O Lannister/O ,/O the/O Lions/O of/O the/O Rock/O ./O 
We/O will/O gladly/O pay/O you/O for/O the/O goat/O we/O ate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O have/O to/O give/O us/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON son/O of/O Tywin/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O the/O one/O who/O named/O himself/O Gunthor/PERSON ,/O who/O seemed/O to/O be/O their/O chief/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O silver/O in/O my/O purse/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O hauberk/O I/O wear/O is/O large/O for/O me/O ,/O but/O it/O should/O fit/O Conn/LOCATION nicely/O ,/O and/O the/O battle-axe/O I/O carry/O would/O suit/O Shagga/PERSON 's/O mighty/O hand/O far/O better/O than/O that/O wood/O -/O axe/O he/O holds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O halfman/O would/O pay/O us/O with/O our/O own/O coin/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Conn./O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Conn/PERSON speaks/O truly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Gunthor/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O silver/O is/O ours/O ./O 
Your/O horses/O are/O ours/O ./O 
Your/O hauberk/O and/O your/O battle-axe/O and/O the/O knife/O at/O your/O belt/O ,/O those/O are/O ours/O too/O ./O 
You/O have/O nothing/O to/O give/O us/O but/O your/O lives/O ./O 
How/O would/O you/O like/O to/O die/O ,/O Tyrion/O son/O of/O Tywin/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O my/O own/O bed/O ,/O with/O a/O belly/O full/O of/O wine/O and/O a/O maiden/O 's/O mouth/O around/O my/O cock/O ,/O at/O the/O age/O of/O eighty/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O huge/O one/O ,/O Shagga/LOCATION ,/O laughed/O first/O and/O loudest/O ./O 
The/O others/O seemed/O less/O amused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Conn/O ,/O take/O their/O horses/O ,/O \/O ''/O Gunthor/PERSON commanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kill/O the/O other/O and/O seize/O the/O halfinan/O ./O 
He/O can/O milk/O the/O goats/O and/O make/O the/O mothers/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON sprang/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O dies/O first/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gunthor/O son/O of/O Gurn/O ,/O hear/O me/O ./O 
My/O House/ORGANIZATION is/O rich/O and/O powerful/O ./O 
If/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O will/O see/O us/O safely/O through/O these/O mountains/O ,/O my/O lord/O father/O will/O shower/O you/O with/O gold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gold/O of/O a/O lowland/O lord/O is/O as/O worthless/O as/O a/O halfman/O 's/O promises/O ,/O \/O ''/O Gunthor/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Haifa/LOCATION man/O I/O may/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O I/O have/O the/O courage/O to/O face/O my/O enemies/O ./O 
What/O do/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O do/O ,/O but/O hide/O behind/O rocks/O and/O shiver/O with/O fear/O as/O the/O knights/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ride/O by/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Shagga/PERSON gave/O a/O roar/O of/O anger/O and/O clashed/O club/O against/O axe/O ./O 
Jaggot/PERSON poked/O at/O Tyrion/ORGANIZATION '/O s/O face/O with/O the/O fire-hardened/O point/O of/O a/O long/O wooden/O spear/O ./O 
He/O did/O his/O best/O not/O to/O flinch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O these/O the/O best/O weapons/O you/O could/O steal/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Good/O enough/O for/O killing/O sheep/O ,/O perhaps/O .../O if/O the/O sheep/O do/O not/O fight/O back/O ./O 
My/O father/O 's/O smiths/O shit/O better/O steel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Little/O boyman/O ,/O \/O ''/O Shagga/PERSON roared/O ,/O \/O ``/O will/O you/O mock/O my/O axe/O after/O I/O chop/O off/O your/O manhood/O and/O feed/O it/O to/O the/O goats/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O But/O Gunthor/PERSON raised/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
I/O would/O hear/O his/O words/O ./O 
The/O mothers/O go/O hungry/O ,/O and/O steel/O fills/O more/O mouths/O than/O gold/O ./O 
What/O would/O you/O give/O us/O for/O your/O lives/O ,/O Tyrion/O son/O of/O Tywin/PERSON ?/O 
Swords/O ?/O 
Lances/O ?/O 
Mail/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O that/O ,/O and/O more/O ,/O Gunthor/PERSON son/O of/O Gurn/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON replied/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O give/O you/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
