-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Are/O you/O well/O ,/O Snow/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON asked/O ,/O scowling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O raven/O squawked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON lied/O .../O loudly/O ,/O as/O if/O that/O could/O make/O it/O true/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O dead/O man/O tried/O to/O kill/O me/O ./O 
How/O well/O could/O I/O be/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O scratched/O under/O his/O chin/O ./O 
His/O shaggy/O grey/O beard/O had/O been/O singed/O in/O the/O fire/O ,/O and/O he/O 'd/O hacked/O it/O off/O ./O 
The/O pale/O stubble/O of/O his/O new/O whiskers/O made/O him/O look/O old/O ,/O disreputable/O ,/O and/O grumpy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O look/O well/O ./O 
How/O is/O your/O hand/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Healing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON flexed/O his/O bandaged/O fingers/O to/O show/O him/O ./O 
He/O had/O burned/O himself/O more/O badly/O than/O he/O knew/O throwing/O the/O flaming/O drapes/O ,/O and/O his/O right/O hand/O was/O swathed/O in/O silk/O halfway/O to/O the/O elbow/O ./O 
At/O the/O time/O he/O 'd/O felt/O nothing/O ;/O the/O agony/O had/O come/O after/O ./O 
His/O cracked/O red/O skin/O oozed/O fluid/O ,/O and/O fearsome/O blood/O blisters/O rose/O between/O his/O fingers/O ,/O big/O as/O roaches/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O maester/O says/O I/O 'll/O have/O scars/O ,/O but/O otherwise/O the/O hand/O should/O be/O as/O good/O as/O it/O was/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O scarred/O hand/O is/O nothing/O ./O 
On/O the/O Wall/O ,/O you/O 'll/O be/O wearing/O gloves/O often/O as/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O not/O the/O thought/O of/O scars/O that/O troubled/O Jon/PERSON ;/O it/O was/O the/O rest/O of/O it/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON had/O given/O him/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O ,/O the/O pain/O had/O been/O hideous/O ./O 
At/O first/O it/O had/O felt/O as/O if/O his/O hand/O were/O still/O aflame/O ,/O burning/O day/O and/O night/O ./O 
Only/O plunging/O it/O into/O basins/O of/O snow/O and/O shaved/O ice/O gave/O any/O relief/O at/O all/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON thanked/O the/O gods/O that/O no/O one/O but/O Ghost/PERSON saw/O him/O writhing/O on/O his/O bed/O ,/O whimpering/O from/O the/O pain/O ./O 
And/O when/O at/O last/O he/O did/O sleep/O ,/O he/O dreamt/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O even/O worse/O ./O 
In/O the/O dream/O ,/O the/O corpse/O he/O fought/O had/O blue/O eyes/O ,/O black/O hands/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O 's/O face/O ,/O but/O he/O dared/O not/O tell/O Mormont/PERSON that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dywen/PERSON and/O Hake/PERSON returned/O last/O night/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O found/O no/O sign/O of/O your/O uncle/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O the/O others/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON had/O dragged/O himself/O to/O the/O common/O hall/O to/O sup/O with/O his/O friends/O ,/O and/O the/O failure/O of/O the/O rangers/O '/O search/O had/O been/O all/O the/O men/O had/O been/O talking/O of/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O is/O it/O that/O everyone/O knows/O everything/O around/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O expect/O an/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O there/O were/O only/O the/O two/O of/O .../O of/O those/O creatures/O ,/O whatever/O they/O were/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O call/O them/O men/O ./O 
And/O thank/O the/O gods/O for/O that/O ./O 
Any/O more/O and/O .../O well/O ,/O that/O does/O n't/O bear/O thinking/O of/O ./O 
There/O will/O be/O more/O ,/O though/O ./O 
I/O can/O feel/O it/O in/O these/O old/O bones/O of/O mine/O ,/O and/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON agrees/O ./O 
The/O cold/O winds/O are/O rising/O ./O 
Summer/O is/O at/O an/O end/O ,/O and/O a/O winter/O is/O coming/O such/O as/O this/O world/O has/O never/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Winter/O is/O coming/O ./O 
The/O Stark/O words/O had/O never/O sounded/O so/O grim/O or/O ominous/O to/O Jon/PERSON as/O they/O did/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O asked/O hesitantly/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O 's/O said/O there/O was/O a/O bird/O last/O night/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O ./O 
What/O of/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O hoped/O for/O some/O word/O of/O my/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O taunted/O the/O old/O raven/O ,/O bobbing/O its/O head/O as/O it/O walked/O across/O Mormont/LOCATION 's/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O reached/O up/O to/O pinch/O its/O beak/O shut/O ,/O but/O the/O raven/O hopped/O up/O on/O his/O head/O ,/O fluttered/O its/O wings/O ,/O and/O flew/O across/O the/O chamber/O to/O light/O above/O a/O window/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Grief/O and/O noise/O ,/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O all/O they/O 're/O good/O for/O ,/O ravens/O ./O 
Why/O I/O put/O up/O with/O that/O pestilential/O bird/O .../O if/O there/O was/O news/O of/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O do/O n't/O you/O think/O I/O would/O have/O sent/O for/O you/O ?/O 
Bastard/O or/O no/O ,/O you/O 're/O still/O his/O blood/O ./O 
The/O message/O concerned/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O ./O 
It/O seems/O he/O 's/O been/O removed/O from/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
They/O gave/O his/O place/O to/O that/O black/O dog/O Clegane/O ,/O and/O now/O Selmy/PERSON 's/O wanted/O for/O treason/O ./O 
The/O fools/O sent/O some/O watchmen/O to/O seize/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O slew/O two/O of/O them/O and/O escaped/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON snorted/O ,/O leaving/O no/O doubt/O of/O his/O view/O of/O men/O who/O 'd/O send/O gold/O cloaks/O against/O a/O knight/O as/O renowed/O as/O Barristan/O the/O Bold/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O white/O shadows/O in/O the/O woods/O and/O unquiet/O dead/O stalking/O our/O halls/O ,/O and/O a/O boy/O sits/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O disgust/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O raven/O laughed/O shrilly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Boy/O ,/O boy/O ,/O boy/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O had/O been/O the/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O best/O hope/O ,/O Jon/PERSON remembered/O ;/O if/O he/O had/O fallen/O ,/O what/O chance/O was/O there/O that/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O letter/O would/O be/O heeded/O ?/O 
He/O curled/O his/O hand/O into/O a/O fist/O ./O 
Pain/O shot/O through/O his/O burned/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O of/O my/O sisters/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O message/O made/O no/O mention/O of/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON or/O the/O girls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O an/O irritated/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O they/O never/O got/O my/O letter/O ./O 
Aemon/PERSON sent/O two/O copies/O ,/O with/O his/O best/O birds/O ,/O but/O who/O can/O say/O ?/O 
More/O like/O ,/O Pycelle/PERSON did/O not/O deign/O to/O reply/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O be/O the/O first/O time/O ,/O nor/O the/O last/O ./O 
I/O fear/O we/O count/O for/O less/O than/O nothing/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
They/O tell/O us/O what/O they/O want/O us/O to/O know/O ,/O and/O that/O 's/O little/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O you/O tell/O me/O what/O you/O want/O me/O to/O know/O ,/O and/O that/O 's/O less/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O resentfully/O ./O 
His/O brother/O Robb/PERSON had/O called/O the/O banners/O and/O ridden/O south/O to/O war/O ,/O yet/O no/O word/O of/O that/O had/O been/O breathed/O to/O him/O .../O save/O by/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON ,/O who/O 'd/O read/O the/O letter/O to/O Maester/O Aemon/O and/O whispered/O its/O contents/O to/O Jon/PERSON that/O night/O in/O secret/O ,/O all/O the/O time/O saying/O how/O he/O should/O n't/O ./O 
Doubtless/O they/O thought/O his/O brother/O 's/O war/O was/O none/O of/O his/O concern/O ./O 
It/O troubled/O him/O more/O than/O he/O could/O say/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON was/O marching/O and/O he/O was/O not/O ./O 
No/O matter/O how/O often/O Jon/PERSON told/O himself/O that/O his/O place/O was/O here/O now/O ,/O with/O his/O new/O brothers/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O he/O still/O felt/O craven/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O was/O crying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O be/O quiet/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O told/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Snow/O ,/O how/O soon/O does/O Maester/O Aemon/O say/O you/O 'll/O have/O use/O of/O that/O hand/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Soon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ./O 
\/O ''/O On/O the/O table/O between/O them/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON laid/O a/O large/O sword/O in/O a/O black/O metal/O scabbard/O banded/O with/O silver/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O be/O ready/O for/O this/O ,/O then/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O raven/O flapped/O down/O and/O landed/O on/O the/O table/O ,/O strutting/O toward/O the/O sword/O ,/O head/O cocked/O curiously/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON hesitated/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O inkling/O what/O this/O meant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O fire/O melted/O the/O silver/O off/O the/O pommel/O and/O burnt/O the/O crossguard/O and/O grip/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O dry/O leather/O and/O old/O wood/O ,/O what/O could/O you/O expect/O ?/O 
The/O blade/O ,/O now/O .../O you/O 'd/O need/O a/O fire/O a/O hundred/O times/O as/O hot/O to/O harm/O the/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON shoved/O the/O scabbard/O across/O the/O rough/O oak/O planks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O the/O rest/O made/O anew/O ./O 
Take/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O echoed/O his/O raven/O ,/O preening/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O it/O ,/O take/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Awkwardly/O ,/O Jon/PERSON took/O the/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
His/O left/O hand/O ;/O his/O bandaged/O right/O was/O still/O too/O raw/O and/O clumsy/O ./O 
Carefully/O he/O pulled/O it/O from/O its/O scabbard/O and/O raised/O it/O level/O with/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O pommel/O was/O a/O hunk/O of/O pale/O stone/O weighted/O with/O lead/O to/O balance/O the/O long/O blade/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O carved/O into/O the/O likeness/O of/O a/O snarling/O wolfs/O head/O ,/O with/O chips/O of/O garnet/O set/O into/O the/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O grip/O was/O virgin/O leather/O ,/O soft/O and/O black/O ,/O as/O yet/O unstained/O by/O sweat/O or/O blood/O ./O 
The/O blade/O itself/O was/O a/O good/O half/O foot/O longer/O than/O those/O Jon/PERSON was/O used/O to/O ,/O tapered/O to/O thrust/O as/O well/O as/O slash/O ,/O with/O three/O fullers/O deeply/O incised/O in/O the/O metal/O ./O 
Where/O Ice/O was/O a/O true/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ,/O this/O was/O a/O hand-and-a-halfer/O ,/O sometimes/O named/O a/O \/O ``/O bastard/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Yet/O the/O wolf/O sword/O actually/O seemed/O lighter/O than/O the/O blades/O he/O had/O wielded/O before/O ./O 
When/O Jon/PERSON turned/O it/O sideways/O ,/O he/O could/O see/O the/O ripples/O in/O the/O dark/O steel/O where/O the/O metal/O had/O been/O folded/O back/O on/O itself/O again/O and/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O wonderingly/O ./O 
His/O father/O had/O let/O him/O handle/O Ice/O often/O enough/O ;/O he/O knew/O the/O look/O ,/O the/O feel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O my/O father/O 's/O sword/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O 's/O before/O him/O ./O 
The/O Mormonts/O have/O carried/O it/O for/O five/O centuries/O ./O 
I/O wielded/O it/O in/O my/O day/O and/O passed/O it/O on/O to/O my/O son/O when/O I/O took/O the/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O is/O giving/O me/O his/O son/O 's/O sword/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O scarcely/O believe/O it/O ./O 
The/O blade/O was/O exquisitely/O balanced/O ./O 
The/O edges/O glimmered/O faintly/O as/O they/O kissed/O the/O light/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O son/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O son/O brought/O dishonor/O to/O House/O Mormont/O ,/O but/O at/O least/O he/O had/O the/O grace/O to/O leave/O the/O sword/O behind/O when/O he/O fled/O ./O 
My/O sister/O returned/O it/O to/O my/O keeping/O ,/O but/O the/O very/O sight/O of/O it/O reminded/O me/O of/O Jorah/PERSON 's/O shame/O ,/O so/O I/O put/O it/O aside/O and/O thought/O no/O more/O of/O it/O until/O we/O found/O it/O in/O the/O ashes/O of/O my/O bedchamber/O ./O 
The/O original/O pommel/O was/O a/O bear/O 's/O head/O ,/O silver/O ,/O yet/O so/O worn/O its/O features/O were/O all/O but/O indistinguishable/O ./O 
For/O you/O ,/O I/O thought/O a/O white/O wolf/O more/O apt/O ./O 
One/O of/O our/O builders/O is/O a/O fair/O stonecarver/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O Jon/PERSON had/O been/O Bran/O 's/O age/O ,/O he/O had/O dreamed/O of/O doing/O great/O deeds/O ,/O as/O boys/O always/O did/O ./O 
The/O details/O of/O his/O feats/O changed/O with/O every/O dreaming/O ,/O but/O quite/O often/O he/O imagined/O saving/O his/O father/O 's/O life/O ./O 
Afterward/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON would/O declare/O that/O Jon/PERSON had/O proved/O himself/O a/O true/O Stark/O ,/O and/O place/O Ice/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
Even/O then/O he/O had/O known/O it/O was/O only/O a/O child/O 's/O folly/O ;/O no/O bastard/O could/O ever/O hope/O to/O wield/O a/O father/O 's/O sword/O ./O 
Even/O the/O memory/O shamed/O him/O ./O 
What/O kind/O of/O man/O stole/O his/O own/O brother/O 's/O birthright/O ?/O 
I/O have/O no/O right/O to/O this/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O to/O ke/O ./O 
He/O twitched/O his/O burned/O fingers/O ,/O feeling/O a/O throb/O of/O pain/O deep/O under/O the/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O you/O honor/O me/O ,/O but/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Spare/O me/O your/O but/O 's/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON interrupted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O not/O be/O sitting/O here/O were/O it/O not/O for/O you/O and/O that/O beast/O of/O yours/O ./O 
You/O fought/O bravely/O .../O and/O more/O to/O the/O point/O ,/O you/O thought/O quickly/O ./O 
Fire/O !/O 
Yes/O ,/O damn/O it/O ./O 
We/O ought/O to/O have/O known/O ./O 
We/O ought/O to/O have/O remembered/O ./O 
The/O Long/O Night/O has/O come/O before/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O eight/O thousand/O years/O is/O a/O good/O while/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O .../O yet/O if/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O does/O not/O remember/O ,/O who/O will/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O chimed/O the/O talkative/O raven/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Truly/O ,/O the/O gods/O had/O heard/O Jon/PERSON 's/O prayer/O that/O night/O ;/O the/O fire/O had/O caught/O in/O the/O dead/O man/O 's/O clothing/O and/O consumed/O him/O as/O if/O his/O flesh/O were/O candle/O wax/O and/O his/O bones/O old/O dry/O wood/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O only/O to/O close/O his/O eyes/O to/O see/O the/O thing/O staggering/O across/O the/O solar/O ,/O crashing/O against/O the/O furniture/O and/O flailing/O at/O the/O flames/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O face/O that/O haunted/O him/O most/O ;/O surrounded/O by/O a/O nimbus/O of/O fire/O ,/O hair/O blazing/O like/O straw/O ,/O the/O dead/O flesh/O melting/O away/O and/O sloughing/O off/O its/O skull/O to/O reveal/O the/O gleam/O of/O bone/O beneath/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Whatever/O demonic/O force/O moved/O Othor/O had/O been/O driven/O out/O by/O the/O flames/O ;/O the/O twisted/O thing/O they/O had/O found/O in/O the/O ashes/O had/O been/O no/O more/O than/O cooked/O meat/O and/O charred/O bone/O ./O 
Yet/O in/O his/O nightmare/O he/O faced/O it/O again/O .../O and/O this/O time/O the/O burning/O corpse/O wore/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O features/O ./O 
It/O was/O his/O father/O 's/O skin/O that/O burst/O and/O blackened/O ,/O his/O father/O 's/O eyes/O that/O ran/O liquid/O down/O his/O cheeks/O like/O jellied/O tears/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON did/O not/O understand/O why/O that/O should/O be/O or/O what/O it/O might/O mean/O ,/O but/O it/O frightened/O him/O more/O than/O he/O could/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O sword/O 's/O small/O payment/O for/O a/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON concluded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O it/O ,/O I/O 'll/O hear/O no/O more/O of/O it/O ,/O is/O that/O understood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O soft/O leather/O gave/O beneath/O Jon/PERSON 's/O fingers/O ,/O as/O if/O the/O sword/O were/O molding/O itself/O to/O his/O grip/O already/O ./O 
He/O knew/O he/O should/O be/O honored/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O ,/O and/O yet/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O is/O not/O my/O father/O ./O 
The/O thought/O leapt/O unbidden/O to/O Jon/PERSON 's/O mind/O ./O 
Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON is/O my/O father/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O forget/O him/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O many/O swords/O they/O give/O me/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O could/O scarcely/O tell/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON that/O it/O was/O another/O man/O 's/O sword/O he/O dreamt/O of/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O no/O courtesies/O either/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O so/O thank/O me/O no/O thanks/O ./O 
Honor/O the/O steel/O with/O deeds/O ,/O not/O words/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O it/O have/O a/O name/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O did/O ,/O once/O ./O 
Longclaw/PERSON ,/O it/O was/O called/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Claw/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O cried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Claw/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Longclaw/O is/O an/O apt/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON tried/O a/O practice/O cut/O ./O 
He/O was/O clumsy/O and/O uncomfortable/O with/O his/O left/O hand/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O the/O steel/O seemed/O to/O flow/O through/O the/O air/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O had/O a/O will/O of/O its/O own/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wolves/O have/O claws/O ,/O as/O much/O as/O bears/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O seemed/O pleased/O by/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O they/O do/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O want/O to/O wear/O that/O over/O the/O shoulder/O ,/O I/O imagine/O ./O 
It/O 's/O too/O long/O for/O the/O hip/O ,/O at/O least/O until/O you/O 've/O put/O on/O a/O few/O inches/O ./O 
And/O you/O 'll/O need/O to/O work/O at/O your/O two-handed/O strikes/O as/O well/O ./O 
Ser/O Endrew/O can/O show/O you/O some/O moves/O ,/O when/O your/O burns/O have/O healed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Endrew/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O know/O the/O name/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Endrew/O Tarth/O ,/O a/O good/O man/O ./O 
He/O 's/O on/O his/O way/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Tower/O to/O assume/O the/O duties/O of/O master-at-arms/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON left/O yestermorn/O for/O Eastwatch-by-the-Sea/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON lowered/O the/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O stupidly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Because/O I/O sent/O him/O ,/O why/O do/O you/O think/O ?/O 
He/O 's/O bringing/O the/O hand/O your/O Ghost/O tore/O off/O the/O end/O of/O Jafer/PERSON Flowers/PERSON 's/O wrist/O ./O 
I/O have/O commanded/O him/O to/O take/O ship/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O lay/O it/O before/O this/O boy/O king/O ./O 
That/O should/O get/O young/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O attention/O ,/O I/O 'd/O think/O .../O and/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O a/O knight/O ,/O highborn/O ,/O anointed/O ,/O with/O old/O friends/O at/O court/O ,/O altogether/O harder/O to/O ignore/O than/O a/O glorified/O crow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Crow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON thought/O the/O raven/O sounded/O faintly/O indignant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O continued/O ,/O ignoring/O the/O bird/O 's/O protest/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O puts/O a/O thousand/O leagues/O twixt/O him/O and/O you/O without/O it/O seeming/O a/O rebuke/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O jabbed/O a/O finger/O up/O at/O Jon/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O do/O n't/O think/O this/O means/O I/O approve/O of/O that/O nonsense/O in/O the/O common/O hall/O ./O 
Valor/O makes/O up/O for/O a/O fair/O amount/O of/O folly/O ,/O but/O you/O 're/O not/O a/O boy/O anymore/O ,/O however/O many/O years/O you/O 've/O seen/O ./O 
That/O 's/O a/O ''/O ,/O ``/O man/O 's/O sword/O you/O have/O there/O ,/O and/O it/O will/O take/O a/O man/O to/O wield/O her/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O expect/O you/O to/O act/O the/O part/O ,/O henceforth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON slid/O the/O sword/O back/O into/O the/O silver-banded/O scabbard/O ./O 
If/O not/O the/O blade/O he/O would/O have/O chosen/O ,/O it/O was/O nonetheless/O a/O noble/O gift/O ,/O and/O freeing/O him/O from/O Alliser/PERSON Thome/PERSON 's/O malignance/O was/O nobler/O still/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O scratched/O at/O his/O chin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O forgotten/O how/O much/O a/O new/O beard/O itches/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O no/O help/O for/O that/O ./O 
Is/O that/O hand/O of/O yours/O healed/O enough/O to/O resume/O your/O duties/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ./O 
The/O night/O will/O be/O cold/O ,/O I/O 'll/O want/O hot/O spice/O wine/O ./O 
Find/O me/O a/O flagon/O of/O red/O ,/O not/O too/O sour/O ,/O and/O do/O n't/O skimp/O on/O the/O spices/O ./O 
And/O tell/O Hobb/PERSON that/O if/O he/O sends/O me/O boiled/O mutton/O again/O I/O 'm/O like/O to/O boil/O him/O ./O 
That/O last/O haunch/O was/O grey/O ./O 
Even/O the/O bird/O would/O n't/O touch/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stroked/O the/O raven/O 's/O head/O with/O his/O thumb/O ,/O and/O the/O bird/O made/O a/O contented/O quorking/O sound/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Away/O with/O you/O ./O 
I/O 've/O work/O to/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O guards/O smiled/O at/O him/O from/O their/O niches/O as/O he/O wound/O his/O way/O down/O the/O turret/O stair/O ,/O carrying/O the/O sword/O in/O his/O good/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O steel/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O man/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O earned/O that/O ,/O Snow/O ,/O \/O ''/O another/O told/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON made/O himself/O smile/O back/O at/O them/O ,/O but/O his/O heart/O was/O not/O in/O it/O ./O 
He/O knew/O he/O should/O be/O pleased/O ,/O yet/O he/O did/O not/O feel/O it/O ./O 
His/O hand/O ached/O ,/O and/O the/O taste/O of/O anger/O was/O in/O his/O mouth/O ,/O though/O he/O could/O not/O have/O said/O who/O he/O was/O angry/O with/O or/O why/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O half/O dozen/O of/O his/O friends/O were/O lurking/O outside/O when/O he/O left/O the/O King/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O where/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON now/O made/O his/O residence/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O hung/O a/O target/O on/O the/O granary/O doors/O ,/O so/O they/O could/O seem/O to/O be/O honing/O their/O skills/O as/O archers/O ,/O but/O he/O knew/O lurkers/O when/O he/O saw/O them/O ./O 
No/O sooner/O did/O he/O emerge/O than/O Pyp/PERSON called/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O come/O about/O ,/O let/O 's/O have/O a/O look/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O At/O what/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Toad/O sidled/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O rosy/O butt/O cheeks/O ,/O what/O else/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O sword/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON stated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O want/O to/O see/O the/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON raked/O them/O with/O an/O accusing/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O knew/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pyp/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 're/O not/O all/O as/O dumb/O as/O Grenn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O insisted/O Grenn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O dumber/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Haider/PERSON gave/O an/O apologetic/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O helped/O Pate/PERSON carve/O the/O stone/O for/O the/O pommel/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O builder/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O your/O friend/O Sam/PERSON bought/O the/O garnets/O in/O Mole/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Town/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O knew/O even/O before/O that/O ,/O though/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rudge/PERSON has/O been/O helping/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON in/O the/O forge/O ./O 
He/O was/O there/O when/O the/O Old/O Bear/O brought/O him/O the/O burnt/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O sword/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Matt/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
The/O others/O took/O up/O the/O chant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sword/O ,/O the/O sword/O ,/O the/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON unsheathed/O Longclaw/PERSON and/O showed/O it/O to/O them/O ,/O turning/O it/O this/O way/O and/O that/O so/O they/O could/O admire/O it/O ./O 
The/O bastard/O blade/O glittered/O in/O the/O pale/O sunlight/O ,/O dark/O and/O deadly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O declared/O solemnly/O ,/O trying/O to/O sound/O as/O pleased/O and/O proud/O as/O he/O ought/O to/O have/O felt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O heard/O of/O a/O man/O who/O had/O a/O razor/O made/O of/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O \/O ''/O declared/O Toad/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O cut/O his/O head/O off/O trying/O to/O shave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pyp/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O thousands/O of/O years/O old/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O 'll/O wager/O Lord/O Snow/O 's/O the/O first/O brother/O ever/O honored/O for/O burning/O down/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O Tower/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O others/O laughed/O ,/O and/O even/O Jon/PERSON had/O to/O smile/O ./O 
The/O fire/O he/O 'd/O started/O had/O not/O ,/O in/O truth/O ,/O burned/O down/O that/O formidable/O stone/O tower/O ,/O but/O it/O had/O done/O a/O fair/O job/O of/O gutting/O the/O interior/O of/O the/O top/O two/O floors/O ,/O where/O the/O Old/LOCATION Bear/LOCATION had/O his/O chambers/O ./O 
No/O one/O seemed/O to/O mind/O that/O very/O much/O ,/O since/O it/O had/O also/O destroyed/O Othor/PERSON 's/O murderous/O corpse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O other/O wight/O ,/O the/O one-handed/O thing/O that/O had/O once/O been/O a/O ranger/O named/O Jafer/PERSON Flowers/PERSON ,/O had/O also/O been/O destroyed/O ,/O cut/O near/O to/O pieces/O by/O a/O dozen/O swords/O .../O but/O not/O before/O it/O had/O slain/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON and/O four/O other/O men/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON had/O finished/O the/O job/O of/O hacking/O its/O head/O off/O ,/O yet/O had/O died/O all/O the/O same/O when/O the/O headless/O corpse/O pulled/O his/O own/O dagger/O from/O its/O sheath/O and/O buried/O it/O in/O his/O bowels/O ./O 
Strength/O and/O courage/O did/O not/O avail/O much/O against/O foemen/O who/O would/O not/O fall/O because/O they/O were/O already/O dead/O ;/O even/O arms/O and/O armor/O offered/O small/O protection/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O grim/O thought/O soured/O Jon/PERSON 's/O fragile/O mood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O need/O to/O see/O Hobb/PERSON about/O the/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O supper/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O brusquely/O ,/O sliding/O Longclaw/LOCATION back/O into/O its/O scabbard/O ./O 
His/O friends/O meant/O well/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O not/O understand/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O their/O fault/O ,/O truly/O ;/O they/O had/O not/O had/O to/O face/O Othor/PERSON ,/O they/O had/O not/O seen/O the/O pale/O glow/O of/O those/O dead/O blue/O eyes/O ,/O had/O not/O felt/O the/O cold/O of/O those/O dead/O black/O fingers/O ./O 
Nor/O did/O they/O know/O of/O the/O fighting/O in/O the/O riverlands/O ./O 
How/O could/O they/O hope/O to/O comprehend/O ?/O 
He/O turned/O away/O from/O them/O abruptly/O and/O strode/O off/O ,/O sullen/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON called/O after/O him/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON paid/O him/O no/O mind/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O moved/O him/O back/O to/O his/O old/O cell/O in/O tumbledown/O Hardin/PERSON 's/O Tower/O after/O the/O fire/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O there/O he/O returned/O ./O 
Ghost/O was/O curled/O up/O asleep/O beside/O the/O door/O ,/O but/O he/O lifted/O his/O head/O at/O the/O sound/O of/O Jon/PERSON 's/O boots/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O s/O red/O eyes/O were/O darker/O than/O garnets/O and/O wiser/O than/O men/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knelt/O ,/O scratched/O his/O ear/O ,/O and/O showed/O him/O the/O pommel/O of/O the/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O ./O 
It/O 's/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ghost/O sniffed/O at/O his/O carved/O stone/O likeness/O and/O tried/O a/O lick/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O the/O one/O deserves/O an/O honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O wolf/O .../O and/O suddenly/O he/O found/O himself/O remembering/O how/O he/O 'd/O found/O him/O ,/O that/O day/O in/O the/O late/O summer/O snow/O ./O 
They/O had/O been/O riding/O off/O with/O the/O other/O pups/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON had/O heard/O a/O noise/O and/O turned/O back/O ,/O and/O there/O he/O was/O ,/O white/O fur/O almost/O invisible/O against/O the/O drifts/O ./O 
He/O was/O all/O alone/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O apart/O from/O the/O others/O in/O the/O litter/O ./O 
He/O was/O different/O ,/O so/O they/O drove/O him/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O up/O ./O 
Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON stood/O rocking/O nervously/O on/O his/O heels/O ./O 
His/O cheeks/O were/O red/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O wrapped/O in/O a/O heavy/O fur/O cloak/O that/O made/O him/O look/O ready/O for/O hibernation/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sam/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O want/O to/O see/O the/O sword/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O If/O the/O others/O had/O known/O ,/O no/O doubt/O Sam/PERSON did/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O fat/O boy/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O heir/O to/O my/O father/O 's/O blade/O once/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O mournfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Heartsbane/O ./O 
Lord/O Randyll/PERSON let/O me/O hold/O it/O a/O few/O times/O ,/O but/O it/O always/O scared/O me/O ./O 
It/O was/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O beautiful/O but/O so/O sharp/O I/O was/O afraid/O I/O 'd/O hurt/O one/O of/O my/O sisters/O ./O 
Dickon/PERSON will/O have/O it/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O wiped/O sweaty/O hands/O on/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ah/O .../O Maester/O Aemon/O wants/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O time/O for/O his/O bandages/O to/O be/O changed/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON frowned/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O demanded/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON looked/O miserable/O ./O 
That/O was/O answer/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O told/O him/O ,/O did/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O angrily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O told/O him/O that/O you/O told/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
he/O .../O Jon/PERSON ,/O I/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O .../O he/O asked/O .../O I/O mean/O I/O think/O he/O knew/O ,/O he/O sees/O things/O no/O one/O else/O sees/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O blind/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON pointed/O out/O forcefully/O ,/O disgusted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O find/O the/O way/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O left/O Sam/PERSON standing/O there/O ,/O openmouthed/O and/O quivering/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O found/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON up/O in/O the/O rookery/O ,/O feeding/O the/O ravens/O ./O 
Clydas/PERSON was/O with/O him/O ,/O carrying/O a/O bucket/O of/O chopped/O meat/O as/O they/O shuffled/O from/O cage/O to/O cage/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sam/PERSON said/O you/O wanted/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O maester/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O indeed/O ./O 
Clydas/O ,/O give/O Jon/PERSON the/O bucket/O ./O 
Perhaps/O he/O will/O be/O kind/O enough/O to/O assist/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O hunched/O ,/O pink-eyed/O brother/O handed/O Jon/PERSON the/O bucket/O and/O scurried/O down/O the/O ladder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Toss/O the/O meat/O into/O the/O cages/O ,/O \/O ''/O Aemon/PERSON instructed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O birds/O will/O do/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shifted/O the/O bucket/O to/O his/O right/O hand/O and/O thrust/O his/O left/O down/O into/O the/O bloody/O bits/O ./O 
The/O ravens/O began/O to/O scream/O noisily/O and/O fly/O at/O the/O bars/O ,/O beating/O at/O the/O metal/O with/O night-black/O wings/O ./O 
The/O meat/O had/O been/O chopped/O into/O pieces/O no/O larger/O than/O a/O finger/O joint/O ./O 
He/O filled/O his/O fist/O and/O tossed/O the/O raw/O red/O morsels/O into/O the/O cage/O ,/O and/O the/O squawking/O and/O squabbling/O grew/O hotter/O ./O 
Feathers/O flew/O as/O two/O of/O the/O larger/O birds/O fought/O over/O a/O choice/O piece/O ./O 
Quickly/O Jon/PERSON grabbed/O a/O second/O handful/O and/O threw/O it/O in/O after/O the/O first/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O raven/O likes/O fruit/O and/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O a/O rare/O bird/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Most/O ravens/O will/O eat/O grain/O ,/O but/O they/O prefer/O flesh/O ./O 
It/O makes/O them/O strong/O ,/O and/O I/O fear/O they/O relish/O the/O taste/O of/O blood/O ./O 
In/O that/O they/O are/O like/O men/O .../O and/O like/O men/O ,/O not/O all/O ravens/O are/O alike/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O nothing/O to/O say/O to/O that/O ./O 
He/O threw/O meat/O ,/O wondering/O why/O he/O 'd/O been/O summoned/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O the/O old/O man/O would/O tell/O him/O ,/O in/O his/O own/O good/O time/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON was/O not/O a/O man/O to/O be/O hurried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Doves/O and/O pigeons/O can/O also/O be/O trained/O to/O carry/O messages/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O went/O on/O ,/O \/O ``/O though/O the/O raven/O is/O a/O stronger/O flyer/O ,/O larger/O ,/O bolder/O ,/O far/O more/O clever/O ,/O better/O able/O to/O defend/O itself/O against/O hawks/O .../O yet/O ravens/O are/O black/O ,/O and/O they/O eat/O the/O dead/O ,/O so/O some/O godly/O men/O abhor/O them/O ./O 
Baelor/O the/O Blessed/O tried/O to/O replace/O all/O the/O ravens/O with/O doves/O ,/O did/O you/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O maester/O turned/O his/O white/O eyes/O on/O Jon/PERSON ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O prefers/O ravens/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O fingers/O were/O in/O the/O bucket/O ,/O blood/O up/O to/O the/O wrist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dywen/PERSON says/O the/O wildlings/O call/O us/O crows/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O uncertainty/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O crow/O is/O the/O raven/O 's/O poor/O cousin/O ./O 
They/O are/O both/O beggars/O in/O black/O ,/O hated/O and/O misunderstood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON wished/O he/O understood/O what/O they/O were/O talking/O about/O ,/O and/O why/O ./O 
What/O did/O he/O care/O about/O ravens/O and/O doves/O ?/O 
If/O the/O old/O man/O had/O something/O to/O say/O to/O him/O ,/O why/O could/O n't/O he/O just/O say/O it/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O did/O you/O ever/O wonder/O why/O the/O men/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O take/O no/O wives/O and/O father/O no/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O scattered/O more/O meat/O ./O 
The/O fingers/O of/O his/O left/O hand/O were/O slimy/O with/O blood/O ,/O and/O his/O right/O throbbed/O from/O the/O weight/O of/O the/O bucket/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O they/O will/O not/O love/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O answered/O ,/O \/O ``/O for/O love/O is/O the/O bane/O of/O honor/O ,/O the/O death/O of/O duty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O did/O not/O sound/O right/O to/O Jon/PERSON ,/O yet/O he/O said/O nothing/O ./O 
The/O maester/O was/O a/O hundred/O years/O old/O ,/O and/O a/O high/O officer/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ;/O it/O was/O not/O his/O place/O to/O contradict/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O seemed/O to/O sense/O his/O doubts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O if/O the/O day/O should/O ever/O come/O when/O your/O lord/O father/O must/O needs/O choose/O between/O honor/O on/O the/O one/O hand/O and/O those/O he/O loves/O on/O the/O other/O ,/O what/O would/O he/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON hesitated/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O say/O that/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON would/O never/O dishonor/O himself/O ,/O not/O even/O for/O love/O ,/O yet/O inside/O a/O small/O sly/O voice/O whispered/O ,/O He/O fathered/O a/O bastard/O ,/O where/O was/O the/O honor/O in/O that/O ?/O 
And/O your/O mother/O ,/O what/O of/O his/O duty/O to/O her/O ,/O he/O will/O not/O even/O say/O her/O name/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O do/O whatever/O was/O right/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O .../O ringingly/O ,/O to/O make/O up/O for/O his/O hesitation/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O matter/O what/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON is/O a/O man/O in/O ten/O thousand/O ./O 
Most/O of/O us/O are/O not/O so/O strong/O ./O 
What/O is/O honor/O compared/O to/O a/O woman/O 's/O love/O ?/O 
What/O is/O duty/O against/O the/O feel/O of/O a/O newborn/O son/O in/O your/O arms/O .../O or/O the/O memory/O of/O a/O brother/O 's/O smile/O ?/O 
Wind/O and/O words/O ./O 
Wind/O and/O words/O ./O 
We/O are/O only/O human/O ,/O and/O the/O gods/O have/O fashioned/O us/O for/O love/O ./O 
That/O is/O our/O great/O glory/O ,/O and/O our/O great/O tragedy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O men/O who/O formed/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O knew/O that/O only/O their/O courage/O shielded/O the/O realm/O from/O the/O darkness/O to/O the/O north/O ./O 
They/O knew/O they/O must/O have/O no/O divided/O loyalties/O to/O weaken/O their/O resolve/O ./O 
So/O they/O vowed/O they/O would/O have/O no/O wives/O nor/O children/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yet/O brothers/O they/O had/O ,/O and/O sisters/O ./O 
Mothers/O who/O gave/O them/O birth/O ,/O fathers/O who/O gave/O them/O names/O ./O 
They/O came/O from/O a/O hundred/O quarrelsome/O kingdoms/O ,/O and/O they/O knew/O times/O may/O change/O ,/O but/O men/O do/O not/O ./O 
So/O they/O pledged/O as/O well/O that/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O would/O take/O no/O part/O in/O the/O battles/O of/O the/O realms/O it/O guarded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O kept/O their/O pledge/O ./O 
When/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION slew/O Black/PERSON Harren/PERSON and/O claimed/O his/O kingdom/O ,/O Harren/PERSON 's/O brother/O was/O Lord/O Commander/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O with/O ten/O thousand/O swords/O to/O hand/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O march/O ./O 
In/O the/O days/O when/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O were/O seven/O kingdoms/O ,/O not/O a/O generation/O passed/O that/O three/O or/O four/O of/O them/O were/O not/O at/O war/O ./O 
The/O Watch/O took/O no/O part/O ./O 
When/O the/O Andals/O crossed/O the/O narrow/O sea/O and/O swept/O away/O the/O kingdoms/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O ,/O the/O sons/O of/O the/O fallen/O kings/O held/O true/O to/O their/O vows/O and/O remained/O at/O their/O posts/O ./O 
So/O it/O has/O always/O been/O ,/O for/O years/O beyond/O counting/O ./O 
Such/O is/O the/O price/O of/O honor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O craven/O can/O be/O as/O brave/O as/O any/O man/O ,/O when/O there/O is/O nothing/O to/O fear/O ./O 
And/O we/O all/O do/O our/O duty/O ,/O when/O there/O is/O no/O cost/O to/O it/O ./O 
How/O easy/O it/O seems/O then/O ,/O to/O walk/O the/O path/O of/O honor/O ./O 
Yet/O soon/O or/O late/O in/O every/O man/O 's/O life/O comes/O a/O day/O when/O it/O is/O not/O easy/O ,/O a/O day/O when/O he/O must/O choose/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Some/O of/O the/O ravens/O were/O still/O eating/O ,/O long/O stringy/O bits/O of/O meat/O dangling/O from/O their/O beaks/O ./O 
The/O rest/O seemed/O to/O be/O watching/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O feel/O the/O weight/O of/O all/O those/O tiny/O black/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O this/O is/O my/O day/O .../O is/O that/O what/O you/O 're/O saying/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON turned/O his/O head/O and/O looked/O at/O him/O with/O those/O dead/O white/O eyes/O ./O 
It/O was/O as/O if/O he/O were/O seeing/O right/O into/O his/O heart/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON felt/O naked/O and/O exposed/O ./O 
He/O took/O the/O bucket/O in/O both/O hands/O and/O flung/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O slops/O through/O the/O bars/O ./O 
Strings/O of/O meat/O and/O blood/O flew/O everywhere/O ,/O scattering/O the/O ravens/O ./O 
They/O took/O to/O the/O air/O ,/O shrieking/O wildly/O ./O 
The/O quicker/O birds/O snatched/O morsels/O on/O the/O wing/O and/O gulped/O them/O down/O greedily/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON let/O the/O empty/O bucket/O clang/O to/O the/O floor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O laid/O a/O withered/O ,/O spotted/O hand/O on/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O hurts/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
Choosing/O .../O it/O has/O always/O hurt/O ./O 
And/O always/O will/O ./O 
I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O bitterly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O knows/O ./O 
Even/O if/O I/O am/O his/O bastard/O ,/O he/O 's/O still/O my/O father/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O heard/O nothing/O I/O 've/O told/O you/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
Do/O you/O think/O you/O are/O the/O first/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O shook/O his/O ancient/O head/O ,/O a/O gesture/O weary/O beyond/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O times/O the/O gods/O saw/O fit/O to/O test/O my/O vows/O ./O 
Once/O when/O I/O was/O a/O boy/O ,/O once/O in/O the/O fullness/O of/O my/O manhood/O ,/O and/O once/O when/O I/O ''/O ,/O ``/O had/O grown/O old/O ./O 
By/O then/O my/O strength/O was/O fled/O ,/O my/O eyes/O grown/O dim/O ,/O yet/O that/O last/O choice/O was/O as/O cruel/O as/O the/O first/O ./O 
My/O ravens/O would/O bring/O the/O news/O from/O the/O south/O ,/O words/O darker/O than/O their/O wings/O ,/O the/O ruin/O of/O my/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O death/O of/O my/O kin/O ,/O disgrace/O and/O desolation/O ./O 
What/O could/O I/O have/O done/O ,/O old/O ,/O blind/O ,/O frail/O ?/O 
I/O was/O helpless/O as/O a/O suckling/O babe/O ,/O yet/O still/O it/O grieved/O me/O to/O sit/O forgotten/O as/O they/O cut/O down/O my/O brother/O 's/O poor/O grandson/O ,/O and/O his/O son/O ,/O and/O even/O the/O little/O children/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O shocked/O to/O see/O the/O shine/O of/O tears/O in/O the/O old/O man/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O quietly/O ,/O almost/O in/O dread/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O toothless/O smile/O quivered/O on/O the/O ancient/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O a/O maester/O of/O the/O Citadel/LOCATION ,/O bound/O in/O service/O to/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
In/O my/O order/O ,/O we/O put/O aside/O our/O house/O names/O when/O we/O take/O our/O vows/O and/O don/O the/O collar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O old/O man/O touched/O the/O maester/O 's/O chain/O that/O hung/O loosely/O around/O his/O thin/O ,/O fleshless/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O was/O Maekar/PERSON ,/O the/O First/O of/O his/O Name/O ,/O and/O my/O brother/O Aegon/PERSON reigned/O after/O him/O in/O my/O stead/O ./O 
My/O grandfather/O named/O me/O for/O Prince/PERSON Aemon/PERSON the/PERSON Dragonknight/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O his/O uncle/O ,/O or/O his/O father/O ,/O depending/O on/O which/O tale/O you/O believe/O ./O 
Aemon/PERSON ,/O he/O called/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aemon/O .../O Targaryen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON could/O scarcely/O believe/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Once/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Once/O ./O 
So/O you/O see/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O I/O do/O know/O .../O and/O knowing/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O tell/O you/O stay/O or/O go/O ./O 
You/O must/O make/O that/O choice/O yourself/O ,/O and/O live/O with/O it/O all/O the/O rest/O of/O your/O days/O ./O 
As/O I/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O fell/O to/O a/O whisper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O I/O have/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
