-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O sea/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON said/O as/O he/O reined/O to/O a/O halt/O beside/O her/O on/O the/O top/O of/O the/O ridge/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Beneath/O them/O ,/O the/O plain/O stretched/O out/O immense/O and/O empty/O ,/O a/O vast/O flat/O expanse/O that/O reached/O to/O the/O distant/O horizon/O and/O beyond/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O sea/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O ./O 
Past/O here/O ,/O there/O were/O no/O hills/O ,/O no/O mountains/O ,/O no/O trees/O nor/O cities/O nor/O roads/O ,/O only/O the/O endless/O grasses/O ,/O the/O tall/O blades/O rippling/O like/O waves/O when/O the/O winds/O blew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O so/O green/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O and/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ought/O to/O see/O it/O when/O it/O blooms/O ,/O all/O dark/O red/O flowers/O from/O horizon/O to/O horizon/O ,/O like/O a/O sea/O of/O blood/O ./O 
Come/O the/O dry/O season/O ,/O and/O the/O world/O turns/O the/O color/O of/O old/O bronze/O ./O 
And/O this/O is/O only/O hranna/O ,/O child/O ./O 
There/O are/O a/O hundred/O kinds/O of/O grass/O out/O there/O ,/O grasses/O as/O yellow/O as/O lemon/O and/O as/O dark/O as/O indigo/O ,/O blue/O grasses/O and/O orange/O grasses/O and/O grasses/O like/O rainbows/O ./O 
Down/O in/O the/O Shadow/O Lands/O beyond/O Asshai/LOCATION ,/O they/O say/O there/O are/O oceans/O of/O ghost/O grass/O ,/O taller/O than/O a/O man/O on/O horseback/O with/O stalks/O as/O pale/O as/O milkglass/O ./O 
It/O murders/O all/O other/O grass/O and/O glows/O in/O the/O dark/O with/O the/O spirits/O of/O the/O damned/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O claim/O that/O someday/O ghost/O grass/O will/O cover/O the/O entire/O world/O ,/O and/O then/O all/O life/O will/O end/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O thought/O gave/O Dany/PERSON the/O shivers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O talk/O about/O that/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O so/O beautiful/O here/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O think/O about/O everything/O dying/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O respectfully/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O heard/O the/O sound/O of/O voices/O and/O turned/O to/O look/O behind/O her/O ./O 
She/O and/O Mormont/PERSON had/O outdistanced/O the/O rest/O of/O their/O party/O ,/O and/O now/O the/O others/O were/O climbing/O the/O ridge/O below/O them/O ./O 
Her/O handmaid/O Irri/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O young/O archers/O of/O her/O khas/O were/O fluid/O as/O centaurs/O ,/O but/O Viserys/PERSON still/O struggled/O with/O the/O short/O stirrups/O and/O the/O flat/O saddle/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O was/O miserable/O out/O here/O ./O 
He/O ought/O never/O have/O come/O ./O 
Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON had/O urged/O him/O to/O wait/O in/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O had/O offered/O him/O the/O hospitality/O of/O his/O manse/O ,/O but/O Viserys/PERSON would/O have/O none/O of/O it/O ./O 
He/O would/O stay/O with/O Drogo/PERSON until/O the/O debt/O had/O been/O paid/O ,/O until/O he/O had/O the/O crown/O he/O had/O been/O promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O he/O tries/O to/O cheat/O me/O ,/O he/O will/O learn/O to/O his/O sorrow/O what/O it/O means/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON had/O vowed/O ,/O laying/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O borrowed/O sword/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON had/O blinked/O at/O that/O and/O wished/O him/O good/O fortune/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON realized/O that/O she/O did/O not/O want/O to/O listen/O to/O any/O of/O her/O brother/O 's/O complaints/O right/O now/O ./O 
The/O day/O was/O too/O perfect/O ./O 
The/O sky/O was/O a/O deep/O blue/O ,/O and/O high/O above/O them/O a/O hunting/O hawk/O circled/O ./O 
The/O grass/O sea/O swayed/O and/O sighed/O with/O each/O breath/O of/O wind/O ,/O the/O air/O was/O warm/O on/O her/O face/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON felt/O at/O peace/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O let/O Viserys/PERSON spoil/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wait/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O them/O all/O to/O stay/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O I/O command/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O knight/O smiled/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON was/O not/O a/O handsome/O man/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O neck/O and/O shoulders/O like/O a/O bull/O ,/O and/O coarse/O black/O hair/O covered/O his/O arms/O and/O chest/O so/O thickly/O that/O there/O was/O none/O left/O for/O his/O head/O ./O 
Yet/O his/O smiles/O gave/O Dany/PERSON comfort/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O learning/O to/O talk/O like/O a/O queen/O ,/O Daenerys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O a/O queen/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O khaleesi/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O wheeled/O her/O horse/O about/O and/O galloped/O down/O the/O ridge/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O descent/O was/O steep/O and/O rocky/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON rode/O fearlessly/O ,/O and/O the/O joy/O and/O the/O danger/O of/O it/O were/O a/O song/O in/O her/O heart/O ./O 
All/O her/O life/O Viserys/PERSON had/O told/O her/O she/O was/O a/O princess/O ,/O but/O not/O until/O she/O rode/O her/O silver/O had/O Daenerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ever/O felt/O like/O one/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O first/O it/O had/O not/O come/O easy/O ./O 
The/O khalasar/O had/O broken/O camp/O the/O morning/O after/O her/O wedding/O ,/O moving/O east/O toward/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O and/O by/O the/O third/O day/O Dany/PERSON thought/O she/O was/O going/O to/O die/O ./O 
Saddle/O sores/O opened/O on/O her/O bottom/O ,/O hideous/O and/O bloody/O ./O 
Her/O thighs/O were/O chafed/O raw/O ,/O her/O hands/O blistered/O from/O the/O reins/O ,/O the/O muscles/O of/O her/O legs/O and/O back/O so/O wracked/O with/O pain/O that/O she/O could/O scarcely/O sit/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O dusk/O fell/O ,/O her/O handmaids/O would/O need/O to/O help/O her/O down/O from/O her/O mount/O ./O 
Even/O the/O nights/O brought/O no/O relief/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ignored/O her/O when/O they/O rode/O ,/O even/O as/O he/O had/O ignored/O her/O during/O their/O wedding/O ,/O and/O spent/O his/O evenings/O drinking/O with/O his/O warriors/O and/O bloodriders/O ,/O racing/O his/O prize/O horses/O ,/O watching/O women/O dance/O and/O men/O die/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON had/O no/O place/O in/O these/O parts/O of/O his/O life/O ./O 
She/O was/O left/O to/O sup/O alone/O ,/O or/O with/O Ser/PERSON Jo/PERSON rah/O and/O her/O brother/O ,/O and/O afterward/O to/O cry/O herself/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
Yet/O every/O night/O ,/O some/O time/O before/O the/O dawn/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON would/O come/O to/O her/O tent/O and/O wake/O her/O in/O the/O dark/O ,/O to/O ride/O her/O as/O relentlessly/O as/O he/O rode/O his/O stallion/O ./O 
He/O always/O took/O her/O from/O behind/O ,/O Dothraki/PERSON fashion/O ,/O for/O which/O Dany/PERSON was/O grateful/O ;/O that/O way/O her/O lord/O husband/O could/O not/O see/O the/O tears/O that/O wet/O her/O face/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O use/O her/O pillow/O to/O muffle/O her/O cries/O of/O pain/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O done/O ,/O he/O would/O close/O his/O eyes/O and/O begin/O to/O snore/O softly/O and/O Dany/PERSON would/O lie/O beside/O him/O ,/O her/O body/O bruised/O and/O sore/O ,/O hurting/O too/O much/O for/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Day/O followed/O day/O ,/O and/O night/O followed/O night/O ,/O until/O Dany/PERSON knew/O she/O could/O not/O endure/O a/O moment/O longer/O ./O 
She/O would/O kill/O herself/O rather/O than/O go/O on/O ,/O she/O decided/O one/O night/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Yet/O when/O she/O slept/O that/O night/O ,/O she/O dreamt/O the/O dragon/O dream/O again/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON was/O not/O in/O it/O this/O time/O ./O 
There/O was/O only/O her/O and/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
Its/O scales/O were/O black/O as/O night/O ,/O wet/O and/O slick/O with/O blood/O ./O 
Her/O blood/O ,/O Dany/PERSON sensed/O ./O 
Its/O eyes/O were/O pools/O of/O molten/O magma/O ,/O and/O when/O it/O opened/O its/O mouth/O ,/O the/O flame/O came/O roaring/O out/O in/O a/O hot/O jet/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O it/O singing/O to/O her/O ,/O She/O opened/O her/O arms/O to/O the/O fire/O ,/O embraced/O it/O ,/O let/O it/O swallow/O her/O whole/O ,/O let/O it/O cleanse/O her/O and/O temper/O her/O and/O scour/O her/O clean/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O her/O flesh/O sear/O and/O blacken/O and/O slough/O away/O ,/O could/O feel/O her/O blood/O boil/O and/O turn/O to/O steam/O ,/O and/O yet/O there/O was/O no/O pain/O ./O 
She/O felt/O strong/O and/O new/O and/O fierce/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O the/O next/O day/O ,/O strangely/O ,/O she/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O hurt/O quite/O so/O much/O ./O 
It/O was/O as/O if/O the/O gods/O had/O heard/O her/O and/O taken/O pity/O ./O 
Even/O her/O handmaids/O noticed/O the/O change/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jhiqui/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O what/O is/O wrong/O ?/O 
Are/O you/O sick/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O answered/O ,/O standing/O over/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O that/O Illyrio/PERSON had/O given/O her/O when/O she/O wed./O ./O 
She/O touched/O one/O ,/O the/O largest/O of/O the/O three/O ,/O running/O her/O hand/O lightly/O over/O the/O shelf/O ./O 
Black-and/O -/O scarlet/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O like/O the/O dragon/O in/O my/O dream/O ./O 
The/O stone/O felt/O strangely/O warm/O beneath/O her/O fingers/O .../O or/O was/O she/O still/O dreaming/O ?/O 
She/O pulled/O her/O hand/O back/O nervously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O that/O hour/O onward/O ,/O each/O day/O was/O easier/O than/O the/O one/O before/O it/O ./O 
Her/O legs/O grew/O stronger/O ;/O her/O blisters/O burst/O and/O her/O hands/O grew/O callused/O ;/O her/O soft/O thighs/O toughened/O ,/O supple/O as/O leather/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O khal/O had/O commanded/O the/O handmaid/O Irri/ORGANIZATION to/O teach/O Dany/PERSON to/O ride/O in/O the/O Dothraki/O fashion/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O the/O filly/O who/O was/O her/O real/O teacher/O ./O 
The/O horse/O seemed/O to/O know/O her/O moods/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O shared/O a/O single/O mind/O ./O 
With/O every/O passing/O day/O ,/O Dany/PERSON felt/O surer/O in/O her/O seat/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O were/O a/O hard/O and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O unsentimental/O people/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O not/O their/O custom/O to/O name/O their/O animals/O ,/O so/O Dany/PERSON thought/O of/O her/O only/O as/O the/O silver/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O loved/O anything/O so/O much/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O the/O riding/O became/O less/O an/O ordeal/O ,/O Dany/PERSON began/O to/O notice/O the/O beauties/O of/O the/O land/O around/O her/O ./O 
She/O rode/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O khalasar/O with/O Drogo/PERSON and/O his/O bloodriders/O ,/O so/O she/O came/O to/O each/O country/O fresh/O and/O unspoiled/O ./O 
Behind/O them/O the/O great/O horde/O might/O tear/O the/O earth/O and/O muddy/O the/O rivers/O and/O send/O up/O clouds/O of/O choking/O dust/O ,/O but/O the/O fields/O ahead/O of/O them/O were/O always/O green/O and/O verdant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O crossed/O the/O rolling/O hills/O of/O Norvos/LOCATION ,/O past/O terraced/O farms/O and/O small/O villages/O where/O the/O townsfolk/O watched/O anxiously/O from/O atop/O white/O stucco/O walls/O ./O 
They/O forded/O three/O wide/O placid/O rivers/O and/O a/O fourth/O that/O was/O swift/O and/O narrow/O and/O treacherous/O ,/O camped/O beside/O a/O high/O blue/O waterfall/O ,/O skirted/O the/O tumbled/O ruins/O of/O a/O vast/O dead/O city/O where/O ghosts/O were/O said/O to/O moan/O among/O blackened/O marble/O columns/O ./O 
They/O raced/O down/O Valyrian/O roads/O a/O thousand/O years/O old/O and/O straight/O as/O a/O Dothraki/O arrow/O ./O 
For/O half/O a/O moon/O ,/O they/O rode/O through/O the/O Forest/O of/O Qohor/LOCATION ,/O where/O the/O leaves/O made/O a/O golden/O canopy/O high/O above/O them/O ,/O and/O the/O trunks/O of/O the/O trees/O were/O as/O wide/O as/O city/O gates/O ./O 
There/O were/O great/O elk/O in/O that/O wood/O ,/O and/O spotted/O tigers/O ,/O and/O lemurs/O with/O silver/O fur/O and/O huge/O purple/O eyes/O ,/O but/O all/O fled/O before/O the/O approach/O of/O the/O khalasar/O and/O Dany/PERSON got/O no/O glimpse/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O then/O her/O agony/O was/O a/O fading/O memory/O ./O 
She/O still/O ached/O after/O a/O long/O day/O 's/O riding/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O the/O pain/O had/O a/O sweetness/O to/O it/O now/O ,/O and/O each/O morning/O she/O came/O willingly/O to/O her/O saddle/O ,/O eager/O to/O know/O what/O wonders/O waited/O for/O her/O in/O the/O lands/O ahead/O ./O 
She/O began/O to/O find/O pleasure/O even/O in/O her/O nights/O ,/O and/O if/O she/O still/O cried/O out/O when/O Drogo/PERSON took/O her/O ,/O it/O was/O not/O always/O in/O pain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O ridge/O ,/O the/O grasses/O rose/O around/O her/O ,/O tall/O and/O supple/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON slowed/O to/O a/O trot/O and/O rode/O out/O onto/O the/O plain/O ,/O losing/O herself/O in/O the/O green/O ,/O blessedly/O alone/O ./O 
In/O the/O khalasar/O she/O was/O never/O alone/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON came/O to/O her/O only/O after/O the/O sun/O went/O down/O ,/O but/O her/O handmaids/O fed/O her/O and/O bathed/O her/O and/O slept/O by/O the/O door/O of/O her/O tent/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O bloodriders/O and/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O were/O never/O far/O ,/O and/O her/O brother/O was/O an/O unwelcome/O shadow/O ,/O day/O and/O night/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON could/O hear/O him/O on/O the/O top/O of/O the/O ridge/O ,/O his/O voice/O shrill/O with/O anger/O as/O he/O shouted/O at/O Ser/O Jorah/O ./O 
She/O rode/O on/O ,/O submerging/O herself/O deeper/O in/O the/O Dothraki/O sea/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O green/O swallowed/O her/O up/O ./O 
The/O air/O was/O rich/O with/O the/O scents/O of/O earth/O and/O grass/O ,/O mixed/O with/O the/O smell/O of/O horseflesh/O and/O Dany/PERSON 's/O sweat/O and/O the/O oil/O in/O her/O hair/O ./O 
Dothraki/PERSON smells/O ./O 
They/O seemed/O to/O belong/O here/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON breathed/O it/O all/O in/O ,/O laughing/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O sudden/O urge/O to/O feel/O the/O ground/O beneath/O her/O ,/O to/O curl/O her/O toes/O in/O that/O thick/O black/O soil/O ./O 
Swinging/O down/O from/O her/O saddle/O ,/O she/O let/O the/O silver/O graze/O while/O she/O pulled/O off/O her/O high/O boots/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Viserys/O came/O upon/O her/O as/O sudden/O as/O a/O summer/O storm/O ,/O his/O horse/O rearing/O beneath/O him/O as/O he/O reined/O up/O too/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O dare/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O screamed/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O give/O commands/O to/O me/O ?/O 
To/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O vaulted/O off/O the/O horse/O ,/O stumbling/O as/O he/O landed/O ./O 
His/O face/O was/O flushed/O as/O he/O struggled/O back/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
He/O grabbed/O her/O ,/O shook/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O forgotten/O who/O you/O are/O ?/O 
Look/O at/O you/O ./O 
Look/O at/O you/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON did/O not/O need/O to/O look/O ./O 
She/O was/O barefoot/O ,/O with/O oiled/O hair/O ,/O wearing/O Dothraki/PERSON riding/O leathers/O and/O a/O painted/O vest/O given/O her/O as/O a/O bride/O gift/O ./O 
She/O looked/O as/O though/O she/O belonged/O here/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON was/O soiled/O and/O stained/O in/O city/O silks/O and/O ringmail/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O still/O screaming/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O command/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
Do/O you/O understand/O ?/O 
I/O am/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O hear/O orders/O from/O some/O horselord/O 's/O slut/O ,/O do/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O His/O hand/O went/O under/O her/O vest/O ,/O his/O fingers/O digging/O painfully/O into/O her/O breast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON shoved/O him/O away/O ,/O hard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON stared/O at/O her/O ,/O his/O lilac/O eyes/O incredulous/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O defied/O him/O ./O 
Never/O fought/O back/O ./O 
Rage/O twisted/O his/O features/O ./O 
He/O would/O hurt/O her/O now/O ,/O and/O badly/O ,/O she/O knew/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Crack/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O whip/O made/O a/O sound/O like/O thunder/O ./O 
The/O coil/O took/O Viserys/O around/O the/O throat/O and/O yanked/O him/O backward/O ./O 
He/O went/O sprawling/O in/O the/O grass/O ,/O stunned/O and/O choking/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O riders/O hooted/O at/O him/O as/O he/O struggled/O to/O free/O himself/O ./O 
The/O one/O with/O the/O whip/O ,/O young/O Jhogo/PERSON ,/O rasped/O a/O question/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON did/O not/O understand/O his/O words/O ,/O but/O by/O then/O Irri/ORGANIZATION was/O there/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O rest/O of/O her/O khas/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON asks/O if/O you/O would/O have/O him/O dead/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON understood/O that/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O others/O barked/O out/O a/O comment/O ,/O and/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON told/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O Quaro/PERSON thinks/O you/O should/O take/O an/O ear/O to/O teach/O him/O respect/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O brother/O was/O on/O his/O knees/O ,/O his/O fingers/O digging/O under/O the/O leather/O coils/O ,/O crying/O incoherently/O ,/O struggling/O for/O breath/O ./O 
The/O whip/O was/O tight/O around/O his/O windpipe/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O them/O I/O do/O not/O wish/O him/O harmed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Irri/O repeated/O her/O words/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
Jhogo/PERSON gave/O a/O pull/O on/O the/O whip/O ,/O yanking/O Viserys/O around/O like/O a/O puppet/O on/O a/O string/O ./O 
He/O went/O sprawling/O again/O ,/O freed/O from/O the/O leather/O embrace/O ,/O a/O thin/O line/O of/O blood/O under/O his/O chin/O where/O the/O whip/O had/O cut/O deep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O warned/O him/O what/O would/O happen/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O told/O him/O to/O stay/O on/O the/O ridge/O ,/O as/O you/O commanded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O you/O did/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON replied/O ,/O watching/O Viserys/O ./O 
He/O lay/O on/O the/O ground/O ,/O sucking/O in/O air/O noisily/O ,/O red-faced/O and/O sobbing/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O pitiful/O thing/O ./O 
He/O had/O always/O been/O a/O pitiful/O thing/O ./O 
Why/O had/O she/O never/O seen/O that/O before/O ?/O 
There/O was/O a/O hollow/O place/O inside/O her/O where/O her/O fear/O had/O been/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O his/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
Viserys/PERSON gaped/O at/O her/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O believe/O what/O he/O was/O hearing/O ;/O nor/O could/O Dany/PERSON quite/O believe/O what/O she/O was/O saying/O ./O 
Yet/O the/O words/O came/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O my/O brother/O walk/O behind/O us/O back/O to/O the/O khalasar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Among/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O the/O man/O who/O does/O not/O ride/O was/O no/O man/O at/O all/O ,/O the/O lowest/O of/O the/O low/O ,/O without/O honor/O or/O pride/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O everyone/O see/O him/O as/O he/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON screamed/O ./O 
He/O turned/O to/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O pleading/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O with/O words/O the/O horsemen/O would/O not/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hit/O her/O ,/O Mormont/LOCATION ./O 
Hurt/O her/O ./O 
Your/O king/O commands/O it/O ./O 
Kill/O these/O Dothraki/O dogs/O and/O teach/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O exile/O knight/O looked/O from/O Dany/PERSON to/O her/O brother/O ;/O she/O barefoot/O ,/O with/O dirt/O between/O her/O toes/O and/O oil/O in/O her/O hair/O ,/O he/O with/O his/O silks/O and/O steel/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON could/O see/O the/O decision/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O shall/O walk/O ,/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O took/O her/O brother/O 's/O horse/O in/O hand/O while/O Dany/PERSON remounted/O her/O silver/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON gaped/O at/O him/O ,/O and/O sat/O down/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
He/O kept/O his/O silence/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O not/O move/O ,/O and/O his/O eyes/O were/O full/O of/O poison/O as/O they/O rode/O away/O ./O 
Soon/O he/O was/O lost/O in/O the/O tall/O grass/O ./O 
When/O they/O could/O not/O see/O him/O anymore/O ,/O Dany/PERSON grew/O afraid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O he/O find/O his/O way/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON as/O they/O rode/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Even/O a/O man/O as/O blind/O as/O your/O brother/O should/O be/O able/O to/O follow/O our/O trail/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O proud/O ./O 
He/O may/O be/O too/O shamed/O to/O come/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jorah/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O else/O should/O he/O go/O ?/O 
If/O he/O can/O not/O find/O the/O khalasar/O ,/O the/O khalasar/O will/O most/O surely/O find/O him/O ./O 
It/O is/O hard/O to/O drown/O in/O the/O Dothraki/LOCATION sea/LOCATION ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON saw/O the/O truth/O of/O that/O ./O 
The/O khalasar/O was/O like/O a/O city/O on/O the/O march/O ,/O but/O it/O did/O not/O march/O blindly/O ./O 
Always/O scouts/O ranged/O far/O ahead/O of/O the/O main/O column/O ,/O alert/O for/O any/O sign/O of/O game/O or/O prey/O or/O enemies/O ,/O while/O outriders/O guarded/O their/O flanks/O ./O 
They/O missed/O nothing/O ,/O not/O here/O ,/O in/O this/O land/O ,/O the/O place/O where/O they/O had/O come/O from/O ./O 
These/O plains/O were/O a/O part/O of/O them/O .../O and/O of/O her/O ,/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hit/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O wonder/O in/O her/O voice/O ./O 
Now/O that/O it/O was/O over/O ,/O it/O seemed/O like/O some/O strange/O dream/O that/O she/O had/O dreamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O do/O you/O think/O .../O he/O 'll/O be/O so/O angry/O when/O he/O gets/O back/O She/O shivered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O woke/O the/O dragon/O ,/O did/O n't/O I/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O you/O wake/O the/O dead/O ,/O girl/O ?/O 
Your/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON was/O the/O last/O dragon/O ,/O and/O he/O died/O on/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
Viserys/O is/O less/O than/O the/O shadow/O of/O a/O snake/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O blunt/O words/O startled/O her/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O as/O though/O all/O the/O things/O she/O had/O always/O believed/O were/O suddenly/O called/O into/O question/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O .../O you/O swore/O him/O your/O sword/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O I/O did/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O your/O brother/O is/O the/O shadow/O of/O a/O snake/O ,/O what/O does/O that/O make/O his/O servants/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O was/O bitter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O still/O the/O true/O king/O ./O 
He/O is/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jorah/PERSON pulled/O up/O his/O horse/O and/O looked/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Truth/O now/O ./O 
Would/O you/O want/O to/O see/O Viserys/O sit/O a/O throne/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON thought/O about/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O not/O be/O a/O very/O good/O king/O ,/O would/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O have/O been/O worse/O .../O but/O not/O many/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O gave/O his/O heels/O to/O his/O mount/O and/O started/O off/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON rode/O close/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Still/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O common/O people/O are/O waiting/O for/O him/O ./O 
Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON says/O they/O are/O sewing/O dragon/O banners/O and/O praying/O for/O Viserys/O to/O return/O from/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O to/O free/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O common/O people/O pray/O for/O rain/O ,/O healthy/O children/O ,/O and/O a/O summer/O that/O never/O ends/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O no/O matter/O to/O them/O if/O the/O high/O lords/O play/O their/O game/O of/O thrones/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O are/O left/O in/O peace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O never/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON rode/O along/O quietly/O for/O a/O time/O ,/O working/O his/O words/O like/O a/O puzzle/O box/O ./O 
It/O went/O against/O everything/O that/O Viserys/PERSON had/O ever/O told/O her/O to/O think/O that/O the/O people/O could/O care/O so/O little/O whether/O a/O true/O king/O or/O a/O usurper/O reigned/O over/O them/O ./O 
Yet/O the/O more/O she/O thought/O on/O Jorah/PERSON 's/O words/O ,/O the/O more/O they/O rang/O of/O truth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O pray/O for/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Home/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
His/O voice/O was/O thick/O with/O longing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O pray/O for/O home/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O believing/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O around/O you/O then/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O But/O it/O was/O not/O the/O plains/O Dany/PERSON saw/O then/O ./O 
It/O was/O King/O 's/O Landing/O and/O the/O great/O Red/O Keep/O that/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O had/O built/O ./O 
It/O was/O Dragonstone/PERSON where/O she/O had/O been/O born/O ./O 
In/O her/O mind/O 's/O eye/O ''/O ,/O ``/O they/O burned/O with/O a/O thousand/O lights/O ,/O a/O fire/O blazing/O in/O every/O window/O ./O 
In/O her/O mind/O 's/O eye/O ,/O all/O the/O doors/O were/O red/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O will/O never/O take/O back/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
She/O had/O known/O that/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
She/O had/O known/O it/O all/O her/O life/O ./O 
Only/O she/O had/O never/O let/O herself/O say/O the/O words/O ,/O even/O in/O a/O whisper/O ,/O but/O now/O she/O said/O them/O for/O Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON and/O all/O the/O world/O to/O hear/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O measuring/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O think/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O could/O not/O lead/O an/O army/O even/O if/O my/O lord/O husband/O gave/O him/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O no/O coin/O and/O the/O only/O knight/O who/O follows/O him/O reviles/O him/O as/O less/O than/O a/O snake/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O make/O mock/O of/O his/O weakness/O ./O 
He/O will/O never/O take/O us/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wise/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O smiled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O no/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O fiercely/O ./O 
Her/O heels/O pressed/O into/O the/O sides/O of/O her/O mount/O ,/O rousing/O the/O silver/O to/O a/O gallop/O ./O 
Faster/O and/O faster/O she/O raced/O ,/O leaving/O Jorah/PERSON and/O Irri/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O others/O far/O behind/O ,/O the/O warm/O wind/O in/O her/O hair/O and/O the/O setting/O sun/O red/O on/O her/O face/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O she/O reached/O the/O khalasar/O ,/O it/O was/O dusk/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O slaves/O had/O erected/O her/O tent/O by/O the/O shore/O of/O a/O spring/O -/O fed/O pool/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O rough/O voices/O from/O the/O woven/O grass/O palace/O on/O the/O hill/O ./O 
Soon/O there/O would/O be/O laughter/O ,/O when/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O told/O the/O story/O of/O what/O had/O happened/O in/O the/O grasses/O today/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O Viserys/PERSON came/O limping/O back/O among/O them/O ,/O every/O man/O ,/O woman/O ,/O and/O child/O in/O the/O camp/O would/O know/O him/O for/O a/O walker/O ./O 
There/O were/O no/O secrets/O in/O the/O khalasar/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON gave/O the/O silver/O over/O to/O the/O slaves/O for/O grooming/O and/O entered/O her/O tent/O ./O 
It/O was/O cool/O and/O dim/O beneath/O the/O silk/O ./O 
As/O she/O let/O the/O door/O flap/O close/O behind/O her/O ,/O Dany/PERSON saw/O a/O finger/O of/O dusty/O red/O light/O reach/O out/O to/O touch/O her/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O across/O the/O tent/O ./O 
For/O an/O instant/O a/O thousand/O droplets/O of/O scarlet/O flame/O swam/O before/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O blinked/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Stone/PERSON ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
They/O are/O only/O stone/O ,/O even/O Illyrio/PERSON said/O so/O ,/O the/O dragons/O are/O all/O dead/O ./O 
She/O put/O her/O palm/O against/O the/O black/O egg/O ,/O fingers/O spread/O gently/O across/O the/O curve/O of/O the/O shell/O ./O 
The/O stone/O was/O warm/O ./O 
Almost/O hot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sun/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sun/O warmed/O them/O as/O they/O rode/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O commanded/O her/O handmaids/O to/O prepare/O her/O a/O bath/O ./O 
Doreah/PERSON built/O a/O fire/O outside/O the/O tent/O ,/O while/O Irri/ORGANIZATION and/O Jhiqui/PERSON fetched/O the/O big/O copper/O tub-another/O bride/O gift/O -/O from/O the/O packhorses/O and/O carried/O water/O from/O the/O pool/O ./O 
When/O the/O bath/O was/O steaming/O ,/O Irri/PERSON helped/O her/O into/O it/O and/O climbed/O in/O after/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Have/O you/O ever/O seen/O a/O dragon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O as/O Irri/PERSON scrubbed/O her/O back/O and/O Jhiqui/PERSON sluiced/O sand/O from/O her/O hair/O ./O 
She/O had/O heard/O that/O the/O first/O dragons/O had/O come/O from/O the/O east/O ,/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Lands/O beyond/O Asshai/LOCATION and/O the/O islands/O of/O the/O Jade/O Sea/O ./O 
Perhaps/O some/O were/O still/O living/O there/O ,/O in/O realms/O strange/O and/O wild/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dragons/O are/O gone/O ,/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O agreed/O Jhiqui/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Long/O and/O long/O ago/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON had/O told/O her/O that/O the/O last/O Targaryen/O dragons/O had/O died/O no/O more/O than/O a/O century/O and/O a/O half/O ago/O ,/O during/O the/O reign/O of/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION ,/O who/O was/O called/O the/O Dragonbane/O ./O 
That/O did/O not/O seem/O so/O long/O ago/O to/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Everywhere/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O disappointed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O in/O the/O east/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Magic/O had/O died/O in/O the/O west/O when/O the/O Doom/O fell/O on/O Valyria/LOCATION and/O the/O Lands/O of/O the/O Long/O Summer/O ,/O and/O neither/O spell/O -/O forged/O steel/O nor/O storms/O ingers/O nor/O dragons/O could/O hold/O it/O back/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON had/O always/O heard/O that/O the/O east/O ''/O ,/O ``/O was/O different/O ./O 
It/O was/O said/O that/O manticores/O prowled/O the/O islands/O of/O the/O Jade/LOCATION Sea/LOCATION ,/O that/O basilisks/O infested/O the/O jungles/O of/O Yi/PERSON Ti/PERSON ,/O that/O spellsingers/O ,/O warlocks/O ,/O and/O aeromancers/O practiced/O their/O arts/O openly/O in/O Asshai/LOCATION ,/O while/O shadowbinders/O and/O bloodmages/O worked/O terrible/O sorceries/O in/O the/O black/O of/O night/O ./O 
Why/O should/O n't/O there/O be/O dragons/O too/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Brave/O men/O kill/O them/O ,/O for/O dragon/O terrible/O evil/O beasts/O ./O 
It/O is/O known/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O known/O ,/O \/O ''/O agreed/O Jhiqui/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O trader/O from/O Qarth/LOCATION once/O told/O me/O that/O dragons/O came/O from/O the/O moon/O ,/O \/O ''/O blond/O Doreah/PERSON said/O as/O she/O warmed/O a/O towel/O over/O the/O fire/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON and/O Irri/ORGANIZATION were/O of/O an/O age/O with/O Dany/PERSON ,/O Dothraki/PERSON girls/O taken/O as/O slaves/O when/O Drogo/PERSON destroyed/O their/O father/O 's/O khalasar/O ./O 
Doreah/PERSON was/O older/O ,/O almost/O twenty/O ./O 
Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON had/O found/O her/O in/O a/O pleasure/O house/O in/O Lys/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Silvery-wet/O hair/O tumbled/O across/O her/O eyes/O as/O Dany/PERSON turned/O her/O head/O ,/O curious/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O moon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O told/O me/O the/O moon/O was/O an/O egg/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lysene/O girl/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Once/O there/O were/O two/O moons/O in/O the/O sky/O ,/O but/O one/O wandered/O too/O close/O to/O the/O sun/O and/O cracked/O from/O the/O heat/O ./O 
A/O thousand/O thousand/O dragons/O poured/O forth/O ,/O and/O drank/O the/O fire/O of/O the/O sun/O ./O 
That/O is/O why/O dragons/O breathe/O flame/O ./O 
One/O day/O the/O other/O moon/O will/O kiss/O the/O sun/O too/O ,/O and/O then/O it/O will/O crack/O and/O the/O dragons/O will/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O two/O Dothraki/O girls/O giggled/O and/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O foolish/O strawhead/O slave/O ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Moon/O is/O no/O egg/O ./O 
Moon/O is/O god/O ,/O woman/O wife/O of/O sun/O ./O 
It/O is/O known/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O known/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jhiqui/PERSON agreed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON 's/O skin/O was/O flushed/O and/O pink/O when/O she/O climbed/O from/O the/O tub/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON laid/O her/O down/O to/O oil/O her/O body/O and/O scrape/O the/O dirt/O from/O her/O pores/O ./O 
Afterward/O Irri/O sprinkled/O her/O with/O spiceflower/O and/O cinnamon/O ./O 
While/O Doreah/PERSON brushed/O her/O hair/O until/O it/O shone/O like/O spun/O silver/O ,/O she/O thought/O about/O the/O moon/O ,/O and/O eggs/O ,/O and/O dragons/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O supper/O was/O a/O simple/O meal/O of/O fruit/O and/O cheese/O and/O fry/O bread/O ,/O with/O a/O jug/O of/O honeyed/O wine/O to/O wash/O it/O down/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Doreah/O ,/O stay/O and/O eat/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON commanded/O when/O she/O sent/O her/O other/O handmaids/O away/O ./O 
The/O Lysene/O girl/O had/O hair/O the/O color/O of/O honey/O ,/O and/O eyes/O like/O the/O summer/O sky/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O lowered/O those/O eyes/O when/O they/O were/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O honor/O me/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O no/O honor/O ,/O only/O service/O ./O 
Long/O after/O the/O moon/O had/O risen/O ,/O they/O sat/O together/O ,/O talking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O night/O ,/O when/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON came/O ,/O Dany/PERSON was/O waiting/O for/O him/O ./O 
He/O stood/O in/O the/O door/O of/O her/O tent/O and/O looked/O at/O her/O with/O surprise/O ./O 
She/O rose/O slowly/O and/O opened/O her/O sleeping/O silks/O and/O let/O them/O fall/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O night/O we/O must/O go/O outside/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O for/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON believed/O that/O all/O things/O of/O importance/O in/O a/O man/O 's/O life/O must/O be/O done/O beneath/O the/O open/O sky/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON followed/O her/O out/O into/O the/O moonlight/O ,/O the/O bells/O in/O his/O hair/O tinkling/O softly/O ./O 
A/O few/O yards/O from/O her/O tent/O was/O a/O bed/O of/O soft/O grass/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O there/O that/O Dany/PERSON drew/O him/O down/O ./O 
When/O he/O tried/O to/O turn/O her/O over/O ,/O she/O put/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O night/O I/O would/O look/O on/O your/O face/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O privacy/O in/O the/O heart/O of/O the/O khalasar/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON felt/O the/O eyes/O on/O her/O as/O she/O undressed/O him/O ,/O heard/O the/O soft/O voices/O as/O she/O did/O the/O things/O that/O Doreah/PERSON had/O told/O her/O to/O do/O ./O 
It/O was/O nothing/O to/O her/O ./O 
Was/O she/O not/O khaleesi/O ?/O 
His/O were/O the/O only/O eyes/O that/O mattered/O ,/O and/O when/O she/O mounted/O him/O she/O saw/O something/O there/O that/O she/O had/O never/O seen/O before/O ./O 
She/O rode/O him/O as/O fiercely/O as/O ever/O she/O had/O ridden/O her/O silver/O ,/O and/O when/O the/O moment/O of/O his/O pleasure/O came/O ,/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON called/O out/O her/O name/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O were/O on/O the/O far/O side/O of/O the/O Dothraki/O sea/O when/O Jhiqui/PERSON brushed/O the/O soft/O swell/O of/O Dany/PERSON 's/O stomach/O with/O her/O fingers/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O you/O are/O with/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
It/O was/O her/O fourteenth/O name/O day/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
