-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O courtyard/O rang/O to/O the/O song/O of/O swords/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Under/O black/O wool/O ,/O boiled/O leather/O ,/O and/O mail/O ,/O sweat/O trickled/O icily/O down/O Jon/PERSON 's/O chest/O as/O he/O pressed/O the/O attack/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON stumbled/O backward/O ,/O defending/O himself/O clumsily/O ./O 
When/O he/O raised/O his/O sword/O ,/O Jon/PERSON went/O underneath/O it/O with/O a/O sweeping/O blow/O that/O crunched/O against/O the/O back/O of/O the/O other/O boy/O 's/O leg/O and/O sent/O him/O staggering/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON '/O s/O downcut/O was/O answered/O by/O an/O overhand/O that/O dented/O his/O helm/O ./O 
When/O he/O tried/O a/O sideswing/O ,/O Jon/PERSON swept/O aside/O his/O blade/O and/O slammed/O a/O mailed/O forearm/O into/O his/O chest/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON lost/O his/O footing/O and/O sat/O down/O hard/O in/O the/O snow/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knocked/O his/O sword/O from/O his/O fingers/O with/O a/O slash/O to/O his/O wrist/O that/O brought/O a/O cry/O of/O pain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Enough/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON had/O a/O voice/O with/O an/O edge/O like/O Valyrian/O steel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grenn/PERSON cradled/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O bastard/O broke/O my/O wrist/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O bastard/O hamstrung/O you/O ,/O opened/O your/O empty/O skull/O ,/O and/O cut/O off/O your/O hand/O ./O 
Or/O would/O have/O ,/O if/O these/O blades/O had/O an/O edge/O ./O 
It/O 's/O fortunate/O for/O you/O that/O the/O Watch/O needs/O stableboys/O as/O well/O as/O rangers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON gestured/O at/O Jeren/LOCATION and/O Toad/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O the/O Aurochs/O on/O his/O feet/O ,/O he/O has/O funeral/O arrangements/O to/O make/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON took/O off/O his/O helm/O as/O the/O other/O boys/O were/O pulling/O Grenn/PERSON to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
The/O frosty/O morning/O air/O felt/O good/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
He/O leaned/O on/O his/O sword/O ,/O drew/O a/O deep/O breath/O ,/O and/O allowed/O himself/O a/O moment/O to/O savor/O the/O victory/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O a/O longsword/O ,/O not/O an/O old/O man/O 's/O cane/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O your/O legs/O hurting/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON hated/O that/O name/O ,/O a/O mockery/O that/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON had/O hung/O on/O him/O the/O first/O day/O he/O came/O to/O practice/O ./O 
The/O boys/O had/O picked/O it/O up/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O heard/O it/O everywhere/O ./O 
He/O slid/O the/O longsword/O back/O into/O its/O scabbard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Thorne/PERSON strode/O toward/O him/O ,/O crisp/O black/O leathers/O whispering/O faintly/O as/O he/O moved/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O compact/O man/O of/O fifty/O years/O ,/O spare/O and/O hard/O ,/O with/O grey/O in/O his/O black/O hair/O and/O eyes/O like/O chips/O of/O onyx/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O truth/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O commanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O tired/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
His/O arm/O burned/O from/O the/O weight/O of/O the/O longsword/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O starting/O to/O feel/O his/O bruises/O now/O that/O the/O fight/O was/O done/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O you/O are/O is/O weak/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O won/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
The/O Aurochs/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O other/O boys/O sniggered/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knew/O better/O than/O to/O reply/O ./O 
He/O had/O beaten/O everyone/O that/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON had/O sent/O against/O him/O ,/O yet/O it/O gained/O him/O nothing/O ./O 
The/O master-at-arms/O served/O up/O only/O derision/O ./O 
Thorne/PERSON hated/O him/O ,/O Jon/PERSON had/O decided/O ;/O of/O course/O ,/O he/O hated/O the/O other/O boys/O even/O worse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O will/O be/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O Thorne/PERSON told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O only/O stomach/O so/O much/O ineptitude/O in/O any/O one/O day/O ./O 
If/O the/O Others/O ever/O come/O for/O us/O ,/O I/O pray/O they/O have/O archers/O ,/O because/O you/O lot/O are/O fit/O for/O nothing/O more/O than/O arrow/O fodder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON followed/O the/O rest/O back/O to/O the/O armory/O ,/O walking/O alone/O ./O 
He/O often/O walked/O alone/O here/O ./O 
There/O were/O almost/O twenty/O in/O the/O group/O he/O trained/O with/O ,/O yet/O not/O one/O he/O could/O call/O a/O friend/O ./O 
Most/O were/O ''/O ,/O ``/O two/O or/O three/O years/O his/O senior/O ,/O yet/O not/O one/O was/O half/O the/O fighter/O Robb/PERSON had/O been/O at/O fourteen/O ./O 
Dareon/PERSON was/O quick/O but/O afraid/O of/O being/O hit/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON used/O his/O sword/O like/O a/O dagger/O ,/O Jeren/PERSON was/O weak/O as/O a/O girl/O ,/O Grenn/PERSON slow/O and/O clumsy/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON 's/O blows/O were/O brutally/O hard/O but/O he/O ran/O right/O into/O your/O attacks/O ./O 
The/O more/O time/O he/O spent/O with/O them/O ,/O the/O more/O Jon/PERSON despised/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O ,/O Jon/PERSON hung/O sword/O and/O scabbard/O from/O a/O hook/O in/O the/O stone/O wall/O ,/O ignoring/O the/O others/O around/O him/O ./O 
Methodically/O ,/O he/O began/O to/O strip/O off/O his/O mail/O ,/O leather/O ,/O and/O sweat-soaked/O woolens/O ./O 
Chunks/O of/O coal/O burned/O in/O iron/O braziers/O at/O either/O end/O of/O the/O long/O room/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON found/O himself/O shivering/O ./O 
The/O chill/O was/O always/O with/O him/O here/O ./O 
In/O a/O few/O years/O he/O would/O forget/O what/O it/O felt/O like/O to/O be/O warm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O weariness/O came/O on/O him/O suddenly/O ,/O as/O he/O donned/O the/O roughspun/O blacks/O that/O were/O their/O everyday/O wear/O ./O 
He/O sat/O on/O a/O bench/O ,/O his/O fingers/O fumbling/O with/O the/O fastenings/O on/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
So/O cold/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O remembering/O the/O warm/O halls/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O where/O the/O hot/O waters/O ran/O through/O the/O walls/O like/O blood/O through/O a/O man/O 's/O body/O ./O 
There/O was/O scant/O warmth/O to/O be/O found/O in/O Castle/O Black/O ;/O the/O walls/O were/O cold/O here/O ,/O and/O the/O people/O colder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O one/O had/O told/O him/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O would/O be/O like/O this/O ;/O no/O one/O except/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ./O 
The/O dwarf/O had/O given/O him/O the/O truth/O on/O the/O road/O north/O ,/O but/O by/O then/O it/O had/O been/O too/O late/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON wondered/O if/O his/O father/O had/O known/O what/O the/O Wall/O would/O be/O like/O ./O 
He/O must/O have/O ,/O he/O thought/O ;/O that/O only/O made/O it/O hurt/O the/O worse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O his/O uncle/O had/O abandoned/O him/O in/O this/O cold/O place/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O ./O 
Up/O here/O ,/O the/O genial/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON he/O had/O known/O became/O a/O different/O person/O ./O 
He/O was/O First/O Ranger/O ,/O and/O he/O spent/O his/O days/O and/O nights/O with/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON and/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON and/O the/O other/O high/O officers/O ,/O while/O Jon/PERSON was/O given/O over/O to/O the/O less/O than/O tender/O charge/O of/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Three/O days/O after/O their/O arrival/O ,/O Jon/PERSON had/O heard/O that/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O to/O lead/O a/O half-dozen/O men/O on/O a/O ranging/O into/O the/O haunted/O forest/O ./O 
That/O night/O he/O sought/O out/O his/O uncle/O in/O the/O great/O timbered/O common/O hall/O and/O pleaded/O to/O go/O with/O him/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON refused/O him/O curtly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O not/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O him/O as/O he/O cut/O his/O meat/O with/O fork/O and/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O On/O the/O Wall/O ,/O a/O man/O gets/O only/O what/O he/O earns/O ./O 
You/O 're/O no/O ranger/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O only/O a/O green/O boy/O with/O the/O smell/O of/O summer/O still/O on/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Stupidly/O ,/O Jon/PERSON argued/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O be/O fifteen/O on/O my/O name/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Almost/O a/O man/O grown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Benjen/O Stark/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O boy/O you/O are/O ,/O and/O a/O boy/O you/O 'll/O remain/O until/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON says/O you/O are/O fit/O to/O be/O a/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
If/O you/O thought/O your/O Stark/O blood/O would/O win/O you/O easy/O favors/O ,/O you/O were/O wrong/O ./O 
We/O put/O aside/O our/O old/O families/O when/O we/O swear/O our/O vows/O ./O 
Your/O father/O will/O always/O have/O a/O place/O in/O my/O heart/O ,/O but/O these/O are/O my/O brothers/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gestured/O with/O his/O dagger/O at/O the/O men/O around/O them/O ,/O all/O the/O hard/O cold/O men/O in/O black/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/O rose/O at/O dawn/O the/O next/O day/O to/O watch/O his/O uncle/O leave/O ./O 
One/O of/O his/O rangers/O ,/O a/O big/O ugly/O man/O ,/O sang/O a/O bawdy/O song/O as/O he/O saddled/O his/O garron/O ,/O his/O breath/O steaming/O in/O the/O cold/O morning/O air/O ./O 
Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON smiled/O at/O that/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O no/O smile/O for/O his/O nephew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O often/O must/O I/O tell/O you/O no/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
We/O 'll/O speak/O when/O I/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O he/O watched/O his/O uncle/O lead/O his/O horse/O into/O the/O tunnel/O ,/O Jon/PERSON had/O remembered/O the/O things/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON told/O him/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O and/O in/O his/O mind/O 's/O eye/O he/O saw/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON lying/O dead/O ,/O his/O blood/O red/O on/O the/O snow/O ./O 
The/O thought/O made/O him/O sick/O ./O 
What/O was/O he/O becoming/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O he/O sought/O out/O Ghost/O in/O the/O loneliness/O of/O his/O cell/O ,/O and/O buried/O his/O face/O in/O his/O thick/O white/O fur/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O he/O must/O be/O alone/O ,/O he/O would/O make/O solitude/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION had/O no/O godswood/O ,/O only/O a/O small/O sept/O and/O a/O drunken/O septon/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON could/O not/O find/O it/O in/O him/O to/O pray/O to/O any/O gods/O ,/O old/O or/O new/O ./O 
If/O they/O were/O real/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O they/O were/O as/O cruel/O and/O implacable/O as/O winter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O missed/O his/O true/O brothers/O :/O little/O Rickon/PERSON ,/O bright/O eyes/O shining/O as/O he/O begged/O for/O a/O sweet/O ;/O Robb/PERSON ,/O his/O rival/O and/O best/O friend/O and/O constant/O companion/O ;/O Bran/O ,/O stubborn/O and/O curious/O ,/O always/O wanting/O to/O follow/O and/O join/O in/O whatever/O Jon/PERSON and/O Robb/PERSON were/O doing/O ./O 
He/O missed/O the/O girls/O too/O ,/O even/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O who/O never/O called/O him/O anything/O but/O \/O ``/O my/O half/O brother/O \/O ''/O since/O she/O was/O old/O enough/O to/O understand/O what/O bastard/O meant/O ./O 
And/O Arya/O .../O he/O missed/O her/O even/O more/O than/O Robb/PERSON ,/O skinny/O little/O thing/O that/O she/O was/O ,/O all/O scraped/O knees/O and/O tangled/O hair/O and/O torn/O clothes/O ,/O so/O fierce/O and/O willful/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON never/O seemed/O to/O fit/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O he/O had/O .../O yet/O she/O could/O always/O make/O Jon/PERSON smile/O ./O 
He/O would/O give/O anything/O to/O be/O with/O her/O now/O ,/O to/O muss/O up/O her/O hair/O once/O more/O and/O watch/O her/O make/O a/O face/O ,/O to/O hear/O her/O finish/O a/O sentence/O with/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O broke/O my/O wrist/O ,/O bastard/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON lifted/O his/O eyes/O at/O the/O sullen/O voice/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON loomed/O over/O him/O ,/O thick/O of/O neck/O and/O red/O of/O face/O ,/O with/O three/O of/O his/O friends/O behind/O him/O ./O 
He/O knew/O Todder/PERSON ,/O a/O short/O ugly/O boy/O with/O an/O unpleasant/O voice/O ./O 
The/O recruits/O all/O called/O him/O Toad/O ./O 
The/O other/O two/O were/O the/O ones/O Yoren/PERSON had/O brought/O north/O with/O them/O ,/O Jon/PERSON remembered/O ,/O rapers/O taken/O down/O in/O the/O Fingers/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O forgotten/O their/O names/O ./O 
He/O hardly/O ever/O spoke/O ,/O to/O them/O ,/O if/O he/O could/O help/O it/O ./O 
They/O were/O brutes/O and/O bullies/O ,/O without/O a/O thimble/O of/O honor/O between/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON stood/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O break/O the/O other/O one/O for/O you/O if/O you/O ask/O nicely/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON was/O sixteen/O and/O a/O head/O taller/O than/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
All/O four/O of/O them/O were/O bigger/O than/O he/O was/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O not/O scare/O him/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O beaten/O every/O one/O of/O them/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O we/O 'll/O break/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O the/O rapers/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Try/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON reached/O back/O for/O his/O sword/O ,/O but/O one/O of/O them/O grabbed/O his/O arm/O and/O twisted/O it/O behind/O his/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O make/O us/O look/O bad/O ,/O \/O ''/O complained/O Toad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O looked/O bad/O before/O I/O ever/O met/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
The/O boy/O who/O had/O his/O arm/O jerked/O upward/O on/O him/O ,/O hard/O ./O 
Pain/O lanced/O through/O him/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON would/O not/O cry/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Toad/PERSON stepped/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O little/O lordling/O has/O a/O mouth/O on/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O had/O pig/O eyes/O ,/O small/O and/O shiny/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O your/O mommy/O 's/O mouth/O ,/O bastard/O ?/O 
What/O was/O she/O ,/O some/O whore/O ?/O 
Tell/O us/O her/O name/O ./O 
Maybe/O I/O had/O her/O a/O time/O or/O two/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON twisted/O like/O an/O eel/O and/O slammed/O a/O heel/O down/O across/O the/O instep/O of/O the/O boy/O holding/O him/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O sudden/O cry/O of/O pain/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O free/O ./O 
He/O flew/O at/O Toad/ORGANIZATION ,/O knocked/O him/O backward/O over/O a/O bench/O ,/O and/O landed/O on/O his/O chest/O with/O both/O hands/O on/O his/O throat/O ,/O slamming/O his/O head/O against/O the/O packed/O earth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O two/O from/O the/O Fingers/O pulled/O him/O off/O ,/O throwing/O him/O roughly/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON began/O to/O kick/O at/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON was/O rolling/O away/O from/O the/O blows/O when/O a/O booming/O voice/O cut/O through/O the/O gloom/O of/O the/O armory/O ./O 
\/O ``/O STOP/O THIS/O !/O 
NOW/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON pulled/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON stood/O glowering/O at/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O yard/O is/O for/O fighting/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O armorer/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O your/O quarrels/O out/O of/O my/O armory/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O make/O them/O my/O quarrels/O ./O 
You/O wo/O n't/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Toad/O sat/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O gingerly/O feeling/O the/O back/O of/O his/O head/O ./O 
His/O fingers/O came/O away/O bloody/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O tried/O to/O kill/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O 'S/O true/O ./O 
I/O saw/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O the/O rapers/O put/O in/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O broke/O my/O wrist/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O again/O ,/O holding/O it/O out/O to/O Noye/PERSON for/O inspection/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O armorer/O gave/O the/O offered/O wrist/O the/O briefest/O of/O glances/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O bruise/O ./O 
Perhaps/O a/O sprain/O ./O 
Maestor/PERSON Aemon/PERSON will/O give/O you/O a/O salve/O ./O 
Go/O with/O him/O ,/O Todder/PERSON ,/O that/O head/O wants/O looking/O after/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O you/O ,/O return/O to/O your/O cells/O ./O 
Not/O you/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
You/O stay/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON sat/O heavily/O on/O the/O long/O wooden/O bench/O as/O the/O others/O left/O ,/O oblivious/O to/O the/O looks/O they/O gave/O him/O ,/O the/O silent/O promises/O of/O future/O retribution/O ./O 
His/O arm/O was/O throbbing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Watch/O has/O need/O of/O every/O man/O it/O can/O get/O ,/O \/O ''/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON said/O when/O they/O were/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O men/O like/O Toad/O ./O 
You/O wo/O n't/O win/O any/O honors/O killing/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O anger/O flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O said/O my/O mother/O was/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O a/O whore/O ./O 
I/O heard/O him/O ./O 
What/O of/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O Stark/O was/O not/O a/O man/O to/O sleep/O with/O whores/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O icily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O honor/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O did/O not/O prevent/O him/O from/O fathering/O a/O bastard/O ./O 
Did/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O cold/O with/O rage/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O I/O go/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O go/O when/O I/O tell/O you/O to/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON stared/O sullenly/O at/O the/O smoke/O rising/O from/O the/O brazier/O ,/O until/O Noye/PERSON took/O him/O under/O the/O chin/O ,/O thick/O fingers/O twisting/O his/O head/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O at/O me/O when/O I/O 'm/O talking/O to/O you/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON looked/O ./O 
The/O armorer/O had/O a/O chest/O like/O a/O keg/O of/O ale/O and/O a/O gut/O to/O match/O ./O 
His/O nose/O was/O flat/O and/O broad/O ,/O and/O he/O always/O seemed/O in/O need/O of/O a/O shave/O ./O 
The/O left/O sleeve/O of/O his/O black/O wool/O tunic/O was/O fastened/O at/O the/O shoulder/O with/O a/O silver/O pin/O in/O the/O shape/O of/O a/O longsword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Words/O wo/O n't/O make/O your/O mother/O a/O whore/O ./O 
She/O was/O what/O she/O was/O ,/O and/O nothing/O Toad/PERSON says/O can/O change/O that/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O we/O have/O men/O on/O the/O Wall/O whose/O mothers/O were/O whores/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Not/O my/O mother/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O stubbornly/O ./O 
He/O knew/O nothing/O of/O his/O mother/O ;/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON would/O not/O talk/O of/O her/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O dreamed/O of/O her/O at/O times/O ,/O so/O often/O that/O he/O could/O almost/O see/O her/O face/O ./O 
In/O his/O dreams/O ,/O she/O was/O beautiful/O ,/O and/O highborn/O ,/O and/O her/O eyes/O were/O kind/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O think/O you/O had/O it/O hard/O ,/O being/O a/O high/O lord/O 's/O bastard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O armorer/O went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O boy/O Jeren/PERSON is/O a/O septon/O 's/O get/O ,/O and/O Cotter/PERSON Pyke/PERSON is/O the/O baseborn/O son/O of/O a/O tavern/O wench/O ./O 
Now/O he/O commands/O Eastwatch/PERSON by/O the/O Sea/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O about/O them/O and/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O about/O you/O or/O Thorne/PERSON or/O Benjen/O Stark/O or/O any/O of/O it/O ./O 
I/O hate/O it/O here/O ./O 
It/O 's/O too/O .../O it/O 's/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Cold/O and/O hard/O and/O mean/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O the/O men/O who/O walk/O it/O ./O 
Not/O like/O the/O stories/O your/O wet/O nurse/O told/O you/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O piss/O on/O the/O stories/O and/O piss/O on/O your/O wet/O nurse/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O way/O it/O is/O ,/O and/O you/O 're/O here/O for/O life/O ,/O same/O as/O the/O rest/O of/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Life/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON repeated/O bitterly/O ./O 
The/O armorer/O could/O talk/O about/O life/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O had/O one/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O only/O taken/O the/O black/O after/O he/O 'd/O lost/O an/O arm/O at/O the/O siege/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ./O 
Before/O that/O he/O 'd/O smithed/O for/O Stannis/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Baratheon/O ,/O the/O king/O 's/O brother/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O seen/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O from/O one/O end/O to/O the/O other/O ;/O he/O 'd/O feasted/O and/O wenched/O and/O fought/O in/O a/O hundred/O battles/O ./O 
They/O said/O it/O was/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON who/O 'd/O forged/O King/O Robert/PERSON 's/O warhammer/O ,/O the/O one/O that/O crushed/O the/O life/O from/O Rhaegar/LOCATION Targaryen/LOCATION on/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O done/O all/O the/O things/O that/O Jon/PERSON would/O never/O do/O ,/O and/O then/O when/O he/O was/O old/O ,/O well/O past/O thirty/O ,/O he/O 'd/O taken/O a/O glancing/O blow/O from/O an/O axe/O and/O the/O wound/O had/O festered/O until/O the/O whole/O arm/O had/O to/O come/O off/O ./O 
Only/O then/O ,/O crippled/O ,/O had/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON come/O to/O the/O Wall/O ,/O when/O his/O life/O was/O all/O but/O over/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O Noye/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O long/O life/O or/O a/O short/O one/O ,/O it/O 's/O up/O to/O you/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
The/O road/O you/O 're/O walking/O ,/O one/O of/O your/O brothers/O will/O slit/O your/O throat/O for/O you/O one/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O not/O my/O brothers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON snapped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O hate/O me/O because/O I/O 'm/O better/O than/O they/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
They/O hate/O you/O because/O you/O act/O like/O you/O 're/O better/O than/O they/O are/O ./O 
They/O look/O at/O you/O and/O see/O a/O castle-bred/O bastard/O who/O thinks/O he/O 's/O a/O lordling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O armorer/O leaned/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O no/O lordling/O ./O 
Remember/O that/O ./O 
You/O 're/O a/O Snow/O ,/O not/O a/O Stark/O ./O 
You/O 're/O a/O bastard/O and/O a/O bully/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O bully/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON almost/O choked/O on/O the/O word/O ./O 
The/O accusation/O was/O so/O unjust/O it/O took/O his/O breath/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O the/O ones/O who/O came/O after/O me/O ./O 
Four/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Four/O that/O you/O 've/O humiliated/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
Four/O who/O are/O probably/O afraid/O of/O you/O ./O 
I/O 've/O watched/O you/O fight/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O training/O with/O you/O ./O 
Put/O a/O good/O edge/O on/O your/O sword/O ,/O and/O they/O 'd/O be/O dead/O meat/O ;/O you/O know/O it/O ,/O I/O know/O it/O ,/O they/O know/O it/O ./O 
You/O leave/O them/O nothing/O ./O 
You/O shame/O them/O ./O 
Does/O that/O make/O you/O proud/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON hesitated/O ./O 
He/O did/O feel/O proud/O when/O he/O won/O ./O 
Why/O should/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
But/O the/O armorer/O was/O taking/O that/O away/O too/O ,/O making/O it/O sound/O as/O if/O he/O were/O doing/O something/O wrong/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O all/O older/O than/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O defensively/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Older/O and/O bigger/O and/O stronger/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O truth/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O wager/O your/O master-at-arms/O taught/O you/O how/O to/O fight/O bigger/O men/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O though/O ./O 
Who/O was/O he/O ,/O some/O old/O knight/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O warily/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O trap/O here/O ./O 
He/O felt/O it/O closing/O around/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON leaned/O forward/O ,/O into/O Jon/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O think/O on/O this/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
None/O of/O these/O others/O have/O ever/O had/O a/O master-at-arms/O until/O Ser/O Alliser/O ./O 
Their/O fathers/O were/O farmers/O and/O wagonmen/O and/O poachers/O ,/O smiths/O and/O miners/O and/O oars/O on/O a/O trading/O galley/O ./O 
What/O they/O know/O of/O fighting/O they/O learned/O between/O decks/O ,/O in/O the/O alleys/O of/O Oldtown/LOCATION and/O Lannisport/LOCATION ,/O in/O wayside/O brothels/O and/O taverns/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
They/O may/O have/O clacked/O a/O few/O sticks/O together/O before/O they/O came/O here/O ,/O but/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O not/O one/O in/O twenty/O was/O ever/O rich/O enough/O to/O own/O a/O real/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O look/O was/O grim/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O how/O do/O you/O like/O the/O taste/O of/O your/O victories/O now/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O call/O me/O that/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O sharply/O ,/O but/O the/O force/O had/O gone/O out/O of/O his/O anger/O ./O 
Suddenly/O he/O felt/O ashamed/O and/O guilty/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O .../O I/O did/O n't/O think/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Best/O you/O start/O thinking/O ,/O \/O ''/O Noye/PERSON warned/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O ,/O or/O sleep/O with/O a/O dagger/O by/O your/O bed/O ./O 
Now/O ''/O ,/O ``/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O Jon/PERSON left/O the/O armory/O ,/O it/O was/O almost/O midday/O ./O 
The/O sun/O had/O broken/O through/O the/O clouds/O ./O 
He/O turned/O his/O back/O on/O it/O and/O lifted/O his/O eyes/O to/O the/O Wall/O ,/O blazing/O blue/O and/O crystalline/O in/O the/O sunlight/O ./O 
Even/O after/O all/O these/O weeks/O ,/O the/O sight/O of/O it/O still/O gave/O him/O the/O shivers/O ./O 
Centuries/O of/O windblown/O dirt/O had/O pocked/O and/O scoured/O it/O ,/O covering/O it/O like/O a/O film/O ,/O and/O it/O often/O seemed/O a/O pale/O ''/O ,/O ``/O grey/O ,/O the/O color/O of/O an/O overcast/O sky/O .../O but/O when/O the/O sun/O caught/O it/O fair/O on/O a/O bright/O day/O ,/O it/O shone/O ,/O alive/O with/O light/O ,/O a/O colossal/O blue/O -/O white/O cliff/O that/O filled/O up/O half/O the/O sky/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O largest/O structure/O ever/O built/O by/O the/O hands/O of/O man/O ,/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O told/O Jon/PERSON on/O the/O kingsroad/O when/O they/O had/O first/O caught/O sight/O of/O the/O Wall/O in/O the/O distance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O beyond/O a/O doubt/O the/O most/O useless/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O added/O with/O a/O grin/O ,/O but/O even/O the/O Imp/O grew/O silent/O as/O they/O rode/O closer/O ./O 
You/O could/O see/O it/O from/O miles/O off/O ,/O a/O pale/O blue/O line/O across/O the/O northern/O horizon/O ,/O stretching/O away/O to/O the/O east/O and/O west/O and/O vanishing/O in/O the/O far/O distance/O ,/O immense/O and/O unbroken/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O ,/O it/O seemed/O to/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O they/O finally/O spied/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION ,/O its/O timbered/O keeps/O and/O stone/O towers/O looked/O like/O nothing/O more/O than/O a/O handful/O of/O toy/O blocks/O scattered/O on/O the/O snow/O ,/O beneath/O the/O vast/O wall/O of/O ice/O ./O 
The/O ancient/O stronghold/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O was/O no/O Winterfell/O ,/O no/O true/O castle/O at/O all/O ./O 
Lacking/O walls/O ,/O it/O could/O not/O be/O defended/O ,/O not/O from/O the/O south/O ,/O or/O east/O ,/O or/O west/O ;/O but/O it/O was/O only/O the/O north/O that/O concerned/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O and/O to/O the/O north/O loomed/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Almost/O seven/O hundred/O feet/O high/O it/O stood/O ,/O three/O times/O the/O height/O of/O the/O tallest/O tower/O in/O the/O stronghold/O it/O sheltered/O ./O 
His/O uncle/O said/O the/O top/O was/O wide/O enough/O for/O a/O dozen/O armored/O knights/O to/O ride/O abreast/O ./O 
The/O gaunt/O outlines/O of/O huge/O catapults/O and/O monstrous/O wooden/O cranes/O stood/O sentry/O up/O there/O ,/O like/O the/O skeletons/O of/O great/O birds/O ,/O and/O among/O them/O walked/O men/O in/O black/O as/O small/O as/O ants/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O he/O stood/O outside/O the/O armory/O looking/O up/O ,/O Jon/PERSON felt/O almost/O as/O overwhelmed/O as/O he/O had/O that/O day/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O when/O he/O 'd/O seen/O it/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
The/O Wall/O was/O like/O that/O ./O 
Sometimes/O he/O could/O almost/O forget/O that/O it/O was/O there/O ,/O the/O way/O you/O forgot/O about/O the/O sky/O or/O the/O earth/O underfoot/O ,/O but/O there/O were/O other/O times/O when/O it/O seemed/O as/O if/O there/O was/O nothing/O else/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
It/O was/O older/O than/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O stood/O beneath/O it/O and/O looked/O up/O ,/O it/O made/O Jon/PERSON dizzy/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O the/O great/O weight/O of/O all/O that/O ice/O pressing/O down/O on/O him/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O were/O about/O to/O topple/O ,/O and/O somehow/O Jon/PERSON knew/O that/O if/O it/O fell/O ,/O the/O world/O fell/O with/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Makes/O you/O wonder/O what/O lies/O beyond/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O familiar/O voice/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON looked/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannister/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O see-I/O mean/O ,/O I/O thought/O I/O was/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O was/O bundled/O in/O furs/O so/O thickly/O he/O looked/O like/O a/O very/O small/O bear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O much/O to/O be/O said/O for/O taking/O people/O unawares/O ./O 
You/O never/O know/O what/O you/O might/O learn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O wo/O n't/O learn/O anything/O from/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
He/O had/O seen/O little/O of/O the/O dwarf/O since/O their/O journey/O ended/O ./O 
As/O the/O queen/O 's/O own/O brother/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O been/O an/O honored/O guest/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
The/O Lord/O Commander/O had/O given/O him/O rooms/O in/O the/O King/O 's/O Tower-so-called/O ,/O though/O no/O king/O had/O visited/O it/O for/O a/O hundred/O years/O and/O Lannister/PERSON dined/O at/O Mormont/LOCATION 's/O own/O table/O and/O spent/O his/O days/O riding/O the/O Wall/O and/O his/O nights/O dicing/O and/O drinking/O with/O Ser/O Alliser/O and/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON and/O the/O other/O high/O officers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O learn/O things/O everywhere/O I/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O little/O man/O gestured/O up/O at/O the/O Wall/O with/O a/O gnarled/O black/O walking/O stick/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O I/O was/O saying/O .../O why/O is/O it/O that/O when/O one/O man/O builds/O a/O wall/O ,/O the/O next/O man/O immediately/O needs/O to/O know/O what/O 's/O on/O the/O other/O side/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O cocked/O his/O head/O and/O looked/O at/O Jon/PERSON with/O his/O curious/O mismatched/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O want/O to/O know/O what/O 's/O on/O the/O other/O side/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O nothing/O special/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O ride/O with/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON on/O his/O rangings/O ,/O deep/O into/O the/O mysteries/O of/O the/O haunted/O forest/O ,/O wanted/O to/O fight/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON 's/O wildlings/O and/O ward/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O realm/O against/O the/O Others/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O better/O not/O to/O speak/O of/O the/O things/O you/O wanted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O rangers/O say/O it/O 's/O just/O woods/O and/O mountains/O and/O frozen/O lakes/O ,/O with/O lots/O of/O snow/O and/O ice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O the/O grumkins/O and/O the/O snarks/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O us/O not/O forget/O them/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ,/O or/O else/O what/O 's/O that/O big/O thing/O for/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O call/O me/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O lifted/O an/O eyebrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O you/O rather/O be/O called/O the/O Imp/O ?/O 
Let/O them/O see/O that/O their/O words/O can/O cut/O you/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O never/O be/O free/O of/O the/O mockery/O ./O 
If/O they/O want/O to/O give/O you/O a/O name/O ,/O take/O it/O ,/O make/O it/O your/O own/O ./O 
Then/O they/O ca/O n't/O hurt/O you/O with/O it/O anymore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gestured/O with/O his/O stick/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O walk/O with/O me/O ./O 
They/O 'll/O be/O serving/O some/O vile/O stew/O in/O the/O common/O hall/O by/O now/O ,/O and/O I/O could/O do/O with/O a/O bowl/O of/O something/O hot/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O hungry/O too/O ,/O so/O he/O fell/O in/O beside/O Lannister/LOCATION and/O slowed/O his/O pace/O to/O match/O the/O dwarfs/O awkward/O ,/O waddling/O steps/O ./O 
The/O wind/O was/O rising/O ,/O and/O they/O could/O hear/O the/O old/O wooden/O buildings/O creaking/O around/O them/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O distance/O a/O heavy/O shutter/O banging/O ,/O over/O and/O over/O ,/O forgotten/O ./O 
Once/O there/O was/O a/O muffled/O thump/O as/O a/O blanket/O of/O snow/O slid/O from/O a/O roof/O and/O landed/O near/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O see/O your/O wolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O as/O they/O walked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O chain/O him/O up/O in/O the/O old/O stables/O when/O we/O 're/O training/O ./O 
They/O board/O all/O the/O horses/O in/O the/O east/O stables/O now/O ,/O so/O no/O one/O bothers/O him/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O the/O time/O he/O stays/O with/O me/O ./O 
My/O sleeping/O cell/O is/O in/O Hardin/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O the/O one/O with/O the/O broken/O battlement/O ,/O no/O ?/O 
Shattered/O stone/O in/O the/O yard/O below/O ,/O and/O a/O lean/O to/O it/O like/O our/O noble/O king/O Robert/PERSON after/O a/O long/O night/O 's/O drinking/O ?/O 
I/O thought/O all/O those/O buildings/O had/O been/O abandoned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O cares/O where/O you/O sleep/O ./O 
Most/O of/O the/O old/O keeps/O are/O empty/O ,/O you/O can/O pick/O any/O cell/O you/O want/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Once/O Castle/O Black/O had/O housed/O five/O thousand/O fighting/O men/O with/O all/O their/O horses/O and/O servants/O and/O weapons/O ./O 
Now/O it/O was/O home/O to/O a/O tenth/O that/O number/O ,/O and/O parts/O of/O it/O were/O falling/O into/O ruin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O 's/O laughter/O steamed/O in/O the/O cold/O air/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O be/O sure/O to/O tell/O your/O father/O to/O arrest/O more/O stonemasons/O ,/O before/O your/O tower/O collapses/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON could/O taste/O the/O mockery/O there/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O denying/O the/O truth/O ./O 
The/O Watch/O had/O built/O nineteen/O great/O strongholds/O along/O the/O Wall/O ,/O but/O only/O three/O were/O still/O occupied/O :/O Eastwatch/O on/O its/O grey/O windswept/O shore/O ,/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION hard/O by/O the/O mountains/O where/O the/O Wall/O ended/O ,/O and/O Castle/O Black/O between/O them/O ,/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
The/O other/O keeps/O ,/O long/O deserted/O ,/O were/O lonely/O ,/O haunted/O places/O ,/O where/O cold/O winds/O whistled/O through/O black/O windows/O and/O the/O spirits/O of/O the/O dead/O manned/O the/O parapets/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O better/O that/O I/O 'm/O by/O myself/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O stubbornly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O rest/O of/O them/O are/O scared/O of/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wise/O boys/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
Then/O he/O changed/O the/O subject/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O talk/O is/O ,/O your/O uncle/O is/O too/O long/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON remembered/O the/O wish/O he/O 'd/O wished/O in/O his/O anger/O ,/O the/O vision/O of/O Benjen/O Stark/O dead/O in/O the/O snow/O ,/O and/O he/O looked/O away/O quickly/O ./O 
The/O dwarf/O had/O a/O way/O of/O sensing/O things/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O want/O him/O to/O see/O the/O guilt/O in/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O said/O he/O 'd/O be/O back/O by/O my/O name/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O admitted/O ./O 
His/O name/O day/O had/O come/O and/O gone/O ,/O unremarked/O ,/O a/O fortnight/O past/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O looking/O for/O Ser/PERSON Waymar/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O father/O is/O bannerman/O to/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON ./O 
Uncle/O Benjen/PERSON said/O they/O might/O search/O as/O far/O as/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
That/O 's/O all/O the/O way/O up/O in/O the/O mountains/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hear/O that/O a/O good/O many/O rangers/O have/O vanished/O of/O late/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O as/O they/O mounted/O the/O steps/O to/O the/O common/O hall/O ./O 
He/O grinned/O and/O pulled/O open/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O the/O grumkins/O are/O hungry/O this/O year/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Inside/O ,/O the/O hall/O was/O immense/O and/O drafty/O ,/O even/O with/O a/O fire/O roaring/O in/O its/O great/O hearth/O ./O 
Crows/O nested/O in/O the/O timbers/O of/O its/O lofty/O ceiling/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON heard/O their/O cries/O overhead/O as/O he/O accepted/O a/O bowl/O of/O stew/O and/O a/O heel/O of/O black/O bread/O from/O the/O day/O 's/O cooks/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON and/O Toad/PERSON and/O some/O of/O the/O others/O were/O seated/O at/O the/O bench/O nearest/O the/O warmth/O ,/O laughing/O and/O cursing/O each/O other/O in/O rough/O voices/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON eyed/O them/O thoughtfully/O for/O a/O moment/O ./O 
Then/O he/O chose/O a/O spot/O at/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O hall/O ,/O well/O away/O from/O the/O other/O diners/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON sat/O across/O from/O him/O ,/O sniffing/O at/O the/O stew/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Barley/O ,/O onion/O ,/O carrot/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Someone/O should/O tell/O the/O cooks/O that/O turnip/O is/O n't/O a/O meat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O mutton/O stew/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON pulled/O off/O his/O gloves/O and/O warmed/O his/O hands/O in/O the/O steam/O rising/O from/O the/O bowl/O ./O 
The/O smell/O made/O his/O mouth/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON knew/O Alliser/PERSON Thome/PERSON 's/O voice/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O a/O curious/O note/O in/O it/O that/O he/O had/O not/O heard/O before/O ./O 
He/O turned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O wants/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
Now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Jon/PERSON was/O too/O frightened/O to/O move/O ./O 
Why/O would/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O want/O to/O see/O him/O ?/O 
They/O had/O heard/O something/O about/O Benjen/PERSON ,/O he/O thought/O wildly/O ,/O he/O was/O dead/O ,/O the/O vision/O had/O come/O true/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O my/O uncle/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O blurted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O he/O returned/O safe/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O is/O not/O accustomed/O to/O waiting/O ,/O \/O ''/O was/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O reply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O I/O am/O not/O accustomed/O to/O having/O my/O commands/O questioned/O by/O bastards/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O swung/O off/O the/O bench/O and/O rose/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O it/O ,/O Thorne/PERSON ./O 
You/O 're/O frightening/O the/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Keep/O out/O of/O matters/O that/O do/O n't/O concern/O you/O ,/O Lannister/LOCATION ./O 
You/O have/O no/O place/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O a/O place/O at/O court/O ,/O though/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O word/O in/O the/O right/O ear/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O die/O a/O sour/O old/O man/O before/O you/O get/O another/O boy/O to/O train/O ./O 
Now/O tell/O Snow/O why/O the/O Old/O Bear/O needs/O to/O see/O him/O ./O 
Is/O there/O news/O of/O his/O uncle/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O another/O matter/O entirely/O ./O 
A/O bird/O arrived/O this/O morning/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O with/O a/O message/O that/O concerns/O his/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O corrected/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O half/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON breathed/O ,/O scrambling/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Something/O 's/O happened/O to/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O laid/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O truly/O sorry/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON scarcely/O heard/O him/O ./O 
He/O brushed/O off/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O hand/O and/O strode/O across/O the/O hall/O ./O 
He/O was/O running/O by/O the/O time/O he/O hit/O the/O doors/O ./O 
He/O raced/O to/O the/O Commander/O 's/O Keep/O ,/O dashing/O through/O drifts/O of/O old/O snow/O ./O 
When/O the/O guards/O passed/O him/O ,/O he/O took/O the/O tower/O steps/O two/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O he/O burst/O into/O the/O presence/O of/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O ,/O his/O boots/O were/O soaked/O and/O Jon/PERSON was/O wild-eyed/O and/O panting/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O does/O it/O say/O about/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jeor/O Mormont/O ,/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O was/O a/O gruff/O old/O man/O with/O an/O immense/O bald/O head/O and/O a/O shaggy/O grey/O beard/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O raven/O on/O his/O arm/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O feeding/O it/O kernels/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O told/O you/O can/O read/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O shook/O the/O raven/O off/O ,/O and/O it/O flapped/O its/O wings/O and/O flew/O to/O the/O window/O ,/O where/O it/O sat/O watching/O as/O Mormont/PERSON drew/O a/O roll/O of/O paper/O from/O his/O belt/O and/O handed/O it/O to/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Com/O ,/O \/O ''/O it/O muttered/O in/O a/O raucous/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Com/O ,/O com/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O finger/O traced/O the/O outline/O of/O the/O direwolf/O in/O the/O white/O wax/O of/O the/O broken/O seat/O ./O 
He/O recognized/O Robb/PERSON 's/O hand/O ,/O but/O the/O letters/O seemed/O to/O blur/O and/O run/O as/O he/O tried/O to/O read/O them/O ./O 
He/O realized/O he/O was/O crying/O ./O 
And/O then/O ,/O through/O the/O tears/O ,/O he/O found/O the/O sense/O in/O the/O words/O ,/O and/O raised/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O woke/O up/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O gave/O him/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Crippled/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sorry/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
Read/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O looked/O at/O the/O words/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O n't/O matter/O ./O 
Nothing/O mattered/O ./O 
Bran/O was/O going/O to/O live/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O is/O going/O to/O live/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
The/O Lord/O Commander/O shook/O his/O head/O ,/O gathered/O up/O a/O fistful/O of/O corn/O ,/O and/O whistled/O ./O 
The/O raven/O flew/O to/O his/O shoulder/O ,/O crying/O ,/O \/O ``/O Live/O !/O 
Live/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ran/O down/O the/O stairs/O ,/O a/O smile/O on/O his/O face/O and/O Robb/PERSON 's/O letter/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O is/O going/O to/O live/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O guards/O ./O 
They/O exchanged/O a/O look/O ./O 
He/O ran/O back/O to/O the/O common/O hall/O ,/O where/O he/O found/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON just/O finishing/O his/O meal/O ./O 
He/O grabbed/O the/O little/O man/O under/O the/O arms/O ,/O hoisted/O him/O up/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O and/O spun/O him/O around/O in/O a/O circle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O is/O going/O to/O live/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O whooped/O ./O 
Lannister/O looked/O startled/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON put/O him/O down/O and/O thrust/O the/O paper/O into/O his/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ,/O read/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Others/O were/O gathering/O around/O and/O looking/O at/O him/O curiously/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON noticed/O Grenn/PERSON a/O few/O feet/O away/O ./O 
A/O thick/O woolen/O bandage/O was/O wrapped/O around/O one/O hand/O ./O 
He/O looked/O anxious/O and/O uncomfortable/O ,/O not/O menacing/O at/O all/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON went/O to/O him/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON edged/O backward/O and/O put/O up/O his/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stay/O away/O from/O me/O now/O ,/O you/O bastard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON smiled/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sorry/O about/O your/O wrist/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON used/O the/O same/O move/O on/O me/O once/O ,/O only/O with/O a/O wooden/O blade/O ./O 
It/O hurt/O like/O seven/O hells/O ,/O but/O yours/O must/O be/O worse/O ./O 
Look/O ,/O if/O you/O want/O ,/O I/O can/O show/O you/O how/O to/O defend/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON overheard/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Snow/O wants/O to/O take/O my/O place/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sneered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O have/O an/O easier/O time/O teaching/O a/O wolf/O to/O juggle/O than/O you/O will/O training/O this/O aurochs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O take/O that/O wager/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O love/O to/O see/O Ghost/O juggle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON heard/O Grenn/PERSON suck/O in/O his/O breath/O ,/O shocked/O ./O 
Silence/O fell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O guffawed/O ./O 
Three/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON black/PERSON brothers/O joined/O in/O from/O a/O nearby/O table/O ./O 
The/O laughter/O spread/O up/O and/O down/O the/O benches/O ,/O until/O even/O the/O cooks/O joined/O in/O ./O 
The/O birds/O stirred/O in/O the/O rafters/O ,/O and/O finally/O even/O Grenn/PERSON began/O to/O chuckle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Alliser/O never/O took/O his/O eyes/O from/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
As/O the/O laughter/O rolled/O around/O him/O ,/O his/O face/O darkened/O ,/O and/O his/O sword/O hand/O curled/O into/O a/O fist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O a/O grievous/O error/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O last/O in/O the/O acid/O tones/O of/O an/O enemy/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
