-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O want/O eat/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mord/PERSON asked/O ,/O glowering/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O plate/O of/O oiled/O beans/O in/O one/O thick/O ,/O stub/O -/O fingered/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O was/O starved/O ,/O but/O he/O refused/O to/O let/O this/O brute/O see/O him/O cringe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O leg/O of/O lamb/O would/O be/O pleasant/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O from/O the/O heap/O of/O soiled/O straw/O in/O the/O corner/O of/O his/O cell/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O a/O dish/O of/O peas/O and/O onions/O ,/O some/O fresh/O baked/O bread/O with/O butter/O ,/O and/O a/O flagon/O of/O mulled/O wine/O to/O wash/O it/O down/O ./O 
Or/O beer/O ,/O if/O that/O 's/O easier/O ./O 
I/O try/O not/O to/O be/O overly/O particular/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O beans/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mord/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O held/O out/O the/O plate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
The/O turnkey/O was/O twenty/O stone/O of/O gross/O stupidity/O ,/O with/O brown/O rotting/O teeth/O and/O small/O dark/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O left/O side/O of/O his/O face/O was/O slick/O with/O scar/O where/O an/O axe/O had/O cut/O off/O his/O ear/O and/O part/O of/O his/O cheek/O ./O 
He/O was/O as/O predictable/O as/O he/O was/O ugly/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O hungry/O ./O 
He/O reached/O up/O for/O the/O plate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON jerked/O it/O away/O ,/O grinning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O holding/O it/O out/O beyond/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O reach/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O climbed/O stiffly/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O every/O joint/O aching/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Must/O we/O play/O the/O same/O fool/O 's/O game/O with/O every/O meal/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O made/O another/O grab/O for/O the/O beans/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON shambled/O backward/O ,/O grinning/O through/O his/O rotten/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O here/O ,/O dwarf/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O held/O the/O plate/O out/O at/O arm/O 's/O length/O ,/O over/O the/O edge/O where/O the/O cell/O ended/O and/O the/O sky/O began/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O not/O want/O eat/O ?/O 
Here/O ./O 
Come/O take/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O 's/O arms/O were/O too/O short/O to/O reach/O the/O plate/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O not/O about/O to/O step/O that/O close/O to/O the/O edge/O ./O 
All/O it/O would/O take/O would/O be/O a/O quick/O shove/O of/O Mord/PERSON 's/O heavy/O white/O belly/O ,/O and/O he/O would/O end/O up/O a/O sickening/O red/O splotch/O on/O the/O stones/O of/O Sky/O ,/O like/O so/O many/O other/O prisoners/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O over/O the/O centuries/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O to/O think/O on/O it/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O hungry/O after/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O declared/O ,/O retreating/O to/O the/O corner/O of/O his/O cell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON grunted/O and/O opened/O his/O thick/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O wind/O took/O the/O plate/O ,/O flipping/O it/O over/O as/O it/O fell/O ./O 
A/O handful/O of/O beans/O sprayed/O back/O at/O them/O as/O the/O food/O tumbled/O out/O of/O sight/O ./O 
The/O turnkey/O laughed/O ,/O his/O gut/O shaking/O like/O a/O bowl/O of/O pudding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O felt/O a/O pang/O of/O rage/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O fucking/O son/O of/O a/O pox-ridden/O ass/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O spat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O you/O die/O of/O a/O bloody/O flux/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O that/O ,/O Mord/PERSON gave/O him/O a/O kick/O ,/O driving/O a/O steel-toed/O boot/O hard/O into/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O ribs/O on/O the/O way/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O take/O it/O back/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O gasped/O as/O he/O doubled/O over/O on/O the/O straw/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O kill/O you/O myself/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O heavy/O ironbound/O door/O slammed/O shut/O ./O 
Tyrion/O heard/O the/O rattle/O of/O keys/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O a/O small/O man/O ,/O he/O had/O been/O cursed/O with/O a/O dangerously/O big/O mouth/O ,/O he/O reflected/O as/O he/O crawled/O back/O to/O his/O corner/O of/O what/O the/O Arryns/O laughably/O called/O their/O dungeon/O ./O 
He/O huddled/O beneath/O the/O thin/O blanket/O that/O was/O his/O only/O bedding/O ,/O staring/O out/O at/O a/O blaze/O of/O empty/O blue/O sky/O and/O distant/O mountains/O that/O seemed/O to/O go/O on/O forever/O ,/O wishing/O he/O still/O had/O the/O shadowskin/O cloak/O he/O 'd/O won/O from/O Marillion/O at/O dice/O ,/O after/O the/O singer/O had/O stolen/O it/O off/O the/O body/O of/O that/O brigand/O chief/O ./O 
The/O skin/O had/O smelled/O of/O blood/O and/O mold/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O warm/O and/O thick/O ./O 
Mord/PERSON had/O taken/O it/O the/O moment/O he/O laid/O eyes/O on/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O wind/O tugged/O at/O his/O blanket/O with/O gusts/O sharp/O as/O talons/O ./O 
His/O cell/O was/O miserably/O small/O ,/O even/O for/O a/O dwarf/O ./O 
Not/O five/O feet/O away/O ,/O where/O a/O wall/O ought/O to/O have/O been/O ,/O where/O a/O wall/O would/O be/O in/O a/O proper/O dungeon/O ,/O the/O floor/O ended/O and/O the/O sky/O began/O ./O 
He/O had/O plenty/O of/O fresh/O air/O and/O sunshine/O ,/O and/O the/O moon/O and/O stars/O by/O night/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON would/O have/O traded/O it/O all/O in/O an/O instant/O for/O the/O dankest/O ,/O gloomiest/O pit/O in/O the/O bowels/O of/O the/O easterly/O Rock/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O fly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mord/PERSON had/O promised/O him/O ,/O when/O he/O 'd/O shoved/O him/O into/O the/O cell/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Twenty/O day/O ,/O thirty/O ,/O fifty/O maybe/O ./O 
Then/O you/O fly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Arryns/O kept/O the/O only/O dungeon/O in/O the/O realm/O where/O the/O prisoners/O were/O welcome/O to/O escape/O at/O will/O ./O 
That/O first/O day/O ,/O after/O girding/O up/O his/O courage/O for/O hours/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O lain/O flat/O on/O his/O stomach/O and/O squirmed/O to/O the/O edge/O ,/O to/O poke/O out/O his/O head/O and/O look/O down/O ./O 
Sky/O was/O six/O hundred/O feet/O below/O ,/O with/O nothing/O between/O but/O empty/O air/O ./O 
If/O he/O craned/O his/O neck/O out/O as/O far/O as/O it/O could/O go/O ,/O he/O could/O see/O other/O cells/O to/O his/O right/O and/O left/O and/O above/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O bee/O in/O a/O stone/O honeycomb/O ,/O and/O someone/O had/O torn/O off/O his/O wings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O cold/O in/O the/O cell/O ,/O the/O wind/O screamed/O night/O and/O day/O ,/O and/O worst/O of/O all/O ,/O the/O floor/O sloped/O ./O 
Ever/O so/O slightly/O ,/O yet/O it/O was/O enough/O ./O 
He/O was/O afraid/O to/O close/O his/O eyes/O ,/O afraid/O that/O he/O might/O roll/O over/O in/O his/O steep/O and/O wake/O in/O sudden/O terror/O as/O he/O went/O sliding/O off/O the/O edge/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O the/O sky/O cells/O drove/O men/O mad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Gods/O save/O me/O ,/O some/O previous/O tenant/O had/O written/O on/O the/O wall/O in/O something/O that/O looked/O suspiciously/O like/O blood/O ,/O the/O blue/O is/O calling/O ./O 
At/O first/O Tyrion/O wondered/O who/O he/O 'd/O been/O ,/O and/O what/O had/O become/O of/O him/O ;/O later/O ,/O he/O decided/O that/O he/O would/O rather/O not/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O only/O he/O had/O shut/O his/O mouth/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wretched/O boy/O had/O started/O it/O ,/O looking/O down/O on/O him/O from/O a/O throne/O of/O carved/O weirwood/O beneath/O the/O moon/O -/O and/O -/O falcon/O banners/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Arryn/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O been/O looked/O down/O on/O all/O his/O life/O ,/O but/O seldom/O by/O rheumy-eyed/O six/O -/O year-olds/O who/O needed/O to/O stuff/O fat/O cushions/O under/O their/O cheeks/O to/O lift/O them/O to/O the/O height/O of/O a/O man/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O he/O the/O bad/O man/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O boy/O had/O asked/O ,/O clutching/O his/O doll/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON had/O said/O from/O the/O lesser/O throne/O beside/O him/O ./O 
She/O was/O all/O in/O blue/O ,/O powdered/O and/O perfumed/O for/O the/O suitors/O who/O filled/O her/O court/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O so/O small/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON said/O ,/O giggling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O Tyrion/O the/O Imp/O ,/O of/O House/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O who/O murdered/O your/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O raised/O her/O voice/O so/O it/O carried/O down/O the/O length/O of/O High/O Hall/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O ringing/O off/O the/O milk-white/O walls/O and/O the/O slender/O pillars/O ,/O so/O every/O man/O could/O hear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O slew/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O did/O I/O kill/O him/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O said/O ,/O like/O a/O fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O would/O have/O been/O a/O very/O good/O time/O to/O have/O kept/O his/O mouth/O closed/O and/O his/O head/O bowed/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O that/O now/O ;/O seven/O hells/O ,/O he/O had/O seen/O it/O then/O ./O 
The/O High/O Hall/O of/O the/O Arryns/O was/O long/O and/O austere/O ,/O with/O a/O forbidding/O coldness/O to/O its/O walls/O of/O blue-veined/O white/O marble/O ,/O but/O the/O faces/O around/O him/O had/O been/O colder/O by/O far/O ./O 
The/O power/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION was/O far/O away/O ,/O and/O there/O were/O no/O friends/O of/O the/O Lannisters/O in/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Submission/O and/O silence/O would/O have/O been/O his/O best/O defenses/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O mood/O had/O been/O too/O foul/O for/O sense/O ./O 
To/O his/O shame/O ,/O he/O had/O faltered/O during/O the/O last/O leg/O of/O their/O day-long/O climb/O up/O to/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON ,/O his/O stunted/O legs/O unable/O to/O take/O him/O any/O higher/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON had/O carried/O him/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O the/O humiliation/O poured/O oil/O on/O the/O flames/O of/O his/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O I/O 've/O been/O a/O busy/O little/O fellow/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O with/O bitter/O sarcasm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O when/O I/O found/O the/O time/O to/O do/O all/O this/O slaying/O and/O murdering/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O ought/O to/O have/O remembered/O who/O he/O was/O dealing/O with/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON and/O her/O half-sane/O weakling/O son/O had/O not/O been/O known/O at/O court/O for/O their/O love/O of/O wit/O ,/O especially/O when/O it/O was/O directed/O at/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Imp/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON said/O coldly/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O will/O guard/O that/O mocking/O tongue/O of/O yours/O and/O speak/O to/O my/O son/O politely/O ,/O or/O I/O promise/O you/O will/O have/O cause/O to/O regret/O it/O ./O 
Remember/O where/O you/O are/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O and/O these/O are/O knights/O of/O the/O Vale/O you/O see/O around/O you/O ,/O true/O men/O who/O loved/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON well/O ./O 
Every/O one/O of/O them/O would/O die/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Arryn/PERSON ,/O should/O any/O harm/O come/O to/O me/O ,/O my/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON will/O be/O pleased/O to/O see/O that/O they/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Even/O as/O he/O spat/O out/O the/O words/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON knew/O they/O were/O folly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O you/O fly/O ,/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O a/O dwarf/O have/O wings/O ?/O 
If/O not/O ,/O you/O would/O be/O wiser/O to/O swallow/O the/O next/O threat/O that/O comes/O to/O mind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O made/O no/O threats/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O a/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Little/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON hopped/O to/O his/O feet/O at/O that/O ,/O so/O upset/O he/O dropped/O his/O doll/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O hurt/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O can/O hurt/O us/O here/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O tell/O him/O he/O ca/O n't/O hurt/O us/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O boy/O began/O to/O twitch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Eyrie/O is/O impregnable/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON declared/O calmly/O ./O 
She/O drew/O her/O son/O close/O ,/O holding/O him/O safe/O in/O the/O circle/O of/O her/O plump/O white/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Imp/O is/O trying/O to/O frighten/O us/O ,/O sweet/O baby/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O are/O all/O liars/O ./O 
No/O one/O will/O hurt/O my/O sweet/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O hell/O of/O it/O was/O ,/O she/O was/O no/O doubt/O right/O ./O 
Having/O seen/O what/O it/O took/O to/O get/O here/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O well/O imagine/O how/O it/O would/O be/O for/O a/O knight/O trying/O to/O fight/O his/O way/O up/O in/O armor/O ,/O while/O stones/O and/O arrows/O poured/O down/O from/O above/O and/O enemies/O contested/O with/O him/O for/O every/O step/O ./O 
Nightmare/O did/O not/O begin/O to/O describe/O it/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON had/O never/O been/O taken/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Still/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O been/O unable/O to/O silence/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O impregnable/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O merely/O inconvenient/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Young/O Robert/PERSON pointed/O down/O ,/O his/O hand/O trembling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O a/O liar/O ./O 
Mother/O ,/O I/O want/O to/O see/O him/O fly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Two/O guardsmen/O in/O sky-blue/O cloaks/O seized/O Tyrion/O by/O the/O arms/O ,/O lifting/O him/O off/O his/O floor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O gods/O only/O know/O what/O might/O have/O happened/O then/O were/O it/O not/O for/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sister/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O from/O where/O she/O stood/O below/O the/O thrones/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O beg/O you/O to/O remember/O ,/O this/O man/O is/O my/O prisoner/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O have/O him/O harmed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON glanced/O at/O her/O sister/O coolly/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O then/O rose/O and/O swept/O down/O on/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O her/O long/O skirts/O trailing/O after/O her/O ./O 
For/O an/O instant/O he/O feared/O she/O would/O strike/O him/O ,/O but/O instead/O she/O commanded/O them/O to/O release/O him/O ./O 
Her/O men/O shoved/O him/O to/O the/O floor/O ,/O his/O legs/O went/O out/O from/O under/O him/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/O fell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O must/O have/O made/O quite/O a/O sight/O as/O he/O struggled/O to/O his/O knees/O ,/O only/O to/O feel/O his/O right/O leg/O spasm/O ,/O sending/O him/O sprawling/O once/O more/O ./O 
Laughter/O boomed/O up/O and/O down/O the/O High/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION of/O the/O Arryns/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O sister/O 's/O little/O guest/O is/O too/O weary/O to/O stand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O ,/O take/O him/O down/O to/O the/O dungeon/O ./O 
A/O rest/O in/O one/O of/O our/O sky/O cells/O will/O do/O him/O much/O good/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O guardsmen/O jerked/O him/O upright/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O dangled/O between/O them/O ,/O kicking/O feebly/O ,/O his/O face/O red/O with/O shame/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O remember/O this/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O them/O all/O as/O they/O carried/O him/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O so/O he/O did/O ,/O for/O all/O the/O good/O it/O did/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O first/O he/O had/O consoled/O himself/O that/O this/O imprisonment/O could/O not/O last/O long/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON wanted/O to/O humble/O him/O ,/O that/O was/O all/O ./O 
She/O would/O send/O for/O him/O again/O ,/O and/O soon/O ./O 
If/O not/O her/O ,/O then/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON would/O want/O to/O question/O him/O ./O 
This/O time/O he/O would/O guard/O his/O tongue/O more/O closely/O ./O 
They/O dare/O not/O kill/O him/O out/O of/O hand/O ;/O he/O was/O still/O a/O Lannister/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O if/O they/O shed/O his/O blood/O ,/O it/O would/O mean/O war/O ./O 
Or/O so/O he/O had/O told/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O he/O was/O not/O so/O certain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Perhaps/O his/O captors/O only/O meant/O to/O let/O him/O rot/O here/O ,/O but/O he/O feared/O he/O did/O not/O have/O the/O strength/O to/O rot/O for/O long/O ./O 
He/O was/O growing/O weaker/O every/O day/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O only/O a/O matter/O of/O time/O until/O Mord/PERSON 's/O kicks/O and/O blows/O did/O him/O serious/O harm/O ,/O provided/O the/O gaoler/O did/O not/O starve/O him/O to/O death/O first/O ./O 
A/O few/O more/O nights/O of/O cold/O and/O hunger/O ,/O and/O the/O blue/O would/O start/O calling/O to/O him/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wondered/O what/O was/O happening/O beyond/O the/O walls/O -LRB-/O such/O as/O they/O were/O -RRB-/O of/O his/O cell/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON would/O surely/O have/O sent/O out/O riders/O when/O the/O word/O reached/O him/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON might/O be/O leading/O a/O host/O through/O the/O Mountains/O of/O the/O Moon/O even/O now/O .../O unless/O he/O was/O riding/O north/O against/O Winterfell/O instead/O ./O 
Did/O anyone/O outside/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION even/O suspect/O where/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O taken/O him/O ?/O 
He/O wondered/O what/O Cersei/PERSON would/O do/O when/O she/O heard/O ./O 
The/O king/O could/O order/O him/O freed/O ,/O but/O would/O Robert/PERSON listen/O to/O his/O queen/O or/O his/O Hand/O ?/O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O no/O illusions/O about/O the/O king/O 's/O love/O for/O his/O sister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O Cersei/PERSON kept/O her/O wits/O about/O her/O ,/O she/O would/O insist/O the/O king/O sit/O in/O judgment/O of/O Tyrion/O himself/O ./O 
Even/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON could/O scarcely/O object/O to/O that/O ,/O not/O without/O impugning/O the/O honor/O of/O the/O king/O ./O 
And/O Tyrion/PERSON would/O be/O only/O too/O glad/O to/O take/O his/O chances/O in/O a/O trial/O ./O 
Whatever/O murders/O they/O might/O lay/O at/O his/O door/O ,/O the/O Starks/PERSON had/O no/O proof/O of/O anything/O so/O far/O as/O he/O could/O see/O ./O 
Let/O them/O make/O their/O case/O before/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O and/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O land/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O the/O end/O of/O them/O ./O 
If/O only/O Cersei/O were/O clever/O enough/O to/O see/O that/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O sighed/O ./O 
His/O sister/O was/O not/O without/O a/O certain/O low/O cunning/O ,/O but/O her/O pride/O blinded/O her/O ./O 
She/O would/O see/O the/O insult/O in/O this/O ,/O not/O the/O opportunity/O ./O 
And/O Jaime/PERSON was/O even/O worse/O ,/O rash/O and/O headstrong/O and/O quick/O to/O anger/O ./O 
His/O brother/O never/O untied/O a/O knot/O when/O he/O could/O slash/O it/O in/O two/O with/O his/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wondered/O which/O of/O them/O had/O sent/O the/O footpad/O to/O silence/O the/O Stark/O boy/O ,/O and/O whether/O they/O had/O truly/O conspired/O at/O the/O death/O of/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON ./O 
If/O the/O old/O Hand/O had/O been/O murdered/O ,/O it/O was/O deftly/O and/O subtly/O done/O ./O 
Men/O of/O his/O age/O died/O of/O sudden/O illness/O all/O the/O time/O ./O 
In/O contrast/O ,/O sending/O some/O oaf/O with/O a/O stolen/O knife/O after/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON struck/O him/O as/O unbelievably/O clumsy/O ./O 
And/O was/O n't/O that/O peculiar/O ,/O come/O to/O think/O on/O it/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O shivered/O ./O 
Now/O there/O was/O a/O nasty/O suspicion/O ./O 
Perhaps/O the/O direwolf/O and/O the/O lion/O were/O not/O the/O only/O beasts/O in/O the/O woods/O ,/O and/O if/O that/O was/O true/O ,/O someone/O was/O using/O him/O as/O a/O catspaw/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O hated/O being/O used/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O would/O have/O to/O get/O out/O of/O here/O ,/O and/O soon/O ./O 
His/O chances/O of/O overpowering/O Mord/O were/O small/O to/O none/O ,/O and/O no/O one/O was/O about/O to/O smuggle/O him/O a/O six-hundred-foot-long/O rope/O ,/O so/O he/O would/O have/O to/O talk/O himself/O free/O ./O 
His/O mouth/O had/O gotten/O him/O into/O this/O cell/O ;/O it/O could/O damn/O well/O get/O him/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON pushed/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O doing/O his/O best/O to/O ignore/O the/O slope/O of/O the/O floor/O beneath/O him/O ,/O with/O its/O ever-so-subtle/O tug/O toward/O the/O edge/O ./O 
He/O hammered/O on/O the/O door/O with/O a/O fist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mord/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Turnkey/O !/O 
Mord/O ,/O I/O want/O you/O !/O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O to/O keep/O it/O up/O a/O good/O ten/O minutes/O before/O he/O heard/O footsteps/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON stepped/O back/O an/O instant/O before/O the/O door/O opened/O with/O a/O crash/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Making/O noise/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mord/PERSON growled/O ,/O with/O blood/O in/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Dangling/O from/O one/O meaty/O hand/O was/O a/O leather/O strap/O ,/O wide/O and/O thick/O ,/O doubled/O over/O in/O his/O fist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Never/O show/O them/O You/O 're/O afraid/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON reminded/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O would/O you/O like/O to/O be/O rich/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/O hit/O him/O ./O 
He/O swung/O the/O strap/O backhand/O ,/O lazily/O ,/O but/O the/O leather/O caught/O Tyrion/LOCATION high/O on/O the/O arm/O ./O 
The/O force/O of/O it/O staggered/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O pain/O made/O him/O grit/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O mouth/O ,/O dwarf/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mord/PERSON warned/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gold/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O miming/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION is/O full/O of/O gold/O .../O ahhhh/O .../O \/O ''/O This/O time/O the/O blow/O was/O a/O forehand/O ,/O and/O Mord/PERSON put/O more/O of/O his/O arm/O into/O the/O swing/O ,/O making/O the/O leather/O crack/O and/O jump/O ./O 
It/O caught/O Tyrion/O in/O the/O ribs/O and/O dropped/O him/O to/O his/O knees/O ,/O wimpering/O ./O 
He/O forced/O himself/O to/O look/O up/O at/O the/O gaoler/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O rich/O as/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O wheezed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O what/O they/O say/O ,/O Mord/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON grunted/O ./O 
The/O strap/O whistled/O through/O the/O air/O and/O smashed/O Tyrion/LOCATION full/O in/O the/O face/O ./O 
The/O pain/O was/O so/O bad/O he/O did/O not/O remember/O falling/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O opened/O his/O eyes/O again/O he/O was/O on/O the/O floor/O of/O his/O cell/O ./O 
His/O ear/O was/O ringing/O ,/O and/O his/O mouth/O was/O full/O of/O blood/O ./O 
He/O groped/O for/O purchase/O ,/O to/O push/O himself/O up/O ,/O and/O his/O fingers/O brushed/O against/O .../O nothing/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON snatched/O his/O hand/O back/O as/O fast/O as/O if/O it/O had/O been/O scalded/O ,/O and/O tried/O his/O best/O to/O stop/O breathing/O ./O 
He/O had/O fallen/O right/O on/O the/O edge/O ,/O inches/O from/O the/O blue/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O More/O to/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mord/PERSON held/O the/O strap/O between/O his/O fists/O and/O gave/O it/O a/O sharp/O pull/O ./O 
The/O snap/O made/O Tyrion/O jump/O ./O 
The/O turnkey/O laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wo/O n't/O push/O me/O over/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O himself/O desperately/O as/O he/O crawled/O away/O from/O the/O edge/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON wants/O me/O alive/O ,/O he/O does/O n't/O dare/O kill/O me/O ./O 
He/O wiped/O the/O blood/O off/O his/O lips/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ,/O grinned/O ,/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O That/O was/O a/O stiff/O one/O ,/O Mord/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O gaoler/O squinted/O at/O him/O ,/O trying/O to/O decide/O if/O he/O was/O being/O mocked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O could/O make/O good/O use/O of/O a/O strong/O man/O like/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O strap/O flew/O at/O him/O ,/O but/O this/O time/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O able/O to/O cringe/O away/O from/O it/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O glancing/O blow/O to/O the/O shoulder/O ,/O nothing/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gold/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O repeated/O ,/O scrambling/O backward/O like/O a/O crab/O ,/O ,/O `/O more/O gold/O than/O you/O 'll/O see/O here/O in/O a/O lifetime/O ./O 
Enough/O to/O buy/O land/O ,/O women/O ,/O horses/O .../O you/O could/O be/O a/O lord/O ./O 
Lord/O Mord/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON hawked/O up/O a/O glob/O of/O blood/O and/O phlegm/O and/O spat/O it/O out/O into/O the/O sky/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O no/O gold/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mord/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O 's/O listening/O !/O 
Tyrion/O thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O relieved/O me/O of/O my/O purse/O when/O they/O captured/O me/O ,/O but/O the/O gold/O is/O still/O mine/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON might/O take/O a/O man/O prisoner/O ,/O but/O she/O 'd/O never/O stoop/O to/O rob/O him/O ./O 
That/O would/O n't/O be/O honorable/O ./O 
Help/O me/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O gold/O is/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mord/PERSON 's/O strap/O licked/O out/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O a/O halfhearted/O ,/O desultory/O swing/O ,/O slow/O and/O contemptuous/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON caught/O the/O leather/O in/O his/O hand/O and/O held/O it/O prisoned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O will/O be/O no/O risk/O to/O you/O ./O 
All/O you/O need/O do/O is/O deliver/O a/O message/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O gaoler/O yanked/O his/O leather/O strap/O free/O of/O Tyrion/O 's/O grasp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Message/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O never/O heard/O the/O word/O before/O ./O 
His/O frown/O made/O deep/O creases/O in/O his/O brow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O heard/O me/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Only/O carry/O my/O word/O to/O your/O lady/O ./O 
Tell/O her/O .../O \/O ''/O \/O ``/O at/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O at/O would/O possibly/O make/O Lysa/PERSON Anyn/PERSON relent/O ?/O 
The/O inspiration/O came/O to/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O suddenly/O ,/O tell/O her/O that/O I/O wish/O to/O confess/O my/O crimes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON raised/O his/O arm/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON braced/O himself/O for/O another/O blow/O ,/O but/O the/O turnkey/O hesitated/O ./O 
Suspicion/O and/O greed/O warred/O in/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O that/O gold/O ,/O yet/O he/O feared/O a/O trick/O ;/O he/O had/O the/O look/O of/O a/O man/O who/O had/O often/O been/O tricked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O lie/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O darkly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dwarf/O man/O cheat/O me/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O put/O my/O promise/O in/O writing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O vowed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Some/O illiterates/O held/O writing/O in/O disdain/O ;/O others/O seemed/O to/O have/O a/O superstitious/O reverence/O for/O the/O written/O word/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O were/O some/O sort/O of/O magic/O ./O 
Fortunately/O ,/O Mord/PERSON was/O one/O of/O the/O latter/O ./O 
The/O turnkey/O lowered/O the/O strap/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Writing/O down/O gold/O ./O 
Much/O gold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O much/O gold/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON assured/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O purse/O is/O just/O a/O taste/O ,/O my/O friend/O ./O 
My/O brother/O wears/O armor/O of/O solid/O gold/O plate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O In/O truth/O ,/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O armor/O was/O gilded/O steel/O ,/O but/O this/O oaf/O would/O never/O know/O the/O difference/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON fingered/O his/O strap/O thoughtfully/O ,/O but/O in/O the/O end/O ,/O he/O relented/O and/O went/O to/O fetch/O paper/O and/O ink/O ./O 
When/O the/O letter/O was/O written/O ,/O the/O gaoler/O frowned/O at/O it/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O deliver/O my/O message/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O urged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O shivering/O in/O his/O sleep/O when/O they/O came/O for/O him/O ,/O late/O that/O night/O ./O 
Mord/PERSON opened/O the/O door/O but/O kept/O his/O silence/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON woke/O Tyrion/PERSON with/O the/O point/O of/O his/O boot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O On/O your/O feet/O ,/O Imp/O ./O 
My/O lady/O wants/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O rubbed/O the/O sleep/O from/O his/O eyes/O and/O put/O on/O a/O grimace/O he/O scarcely/O felt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O doubt/O she/O does/O ,/O but/O what/O makes/O you/O think/O I/O wish/O to/O see/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O frowned/O ./O 
Tyrion/O remembered/O him/O well/O from/O the/O years/O he/O had/O spent/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O as/O the/O captain/O of/O the/O Hand/O 's/O household/O guard/O ./O 
A/O square/O ,/O plain/O face/O ,/O silver/O hair/O ,/O a/O heavy/O build/O ,/O and/O no/O humor/O whatsoever/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O wishes/O are/O not/O my/O concern/O ./O 
On/O your/O feet/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O have/O you/O carried/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O clambered/O awkwardly/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O cold/O night/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O casually/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O the/O High/O Hall/O is/O so/O drafty/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O wish/O to/O catch/O a/O chill/O ./O 
Mord/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O good/O ,/O fetch/O my/O cloak/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O gaoler/O squinted/O at/O him/O ,/O face/O dull/O with/O suspicion/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O cloak/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O repeated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O shadowskin/O you/O took/O from/O me/O for/O safekeeping/O ./O 
You/O recall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Get/O him/O the/O damnable/O cloak/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mord/PERSON did/O not/O dare/O grumble/O ./O 
He/O gave/O Tyrion/PERSON a/O glare/O that/O promised/O future/O retribution/O ,/O yet/O he/O went/O for/O the/O cloak/O ./O 
When/O he/O draped/O it/O around/O his/O prisoner/O 's/O neck/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O thanks/O ./O 
I/O shall/O think/O of/O you/O whenever/O I/O wear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O flung/O the/O trailing/O end/O of/O the/O long/O fur/O over/O his/O right/O shoulder/O ,/O and/O felt/O warm/O for/O the/O first/O time/O in/O days/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lead/O on/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O High/O Hall/O of/O the/O Arryns/O was/O aglow/O with/O the/O light/O of/O fifty/O torches/O ,/O burning/O in/O the/O sconces/O along/O the/O walls/O ./O 
The/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON wore/O black/O silk/O ,/O with/O the/O moon-and/O -/O falcon/O sewn/O on/O her/O breast/O in/O pearls/O ./O 
Since/O she/O did/O not/O look/O the/O sort/O to/O join/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O only/O imagine/O that/O she/O had/O decided/O mourning/O clothes/O were/O appropriate/O garb/O for/O a/O confession/O ./O 
Her/O long/O auburn/O hair/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O woven/O into/O an/O elaborate/O braid/O ,/O fell/O across/O her/O left/O shoulder/O ./O 
The/O taller/O throne/O beside/O her/O was/O empty/O ;/O no/O doubt/O the/O little/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O was/O off/O shaking/O in/O his/O sleep/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON was/O thankful/O for/O that/O much/O ,/O at/O least/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O bowed/O deeply/O and/O took/O a/O moment/O to/O glance/O around/O the/O hall/O ./O 
Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O summoned/O her/O knights/O and/O retainers/O to/O hear/O his/O confession/O ,/O as/O he/O had/O hoped/O ./O 
He/O saw/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON 's/O craggy/O face/O and/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON Royce/PERSON 's/O bluff/O one/O ./O 
Beside/O Nestor/PERSON stood/O a/O younger/O man/O with/O fierce/O black/O side/O -/O whiskers/O who/O could/O only/O be/O his/O heir/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Albar/PERSON ./O 
Most/O of/O the/O principal/O houses/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION were/O represented/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON noted/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON ,/O slender/O as/O a/O sword/O ,/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON with/O his/O gouty/O legs/O ,/O the/O widowed/O Lady/PERSON Waynwood/PERSON surrounded/O by/O her/O sons/O ./O 
Others/O sported/O sigils/O he/O did/O not/O know/O ;/O broken/O lance/O ,/O green/O viper/O ,/O burning/O tower/O ,/O winged/O chalice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Among/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION were/O several/O of/O his/O companions/O from/O the/O high/O road/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ,/O pale/O from/O half-healed/O wounds/O ,/O stood/O with/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON beside/O him/O ./O 
Marillion/O the/O singer/O had/O found/O a/O new/O woodharp/O ./O 
Tyrion/O smiled/O ;/O whatever/O happened/O here/O tonight/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O wish/O it/O to/O happen/O in/O secret/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O no/O one/O like/O a/O singer/O for/O spreading/O a/O story/O near/O and/O far/O ./O 
In/O the/O rear/O of/O the/O hall/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON lounged/O beneath/O a/O pillar/O ./O 
The/O freerider/O 's/O black/O eyes/O were/O fixed/O on/O Tyrion/O ,/O and/O his/O hand/O lay/O lightly/O on/O the/O pommel/O of/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Tyrion/O gave/O him/O a/O long/O look/O ,/O wondering/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O spoke/O first/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O wish/O to/O confess/O your/O crimes/O ,/O we/O are/O told/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON answered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON smiled/O at/O her/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sky/O cells/O always/O break/O them/O ./O 
The/O gods/O can/O see/O them/O there/O ,/O and/O there/O is/O no/O darkness/O to/O hide/O in/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O does/O not/O look/O broken/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON paid/O her/O no/O mind/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Say/O what/O you/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O Tyrion/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O now/O to/O roll/O the/O dice/O ,/O he/O thought/O with/O another/O quick/O glance/O back/O at/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O to/O begin/O ?/O 
I/O am/O a/O vile/O little/O man/O ,/O I/O confess/O it/O ./O 
My/O crimes/O and/O sins/O are/O beyond/O counting/O ,/O my/O lords/O and/O ladies/O ./O 
I/O have/O lain/O with/O whores/O ,/O not/O once/O but/O hundreds/O of/O times/O ./O 
I/O have/O wished/O my/O own/O lord/O father/O dead/O ,/O and/O my/O sister/O ,/O our/O gracious/O queen/O ,/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Behind/O him/O ,/O someone/O chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O always/O treated/O my/O servants/O with/O kindness/O ./O 
I/O have/O gambled/O ./O 
I/O have/O even/O cheated/O ,/O I/O blush/O to/O admit/O ./O 
I/O have/O said/O many/O cruel/O and/O malicious/O things/O about/O the/O noble/O lords/O and/O ladies/O of/O the/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O That/O drew/O outright/O laughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Once/O I/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Silence/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O pale/O round/O face/O had/O turned/O a/O burning/O pink/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O imagine/O you/O are/O doing/O ,/O dwarf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O cocked/O his/O head/O to/O one/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O confessing/O my/O crimes/O ,/O my/O lady/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O took/O a/O step/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O accused/O of/O sending/O a/O hired/O knife/O to/O slay/O my/O son/O Bran/O in/O his/O bed/O ,/O and/O of/O conspiring/O to/O murder/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O gave/O a/O helpless/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Those/O crimes/O I/O can/O not/O confess/O ,/O I/O fear/O ./O 
I/O know/O nothing/O of/O any/O murders/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON rose/O from/O her/O weirwood/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O be/O made/O mock/O of/O ./O 
You/O have/O had/O your/O little/O jape/O ,/O Imp/O ./O 
I/O trust/O you/O enjoyed/O it/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON ,/O take/O him/O back/O to/O the/O dungeon/O .../O but/O this/O time/O find/O him/O a/O smaller/O cell/O ,/O with/O a/O floor/O more/O sharply/O sloped/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O this/O how/O justice/O is/O done/O in/O the/O Vale/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON roared/O ,/O so/O loudly/O that/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON froze/O for/O an/O instant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O honor/O stop/O at/O the/O Bloody/LOCATION Gate/LOCATION ?/O 
You/O accuse/O me/O of/O crimes/O ,/O I/O deny/O them/O ,/O so/O you/O throw/O me/O into/O an/O open/O cell/O to/O freeze/O and/O starve/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O lifted/O his/O head/O ,/O to/O give/O them/O all/O a/O good/O look/O at/O the/O bruises/O Mord/PERSON had/O left/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O is/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ?/O 
Is/O the/O Eyrie/O not/O part/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ?/O 
I/O stand/O accused/O ,/O you/O say/O ./O 
Very/O well/O ./O 
I/O demand/O a/O trial/O !/O 
Let/O me/O speak/O ,/O and/O let/O my/O truth/O or/O falsehood/O be/O judged/O openly/O ,/O in/O the/O sight/O of/O gods/O and/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O low/O murmuring/O filled/O the/O High/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
He/O had/O her/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON knew/O ./O 
He/O was/O highborn/O ,/O the/O son/O of/O the/O most/O powerful/O lord/O in/O the/O realm/O ,/O the/O brother/O of/O the/O queen/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O be/O denied/O a/O trial/O ./O 
Guardsmen/O in/O sky-blue/O cloaks/O had/O started/O toward/O Tyrion/O ,/O but/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON bid/O them/O halt/O and/O looked/O to/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O small/O mouth/O twitched/O in/O a/O petulant/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O are/O tried/O and/O found/O to/O be/O guilty/O of/O the/O crimes/O for/O which/O you/O stand/O accused/O ,/O then/O by/O the/O king/O 's/O own/O laws/O ,/O you/O must/O pay/O with/O your/O life/O 's/O blood/O ./O 
We/O keep/O no/O headsman/O in/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O ./O 
Open/O the/O Moon/LOCATION Door/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O press/O of/O spectators/O parted/O ./O 
A/O narrow/O weirwood/O door/O stood/O between/O two/O slender/O marble/O pillars/O ,/O a/O crescent/O moon/O carved/O in/O the/O white/O wood/O ./O 
Those/O standing/O closest/O edged/O backward/O as/O a/O pair/O of/O guardsmen/O marched/O through/O ./O 
One/O man/O removed/O the/O heavy/O bronze/O bars/O ;/O the/O second/O pulled/O the/O door/O inward/O ./O 
Their/O blue/O cloaks/O rose/O snapping/O from/O their/O shoulders/O ,/O caught/O in/O the/O sudden/O gust/O of/O wind/O that/O came/O howling/O through/O the/O open/O door/O ./O 
Beyond/O was/O the/O emptiness/O of/O the/O night/O sky/O ,/O speckled/O with/O cold/O uncaring/O stars/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Behold/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON said/O ./O 
Torch/O flames/O fluttered/O like/O permons/O along/O the/O walls/O ,/O and/O here/O and/O there/O the/O odd/O torch/O guttered/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O I/O think/O this/O unwise/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O as/O the/O black/O wind/O swirled/O around/O the/O hall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O sister/O ignored/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O want/O a/O trial/O ,/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O ./O 
Very/O well/O ,/O a/O trial/O you/O shall/O have/O ./O 
My/O son/O will/O listen/O to/O whatever/O you/O care/O to/O say/O ,/O and/O you/O shall/O hear/O his/O judgment/O ./O 
Then/O you/O may/O leave/O .../O by/O one/O door/O or/O the/O other/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O looked/O so/O pleased/O with/O herself/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O and/O small/O wonder/O ./O 
How/O could/O a/O trial/O threaten/O her/O ,/O when/O her/O weakling/O son/O was/O the/O lord/O judge/O ?/O 
Tyrion/PERSON glanced/O at/O her/O Moon/LOCATION Door/LOCATION ./O 
Mother/O ,/O I/O want/O to/O see/O him/O fly/O !/O 
the/O boy/O had/O said/O ./O 
How/O many/O men/O had/O the/O snot-nosed/O little/O wretch/O sent/O through/O that/O door/O already/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O ,/O my/O good/O lady/O ,/O but/O I/O see/O no/O need/O to/O trouble/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O politely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O know/O the/O truth/O of/O my/O innocence/O ./O 
I/O will/O have/O their/O verdict/O ,/O not/O the/O judgment/O of/O men/O ./O 
I/O demand/O trial/O by/O combat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O storm/O of/O sudden/O laughter/O filled/O the/O High/O Hall/O of/O the/O Arryns/O ./O 
Lord/O Nestor/PERSON Royce/PERSON snorted/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON chuckled/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON guffawed/O ,/O and/O others/O threw/O back/O their/O heads/O and/O howled/O until/O tears/O ran/O down/O their/O faces/O ./O 
Marillion/PERSON clumsily/O plucked/O a/O gay/O note/O on/O his/O new/O woodharp/O with/O the/O fingers/O of/O his/O broken/O hand/O ./O 
Even/O the/O wind/O seemed/O to/O whistle/O with/O derision/O as/O it/O came/O skirling/O through/O the/O Moon/O Door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O watery/O blue/O eyes/O looked/O uncertain/O ./O 
He/O had/O caught/O her/O off/O balance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O that/O right/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O young/O knight/O with/O the/O green/O viper/O embroidered/O on/O his/O surcoat/O stepped/O forward/O and/O went/O to/O one/O knee/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O I/O beg/O the/O boon/O of/O championing/O your/O cause/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O honor/O should/O be/O mine/O ,/O \/O ''/O old/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O the/O love/O I/O bore/O your/O lord/O husband/O ,/O let/O me/O avenge/O his/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O father/O served/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON faithfully/O as/O High/O Steward/O of/O the/O Vale/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Albar/PERSON Royce/PERSON boomed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O serve/O his/O son/O in/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gods/O favor/O the/O man/O with/O the/O just/O cause/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O often/O that/O turns/O out/O to/O be/O the/O man/O with/O the/O surest/O sword/O ./O 
We/O all/O know/O who/O that/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O modestly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O dozen/O other/O men/O all/O spoke/O at/O once/O ,/O clamoring/O to/O be/O heard/O ./O 
Tyrion/O found/O it/O disheartening/O to/O realize/O so/O many/O strangers/O were/O eager/O to/O kill/O him/O ./O 
Perhaps/O this/O had/O not/O been/O such/O a/O clever/O plan/O after/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON raised/O a/O hand/O for/O silence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O as/O I/O know/O my/O son/O would/O thank/O you/O if/O he/O were/O among/O us/O ./O 
No/O men/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O are/O as/O bold/O and/O true/O as/O the/O knights/O of/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
Would/O that/O I/O could/O grant/O you/O all/O this/O honor/O ./O 
Yet/O I/O can/O choose/O only/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O gestured/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON ,/O you/O were/O ever/O my/O lord/O husband/O 's/O good/O right/O hand/O ./O 
You/O shall/O be/O our/O champion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O had/O been/O singularly/O silent/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O gravely/O ,/O sinking/O to/O one/O knee/O ,/O \/O ``/O pray/O give/O this/O burden/O to/O another/O ,/O I/O have/O no/O taste/O for/O it/O ./O 
The/O man/O is/O no/O warrior/O ./O 
Look/O at/O him/O ./O 
A/O dwarf/O ,/O half/O my/O size/O and/O lame/O in/O the/O legs/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O shameful/O to/O slaughter/O such/O a/O man/O and/O call/O it/O justice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O excellent/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O agree/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON glared/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O demanded/O a/O trial/O by/O combat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O now/O I/O demand/O a/O champion/O ,/O such/O as/O you/O have/O chosen/O for/O yourself/O ./O 
My/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON will/O gladly/O take/O my/O part/O ,/O I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O precious/O Kingslayer/O is/O hundreds/O of/O leagues/O from/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O snapped/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Send/O a/O bird/O for/O him/O ./O 
I/O will/O gladly/O await/O his/O arrival/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O face/O Ser/O Vardis/O on/O the/O morrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Singer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O turning/O to/O Marillion/LOCATION ,/O \/O ``/O when/O you/O make/O a/O ballad/O of/O this/O ,/O be/O certain/O you/O tell/O them/O how/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON denied/O the/O dwarf/O the/O right/O to/O a/O champion/O ,/O and/O sent/O him/O forth/O lame/O and/O bruised/O and/O hobbling/O to/O face/O her/O finest/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O deny/O you/O nothing/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON said/O ,/O her/O voice/O peeved/O and/O shrill/O with/O irritation/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Name/O your/O champion/O ,/O Imp/O .../O if/O you/O think/O you/O can/O find/O a/O man/O to/O die/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O it/O is/O all/O the/O same/O to/O you/O ,/O I/O 'd/O sooner/O find/O one/O to/O kill/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O looked/O over/O the/O long/O hall/O ./O 
No/O one/O moved/O ./O 
For/O a/O long/O moment/O he/O wondered/O if/O it/O had/O all/O been/O a/O colossal/O blunder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O there/O was/O a/O stirring/O in/O the/O rear/O of/O the/O chamber/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O stand/O for/O the/O dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON called/O out/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
