-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Somewhere/O in/O the/O great/O stone/O maze/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O a/O wolf/O howled/O ./O 
The/O sound/O hung/O over/O the/O castle/O like/O a/O flag/O of/O mourning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O looked/O up/O from/O his/O books/O and/O shivered/O ,/O though/O the/O library/O was/O snug/O and/O warm/O ./O 
Something/O about/O the/O howling/O of/O a/O wolf/O took/O a/O man/O right/O out/O of/O his/O here/O and/O now/O and/O left/O him/O in/O a/O dark/O forest/O of/O the/O mind/O ,/O running/O naked/O before/O the/O pack/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O direwo/O If/O howled/O again/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON shut/O the/O heavy/O leatherbound/O cover/O on/O the/O book/O he/O was/O reading/O ,/O a/O hundred/O year-old/O discourse/O on/O the/O changing/O of/O the/O seasons/O by/O a/O long-dead/O maester/O ./O 
He/O covered/O a/O yawn/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ./O 
His/O reading/O lamp/O was/O flickering/O ,/O its/O oil/O all/O but/O gone/O ,/O as/O dawn/O light/O leaked/O through/O the/O high/O windows/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O at/O it/O all/O night/O ,/O but/O that/O was/O nothing/O new/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O was/O not/O much/O a/O one/O for/O sleeping/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O legs/O were/O stiff/O and/O sore/O as/O he/O eased/O down/O off/O the/O bench/O ./O 
He/O massaged/O some/O life/O back/O into/O them/O and/O limped/O heavily/O to/O the/O table/O where/O the/O septon/O was/O snoring/O softly/O ,/O his/O head/O pillowed/O on/O an/O open/O book/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON glanced/O at/O the/O title/O ./O 
A/O life/O of/O the/O Grand/O Maester/O Aethelmure/O ,/O no/O wonder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Chayle/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O softly/O ./O 
The/O young/O man/O jerked/O up/O ,/O blinking/O ,/O confused/O ,/O the/O crystal/O of/O his/O order/O swinging/O wildly/O on/O its/O silver/O chain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O off/O to/O break/O my/O fast/O ./O 
See/O that/O you/O return/O the/O books/O to/O the/O shelves/O ./O 
Be/O gentle/O with/O the/O Valyrian/O scrolls/O ,/O the/O parchment/O is/O very/O dry/O ./O 
Ayrmidon/PERSON 's/O Engines/O of/O War/O is/O quite/O rare/O ,/O and/O yours/O is/O the/O only/O complete/O copy/O I/O 've/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Chayle/PERSON gaped/O at/O him/O ,/O still/O half/O asleep/O ./O 
Patiently/O ,/O Tyrion/O repeated/O his/O instructions/O ,/O then/O clapped/O the/O septon/O on/O the/O shoulder/O and/O left/O him/O to/O his/O tasks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON swallowed/O a/O lungful/O of/O the/O cold/O morning/O air/O and/O began/O his/O laborious/O descent/O of/O the/O steep/O stone/O steps/O that/O corkscrewed/O around/O the/O exterior/O of/O the/O library/O tower/O ./O 
It/O was/O slow/O going/O ;/O the/O steps/O were/O cut/O high/O and/O narrow/O ,/O while/O his/O legs/O were/O short/O and/O twisted/O ./O 
The/O rising/O sun/O had/O not/O yet/O cleared/O the/O walls/O of/O Winterfell/O ,/O but/O the/O men/O were/O already/O hard/O at/O it/O in/O the/O yard/O below/O ./O 
Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON 's/O rasping/O voice/O drifted/O up/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O is/O a/O long/O time/O dying/O ./O 
I/O wish/O he/O would/O be/O quicker/O about/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O glanced/O down/O and/O saw/O the/O Hound/O standing/O with/O young/O Joffrey/PERSON as/O squires/O swarmed/O around/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O least/O he/O dies/O quietly/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O prince/O replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O the/O wolf/O that/O makes/O the/O noise/O ./O 
I/O could/O scarce/O sleep/O last/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Clegane/O cast/O a/O long/O shadow/O across/O the/O hard-packed/O earth/O as/O his/O squire/O lowered/O the/O black/O helm/O over/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O could/O silence/O the/O creature/O ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O through/O his/O open/O visor/O ./O 
His/O boy/O placed/O a/O longsword/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
He/O tested/O the/O weight/O of/O it/O ,/O slicing/O at/O the/O cold/O morning/O air/O ./O 
Behind/O him/O ,/O the/O yard/O rang/O to/O the/O clangor/O of/O steel/O on/O steel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O notion/O seemed/O to/O delight/O the/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O a/O dog/O to/O kill/O a/O dog/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O exclaimed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Winterfell/O is/O so/O infested/O with/O wolves/O ,/O the/O Starks/PERSON would/O never/O miss/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O hopped/O off/O the/O last/O step/O onto/O the/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O beg/O to/O differ/O ,/O nephew/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Starks/PERSON can/O count/O past/O six/O ./O 
Unlike/O some/O princes/O I/O might/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON had/O the/O grace/O at/O least/O to/O blush/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O voice/O from/O nowhere/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sandor/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O peered/O through/O his/O helm/O ,/O looking/O this/O way/O and/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Spirits/O of/O the/O air/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O prince/O laughed/O ,/O as/O he/O always/O laughed/O when/O his/O bodyguard/O did/O this/O mummer/O 's/O farce/O ./O 
Tyrion/O was/O used/O to/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Down/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O tall/O man/O peered/O down/O at/O the/O ground/O ,/O and/O pretended/O to/O notice/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O little/O lord/O Tyrion/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O pardons/O ./O 
I/O did/O not/O see/O you/O standing/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O in/O no/O mood/O for/O your/O insolence/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON turned/O to/O his/O nephew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/O ,/O it/O is/O past/O time/O you/O called/O on/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON and/O his/O lady/O ,/O to/O offer/O them/O your/O comfort/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/O looked/O as/O petulant/O as/O only/O a/O boy/O prince/O can/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O good/O will/O my/O comfort/O do/O them/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O None/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O it/O is/O expected/O of/O you/O ./O 
Your/O absence/O has/O been/O noted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Stark/O boy/O is/O nothing/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O not/O abide/O the/O wailing/O of/O women/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O reached/O up/O and/O slapped/O his/O nephew/O hard/O across/O the/O face/O ./O 
The/O boy/O 's/O cheek/O began/O to/O redden/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O One/O word/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O will/O hit/O you/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O tell/O Mother/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON exclaimed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O hit/O him/O again/O ./O 
Now/O both/O cheeks/O flamed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O tell/O your/O mother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O first/O you/O get/O yourself/O to/O Lord/O and/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O fall/O to/O your/O knees/O in/O front/O of/O them/O ,/O and/O you/O tell/O them/O how/O very/O sorry/O you/O are/O ,/O and/O that/O you/O are/O at/O their/O service/O if/O there/O is/O the/O slightest/O thing/O you/O can/O do/O for/O them/O or/O theirs/O in/O this/O desperate/O hour/O ,/O and/O that/O all/O your/O prayers/O go/O with/O them/O ./O 
Do/O you/O understand/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O boy/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O was/O going/O to/O cry/O ./O 
Instead/O ,/O he/O managed/O a/O weak/O nod/O ./O 
Then/O he/O turned/O and/O fled/O headlong/O from/O the/O yard/O ,/O holding/O his/O cheek/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON watched/O him/O run/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O shadow/O fell/O across/O his/O face/O ./O 
He/O turned/O to/O find/O Clegane/PERSON looming/O overhead/O like/O a/O cliff/O ./O 
His/O soot-dark/O armor/O seemed/O to/O blot/O out/O the/O sun/O ./O 
He/O had/O lowered/O the/O visor/O on/O his/O helm/O ./O 
It/O was/O fashioned/O in/O the/O likeness/O of/O a/O snarling/O black/O hound/O ,/O fearsome/O to/O behold/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O always/O thought/O it/O a/O great/O improvement/O over/O Clegane/PERSON 's/O hideously/O burned/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O prince/O will/O remember/O that/O ,/O little/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Hound/O warned/O him/O ./O 
The/O helm/O turned/O his/O laugh/O into/O a/O hollow/O rumble/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O pray/O he/O does/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O he/O forgets/O ,/O be/O a/O good/O dog/O and/O remind/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O glanced/O around/O the/O courtyard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O know/O where/O I/O might/O find/O my/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Breaking/O fast/O with/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O gave/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON a/O perfunctory/O nod/O and/O walked/O away/O as/O briskly/O as/O his/O stunted/O legs/O would/O carry/O him/O ,/O whistling/O ./O 
He/O pitied/O the/O first/O knight/O to/O try/O the/O Hound/O today/O ./O 
The/O man/O did/O have/O a/O temper/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O cold/O ,/O cheerless/O meal/O had/O been/O laid/O out/O in/O the/O morning/O room/O of/O the/O Guest/LOCATION House/LOCATION ./O 
Jaime/PERSON sat/O at/O table/O with/O Cersei/PERSON and/O the/O children/O ,/O talking/O in/O low/O ,/O hushed/O voices/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O Robert/PERSON still/O abed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O as/O he/O seated/O himself/O ,/O uninvited/O ,/O at/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O sister/O peered/O at/O him/O with/O the/O same/O expression/O of/O faint/O distaste/O she/O had/O worn/O since/O the/O day/O he/O was/O born/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O has/O not/O slept/O at/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O with/O Lord/O Eddard/O ./O 
He/O has/O taken/O their/O sorrow/O deeply/O to/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O has/O a/O large/O heart/O ,/O our/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON said/O with/O a/O lazy/O smile/O ./O 
There/O was/O very/O little/O that/O Jaime/PERSON took/O seriously/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON knew/O that/O about/O his/O brother/O ,/O and/O forgave/O it/O ./O 
During/O all/O the/O terrible/O long/O years/O of/O his/O childhood/O ,/O only/O Jaime/PERSON had/O ever/O shown/O him/O the/O smallest/O measure/O of/O affection/O or/O respect/O ,/O and/O for/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O willing/O to/O forgive/O him/O most/O anything/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O servant/O approached/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bread/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O two/O of/O those/O little/O fish/O ,/O and/O a/O mug/O of/O that/O good/O dark/O beer/O to/O wash/O them/O down/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O and/O some/O bacon/O ./O 
Burn/O it/O until/O it/O turns/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O bowed/O and/O moved/O off/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O his/O siblings/O ./O 
Twins/O ,/O male/O and/O female/O ./O 
They/O looked/O very/O much/O the/O part/O this/O morning/O ./O 
Both/O had/O chosen/O a/O deep/O green/O that/O matched/O their/O eyes/O ./O 
Their/O blond/O curls/O were/O all/O a/O fashionable/O tumble/O ,/O and/O gold/O ornaments/O shone/O at/O wrists/O and/O fingers/O and/O throats/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O wondered/O what/O it/O would/O be/O like/O to/O have/O a/O twin/O ,/O and/O decided/O that/O he/O would/O rather/O not/O know/O ./O 
Bad/O enough/O to/O face/O himself/O in/O a/O looking/O glass/O every/O day/O ./O 
Another/O him/O was/O a/O thought/O too/O dreadful/O to/O contemplate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Prince/O Tommen/PERSON spoke/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O news/O of/O Bran/O ,/O Uncle/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O stopped/O by/O the/O sickroom/O last/O night/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O change/O ./O 
The/O maester/O thought/O that/O a/O hopeful/O sign/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O Brandon/PERSON to/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tommen/PERSON said/O timorously/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O sweet/O boy/O ./O 
Not/O like/O his/O brother/O ,/O but/O then/O Jaime/PERSON and/O Tyrion/LOCATION were/O somewhat/O less/O than/O peas/O in/O a/O pod/O themselves/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON had/O a/O brother/O named/O Brandon/PERSON as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON mused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O hostages/O murdered/O by/O Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
It/O seems/O to/O be/O an/O unlucky/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O not/O so/O unlucky/O as/O all/O that/O ,/O surely/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O servant/O brought/O his/O plate/O ./O 
He/O ripped/O off/O a/O chunk/O of/O black/O bread/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON was/O studying/O him/O warily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O mean/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O gave/O her/O a/O crooked/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O only/O that/O Tommen/PERSON may/O get/O his/O wish/O ./O 
The/O maester/O thinks/O the/O boy/O may/O yet/O live/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O a/O sip/O of/O beer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Myrcella/PERSON gave/O a/O happy/O gasp/O ,/O and/O Tommen/PERSON smiled/O nervously/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O not/O the/O children/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O watching/O ./O 
The/O glance/O that/O passed/O between/O Jaime/PERSON and/O Cersei/PERSON lasted/O no/O more/O than/O a/O second/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O miss/O it/O ./O 
Then/O his/O sister/O dropped/O her/O gaze/O to/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O no/O mercy/O ./O 
These/O northern/O gods/O are/O cruel/O to/O let/O the/O child/O linger/O in/O such/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O were/O the/O maester/O 's/O words/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O bacon/O crunched/O when/O he/O bit/O into/O it/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON chewed/O thoughtfully/O for/O a/O moment/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O He/O thinks/O that/O if/O the/O boy/O were/O going/O to/O die/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O done/O so/O already/O ./O 
It/O has/O been/O four/O days/O with/O no/O change/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O Bran/O get/O better/O ,/O Uncle/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O little/O Myrcella/PERSON asked/O ./O 
She/O had/O all/O of/O her/O mother/O 's/O beauty/O ,/O and/O none/O of/O her/O nature/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O back/O is/O broken/O ,/O little/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O fall/O shattered/O his/O legs/O as/O well/O ./O 
They/O keep/O him/O alive/O with/O honey/O and/O water/O ,/O or/O he/O would/O starve/O to/O death/O ./O 
Perhaps/O ,/O if/O he/O wakes/O ,/O he/O will/O be/O able/O to/O eat/O real/O food/O ,/O but/O he/O will/O never/O walk/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O wakes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/O repeated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O likely/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gods/O alone/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O maester/O only/O hopes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O chewed/O some/O more/O bread/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O swear/O that/O wolf/O of/O his/O is/O keeping/O the/O boy/O alive/O ./O 
The/O creature/O is/O outside/O his/O window/O day/O and/O night/O ,/O howling/O ./O 
Every/O time/O they/O chase/O it/O away/O ,/O it/O returns/O ./O 
The/O maester/O said/O they/O closed/O the/O window/O once/O ,/O to/O shut/O out/O the/O noise/O ,/O and/O Bran/O seemed/O to/O weaken/O ./O 
When/O they/O opened/O it/O again/O ,/O his/O heart/O beat/O stronger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O shuddered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O something/O unnatural/O about/O those/O animals/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O are/O dangerous/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O have/O any/O of/O them/O coming/O south/O with/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O 'll/O have/O a/O hard/O time/O stopping/O them/O ,/O sister/O ./O 
They/O follow/O those/O girls/O everywhere/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O started/O on/O his/O fish/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O leaving/O soon/O ,/O then/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O near/O soon/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON said/O ./O 
Then/O she/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O we/O leaving/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O echoed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O about/O you/O ?/O 
Gods/O ,/O do/O n't/O tell/O me/O you/O are/O staying/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Benjen/O Stark/O is/O returning/O to/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O with/O his/O brother/O 's/O bastard/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O mind/O to/O go/O with/O them/O and/O see/O this/O Wall/O we/O have/O all/O heard/O so/O much/O of/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O you/O 're/O not/O thinking/O of/O taking/O the/O black/O on/O us/O ,/O sweet/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O ,/O me/O ,/O celibate/O ?/O 
The/O whores/O would/O go/O begging/O from/O Dome/LOCATION to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O 
No/O ,/O I/O just/O want/O to/O stand/O on/O top/O of/O the/O Wall/O and/O piss/O off/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON stood/O abruptly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O children/O do/O n't/O need/O to/O hear/O this/O filth/O ./O 
Tommen/PERSON ,/O Myrcella/PERSON ,/O come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O strode/O briskly/O from/O the/O morning/O room/O ,/O her/O train/O and/O her/O pups/O trailing/O behind/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON regarded/O his/O brother/O thoughtfully/O with/O those/O cool/O green/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stark/O will/O never/O consent/O to/O leave/O Winterfell/PERSON with/O his/O son/O lingering/O in/O the/O shadow/O of/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O if/O Robert/PERSON commands/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Robert/PERSON will/O command/O it/O ./O 
There/O is/O nothing/O Lord/O Eddard/O can/O do/O for/O the/O boy/O in/O any/O case/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O could/O end/O his/O torment/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O ,/O if/O it/O were/O my/O son/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O a/O mercy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O advise/O against/O putting/O that/O suggestion/O to/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O sweet/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O not/O take/O it/O kindly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Even/O if/O the/O boy/O does/O live/O ,/O he/O will/O be/O a/O cripple/O ./O 
Worse/O than/O a/O cripple/O ./O 
A/O grotesque/O ./O 
Give/O me/O a/O good/O clean/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O shrug/O that/O accentuated/O the/O twist/O of/O his/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Speaking/O for/O the/O grotesques/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O beg/O to/O differ/O ./O 
Death/O is/O so/O terribly/O final/O ,/O while/O life/O is/O full/O of/O possibilities/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O perverse/O little/O imp/O ,/O are/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O the/O boy/O does/O wake/O ./O 
I/O would/O be/O most/O interested/O to/O hear/O what/O he/O might/O have/O to/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O brother/O 's/O smile/O curdled/O like/O sour/O milk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O ,/O my/O sweet/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O darkly/O ,/O \/O ``/O there/O are/O times/O when/O you/O give/O me/O cause/O to/O wonder/O whose/O side/O you/O are/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O 's/O mouth/O was/O full/O of/O bread/O and/O fish/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O swallow/O of/O strong/O black/O beer/O to/O wash/O it/O all/O down/O ,/O and/O grinned/O up/O wolfishly/O at/O Jaime/LOCATION ,/O \/O ``/O Why/O ,/O Jaime/PERSON ,/O my/O sweet/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O wound/O me/O ./O 
You/O know/O how/O much/O I/O love/O my/O family/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
