-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O heart/O was/O steaming/O in/O the/O cool/O evening/O air/O when/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON set/O it/O before/O her/O ,/O raw/O and/O bloody/O ./O 
His/O arms/O were/O red/O to/O the/O elbow/O ./O 
Behind/O him/O ,/O his/O bloodriders/O knelt/O on/O the/O sand/O beside/O the/O corpse/O of/O the/O wild/O stallion/O ,/O stone/O knives/O in/O their/O hands/O ./O 
The/O stallion/O 's/O blood/O looked/O black/O in/O the/O flickering/O orange/O glare/O of/O the/O torches/O that/O ringed/O the/O high/O chalk/O walls/O of/O the/O pit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON touched/O the/O soft/O swell/O of/O her/O belly/O ./O 
Sweat/O beaded/O her/O skin/O and/O trickled/O down/O her/O brow/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O old/O women/O watching/O her/O ,/O the/O ancient/O crones/O of/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O with/O eyes/O that/O shone/O dark/O as/O polished/O flint/O in/O their/O wrinkled/O faces/O ./O 
She/O must/O not/O flinch/O or/O look/O afraid/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O as/O she/O took/O the/O stallion/O 's/O heart/O in/O both/O hands/O ,/O lifted/O it/O to/O her/O mouth/O ,/O and/O plunged/O her/O teeth/O into/O the/O tough/O ,/O stringy/O flesh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Warm/O blood/O filled/O her/O mouth/O and/O ran/O down/O over/O her/O chin/O ./O 
The/O taste/O threatened/O to/O gag/O her/O ,/O but/O she/O made/O herself/O chew/O and/O swallow/O ./O 
The/O heart/O of/O a/O stallion/O would/O make/O her/O son/O strong/O and/O swift/O and/O fearless/O ,/O or/O so/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON believed/O ,/O but/O only/O if/O the/O mother/O could/O eat/O it/O all/O ./O 
If/O she/O choked/O on/O the/O blood/O or/O retched/O up/O the/O flesh/O ,/O the/O omens/O were/O less/O favorable/O ;/O the/O child/O might/O be/O stillborn/O ,/O or/O come/O forth/O weak/O ,/O deformed/O ,/O or/O female/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O handmaids/O had/O helped/O her/O ready/O herself/O for/O the/O ceremony/O ./O 
Despite/O the/O tender/O mother/O 's/O stomach/O that/O had/O afflicted/O her/O these/O past/O two/O moons/O ,/O Dany/PERSON had/O dined/O on/O bowls/O of/O half-clotted/O blood/O to/O accustom/O herself/O to/O the/O taste/O ,/O and/O Irri/PERSON made/O her/O chew/O strips/O of/O dried/O horseflesh/O until/O her/O jaws/O were/O aching/O ./O 
She/O had/O starved/O herself/O for/O a/O day/O and/O a/O night/O before/O the/O ceremony/O in/O the/O hopes/O that/O hunger/O would/O help/O her/O keep/O down/O the/O raw/O meat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O wild/O stallion/O 's/O heart/O was/O all/O muscle/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON had/O to/O worry/O it/O with/O her/O teeth/O and/O chew/O each/O mouthful/O a/O long/O time/O ./O 
No/O steel/O was/O permitted/O within/O the/O sacred/O confines/O of/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O beneath/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION ;/O she/O had/O to/O rip/O the/O heart/O apart/O with/O teeth/O and/O nails/O ./O 
Her/O stomach/O roiled/O and/O heaved/O ,/O yet/O she/O kept/O on/O ,/O her/O face/O smeared/O with/O the/O heartsblood/O that/O sometimes/O seemed/O to/O explode/O against/O her/O lips/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON stood/O over/O her/O as/O she/O ate/O ,/O his/O face/O as/O hard/O as/O a/O bronze/O shield/O ./O 
His/O long/O black/O braid/O was/O shiny/O with/O oil/O ./O 
He/O wore/O gold/O rings/O in/O his/O mustache/O ,/O gold/O bells/O in/O his/O braid/O ,/O and/O a/O heavy/O belt/O of/O solid/O gold/O medallions/O around/O his/O waist/O ,/O but/O his/O chest/O was/O bare/O ./O 
She/O looked/O at/O him/O whenever/O she/O felt/O her/O strength/O failing/O ;/O looked/O at/O him/O ,/O and/O chewed/O and/O swallowed/O ,/O chewed/O and/O swallowed/O ,/O chewed/O and/O swallowed/O ./O 
Toward/O the/O end/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O she/O glimpsed/O a/O fierce/O pride/O in/O his/O dark/O ,/O almond/O shaped/O eyes/O ,/O but/O she/O could/O not/O be/O sure/O ./O 
The/O khal/O 's/O face/O did/O not/O often/O betray/O the/O thoughts/O within/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O finally/O it/O was/O done/O ./O 
Her/O cheeks/O and/O fingers/O were/O sticky/O as/O she/O forced/O down/O the/O last/O of/O it/O ./O 
Only/O then/O did/O she/O turn/O her/O eyes/O back/O to/O the/O old/O women/O ,/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khalakka/O dothrae/O mranha/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O proclaimed/O in/O her/O best/O Dothraki/PERSON ./O 
A/O prince/O tides/O inside/O me/O !/O 
She/O had/O practiced/O the/O phrase/O for/O days/O with/O her/O handmaid/O Jhiqui/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O oldest/O of/O the/O crones/O ,/O a/O bent/O and/O shriveled/O stick/O of/O a/O woman/O with/O a/O single/O black/O eye/O ,/O raised/O her/O arms/O on/O high/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khalakka/O dothrae/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O shrieked/O ./O 
The/O prince/O is/O tiding/O !/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O tiding/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O other/O women/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rakh/O !/O 
Rakh/O !/O 
Rakh/O haj/O !/O 
\/O ''/O they/O proclaimed/O ./O 
A/O boy/O ,/O a/O boy/O ,/O a/O strong/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bells/O rang/O ,/O a/O sudden/O clangor/O of/O bronze/O birds/O ./O 
A/O deep-throated/O warhorn/O sounded/O its/O long/O low/O note/O ./O 
The/O old/O women/O began/O to/O chant/O ./O 
Underneath/O their/O painted/O leather/O vests/O ,/O their/O withered/O dugs/O swayed/O back/O and/O forth/O ,/O shiny/O with/O oil/O and/O sweat/O ./O 
The/O eunuchs/O who/O served/O them/O threw/O bundles/O of/O dried/O grasses/O into/O a/O great/O bronze/O brazier/O ,/O and/O clouds/O of/O fragrant/O smoke/O rose/O up/O toward/O the/O moon/O and/O the/O stars/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON believed/O the/O stars/O were/O horses/O made/O of/O fire/O ,/O a/O great/O herd/O that/O galloped/O across/O the/O sky/O by/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O the/O smoke/O ascended/O ,/O the/O chanting/O died/O away/O and/O the/O ancient/O crone/O closed/O her/O single/O eye/O ,/O the/O better/O to/O peer/O into/O the/O future/O ./O 
The/O silence/O that/O fell/O was/O complete/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON could/O hear/O the/O distant/O call/O of/O night/O birds/O ,/O the/O hiss/O and/O crackle/O of/O the/O torches/O ,/O the/O gentle/O lapping/O of/O water/O from/O the/O lake/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON stared/O at/O her/O with/O eyes/O of/O night/O ,/O waiting/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON laid/O his/O hand/O on/O Dany/PERSON 's/O arm/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O tension/O in/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
Even/O a/O khal/O as/O mighty/O as/O Drogo/PERSON could/O know/O fear/O when/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O peered/O into/O smoke/O of/O the/O future/O ./O 
At/O her/O back/O ,/O her/O handmaids/O fluttered/O anxiously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Finally/O the/O crone/O opened/O her/O eye/O and/O lifted/O her/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O seen/O his/O face/O ,/O and/O heard/O the/O thunder/O of/O his/O hooves/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O proclaimed/O in/O a/O thin/O ,/O wavery/O voice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O thunder/O of/O his/O hooves/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O others/O chorused/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O swift/O as/O the/O wind/O he/O rides/O ,/O and/O behind/O him/O his/O khalasar/O covers/O the/O earth/O ,/O men/O without/O number/O ,/O with/O arakhs/O shining/O in/O their/O hands/O like/O blades/O of/O razor/O grass/O ./O 
Fierce/O as/O a/O storm/O this/O prince/O will/O be/O ./O 
His/O enemies/O will/O tremble/O before/O him/O ,/O and/O their/O wives/O will/O weep/O tears/O of/O blood/O and/O rend/O their/O flesh/O in/O grief/O ./O 
The/O bells/O in/O his/O hair/O will/O sing/O his/O coming/O ,/O and/O the/O milk/O men/O in/O the/O stone/O tents/O will/O fear/O his/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O old/O woman/O trembled/O and/O looked/O at/O Dany/PERSON almost/O as/O if/O she/O were/O afraid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O prince/O is/O riding/O ,/O and/O he/O shall/O be/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O onlookers/O cried/O in/O echo/O ,/O until/O the/O night/O rang/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O their/O voices/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O one-eyed/O crone/O peered/O at/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O shall/O he/O be/O called/O ,/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O stood/O to/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O shall/O be/O called/O Rhaego/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O using/O the/O words/O that/O Jhiqui/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O ./O 
Her/O hands/O touched/O the/O swell/O beneath/O her/O breasts/O protectively/O as/O a/O roar/O went/O up/O from/O the/O Dothraki/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaego/O ,/O \/O ''/O they/O screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaego/O ,/O Rhaego/O ,/O Rhaego/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O name/O was/O still/O ringing/O in/O her/O ears/O as/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON led/O her/O from/O the/O pit/O ./O 
His/O bloodriders/O fell/O in/O behind/O them/O ./O 
A/O procession/O followed/O them/O out/O onto/O the/O godsway/O ,/O the/O broad/O grassy/O road/O that/O ran/O through/O the/O heart/O of/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O from/O the/O horse/O gate/O to/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION ./O 
The/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O came/O first/O ,/O with/O their/O eunuchs/O and/O slaves/O ./O 
Some/O supported/O themselves/O with/O tall/O carved/O staffs/O as/O they/O struggled/O along/O on/O ancient/O ,/O shaking/O legs/O ,/O while/O others/O walked/O as/O proud/O as/O any/O horselord/O ./O 
Each/O of/O the/O old/O women/O had/O been/O a/O khaleesi/O once/O ./O 
When/O their/O lord/O husbands/O died/O and/O a/O new/O khal/O took/O his/O place/O at/O the/O front/O of/O his/O riders/O ,/O with/O a/O new/O khaleesi/O mounted/O beside/O him/O ,/O they/O were/O sent/O here/O ,/O to/O reign/O over/O the/O vast/O Dothraki/O nation/O ./O 
Even/O the/O mightiest/O of/O khals/O ''/O ,/O ``/O bowed/O to/O the/O wisdom/O and/O authority/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O it/O gave/O Dany/PERSON the/O shivers/O to/O think/O that/O one/O day/O she/O might/O be/O sent/O to/O join/O them/O ,/O whether/O she/O willed/O it/O or/O no/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Behind/O the/O wise/O women/O came/O the/O others/O ;/O Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON and/O his/O son/O ,/O the/O khalakka/O Fogo/O ,/O Khal/PERSON Jommo/PERSON and/O his/O wives/O ,/O the/O chief/O men/O of/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O khalasar/O ,/O Dany/PERSON 's/O handmaids/O ,/O the/O khal/O 's/O servants/O and/O slaves/O ,/O and/O more/O ./O 
Bells/O rang/O and/O drums/O beat/O a/O stately/O cadence/O as/O they/O marched/O along/O the/O godsway/O ./O 
Stolen/O heroes/O and/O the/O gods/O of/O dead/O peoples/O brooded/O in/O the/O darkness/O beyond/O the/O road/O ./O 
Alongside/O the/O procession/O ,/O slaves/O ran/O lightly/O through/O the/O grass/O with/O torches/O in/O their/O hands/O ,/O and/O the/O flickering/O flames/O made/O the/O great/O monuments/O seem/O almost/O alive/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O is/O meaning/O ,/O name/O Rhaego/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON asked/O as/O they/O walked/O ,/O using/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O teaching/O him/O a/O few/O words/O when/O she/O could/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON was/O quick/O to/O learn/O when/O he/O put/O his/O mind/O to/O it/O ,/O though/O his/O accent/O was/O so/O thick/O and/O barbarous/O that/O neither/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON nor/O Viserys/PERSON could/O understand/O a/O word/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON was/O a/O fierce/O warrior/O ,/O my/O sun-and-stars/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O died/O before/O I/O was/O born/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON says/O that/O he/O was/O the/O last/O of/O the/O dragons/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON looked/O down/O at/O her/O ./O 
His/O face/O was/O a/O copper/O mask/O ,/O yet/O under/O the/O long/O black/O mustache/O ,/O drooping/O beneath/O the/O weight/O of/O its/O gold/O rings/O ,/O she/O thought/O she/O glimpsed/O the/O shadow/O of/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O good/O name/O ,/O Dan/PERSON Ares/PERSON wife/O ,/O moon/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O rode/O to/O the/O lake/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON called/O the/O Womb/O of/O the/O World/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O a/O fringe/O of/O reeds/O ,/O its/O water/O still/O and/O calm/O ./O 
A/O thousand/O thousand/O years/O ago/O ,/O Jhiqui/PERSON told/O her/O ,/O the/O first/O man/O had/O emerged/O from/O its/O depths/O ,/O riding/O upon/O the/O back/O of/O the/O first/O horse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O procession/O waited/O on/O the/O grassy/O shore/O as/O Dany/PERSON stripped/O and/O let/O her/O soiled/O clothing/O fall/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Naked/O ,/O she/O stepped/O gingerly/O into/O the/O water/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON said/O the/O lake/O had/O no/O bottom/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON felt/O soft/O mud/O squishing/O between/O her/O toes/O as/O she/O pushed/O through/O the/O tall/O reeds/O ./O 
The/O moon/O floated/O on/O the/O still/O black/O waters/O ,/O shattering/O and/O re-forming/O as/O her/O ripples/O washed/O over/O it/O ./O 
Goose/O pimples/O rose/O on/O her/O pale/O skin/O as/O the/O coldness/O crept/O up/O her/O thighs/O and/O kissed/O her/O lower/O lips/O ./O 
The/O stallion/O 's/O blood/O had/O dried/O on/O her/O hands/O and/O around/O her/O mouth/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON cupped/O her/O fingers/O and/O lifted/O the/O sacred/O waters/O over/O her/O head/O ,/O cleansing/O herself/O and/O the/O child/O inside/O her/O while/O the/O khal/O and/O the/O others/O looked/O on/O ./O 
She/O heard/O the/O old/O women/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O muttering/O to/O each/O other/O as/O they/O watched/O ,/O and/O wondered/O what/O they/O were/O saying/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O emerged/O from/O the/O lake/O ,/O shivering/O and/O dripping/O ,/O her/O handmaid/O Doreah/PERSON hurried/O to/O her/O with/O a/O robe/O of/O painted/O sandsilk/O ,/O but/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON waved/O her/O away/O ./O 
He/O was/O looking/O on/O her/O swollen/O breasts/O and/O the/O curve/O of/O her/O belly/O with/O approval/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON could/O see/O the/O shape/O of/O his/O manhood/O pressing/O through/O his/O horsehide/O trousers/O ,/O below/O the/O heavy/O gold/O medallions/O of/O his/O belt/O ./O 
She/O went/O to/O him/O and/O helped/O him/O unlace/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O her/O huge/O khal/O took/O her/O by/O the/O hips/O and/O lifted/O her/O into/O the/O air/O ,/O as/O he/O might/O lift/O a/O child/O ./O 
The/O bells/O in/O his/O hair/O rang/O softly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON wrapped/O her/O arms/O around/O his/O shoulders/O and/O pressed/O her/O face/O against/O his/O neck/O as/O he/O thrust/O himself/O inside/O her/O ./O 
Three/O quick/O strokes/O and/O it/O was/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ,/O \/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON whispered/O hoarsely/O ./O 
His/O hands/O still/O smelled/O of/O horse/O blood/O ./O 
He/O bit/O at/O her/O throat/O ,/O hard/O ,/O in/O the/O moment/O of/O his/O pleasure/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O lifted/O her/O off/O ,/O his/O seed/O filled/O her/O and/O trickled/O down/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O inside/O of/O her/O thighs/O ./O 
Only/O then/O was/O Doreah/PERSON permitted/O to/O drape/O her/O in/O the/O scented/O sandsilk/O ,/O and/O Irri/ORGANIZATION to/O fit/O soft/O slippers/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON laced/O himself/O up/O and/O spoke/O a/O command/O ,/O and/O horses/O were/O brought/O to/O the/O lakeshore/O ./O 
Cohollo/PERSON had/O the/O honor/O of/O helping/O the/O khaleesi/O onto/O her/O silver/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON spurred/O his/O stallion/O ,/O and/O set/O off/O down/O the/O godsway/O beneath/O the/O moon/O and/O stars/O ./O 
On/O her/O silver/O ,/O Dany/PERSON easily/O kept/O pace/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O silk/O tenting/O that/O roofed/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O hall/O had/O been/O rolled/O up/O tonight/O ,/O and/O the/O moon/O followed/O them/O inside/O ./O 
Flames/O leapt/O ten/O feet/O in/O the/O air/O from/O three/O huge/O stone-lined/O firepits/O ./O 
The/O air/O was/O thick/O with/O the/O smells/O of/O roasting/O meat/O and/O curdled/O ,/O fermented/O mare/O 's/O milk/O ./O 
The/O hall/O was/O crowded/O and/O noisy/O when/O they/O entered/O ,/O the/O cushions/O packed/O with/O those/O whose/O rank/O and/O name/O were/O not/O sufficient/O to/O allow/O them/O at/O the/O ceremony/O ./O 
As/O Dany/PERSON rode/O beneath/O the/O arched/O entry/O and/O up/O the/O center/O aisle/O ,/O every/O eye/O was/O on/O her/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON screamed/O out/O comments/O on/O her/O belly/O and/O her/O breasts/O ,/O hailing/O the/O life/O within/O her/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O understand/O all/O they/O shouted/O ,/O but/O one/O phrase/O came/O clear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stallion/O that/O mounts/O the/O world/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O heard/O ,/O bellowed/O in/O a/O thousand/O voices/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sounds/O of/O drums/O and/O horns/O swirled/O up/O into/O the/O night/O ./O 
Halfclothed/O women/O spun/O and/O danced/O on/O the/O low/O tables/O ,/O amid/O joints/O of/O meat/O and/O platters/O piled/O high/O with/O plums/O and/O dates/O and/O pomegranates/O ./O 
Many/O of/O the/O men/O were/O drunk/O on/O clotted/O mare/O 's/O milk/O ,/O yet/O Dany/PERSON knew/O no/O arakhs/O would/O clash/O tonight/O ,/O not/O here/O in/O the/O sacred/O city/O ,/O where/O blades/O and/O bloodshed/O were/O forbidden/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON dismounted/O and/O took/O his/O place/O on/O the/O high/O bench/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Jommo/PERSON and/O Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O been/O in/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON with/O their/O khalasars/O when/O they/O arrived/O ,/O were/O given/O seats/O of/O high/O honor/O to/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O right/O and/O left/O ./O 
The/O bloodriders/O of/O the/O three/O khals/O sat/O below/O them/O ,/O and/O farther/O down/O Khal/PERSON Jommo/PERSON 's/O four/O wives/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON climbed/O off/O her/O silver/O and/O gave/O the/O reins/O to/O one/O of/O the/O slaves/O ./O 
As/O Doreah/PERSON and/O Irri/PERSON arranged/O her/O cushions/O ,/O she/O searched/O for/O her/O brother/O ./O 
Even/O across/O the/O length/O of/O the/O crowded/O hall/O ,/O Viserys/PERSON should/O have/O been/O conspicuous/O with/O his/O pale/O skin/O ,/O silvery/O hair/O ,/O and/O beggar/O 's/O rags/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O not/O see/O him/O anywhere/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O glance/O roamed/O the/O crowded/O tables/O near/O the/O walls/O ,/O where/O men/O whose/O braids/O were/O even/O shorter/O than/O their/O manhoods/O sat/O on/O frayed/O rugs/O and/O flat/O cushions/O around/O the/O low/O tables/O ,/O but/O all/O the/O faces/O she/O saw/O had/O black/O eyes/O and/O copper/O skin/O ./O 
She/O spied/O Ser/O Jorah/O Mormont/O near/O the/O center/O of/O the/O hall/O ,/O close/O to/O the/O middle/O firepit/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O place/O of/O respect/O ,/O if/O not/O high/O honor/O ;/O the/O Dothraki/O esteemed/O the/O knight/O 's/O prowess/O with/O a/O sword/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON sent/O Jhiqui/PERSON to/O bring/O him/O to/O her/O table/O ./O 
Mormont/O came/O at/O once/O ,/O and/O went/O to/O one/O knee/O before/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O yours/O to/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O patted/O the/O stuffed/O horsehide/O cushion/O beside/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sit/O and/O talk/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O honor/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O seated/O himself/O cross-legged/O on/O the/O cushion/O ./O 
A/O slave/O knelt/O before/O him/O ,/O offering/O a/O wooden/O platter/O full/O of/O ripe/O figs/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON took/O one/O and/O bit/O it/O in/O half/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Where/O is/O my/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O ought/O to/O have/O come/O by/O now/O ,/O for/O the/O feast/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O saw/O His/O Grace/O this/O morning/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O told/O me/O he/O was/O going/O to/O the/O Western/O Market/O ,/O in/O search/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wine/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O doubtfully/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON could/O not/O abide/O the/O taste/O of/O the/O fermented/O mare/O 's/O milk/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON drank/O ,/O she/O knew/O that/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O oft/O at/O the/O bazaars/O these/O days/O ,/O drinking/O with/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O traders/O who/O came/O in/O the/O great/O caravans/O from/O east/O and/O west/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O find/O their/O company/O more/O congenial/O than/O hers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wine/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON confirmed/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O he/O has/O some/O thought/O to/O recruit/O men/O for/O his/O army/O from/O the/O sellswords/O who/O guard/O the/O caravans/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O serving/O girl/O laid/O a/O blood/O pie/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O attacked/O it/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O wise/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O no/O gold/O to/O pay/O soldiers/O ./O 
What/O if/O he/O 's/O betrayed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Caravan/O guards/O were/O seldom/O troubled/O much/O by/O thoughts/O of/O honor/O ,/O and/O the/O Usurper/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O would/O pay/O well/O for/O her/O brother/O 's/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ought/O to/O have/O gone/O with/O him/O ,/O to/O keep/O him/O safe/O ./O 
You/O are/O his/O sworn/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O are/O in/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O reminded/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O may/O carry/O a/O blade/O here/O or/O shed/O a/O man/O 's/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yet/O men/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON told/O me/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O traders/O have/O eunuchs/O with/O them/O ,/O huge/O men/O who/O strangle/O thieves/O with/O wisps/O of/O silk/O ./O 
That/O way/O no/O blood/O is/O shed/O and/O the/O gods/O are/O not/O angered/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O let/O us/O hope/O your/O brother/O will/O be/O wise/O enough/O not/O to/O steal/O anything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON wiped/O the/O grease/O off/O his/O mouth/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O and/O leaned/O close/O over/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O had/O planned/O to/O take/O your/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O ,/O until/O I/O warned/O him/O that/O I/O 'd/O cut/O off/O his/O hand/O if/O he/O so/O much/O as/O touched/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Dany/PERSON was/O so/O shocked/O she/O had/O no/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O eggs/O .../O but/O they/O 're/O mine/O ,/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON gave/O them/O to/O me/O ,/O a/O bride/O gift/O ,/O why/O would/O Viserys/O want/O .../O they/O 're/O only/O stones/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O same/O could/O be/O said/O of/O rubies/O and/O diamonds/O and/O fire/O opals/O ,/O Princess/O .../O and/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O are/O rarer/O by/O far/O ./O 
Those/O traders/O he/O 's/O been/O drinking/O with/O would/O sell/O their/O own/O manhoods/O for/O even/O one/O of/O those/O stones/O ,/O and/O with/O all/O three/O Viserys/PERSON could/O buy/O as/O many/O sellswords/O as/O he/O might/O need/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON had/O not/O known/O ,/O had/O not/O even/O suspected/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O .../O he/O should/O have/O them/O ./O 
He/O does/O not/O need/O to/O steal/O them/O ./O 
He/O had/O only/O to/O ask/O ./O 
He/O is/O my/O brother/O .../O and/O my/O true/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O your/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON acknowledged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O understand/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O mother/O died/O giving/O me/O birth/O ,/O and/O my/O father/O and/O my/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON even/O before/O that/O ./O 
I/O would/O never/O have/O known/O so/O much/O as/O their/O names/O if/O Viserys/PERSON had/O not/O been/O there/O to/O tell/O me/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O only/O one/O left/O ./O 
The/O only/O one/O ./O 
He/O is/O all/O I/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Once/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O longer/O ,/O Khaleesi/O ./O 
You/O belong/O to/O the/O Dothraki/O now/O ./O 
In/O your/O womb/O rides/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O held/O out/O his/O cup/O ,/O and/O a/O slave/O filled/O it/O with/O fermented/O mare/O 's/O milk/O ,/O sour-smelling/O and/O thick/O with/O clots/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON waved/O her/O away/O ./O 
Even/O the/O smell/O of/O it/O made/O her/O feel/O ill/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O take/O no/O chances/O of/O bringing/O up/O the/O horse/O heart/O she/O had/O forced/O herself/O to/O eat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O does/O it/O mean/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O this/O stallion/O ?/O 
Everyone/O was/O shouting/O it/O at/O me/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O n't/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O stallion/O is/O the/O khal/O of/O khals/O promised/O in/O ancient/O prophecy/O ,/O child/O ./O 
He/O will/O unite/O the/O Dothraki/O into/O a/O single/O khalasar/O and/O ride/O to/O the/O ends/O of/O the/O earth/O ,/O or/O so/O it/O was/O promised/O ./O 
All/O the/O people/O of/O the/O world/O will/O be/O his/O herd/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O in/O a/O small/O voice/O ./O 
Her/O hand/O smoothed/O her/O robe/O down/O over/O the/O swell/O of/O her/O stomach/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O named/O him/O Rhaego/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O name/O to/O make/O the/O Usurper/O 's/O blood/O run/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Suddenly/O Doreah/PERSON was/O tugging/O at/O her/O elbow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O handmaid/O whispered/O urgently/O ,/O \/O ``/O your/O brother/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON looked/O down/O the/O length/O of/O the/O long/O ,/O roofless/O hall/O and/O there/O he/O was/O ,/O striding/O toward/O her/O ./O 
From/O the/O lurch/O in/O his/O step/O ,/O she/O could/O tell/O at/O once/O that/O Viserys/PERSON had/O found/O his/O wine/O .../O and/O something/O that/O passed/O for/O courage/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O wearing/O his/O scarlet/O silks/O ,/O soiled/O and/O travel-stained/O ./O 
His/O cloak/O and/O gloves/O were/O black/O velvet/O ,/O faded/O from/O the/O sun/O ./O 
His/O boots/O were/O dry/O and/O cracked/O ,/O his/O silver-blond/O hair/O matted/O and/O tangled/O ./O 
A/O longsword/O swung/O from/O his/O belt/O in/O a/O leather/O scabbard/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON eyed/O the/O sword/O as/O he/O passed/O ;/O Dany/PERSON heard/O curses/O and/O threats/O and/O angry/O muttering/O rising/O all/O around/O her/O ,/O like/O a/O tide/O ./O 
The/O music/O died/O away/O in/O a/O nervous/O stammering/O of/O drums/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O sense/O of/O dread/O closed/O around/O her/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O to/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O him/O ./O 
Bring/O him/O here/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O he/O can/O have/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O if/O that/O is/O what/O he/O wants/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O rose/O swiftly/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Where/O is/O my/O sister/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON shouted/O ,/O his/O voice/O thick/O with/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O come/O for/O her/O feast/O ./O 
How/O dare/O you/O presume/O to/O eat/O without/O me/O ?/O 
No/O one/O eats/O before/O the/O king/O ./O 
Where/O is/O she/O ?/O 
The/O whore/O ca/O n't/O hide/O from/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O stopped/O beside/O the/O largest/O of/O the/O three/O firepits/O ,/O peering/O around/O at/O the/O faces/O of/O the/O Dothraki/O ./O 
There/O were/O five/O thousand/O men/O in/O the/O hall/O ,/O but/O only/O a/O handful/O who/O knew/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ./O 
Yet/O even/O if/O his/O words/O were/O incomprehensible/O ,/O you/O had/O only/O to/O look/O at/O him/O to/O know/O that/O he/O was/O drunk/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON went/O to/O him/O swiftly/O ,/O whispered/O something/O in/O his/O ear/O ,/O and/O took/O him/O by/O the/O arm/O ,/O but/O Viserys/PERSON wrenched/O free/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O your/O hands/O off/O me/O !/O 
No/O one/O touches/O the/O dragon/O without/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON glanced/O anxiously/O up/O at/O the/O high/O bench/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON was/O saying/O something/O to/O the/O other/O khals/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Jommo/PERSON grinned/O ,/O and/O Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON began/O to/O guffaw/O loudly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sound/O of/O laughter/O made/O Viserys/PERSON lift/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O thickly/O ,/O his/O voice/O almost/O polite/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O here/O for/O the/O feast/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O staggered/O away/O from/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O making/O to/O join/O the/O three/O khals/O on/O the/O high/O bench/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON rose/O ,/O spat/O out/O a/O dozen/O words/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ,/O faster/O than/O Dany/PERSON could/O understand/O ,/O and/O pointed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON says/O your/O place/O is/O not/O on/O the/O high/O bench/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON translated/O for/O her/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON says/O your/O place/O is/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O glanced/O where/O the/O khal/O was/O pointing/O ./O 
At/O the/O back/O of/O the/O long/O hall/O ,/O in/O a/O corner/O by/O the/O wall/O ,/O deep/O in/O shadow/O so/O better/O men/O would/O not/O need/O to/O look/O on/O them/O ,/O sat/O the/O lowest/O of/O the/O low/O ;/O raw/O unblooded/O boys/O ,/O old/O men/O with/O clouded/O eyes/O and/O stiff/O joints/O ,/O the/O dim-witted/O and/O the/O maimed/O ./O 
Far/O from/O the/O meat/O ,/O and/O farther/O from/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O no/O place/O for/O a/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O brother/O declared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O place/O ,/O \/O ''/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON answered/O ,/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O that/O Dany/PERSON had/O taught/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O for/O Sorefoot/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O clapped/O his/O hands/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O cart/O !/O 
Bring/O cart/O for/O Khal/PERSON Rhaggat/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Five/O thousand/O Dothraki/PERSON began/O to/O laugh/O and/O shout/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON was/O standing/O beside/O Viserys/PERSON ,/O screaming/O in/O his/O ear/O ,/O but/O the/O roar/O in/O the/O hall/O was/O so/O thunderous/O that/O Dany/PERSON could/O not/O hear/O what/O he/O ''/O ,/O ``/O was/O saying/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O shouted/O back/O and/O the/O two/O men/O grappled/O ,/O until/O Mormont/PERSON knocked/O Viserys/O bodily/O to/O the/O floor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O brother/O drew/O his/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O bared/O steel/O shone/O a/O fearful/O red/O in/O the/O glare/O from/O the/O firepits/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O away/O from/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON hissed/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON backed/O off/O a/O step/O ,/O and/O her/O brother/O climbed/O unsteadily/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
He/O waved/O the/O sword/O over/O his/O head/O ,/O the/O borrowed/O blade/O that/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON had/O given/O him/O to/O make/O him/O seem/O more/O kingly/O ./O 
Dothraki/PERSON were/O shrieking/O at/O him/O from/O all/O sides/O ,/O screaming/O vile/O curses/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON gave/O a/O wordless/O cry/O of/O terror/O ./O 
She/O knew/O what/O a/O drawn/O sword/O meant/O here/O ,/O even/O if/O her/O brother/O did/O not/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O voice/O made/O Viserys/O turn/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O he/O saw/O her/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O she/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
He/O stalked/O toward/O her/O ,/O slashing/O at/O the/O air/O as/O if/O to/O cut/O a/O path/O through/O a/O wall/O of/O enemies/O ,/O though/O no/O one/O tried/O to/O bar/O his/O way/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O blade/O .../O you/O must/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O begged/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O Viserys/O ./O 
It/O is/O forbidden/O ./O 
Put/O down/O the/O sword/O and/O come/O share/O my/O cushions/O ./O 
There/O 's/O drink/O ,/O food/O .../O is/O it/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O you/O want/O ?/O 
You/O can/O have/O them/O ,/O only/O throw/O away/O the/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O as/O she/O tells/O you/O ,/O fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON shouted/O ,/O \/O ``/O before/O you/O get/O us/O all/O killed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O ca/O n't/O kill/O us/O ./O 
They/O ca/O n't/O shed/O blood/O here/O in/O the/O sacred/O city/O .../O but/O I/O can/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laid/O the/O point/O of/O his/O sword/O between/O Daenerys/PERSON 's/O breasts/O and/O slid/O it/O downward/O ,/O over/O the/O curve/O of/O her/O belly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O what/O I/O came/O for/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O the/O crown/O he/O promised/O me/O ./O 
He/O bought/O you/O ,/O but/O he/O never/O paid/O for/O you/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O I/O want/O what/O I/O bargained/O for/O ,/O or/O I/O 'm/O taking/O you/O back/O ./O 
You/O and/O the/O eggs/O both/O ./O 
He/O can/O keep/O his/O bloody/O foal/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O cut/O the/O bastard/O out/O and/O leave/O it/O for/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O sword/O point/O pushed/O through/O her/O silks/O and/O pricked/O at/O her/O navel/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON was/O weeping/O ,/O she/O saw/O ;/O weeping/O and/O laughing/O ,/O both/O at/O the/O same/O time/O ,/O this/O man/O who/O had/O once/O been/O her/O brother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Distantly/O ,/O as/O from/O far/O away/O ,/O Dany/PERSON heard/O her/O handmaid/O Jhiqui/PERSON sobbing/O in/O fear/O ,/O pleading/O that/O she/O dared/O not/O translate/O ,/O that/O the/O khal/O would/O bind/O her/O and/O drag/O her/O behind/O his/O horse/O all/O the/O way/O up/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION ./O 
She/O put/O her/O arm/O around/O the/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O tell/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O did/O not/O know/O if/O she/O had/O enough/O words/O ,/O yet/O when/O she/O was/O done/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON spoke/O a/O few/O brusque/O sentences/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ,/O and/O she/O knew/O he/O understood/O ./O 
The/O sun/O of/O her/O life/O stepped/O down/O from/O the/O high/O bench/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O did/O he/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O man/O who/O had/O been/O her/O brother/O asked/O her/O ,/O flinching/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O had/O grown/O so/O silent/O in/O the/O hall/O that/O she/O could/O hear/O the/O bells/O in/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O hair/O ,/O chiming/O softly/O with/O each/O step/O he/O took/O ./O 
His/O bloodriders/O followed/O him/O ,/O like/O three/O copper/O shadows/O ./O 
Daenerys/PERSON had/O gone/O cold/O all/O over/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O says/O you/O shall/O have/O a/O splendid/O golden/O crown/O that/O men/O shall/O tremble/O to/O behold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON smiled/O and/O lowered/O his/O sword/O ./O 
That/O was/O the/O saddest/O thing/O ,/O the/O thing/O that/O tore/O at/O her/O afterward/O .../O the/O way/O he/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O all/O I/O wanted/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O was/O promised/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O the/O sun/O of/O her/O life/O reached/O her/O ,/O Dany/PERSON slid/O an/O arm/O around/O his/O waist/O ./O 
The/O khal/O said/O a/O word/O ,/O and/O his/O bloodriders/O leapt/O forward/O ./O 
Qotho/PERSON seized/O the/O man/O who/O had/O been/O her/O brother/O by/O the/O arms/O ./O 
Haggo/PERSON shattered/O his/O wrist/O with/O a/O single/O ,/O sharp/O twist/O of/O his/O huge/O hands/O ./O 
Cohollo/O pulled/O the/O sword/O ''/O ,/O ``/O from/O his/O limp/O fingers/O ./O 
Even/O now/O Viserys/PERSON did/O not/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O can/O not/O touch/O me/O ,/O I/O am/O the/O dragon/O ,/O the/O dragon/O ,/O and/O I/O will/O be/O crowned/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON unfastened/O his/O belt/O ./O 
The/O medallions/O were/O pure/O gold/O ,/O massive/O and/O ornate/O ,/O each/O one/O as/O large/O as/O a/O man/O 's/O hand/O ./O 
He/O shouted/O a/O command/O ./O 
Cook/PERSON slaves/O pulled/O a/O heavy/O iron/O stew/O pot/O from/O the/O firepit/O ,/O dumped/O the/O stew/O onto/O the/O ground/O ,/O and/O returned/O the/O pot/O to/O the/O flames/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON tossed/O in/O the/O belt/O and/O watched/O without/O expression/O as/O the/O medallions/O turned/O red/O and/O began/O to/O lose/O their/O shape/O ./O 
She/O could/O see/O fires/O dancing/O in/O the/O onyx/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
A/O slave/O handed/O him/O a/O pair/O of/O thick/O horsehair/O mittens/O ,/O and/O he/O pulled/O them/O on/O ,/O never/O so/O much/O as/O looking/O at/O the/O man/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Viserys/O began/O to/O scream/O the/O high/O ,/O wordless/O scream/O of/O the/O coward/O facing/O death/O ./O 
He/O kicked/O and/O twisted/O ,/O whimpered/O like/O a/O dog/O and/O wept/O like/O a/O child/O ,/O but/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON held/O him/O tight/O between/O them/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O made/O his/O way/O to/O Dany/PERSON 's/O side/O ./O 
He/O put/O a/O hand/O on/O her/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Turn/O away/O ,/O my/O princess/O ,/O I/O beg/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O folded/O her/O arms/O across/O the/O swell/O of/O her/O belly/O ,/O protectively/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O the/O last/O ,/O Viserys/PERSON looked/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sister/O ,/O please/O .../O Dany/PERSON ,/O tell/O them/O .../O make/O them/O .../O sweet/O sister/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O the/O gold/O was/O half-melted/O and/O starting/O to/O run/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON reached/O into/O the/O flames/O ,/O snatched/O out/O the/O pot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Crown/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O roared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
A/O crown/O for/O Cart/O King/O !/O 
\/O ''/O And/O upended/O the/O pot/O over/O the/O head/O of/O the/O man/O who/O had/O been/O her/O brother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sound/O Viserys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON made/O when/O that/O hideous/O iron/O helmet/O covered/O his/O face/O was/O like/O nothing/O human/O ./O 
His/O feet/O hammered/O a/O frantic/O beat/O against/O the/O dirt/O floor/O ,/O slowed/O ,/O stopped/O ./O 
Thick/O globs/O of/O molten/O gold/O dripped/O down/O onto/O his/O chest/O ,/O setting/O the/O scarlet/O silk/O to/O smoldering/O .../O yet/O no/O drop/O of/O blood/O was/O spilled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O no/O dragon/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O ,/O curiously/O calm/O ./O 
Fire/O can/O not/O kill/O a/O dragon/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
