-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O have/O my/O son/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O do/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O messenger/O 's/O voice/O was/O dulled/O by/O exhaustion/O ./O 
On/O the/O breast/O of/O his/O torn/O surcoat/O ,/O the/O brindled/O boar/O of/O Crake/O hall/O was/O half-obscured/O by/O dried/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O One/O of/O your/O sons/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O sip/O of/O wine/O and/O said/O not/O a/O word/O ,/O thinking/O of/O Jaime/O ./O 
When/O he/O lifted/O his/O arm/O ,/O pain/O shot/O through/O his/O elbow/O ,/O reminding/O him/O of/O his/O own/O brief/O taste/O of/O battle/O ./O 
He/O loved/O his/O brother/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O not/O have/O wanted/O to/O be/O with/O him/O in/O the/O Whispering/LOCATION Wood/LOCATION for/O all/O the/O gold/O in/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O lord/O father/O 's/O assembled/O captains/O and/O bannermen/O had/O fallen/O very/O quiet/O as/O the/O courier/O told/O his/O tale/O ./O 
The/O only/O sound/O was/O the/O crackle/O and/O hiss/O of/O the/O log/O burning/O in/O the/O hearth/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O long/O ,/O drafty/O common/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O the/O hardships/O of/O the/O long/O relentless/O drive/O south/O ,/O the/O prospect/O of/O even/O a/O single/O night/O in/O an/O inn/O had/O cheered/O Tyrion/O mightily/O .../O though/O he/O rather/O wished/O it/O had/O not/O been/O this/O inn/O again/O ,/O with/O all/O its/O memories/O ./O 
His/O father/O had/O set/O a/O grueling/O pace/O ,/O and/O it/O had/O taken/O its/O toll/O ./O 
Men/O wounded/O in/O the/O battle/O kept/O up/O as/O best/O they/O could/O or/O were/O abandoned/O to/O fend/O for/O themselves/O ./O 
Every/O morning/O they/O left/O a/O few/O more/O by/O the/O roadside/O ,/O men/O who/O went/O to/O sleep/O never/O to/O wake/O ./O 
Every/O afternoon/O a/O few/O more/O collapsed/O along/O the/O way/O ./O 
And/O every/O evening/O a/O few/O more/O deserted/O ,/O stealing/O off/O into/O the/O dusk/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O been/O half-tempted/O to/O go/O with/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O been/O upstairs/O ,/O enjoying/O the/O comfort/O of/O a/O featherbed/O and/O the/O warmth/O of/O Shae/PERSON 's/O body/O beside/O him/O ,/O when/O his/O squire/O had/O woken/O him/O to/O say/O that/O a/O rider/O had/O arrived/O with/O dire/O news/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
So/O it/O had/O all/O been/O for/O nothing/O ./O 
The/O rush/O south/O ,/O the/O endless/O forced/O marches/O ,/O the/O bodies/O left/O beside/O the/O road/O .../O all/O for/O naught/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O reached/O Riverrun/LOCATION days/O and/O days/O ago/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O could/O this/O happen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Harys/PERSON Swyft/PERSON moaned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O ?/O 
Even/O after/O the/O Whispering/PERSON Wood/PERSON ,/O you/O had/O Riverrun/PERSON ringed/O in/O iron/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O a/O great/O host/O .../O what/O madness/O made/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON decide/O to/O split/O his/O men/O into/O three/O separate/O camps/O ?/O 
Surely/O he/O knew/O how/O vulnerable/O that/O would/O leave/O them/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Better/O than/O you/O ,/O you/O chinless/O craven/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON might/O have/O lost/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O but/O it/O angered/O him/O to/O hear/O his/O brother/O slandered/O by/O the/O likes/O of/O Swyft/LOCATION ,/O a/O shameless/O lickspittle/O whose/O greatest/O accomplishment/O was/O marrying/O his/O equally/O chinless/O daughter/O to/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON ,/O and/O thereby/O attaching/O himself/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O have/O done/O the/O same/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O uncle/O responded/O ,/O a/O good/O deal/O more/O calmly/O than/O Tyrion/O might/O have/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O never/O seen/O Riverrun/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Harys/PERSON ,/O or/O you/O would/O know/O that/O Jaime/PERSON had/O little/O choice/O in/O the/O matter/O ./O 
The/O castle/O is/O situated/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O point/O of/O land/O where/O the/O Tumblestone/LOCATION flows/O into/O the/O Red/O Fork/O of/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
The/O rivers/O form/O two/O sides/O of/O a/O triangle/O ,/O and/O when/O danger/O threatens/O ,/O the/O Tullys/O open/O their/O sluice/O gates/O upstream/O to/O create/O a/O wide/O moat/O on/O the/O third/O side/O ,/O turning/O Riverrun/PERSON into/O an/O island/O ./O 
The/O walls/O rise/O sheer/O from/O the/O water/O ,/O and/O from/O their/O towers/O the/O defenders/O have/O a/O commanding/O view/O of/O the/O opposite/O shores/O for/O many/O leagues/O around/O ./O 
To/O cut/O off/O all/O the/O approaches/O ,/O a/O besieger/O must/O needs/O place/O one/O camp/O north/O of/O the/O Tumblestone/LOCATION ,/O one/O south/O of/O the/O Red/O Fork/O ,/O and/O a/O third/O between/O the/O rivers/O ,/O west/O of/O the/O moat/O ./O 
There/O is/O no/O other/O way/O ,/O none/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON speaks/O truly/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O courier/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 'd/O built/O palisades/O of/O sharpened/O stakes/O around/O the/O camps/O ,/O yet/O it/O was/O not/O enough/O ,/O not/O with/O no/O warning/O and/O the/O rivers/O cutting/O us/O off/O from/O each/O other/O ./O 
They/O came/O down/O on/O the/O north/O camp/O first/O ./O 
No/O one/O was/O expecting/O an/O attack/O ./O 
Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON had/O been/O raiding/O our/O supply/O trains/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O no/O more/O than/O fifty/O men/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON had/O gone/O out/O to/O deal/O with/O them/O the/O night/O before/O .../O well/O ,/O with/O what/O we/O thought/O was/O them/O ./O 
We/O were/O told/O the/O Stark/O host/O was/O east/O of/O the/O Green/LOCATION Fork/LOCATION ,/O marching/O south/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O your/O outriders/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON 's/O face/O might/O have/O been/O hewn/O from/O rock/O ./O 
The/O fire/O in/O the/O hearth/O gave/O a/O somber/O orange/O cast/O to/O his/O skin/O and/O put/O deep/O shadows/O in/O the/O hollows/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O saw/O nothing/O ?/O 
They/O gave/O you/O no/O warning/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O bloodstained/O messenger/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Our/O outriders/O had/O been/O vanishing/O ./O 
Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON 's/O work/O ,/O we/O thought/O ./O 
The/O ones/O who/O did/O come/O back/O had/O seen/O nothing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O man/O who/O sees/O nothing/O has/O no/O use/O for/O his/O eyes/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Mountain/O declared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cut/O them/O out/O and/O give/O them/O to/O your/O next/O outrider/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O you/O hope/O that/O four/O eyes/O might/O see/O better/O than/O two/O .../O and/O if/O not/O ,/O the/O man/O after/O him/O will/O have/O six/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON turned/O his/O face/O to/O study/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON ./O 
Tyrion/O saw/O a/O glimmer/O of/O gold/O as/O the/O light/O shone/O off/O his/O father/O 's/O pupils/O ,/O but/O he/O could/O not/O have/O said/O whether/O the/O look/O was/O one/O of/O approval/O or/O disgust/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON was/O oft/O quiet/O in/O council/O ,/O preferring/O to/O listen/O before/O he/O spoke/O ,/O a/O habit/O Tyrion/O himself/O tried/O to/O emulate/O ./O 
Yet/O this/O silence/O was/O uncharacteristic/O even/O for/O him/O ,/O and/O his/O wine/O was/O untouched/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O said/O they/O came/O at/O night/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON prompted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O man/O gave/O a/O weary/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Blackfish/O led/O the/O van/O ,/O cutting/O down/O our/O sentries/O and/O clearing/O away/O the/O palisades/O for/O the/O main/O assault/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O our/O men/O knew/O what/O was/O happening/O ,/O riders/O were/O pouring/O over/O the/O ditch/O banks/O and/O galloping/O through/O the/O camp/O with/O swords/O and/O torches/O in/O hand/O ./O 
I/O was/O sleeping/O in/O the/O west/O camp/O ,/O between/O the/O rivers/O ./O 
When/O we/O heard/O the/O fighting/O and/O saw/O the/O tents/O being/O fired/O ,/O Lord/O Brax/PERSON led/O us/O to/O the/O rafts/O and/O we/O tried/O to/O pole/O across/O ,/O but/O the/O current/O pushed/O us/O downstream/O and/O the/O Tullys/O started/O flinging/O rocks/O at/O us/O with/O the/O catapults/O on/O their/O walls/O ./O 
I/O saw/O one/O raft/O smashed/O to/O kindling/O and/O three/O others/O overturned/O ,/O men/O swept/O into/O the/O river/O and/O drowned/O .../O and/O those/O who/O did/O make/O it/O across/O found/O the/O Starks/PERSON waiting/O for/O them/O on/O the/O riverbanks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Flement/O Brax/O wore/O a/O silver-and-purple/O tabard/O and/O the/O look/O of/O a/O man/O who/O can/O not/O comprehend/O what/O he/O has/O just/O heard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sorry/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O messenger/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Brax/PERSON was/O clad/O in/O plate-and-mail/O when/O his/O raft/O overturned/O ./O 
He/O was/O very/O gallant/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O a/O fool/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O swirling/O his/O cup/O and/O staring/O down/O into/O the/O winy/O depths/O ./O 
Crossing/O a/O river/O at/O night/O on/O a/O crude/O raft/O ,/O wearing/O armor/O ,/O with/O an/O enemy/O waiting/O on/O the/O other/O side/O -/O if/O that/O was/O gallantry/O ,/O he/O would/O take/O cowardice/O every/O time/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O if/O Lord/O Brax/PERSON had/O felt/O especially/O gallant/O as/O the/O weight/O of/O his/O steel/O pulled/O him/O under/O the/O black/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O camp/O between/O the/O rivers/O was/O overrun/O as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O messenger/O was/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O While/O we/O were/O trying/O to/O cross/O ,/O more/O Starks/PERSON swept/O in/O from/O the/O west/O ,/O two/O columns/O of/O armored/O horse/O ./O 
I/O saw/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Umber/O 's/O giant-in-chains/O and/O the/O Mallister/O eagle/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O the/O boy/O who/O led/O them/O ,/O with/O a/O monstrous/O wolf/O running/O at/O his/O side/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O there/O to/O see/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O said/O the/O beast/O killed/O four/O men/O and/O ripped/O apart/O a/O dozen/O horses/O ./O 
Our/O spearmen/O formed/O up/O a/O shieldwall/O and/O held/O against/O their/O first/O charge/O ,/O but/O when/O the/O Tullys/O saw/O them/O engaged/O ,/O they/O opened/O the/O gates/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION and/O Tytos/PERSON Blackwood/PERSON led/O a/O sortie/O across/O the/O drawbridge/O and/O took/O them/O in/O the/O rear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O save/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON swore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Greatjon/O Umber/O fired/O the/O siege/O towers/O we/O were/O building/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON found/O Ser/PERSON Edmure/PERSON Tully/PERSON in/O chains/O among/O the/O other/O captives/O ,/O and/O made/O off/O with/O them/O all/O ./O 
Our/O south/O camp/O was/O under/O the/O command/O of/O Ser/O Forley/O Prester/O ./O 
He/O retreated/O in/O good/O order/O when/O he/O saw/O that/O the/O other/O camps/O were/O lost/O ,/O with/O two/O thousand/O spears/O and/O as/O many/O bowmen/O ,/O but/O the/O Tyroshi/O sellsword/O who/O led/O his/O freeriders/O struck/O his/O banners/O and/O went/O over/O to/O the/O foe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Curse/O the/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O uncle/O Kevan/PERSON sounded/O more/O angry/O than/O surprised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O warned/O Jaime/PERSON not/O to/O trust/O that/O one/O ./O 
A/O man/O who/O fights/O for/O coin/O is/O loyal/O only/O to/O his/O purse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON wove/O his/O fingers/O together/O under/O his/O chin/O ./O 
Only/O his/O eyes/O moved/O as/O he/O listened/O ./O 
His/O bristling/O golden/O side-whiskers/O framed/O a/O face/O so/O still/O it/O might/O have/O been/O a/O mask/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O see/O tiny/O beads/O of/O sweat/O dappling/O his/O father/O 's/O shaven/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O could/O it/O happen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Harys/PERSON Swyft/PERSON wailed/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Jaime/O taken/O ,/O the/O siege/O broken/O .../O this/O is/O a/O catastrophe/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Addarn/O Marbrand/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O sure/O we/O are/O all/O grateful/O to/O you/O for/O pointing/O out/O the/O obvious/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Harys/PERSON ./O 
The/O question/O is/O ,/O what/O shall/O we/O do/O about/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O can/O we/O do/O ?/O 
Jaime/PERSON 's/O host/O is/O all/O slaughtered/O or/O taken/O or/O put/O to/O flight/O ,/O and/O the/O Starks/PERSON and/O the/O Tullys/O sit/O squarely/O across/O our/O line/O of/O supply/O ./O 
We/O are/O cut/O off/O from/O the/O west/O !/O 
They/O can/O march/O on/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION if/O they/O so/O choose/O ,/O and/O what/O 's/O to/O stop/O them/O ?/O 
My/O lords/O ,/O we/O are/O beaten/O ./O 
We/O must/O sue/O for/O peace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Peace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON swirled/O his/O wine/O thoughtfully/O ,/O took/O a/O deep/O draft/O ,/O and/O hurled/O his/O empty/O cup/O to/O the/O floor/O ,/O where/O it/O shattered/O into/O a/O thousand/O pieces/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O your/O peace/O ,/O Ser/O Harys/O ./O 
My/O sweet/O nephew/O broke/O it/O for/O good/O and/O all/O when/O he/O decided/O to/O ornament/O the/O Red/O Keep/O with/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O head/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O have/O an/O easier/O time/O drinking/O wine/O from/O that/O cup/O than/O you/O will/O convincing/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON to/O make/O peace/O now/O ./O 
He/O 's/O winning/O .../O or/O had/O n't/O you/O noticed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Two/O battles/O do/O not/O make/O a/O war/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O far/O from/O lost/O ./O 
I/O should/O welcome/O the/O chance/O to/O try/O my/O own/O steel/O against/O this/O Stark/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O they/O would/O consent/O to/O a/O truce/O ,/O and/O allow/O us/O to/O trade/O our/O prisoners/O for/O theirs/O ,/O \/O ''/O offered/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unless/O they/O trade/O three-for-one/O ,/O we/O still/O come/O out/O light/O on/O those/O scales/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O acidly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O are/O we/O to/O offer/O for/O my/O brother/O ?/O 
Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O rotting/O head/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O heard/O that/O Queen/PERSON Cersei/PERSON has/O the/O Hand/O 's/O daughters/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lefford/PERSON said/O hopefully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O give/O the/O lad/O his/O sisters/O back/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Addam/O snorted/O disdainfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O have/O to/O be/O an/O utter/O ass/O to/O trade/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O life/O for/O two/O girls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O we/O must/O ransom/O Ser/O Jaime/O ,/O whatever/O it/O costs/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O rolled/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O Starks/PERSON feel/O the/O need/O for/O gold/O ,/O they/O can/O melt/O down/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O armor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O if/O we/O ask/O for/O a/O truce/O ,/O they/O will/O think/O us/O weak/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Addarn/PERSON argued/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O should/O march/O on/O them/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Surely/O our/O friends/O at/O court/O could/O be/O prevailed/O upon/O to/O join/O us/O with/O fresh/O troops/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/O Harys/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O someone/O might/O return/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION to/O raise/O a/O new/O host/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON rose/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O have/O my/O son/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O once/O more/O ,/O in/O a/O voice/O that/O cut/O through/O the/O babble/O like/O a/O sword/O through/O suet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Leave/O me/O ./O 
All/O of/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ever/O the/O soul/O of/O obedience/O ,/O Tyrion/O rose/O to/O depart/O with/O the/O rest/O ,/O but/O his/O father/O gave/O him/O a/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O you/O ,/O Tyrion/O ./O 
Remain/O ./O 
And/O you/O as/O well/O ,/O Kevan/PERSON ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O you/O ,/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O eased/O himself/O back/O onto/O the/O bench/O ,/O startled/O into/O speechlessness/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON crossed/O the/O room/O to/O the/O wine/O casks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Uncle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O called/O ,/O \/O ``/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O father/O offered/O him/O his/O cup/O ,/O the/O wine/O untouched/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O Tyrion/O truly/O was/O nonplussed/O ./O 
He/O drank/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON seated/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O the/O right/O of/O it/O about/O Stark/O ./O 
Alive/O ,/O we/O might/O have/O used/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON to/O forge/O a/O peace/O with/O Winterfell/PERSON and/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O a/O peace/O that/O would/O have/O given/O us/O the/O time/O we/O need/O to/O deal/O with/O Robert/PERSON 's/O brothers/O ./O 
Dead/O His/O hand/O curled/O into/O a/O fist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Madness/O ./O 
Rank/O madness/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Joff/PERSON s/O only/O a/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O his/O age/O ,/O I/O committed/O a/O few/O follies/O of/O my/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O father/O gave/O him/O a/O sharp/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O we/O ought/O to/O be/O grateful/O that/O he/O has/O not/O yet/O married/O a/O whore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O sipped/O at/O his/O wine/O ,/O wondering/O how/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON would/O look/O if/O he/O flung/O the/O cup/O in/O his/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Our/O position/O is/O worse/O than/O you/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O we/O have/O a/O new/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Kevan/PERSON looked/O poleaxed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O new-who/O ?/O 
What/O have/O they/O done/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O faintest/O flicker/O of/O distaste/O played/O across/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O thin/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nothing/O .../O yet/O ./O 
My/O grandson/O still/O sits/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O but/O the/O eunuch/O has/O heard/O whispers/O from/O the/O south/O ./O 
Renly/O Baratheon/O wed/O Margaery/ORGANIZATION Tyrell/ORGANIZATION at/O Highgarden/LOCATION this/O fortnight/O past/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O has/O claimed/O the/O crown/O ./O 
The/O bride/O 's/O father/O and/O brothers/O have/O bent/O the/O knee/O and/O sworn/O him/O their/O swords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Those/O are/O grave/O tidings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O When/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON frowned/O ,/O the/O furrows/O in/O his/O brow/O grew/O deep/O as/O canyons/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O daughter/O commands/O us/O to/O ride/O for/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O at/O once/O ,/O to/O defend/O the/O Red/O Keep/O against/O King/O Renly/O and/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O mouth/O tightened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Commands/O us/O ,/O mind/O you/O ./O 
In/O the/O name/O of/O the/O king/O and/O council/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O is/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON taking/O the/O news/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O with/O a/O certain/O black/O amusement/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON has/O not/O seen/O fit/O to/O tell/O him/O yet/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O fears/O he/O might/O insist/O on/O marching/O against/O Renly/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O With/O what/O army/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O plan/O to/O give/O him/O this/O one/O ,/O I/O hope/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O talks/O of/O leading/O the/O City/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O takes/O the/O Watch/O ,/O he/O 'll/O leave/O the/O city/O undefended/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O with/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON on/O Dragonstone/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON looked/O down/O at/O his/O son/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O thought/O you/O were/O the/O one/O made/O for/O motley/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O but/O it/O would/O appear/O that/O I/O was/O wrong/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Tyrion/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O that/O almost/O sounds/O like/O praise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O forward/O intently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O of/O Stannis/O ?/O 
He/O 's/O the/O elder/O ,/O not/O Renly/O ./O 
How/O does/O he/O feel/O about/O his/O brother/O 's/O claim/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O father/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O felt/O from/O the/O beginning/O that/O Stannis/PERSON was/O a/O greater/O danger/O than/O all/O the/O others/O combined/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O does/O nothing/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O Varys/PERSON hears/O his/O whispers/O ./O 
Stannis/O is/O building/O ships/O ,/O Stannis/O is/O hiring/O sellswords/O ,/O Stannis/O is/O bringing/O a/O shadowbinder/O from/O Asshai/LOCATION ./O 
What/O does/O it/O mean/O ?/O 
Is/O any/O of/O it/O true/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O an/O irritated/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kevan/PERSON ,/O bring/O us/O the/O map/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON did/O as/O he/O was/O bid/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON unrolled/O the/O leather/O ,/O smoothing/O it/O flat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON has/O left/O us/O in/O a/O bad/O way/O ./O 
Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON and/O the/O remnants/O of/O his/O host/O are/O north/O of/O us/O ./O 
Our/O enemies/O hold/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION and/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ./O 
Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON sits/O to/O the/O west/O ,/O so/O we/O can/O not/O retreat/O to/O Lannisport/LOCATION and/O the/O Rock/O unless/O we/O choose/O to/O give/O battle/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON is/O taken/O ,/O and/O his/O army/O for/O all/O purposes/O has/O ceased/O to/O exist/O ./O 
Thoros/O of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION and/O Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON continue/O to/O plague/O our/O foraging/O parties/O ./O 
To/O our/O east/O we/O have/O the/O Arryns/O ,/O Stannis/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON sits/O on/O Dragonstone/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O south/O Highgarden/LOCATION and/O Storm/O 's/O End/O are/O calling/O their/O banners/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O smiled/O crookedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O heart/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
At/O least/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON is/O still/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O hoped/O you/O might/O have/O more/O to/O offer/O us/O than/O japes/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON frowned/O over/O the/O map/O ,/O forehead/O creasing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON will/O have/O Edmure/PERSON Tully/PERSON and/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O Trident/O with/O him/O now/O ./O 
Their/O combined/O power/O may/O exceed/O our/O own/O ./O 
And/O with/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON behind/O us/O .../O Tywin/O ,/O if/O we/O remain/O here/O ,/O I/O fear/O we/O might/O be/O caught/O between/O three/O armies/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O no/O intention/O of/O remaining/O here/O ./O 
We/O must/O finish/O our/O business/O with/O young/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON before/O Renly/O Baratheon/O can/O march/O from/O Highgarden/LOCATION ./O 
Bolton/PERSON does/O not/O concern/O me/O ./O 
He/O is/O a/O wary/O man/O ,/O and/O we/O made/O him/O warier/O on/O the/O Green/LOCATION Fork/LOCATION ./O 
He/O will/O be/O slow/O to/O give/O pursuit/O ./O 
So/O .../O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O we/O make/O for/O Harrenhal/O ./O 
Kevan/PERSON ,/O I/O want/O Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON 's/O outriders/O to/O screen/O our/O movements/O ./O 
Give/O him/O as/O many/O men/O as/O he/O requires/O ,/O and/O send/O them/O out/O in/O groups/O of/O four/O ./O 
I/O will/O have/O no/O vanishings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O .../O why/O Harrenhal/PERSON ?/O 
That/O is/O a/O grim/O ,/O unlucky/O place/O ./O 
Some/O call/O it/O cursed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Unleash/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON and/O send/O him/O before/O us/O with/O his/O reavers/O ./O 
Send/O forth/O Vargo/PERSON Hoat/PERSON and/O his/O freeriders/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Amory/PERSON Lorch/PERSON ./O 
Each/O is/O to/O have/O three/O hundred/O horse/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O I/O want/O to/O see/O the/O riverlands/O afire/O from/O the/O Gods/O Eye/O to/O the/O Red/O Fork/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O will/O burn/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ,/O rising/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O give/O the/O commands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O bowed/O and/O made/O for/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O they/O were/O alone/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON glanced/O at/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O savages/O might/O relish/O a/O bit/O of/O rapine/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O they/O may/O ride/O with/O Vargo/PERSON Hoat/PERSON and/O plunder/O as/O they/O like-goods/O ,/O stock/O ,/O women/O ,/O they/O may/O take/O what/O they/O want/O and/O burn/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Telling/O Shagga/O and/O Timett/PERSON how/O to/O pillage/O is/O like/O telling/O a/O rooster/O how/O to/O crow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON commented/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O should/O prefer/O to/O keep/O them/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Uncouth/O and/O unruly/O they/O might/O be/O ,/O yet/O the/O wildlings/O were/O his/O ,/O and/O he/O trusted/O them/O more/O than/O any/O of/O his/O father/O 's/O men/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O about/O to/O hand/O them/O over/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O you/O had/O best/O learn/O to/O control/O them/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O have/O the/O city/O plundered/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O city/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O city/O would/O that/O be/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O King/O 's/O Landing/O ./O 
I/O am/O sending/O you/O to/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O last/O thing/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O would/O ever/O have/O anticipated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O reached/O for/O his/O wine/O ,/O and/O considered/O for/O a/O moment/O as/O he/O sipped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O am/O I/O to/O do/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rule/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O curtly/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O hooted/O with/O laughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sweet/O sister/O might/O have/O a/O word/O or/O two/O to/O say/O about/O that/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O her/O say/O what/O she/O likes/O ./O 
Her/O son/O needs/O to/O be/O taken/O in/O hand/O before/O he/O ruins/O us/O all/O ./O 
I/O blame/O those/O jackanapes/O on/O the/O council-our/O friend/O Petyr/PERSON ,/O the/O venerable/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION ,/O and/O that/O cockless/O wonder/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
What/O sort/O of/O counsel/O are/O they/O giving/O Joffrey/PERSON when/O he/O lurches/O from/O one/O folly/O to/O the/O next/O ?/O 
Whose/O notion/O was/O it/O to/O make/O this/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON a/O lord/O ?/O 
The/O man/O 's/O father/O was/O a/O butcher/O ,/O and/O they/O grant/O him/O Harrenhal/O ./O 
Harrenhal/PERSON ,/O that/O was/O the/O seat/O of/O kings/O !/O 
Not/O that/O he/O will/O ever/O set/O foot/O inside/O it/O ,/O if/O I/O have/O a/O say/O ./O 
I/O am/O told/O he/O took/O a/O bloody/O spear/O for/O his/O sigil/O ./O 
A/O bloody/O cleaver/O would/O have/O been/O my/O choice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O father/O had/O not/O raised/O his/O voice/O ,/O yet/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O see/O the/O anger/O in/O the/O gold/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O dismissing/O Selmy/O ,/O where/O was/O the/O sense/O in/O that/O ?/O 
Yes/O ,/O the/O man/O was/O old/O ,/O but/O the/O name/O of/O Barristan/LOCATION the/O Bold/O still/O has/O meaning/O in/O the/O realm/O ./O 
He/O lent/O honor/O to/O any/O man/O he/O served/O ./O 
Can/O anyone/O say/O the/O same/O of/O the/O Hound/O ?/O 
You/O feed/O your/O dog/O bones/O under/O the/O table/O ,/O you/O do/O not/O seat/O him/O beside/O you/O on/O the/O high/O bench/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pointed/O a/O finger/O at/O Tyrion/ORGANIZATION 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Cersei/O can/O not/O curb/O the/O boy/O ,/O you/O must/O ./O 
And/O if/O these/O councillors/O are/O playing/O us/O false/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O knew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Spikes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Heads/O ./O 
Walls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O you/O have/O taken/O a/O few/O lessons/O from/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O More/O than/O you/O know/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O answered/O quietly/O ./O 
He/O finished/O his/O wine/O and/O set/O the/O cup/O aside/O ,/O thoughtful/O ./O 
A/O part/O of/O him/O was/O more/O pleased/O than/O he/O cared/O to/O admit/O ./O 
Another/O part/O was/O remembering/O the/O battle/O upriver/O ,/O and/O wondering/O if/O he/O was/O being/O sent/O to/O hold/O the/O left/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ,/O cocking/O his/O head/O to/O one/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O not/O my/O uncle/O ?/O 
Why/O not/O Ser/O Addam/O or/O Ser/O Flement/O or/O Lord/O Serrett/PERSON ?/O 
Why/O not/O a./O ./O 
./O 
bigger/O man/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON rose/O abruptly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O my/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O was/O when/O he/O knew/O ./O 
You/O have/O given/O him/O up/O for/O lost/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
You/O bloody/O bastard/O ,/O you/O think/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O good/O as/O dead/O ,/O so/O I/O 'm/O all/O you/O have/O left/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON wanted/O to/O slap/O him/O ,/O to/O spit/O in/O his/O face/O ,/O to/O draw/O his/O dagger/O and/O cut/O the/O heart/O out/O of/O him/O and/O see/O if/O it/O was/O made/O of/O old/O hard/O gold/O ,/O the/O way/O the/O smallfolks/O said/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O sat/O there/O ,/O silent/O and/O still/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O shards/O of/O the/O broken/O cup/O crunched/O beneath/O his/O father/O 's/O heels/O as/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON crossed/O the/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O One/O last/O thing/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O not/O take/O the/O whore/O to/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O sat/O alone/O in/O the/O common/O room/O for/O a/O long/O while/O after/O his/O father/O was/O gone/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O climbed/O the/O steps/O to/O his/O cozy/O garret/O beneath/O the/O bell/O tower/O ./O 
The/O ceiling/O was/O low/O ,/O but/O that/O was/O scarcely/O a/O drawback/O for/O a/O dwarf/O ./O 
From/O the/O window/O ,/O he/O could/O see/O the/O gibbet/O his/O father/O had/O erected/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
The/O innkeep/O 's/O body/O turned/O slowly/O on/O its/O rope/O whenever/O the/O night/O wind/O gusted/O ./O 
Her/O flesh/O had/O grown/O as/O thin/O and/O ragged/O as/O Lannister/O hopes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Shae/PERSON murmured/O sleepily/O and/O rolled/O toward/O him/O when/O he/O sat/O on/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O featherbed/O ./O 
He/O slid/O his/O hand/O under/O the/O blanket/O and/O cupped/O a/O soft/O breast/O ,/O and/O her/O eyes/O opened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O M'lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O with/O a/O drowsy/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O felt/O her/O nipple/O stiffen/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON kissed/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O a/O mind/O to/O take/O you/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O sweetling/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
