-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O had/O left/O before/O dawn/O ,/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON informed/O Sansa/O as/O they/O broke/O their/O fast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O sent/O for/O him/O ./O 
Another/O hunt/O ,/O I/O do/O believe/O ./O 
There/O are/O still/O wild/O aurochs/O in/O these/O lands/O ,/O I/O am/O told/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O never/O seen/O an/O aurochs/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O feeding/O a/O piece/O of/O bacon/O to/O Lady/O under/O the/O table/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O took/O it/O from/O her/O hand/O ,/O as/O delicate/O as/O a/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/O sniffed/O in/O disapproval/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O noble/O lady/O does/O not/O feed/O dogs/O at/O her/O table/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O breaking/O off/O another/O piece/O of/O comb/O and/O letting/O the/O honey/O drip/O down/O onto/O her/O bread/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O not/O a/O dog/O ,/O she/O 's/O a/O direwolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON pointed/O out/O as/O Lady/O licked/O her/O fingers/O with/O a/O rough/O tongue/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Anyway/O ,/O Father/PERSON said/O we/O could/O keep/O them/O with/O us/O if/O we/O want/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O septa/O was/O not/O appeased/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O a/O good/O girl/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O but/O I/O do/O vow/O ,/O when/O it/O comes/O to/O that/O creature/O you/O 're/O as/O willful/O as/O your/O sister/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O scowled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O where/O is/O Arya/PERSON this/O morning/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O n't/O hungry/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O knowing/O full/O well/O that/O her/O sister/O had/O probably/O stolen/O down/O to/O the/O kitchen/O hours/O ago/O and/O wheedled/O a/O breakfast/O out/O of/O some/O cook/O 's/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O remind/O her/O to/O dress/O nicely/O today/O ./O 
The/O grey/O velvet/O ,/O perhaps/O ./O 
We/O are/O all/O invited/O to/O ride/O with/O the/O queen/O and/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON in/O the/O royal/O wheelhouse/O ,/O and/O we/O must/O look/O our/O best/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O already/O looked/O her/O best/O ./O 
She/O had/O brushed/O out/O her/O long/O auburn/O hair/O until/O it/O shone/O ,/O and/O picked/O her/O nicest/O blue/O silks/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O looking/O forward/O to/O today/O for/O more/O than/O a/O week/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O great/O honor/O to/O ride/O with/O the/O queen/O ,/O and/O besides/O ,/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON might/O be/O there/O ./O 
Her/O betrothed/O ./O 
Just/O thinking/O it/O made/O her/O feel/O a/O strange/O fluttering/O inside/O ,/O even/O though/O they/O were/O not/O to/O marry/O for/O years/O and/O years/O ./O 
Sansa/O did/O not/O really/O know/O Joffrey/PERSON yet/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O already/O in/O love/O with/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O all/O she/O ever/O dreamt/O her/O prince/O should/O be/O ,/O tall/O and/O handsome/O and/O strong/O ,/O with/O hair/O like/O gold/O ./O 
She/O treasured/O every/O chance/O to/O spend/O time/O with/O him/O ,/O few/O as/O they/O were/O ./O 
The/O only/O thing/O that/O scared/O her/O about/O today/O was/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O a/O way/O of/O ruining/O everything/O ./O 
You/O never/O knew/O what/O she/O would/O do/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O tell/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O uncertainly/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O she/O 'll/O dress/O the/O way/O she/O always/O does/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O hoped/O it/O would/O n't/O be/O too/O embarrassing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O I/O be/O excused/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O may/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON helped/O herself/O to/O more/O bread/O and/O honey/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON slid/O from/O the/O bench/O ./O 
Lady/O followed/O at/O her/O heels/O as/O she/O ran/O from/O the/O inn/O 's/O common/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O ,/O she/O stood/O for/O a/O moment/O amidst/O the/O shouts/O and/O curses/O and/O the/O creak/O of/O wooden/O wheels/O as/O the/O men/O broke/O down/O the/O tents/O and/O pavilions/O and/O loaded/O the/O wagons/O for/O another/O day/O 's/O march/O ./O 
The/O inn/O was/O a/O sprawling/O three-story/O structure/O of/O pale/O stone/O ,/O the/O biggest/O that/O Sansa/PERSON had/O ever/O seen/O ,/O but/O even/O so/O ,/O it/O had/O accommodations/O for/O less/O than/O a/O third/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O party/O ,/O which/O had/O swollen/O to/O more/O than/O four/O hundred/O with/O the/O addition/O of/O her/O father/O 's/O household/O and/O the/O freeriders/O who/O had/O joined/O them/O on/O the/O road/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O found/O Arya/PERSON on/O the/O banks/O of/O the/O Trident/O ,/O trying/O to/O hold/O Nymeria/LOCATION still/O while/O she/O brushed/O dried/O mud/O from/O her/O fur/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O was/O not/O enjoying/O the/O process/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O wearing/O the/O same/O riding/O leathers/O she/O had/O worn/O yesterday/O and/O the/O day/O before/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O better/O put/O on/O something/O pretty/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON said/O so/O ./O 
We/O 're/O traveling/O in/O the/O queen/O 's/O wheelhouse/O with/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ,/O trying/O to/O brush/O a/O tangle/O out/O of/O Nymeria/LOCATION 's/O matted/O grey/O fur/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mycah/O and/O I/O are/O going/O to/O ride/O upstream/O and/O look/O for/O rubies/O at/O the/O ford/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rubies/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O said/O ,/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O rubies/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O look/O like/O she/O was/O so/O stupid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaegar/O 's/O rubies/O ./O 
This/O is/O where/O King/O Robert/PERSON killed/O him/O and/O won/O the/O crown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O regarded/O her/O scrawny/O little/O sister/O in/O disbelief/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O look/O for/O rubies/O ,/O the/O princess/O is/O expecting/O us/O ./O 
The/O queen/O invited/O us/O both/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wheelhouse/O does/O n't/O even/O have/O windows/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O see/O a/O thing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O could/O you/O want/O to/O see/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O annoyed/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O thrilled/O by/O the/O invitation/O ,/O and/O her/O stupid/O sister/O was/O going/O to/O ruin/O everything/O ,/O just/O as/O she/O 'd/O feared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O all/O just/O fields/O and/O farms/O and/O holdfasts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O stubbornly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O came/O with/O us/O sometimes/O ,/O you/O 'd/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hate/O riding/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O fervently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O it/O does/O is/O get/O you/O soiled/O and/O dusty/O and/O sore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hold/O still/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O snapped/O at/O Nymeria/LOCATION ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O hurting/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Then/O to/O Sansa/PERSON she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O When/O we/O were/O crossing/O the/O Neck/O ,/O I/O counted/O thirty-six/O flowers/O I/O never/O saw/O before/O ,/O and/O Mycah/PERSON showed/O me/O a/O lizard-lion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O shuddered/O ./O 
They/O had/O been/O twelve/O days/O crossing/O the/O Neck/O ,/O rumbling/O down/O a/O crooked/O causeway/O through/O an/O endless/O black/O bog/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O hated/O every/O moment/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O air/O had/O been/O damp/O and/O clammy/O ,/O the/O causeway/O so/O narrow/O they/O could/O not/O even/O make/O proper/O camp/O at/O night/O ,/O they/O had/O to/O stop/O right/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
Dense/O thickets/O of/O halfdrowned/O trees/O pressed/O close/O around/O them/O ,/O branches/O dripping/O with/O curtains/O of/O pale/O fungus/O ./O 
Huge/O flowers/O bloomed/O in/O the/O mud/O and/O floated/O on/O pools/O of/O stagnant/O water/O ,/O but/O if/O you/O were/O stupid/O enough/O to/O leave/O the/O causeway/O to/O pluck/O them/O ,/O there/O were/O quicksands/O waiting/O to/O suck/O you/O down/O ,/O and/O snakes/O watching/O from/O the/O trees/O ,/O and/O lizard-lions/O floating/O half-submerged/O in/O the/O water/O ,/O like/O black/O logs/O with/O eyes/O and/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O None/O of/O which/O stopped/O Arya/PERSON ,/O of/O course/O ./O 
One/O day/O she/O came/O back/O grinning/O her/O horsey/O grin/O ,/O her/O hair/O all/O tangled/O and/O her/O clothes/O covered/O in/O mud/O ,/O clutching/O a/O raggedy/O bunch/O of/O purple/O and/O green/O flowers/O for/O Father/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON kept/O hoping/O he/O would/O tell/O Arya/PERSON to/O behave/O herself/O and/O act/O like/O the/O highborn/O lady/O she/O was/O supposed/O to/O be/O ,/O but/O he/O never/O did/O ,/O he/O only/O hugged/O her/O and/O thanked/O her/O for/O the/O flowers/O ./O 
That/O just/O made/O her/O worse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O it/O turned/O out/O the/O purple/O flowers/O were/O called/O poison/O kisses/O ,/O and/O Arya/PERSON got/O a/O rash/O on/O her/O arms/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON would/O have/O thought/O that/O might/O have/O taught/O her/O a/O lesson/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON laughed/O about/O it/O ,/O and/O the/O next/O day/O she/O rubbed/O mud/O all/O over/O her/O arms/O like/O some/O ignorant/O bog/O woman/O just/O because/O her/O friend/O Mycah/PERSON told/O her/O it/O would/O stop/O the/O itching/O ./O 
She/O had/O bruises/O on/O her/O arms/O and/O shoulders/O too/O ,/O dark/O purple/O welts/O and/O faded/O green-and/O -/O yellow/O splotches/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON had/O seen/O them/O when/O her/O sister/O undressed/O for/O sleep/O ./O 
How/O she/O had/O gotten/O those/O only/O the/O seven/O gods/O knew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON was/O still/O going/O on/O ,/O brushing/O out/O Nymeria/LOCATION 's/O tangles/O and/O chattering/O about/O things/O she/O 'd/O seen/O on/O the/O trek/O south/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Last/O week/O we/O found/O this/O haunted/O watchtower/O ,/O and/O the/O day/O before/O we/O chased/O a/O herd/O of/O wild/O horses/O ./O 
You/O should/O have/O seen/O them/O run/O when/O they/O caught/O a/O scent/O of/O Nymeria/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O wolf/O wriggled/O in/O her/O grasp/O and/O Arya/PERSON scolded/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O that/O ,/O I/O have/O to/O do/O the/O other/O side/O ,/O you/O 're/O all/O muddy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O not/O supposed/O to/O leave/O the/O column/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O reminded/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O said/O so/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O go/O far/O ./O 
Anyway/O ,/O Nymeria/LOCATION was/O with/O me/O the/O whole/O time/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O always/O go/O off/O ,/O either/O ./O 
Sometimes/O it/O 's/O fun/O just/O to/O ride/O along/O with/O the/O wagons/O and/O talk/O to/O people/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O knew/O all/O about/O the/O sorts/O of/O people/O Arya/PERSON liked/O to/O talk/O to/O :/O squires/O and/O grooms/O and/O serving/O girls/O ,/O old/O men/O and/O naked/O children/O ,/O rough-spoken/O freeriders/O of/O uncertain/O birth/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON would/O make/O friends/O with/O anybody/O ./O 
This/O Mycah/PERSON was/O the/O worst/O ;/O a/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ,/O thirteen/O and/O wild/O ,/O he/O slept/O in/O the/O meat/O wagon/O and/O smelled/O of/O the/O slaughtering/O block/O ./O 
Just/O the/O sight/O of/O him/O was/O enough/O to/O make/O Sansa/O feel/O sick/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON seemed/O to/O prefer/O his/O company/O to/O hers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O was/O running/O out/O of/O patience/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O to/O come/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O her/O sister/O firmly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O refuse/O the/O queen/O ./O 
Septa/O Mordane/O will/O expect/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ignored/O her/O ./O 
She/O gave/O a/O hard/O yank/O with/O the/O brush/O ./O 
Nymeria/PERSON growled/O and/O spun/O away/O ,/O affronted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O back/O here/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O lemon/O cakes/O and/O tea/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O went/O on/O ,/O all/O adult/O and/O reasonable/O ./O 
Lady/O brushed/O against/O her/O leg/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON scratched/O her/O ears/O the/O way/O she/O liked/O ,/O and/O Lady/PERSON sat/O beside/O her/O on/O her/O haunches/O ,/O watching/O Arya/PERSON chase/O Nymeria/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O would/O you/O want/O to/O ride/O a/O smelly/O old/O horse/O and/O get/O all/O sore/O and/O sweaty/O when/O you/O could/O recline/O on/O feather/O pillows/O and/O eat/O cakes/O with/O the/O queen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O like/O the/O queen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O casually/O ./O 
Sansa/O sucked/O in/O her/O breath/O ,/O shocked/O that/O even/O Arya/PERSON would/O say/O such/O a/O thing/O ,/O but/O her/O sister/O prattled/O on/O ,/O heedless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O wo/O n't/O even/O let/O me/O bring/O Nymeria/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O thrust/O the/O brush/O under/O her/O belt/O and/O stalked/O her/O wolf/O ./O 
Nymeria/PERSON watched/O her/O approach/O warily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O royal/O wheelhouse/O is/O no/O place/O for/O a/O wolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON is/O afraid/O of/O them/O ,/O you/O know/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Myrcella/O is/O a/O little/O baby/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON grabbed/O Nymeria/LOCATION around/O her/O neck/O ,/O but/O the/O moment/O she/O pulled/O out/O the/O brush/O again/O the/O direwo/O If/O wriggled/O free/O and/O bounded/O off/O ./O 
Frustrated/O ,/O Arya/PERSON threw/O down/O the/O brush/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bad/O wolf/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O shouted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O could/O n't/O help/O but/O smile/O a/O little/O ./O 
The/O kennelmaster/O once/O told/O her/O that/O an/O animal/O takes/O after/O its/O master/O ./O 
She/O gave/O Lady/O a/O quick/O little/O hug/O ./O 
Lady/O licked/O her/O cheek/O ./O 
Sansa/O giggled/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON heard/O and/O whirled/O around/O ,/O glaring/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O what/O you/O say/O ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O out/O riding/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O long/O horsey/O face/O got/O the/O stubborn/O look/O that/O meant/O she/O was/O going/O to/O do/O something/O willful/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O be/O true/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ,/O sometimes/O you/O act/O like/O such/O a/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O go/O by/O myself/O then/O ./O 
It/O will/O be/O ever/O so/O much/O nicer/O that/O way/O ./O 
Lady/O and/O I/O will/O eat/O all/O the/O lemon/O cakes/O and/O just/O have/O the/O best/O time/O without/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O turned/O to/O walk/O off/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON shouted/O after/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O They/O wo/O n't/O let/O you/O bring/O Lady/O either/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O was/O gone/O before/O Sansa/O could/O think/O of/O a/O reply/O ,/O chasing/O Nymeria/LOCATION along/O the/O river/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Alone/O and/O humiliated/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON took/O the/O long/O way/O back/O to/O the/O inn/O ,/O where/O she/O knew/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON would/O be/O waiting/O ./O 
Lady/O padded/O quietly/O by/O her/O side/O ./O 
She/O was/O almost/O in/O tears/O ./O 
All/O she/O wanted/O was/O for/O things/O to/O be/O nice/O and/O pretty/O ,/O the/O way/O they/O were/O in/O the/O songs/O ./O 
Why/O could/O n't/O Arya/PERSON be/O sweet/O and/O delicate/O and/O kind/O ,/O like/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON ?/O 
She/O would/O have/O liked/O a/O sister/O like/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O could/O never/O understand/O how/O two/O sisters/O ,/O born/O only/O two/O years/O apart/O ,/O could/O be/O so/O different/O ./O 
It/O would/O have/O been/O easier/O if/O Arya/PERSON had/O been/O a/O bastard/O ,/O like/O their/O half/O brother/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
She/O even/O looked/O like/O Jon/PERSON ,/O with/O the/O long/O face/O and/O brown/O hair/O of/O the/O Starks/PERSON ,/O and/O nothing/O of/O their/O lady/O mother/O in/O her/O face/O or/O her/O coloring/O ./O 
And/O Jon/PERSON 's/O mother/O had/O been/O common/O ,/O or/O so/O people/O whispered/O ./O 
Once/O ,/O when/O she/O was/O littler/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON had/O even/O asked/O Mother/PERSON if/O perhaps/O there/O had/O n't/O been/O some/O mistake/O ./O 
Perhaps/O the/O grumkins/O had/O stolen/O her/O real/O sister/O ./O 
But/O Mother/PERSON had/O only/O laughed/O and/O said/O no/O ,/O Arya/PERSON was/O her/O daughter/O and/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O trueborn/O sister/O ,/O blood/O of/O their/O blood/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON could/O not/O think/O why/O Mother/PERSON would/O want/O to/O lie/O about/O it/O ,/O so/O she/O supposed/O it/O had/O to/O be/O true/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O she/O neared/O the/O center/O of/O camp/O ,/O her/O distress/O was/O quickly/O forgotten/O ./O 
A/O crowd/O had/O gathered/O around/O the/O queen/O 's/O wheelhouse/O ./O 
Sansa/O heard/O excited/O voices/O buzzing/O like/O a/O hive/O of/O bees/O ./O 
The/O doors/O had/O been/O thrown/O open/O ,/O she/O saw/O ,/O and/O the/O queen/O stood/O at/O the/O top/O of/O the/O wooden/O steps/O ,/O smiling/O down/O at/O someone/O ./O 
She/O heard/O her/O saying/O ,/O \/O ``/O The/O council/O does/O us/O great/O honor/O ,/O my/O good/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O 's/O happening/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O a/O squire/O she/O knew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O council/O sent/O riders/O from/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O to/O escort/O us/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O An/O honor/O guard/O for/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Anxious/O to/O see/O ,/O Sansa/O let/O Lady/O clear/O a/O path/O through/O the/O crowd/O ./O 
People/O moved/O aside/O hastily/O for/O the/O direwolf/O When/O she/O got/O closer/O ,/O she/O saw/O two/O knights/O kneeling/O before/O the/O queen/O ,/O in/O armor/O so/O fine/O and/O gorgeous/O that/O it/O made/O her/O blink/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O One/O knight/O wore/O an/O intricate/O suit/O of/O white/O enameled/O scales/O ,/O brilliant/O as/O a/O field/O of/O new-fallen/O snow/O ,/O with/O silver/O chasings/O and/O clasps/O that/O glittered/O in/O the/O sun/O ./O 
When/O he/O removed/O his/O helm/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON saw/O that/O he/O was/O an/O old/O man/O with/O hair/O as/O pale/O as/O his/O armor/O ,/O yet/O he/O seemed/O strong/O and/O graceful/O for/O all/O that/O ./O 
From/O his/O shoulders/O hung/O the/O pure/O white/O cloak/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O companion/O was/O a/O man/O near/O twenty/O whose/O armor/O was/O steel/O plate/O of/O a/O deep/O forest-green/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O handsomest/O man/O Sansa/PERSON had/O ever/O set/O eyes/O upon/O ;/O tall/O and/O powerfully/O made/O ,/O with/O jet-black/O hair/O that/O fell/O to/O his/O shoulders/O and/O framed/O a/O clean-shaven/O face/O ,/O and/O laughing/O green/O eyes/O to/O match/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Cradled/O under/O one/O arm/O was/O an/O antlered/O helm/O ,/O its/O magnificent/O rack/O shimmering/O in/O gold/O ./O 
At/O first/O Sansa/O did/O not/O notice/O the/O third/O stranger/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O kneel/O with/O the/O others/O ./O 
He/O stood/O to/O one/O side/O ,/O beside/O their/O horses/O ,/O a/O gaunt/O grim/O man/O who/O watched/O the/O proceedings/O in/O silence/O ./O 
His/O face/O was/O pockmarked/O and/O beardless/O ,/O with/O deepset/O eyes/O and/O hollow/O cheeks/O ./O 
Though/O he/O was/O not/O an/O old/O man/O ,/O only/O a/O few/O wisps/O of/O hair/O remained/O to/O him/O ,/O sprouting/O above/O his/O ears/O ,/O but/O those/O he/O had/O grown/O long/O as/O a/O woman/O 's/O ./O 
His/O armor/O was/O iron-grey/O chainmail/O over/O layers/O of/O boiled/O leather/O ,/O plain/O and/O unadorned/O ,/O and/O it/O spoke/O of/O age/O and/O hard/O use/O ./O 
Above/O his/O right/O shoulder/O the/O stained/O leather/O hilt/O of/O the/O blade/O strapped/O to/O his/O back/O was/O visible/O ;/O a/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ,/O too/O long/O to/O be/O worn/O at/O his/O side/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O is/O gone/O hunting/O ,/O but/O I/O know/O he/O will/O be/O pleased/O to/O see/O you/O when/O he/O returns/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O was/O saying/O to/O the/O two/O knights/O who/O knelt/O before/O her/O ,/O but/O Sansa/PERSON could/O not/O take/O her/O eyes/O off/O the/O third/O man/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O feel/O the/O weight/O of/O her/O gaze/O ./O 
Slowly/O he/O turned/O his/O head/O ./O 
Lady/O growled/O ./O 
A/O terror/O as/O overwhelming/O as/O anything/O Sansa/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O ever/O felt/O filled/O her/O suddenly/O ./O 
She/O stepped/O backward/O and/O Bumped/O into/O someone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Strong/O hands/O grasped/O her/O by/O the/O shoulders/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O moment/O Sansa/O thought/O it/O was/O her/O father/O ,/O but/O when/O she/O turned/O ,/O it/O was/O the/O burned/O face/O of/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON looking/O down/O at/O her/O ,/O his/O mouth/O twisted/O in/O a/O terrible/O mockery/O of/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O shaking/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O voice/O rasping/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O I/O frighten/O you/O so/O much/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O did/O ,/O and/O had/O since/O she/O had/O first/O laid/O eyes/O on/O the/O ruin/O that/O fire/O had/O made/O of/O his/O face/O ,/O though/O it/O seemed/O to/O her/O now/O that/O he/O was/O not/O half/O so/O terrifying/O as/O the/O other/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON wrenched/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O Hound/O laughed/O ,/O and/O Lady/O moved/O between/O them/O ,/O rumbling/O a/O warning/O ./O 
Sansa/O dropped/O to/O her/O knees/O to/O wrap/O her/O arms/O around/O the/O wolf/O ./O 
They/O were/O all/O gathered/O around/O gaping/O ,/O she/O could/O feel/O their/O eyes/O on/O her/O ,/O and/O here/O and/O there/O she/O heard/O muttered/O comments/O and/O titters/O of/O laughter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O man/O said/O ,/O and/O someone/O else/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O ,/O that/O 's/O a/O direwolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O the/O first/O man/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O What/O 's/O it/O doing/O in/O camp/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O and/O the/O Hound/O 's/O rasping/O voice/O replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O The/O Starks/O use/O them/O for/O wet/O nurses/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O Sansa/PERSON realized/O that/O the/O two/O stranger/O knights/O were/O looking/O down/O on/O her/O and/O Lady/O ,/O swords/O in/O their/O hands/O ,/O and/O then/O she/O was/O frightened/O again/O ,/O and/O ashamed/O ./O 
Tears/O filled/O her/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O heard/O the/O queen/O say/O ,/O \/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O go/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O her/O prince/O was/O there/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Leave/O her/O alone/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O stood/O over/O her/O ,/O beautiful/O in/O blue/O wool/O and/O black/O leather/O ,/O his/O golden/O curls/O shining/O in/O the/O sun/O like/O a/O crown/O ./O 
He/O gave/O her/O his/O hand/O ,/O drew/O her/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ?/O 
Why/O are/O you/O afraid/O ?/O 
No/O one/O will/O hurt/O you/O ./O 
Put/O away/O your/O swords/O ,/O all/O of/O you/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O is/O her/O little/O pet/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O at/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O you/O ,/O dog/O ,/O away/O with/O you/O ,/O you/O 're/O scaring/O my/O betrothed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O ,/O ever/O faithful/O ,/O bowed/O and/O slid/O away/O quietly/O through/O the/O press/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON struggled/O to/O steady/O herself/O ./O 
She/O felt/O like/O such/O a/O fool/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O Stark/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O a/O noble/O lady/O ,/O and/O someday/O she/O would/O be/O a/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O him/O ,/O my/O sweet/O prince/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O tried/O to/O explain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O other/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O two/O stranger/O knights/O exchanged/O a/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Payne/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O chuckled/O the/O young/O man/O in/O the/O green/O armor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O older/O man/O in/O white/O spoke/O to/O Sansa/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ofttimes/O Ser/O Ilyn/O frightens/O me/O as/O well/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
He/O has/O a/O fearsome/O aspect/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O well/O he/O should/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O queen/O had/O descended/O from/O the/O wheelhouse/O ./O 
The/O spectators/O parted/O to/O make/O way/O for/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O wicked/O do/O not/O fear/O the/O Mng/LOCATION 's/O Justice/O ,/O you/O have/O put/O the/O wrong/O man/O in/O the/O office/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O finally/O found/O her/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O surely/O you/O have/O chosen/O the/O right/O one/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O and/O a/O gale/O of/O laughter/O erupted/O all/O around/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O spoken/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O old/O man/O in/O white/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O befits/O the/O daughter/O of/O Eddard/O Stark/O ./O 
I/O am/O honored/O to/O know/O you/O ,/O however/O irregular/O the/O manner/O of/O our/O meeting/O ./O 
I/O am/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON ,/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O bowed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O knew/O the/O name/O ,/O and/O now/O the/O courtesies/O that/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O over/O the/O years/O came/O back/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O councillor/O to/O Robert/PERSON ''/O ,/O ``/O our/O king/O and/O to/O Aerys/O Targaryen/O before/O him/O ./O 
The/O honor/O is/O mine/O ,/O good/O knight/O ./O 
Even/O in/O the/O far/O north/O ,/O the/O singers/O praise/O the/O deeds/O of/O Barristan/LOCATION the/O Bold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O green/O knight/O laughed/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Barristan/O the/O Old/O ,/O you/O mean/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O flatter/O him/O too/O sweetly/O ,/O child/O ,/O he/O thinks/O overmuch/O of/O himself/O already/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O ,/O wolf/O girl/O ,/O if/O you/O can/O put/O a/O name/O to/O me/O as/O well/O ,/O then/O I/O must/O concede/O that/O you/O are/O truly/O our/O Hand/O 's/O daughter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON stiffened/O beside/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O a/O care/O how/O you/O address/O my/O betrothed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O answer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O quickly/O ,/O to/O quell/O her/O prince/O 's/O anger/O ./O 
She/O smiled/O at/O the/O green/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O helmet/O bears/O golden/O antlers/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
The/O stag/O is/O the/O sigil/O of/O the/O royal/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
King/O Robert/PERSON has/O two/O brothers/O ./O 
By/O your/O extreme/O youth/O ,/O you/O can/O only/O be/O Renly/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O and/O councillor/O to/O the/O king/O ,/O and/O so/O I/O name/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O his/O extreme/O youth/O ,/O he/O can/O only/O be/O a/O prancing/O jackanapes/O ,/O and/O so/O I/O name/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O general/O laughter/O ,/O led/O by/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON himself/O ./O 
The/O tension/O of/O a/O few/O moments/O ago/O was/O gone/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON was/O beginning/O to/O feel/O comfortable/O .../O until/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON shouldered/O two/O men/O aside/O ,/O and/O stood/O before/O her/O ,/O unsmiling/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O say/O a/O word/O ./O 
Lady/O bared/O her/O teeth/O and/O began/O to/O growl/O ,/O a/O low/O rumble/O full/O of/O menace/O ,/O but/O this/O time/O Sansa/O silenced/O the/O wolf/O with/O a/O gentle/O hand/O to/O the/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O sorry/O if/O I/O offended/O you/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O waited/O for/O an/O answer/O ,/O but/O none/O came/O ./O 
As/O the/O headsman/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O his/O pale/O colorless/O eyes/O seemed/O to/O strip/O the/O clothes/O away/O from/O her/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O skin/O ,/O leaving/O her/O soul/O naked/O before/O him/O ./O 
Still/O silent/O ,/O he/O turned/O and/O walked/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O did/O not/O understand/O ./O 
She/O looked/O at/O her/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O I/O say/O something/O wrong/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ?/O 
Why/O will/O he/O not/O speak/O to/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Ilyn/O has/O not/O been/O feeling/O talkative/O these/O past/O fourteen/O years/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON commented/O with/O a/O sly/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON gave/O his/O uncle/O a/O look/O of/O pure/O loathing/O ,/O then/O took/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O hands/O in/O his/O own/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON had/O his/O tongue/O ripped/O out/O with/O hot/O pincers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O speaks/O most/O eloquently/O with/O his/O sword/O ,/O however/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O his/O devotion/O to/O our/O realm/O is/O unquestioned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Then/O she/O smiled/O graciously/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O the/O good/O councilors/O and/O I/O must/O speak/O together/O until/O the/O king/O returns/O with/O your/O father/O ./O 
I/O fear/O we/O shall/O have/O to/O postpone/O your/O day/O with/O Myrcella/PERSON ./O 
Please/O give/O your/O sweet/O sister/O my/O apologies/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON ,/O perhaps/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O as/O to/O entertain/O our/O guest/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O be/O my/O pleasure/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O very/O formally/O ./O 
He/O took/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O and/O led/O her/O away/O from/O the/O wheelhouse/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O spirits/O took/O flight/O ./O 
A/O whole/O day/O with/O her/O prince/O !/O 
She/O gazed/O at/O Joffrey/ORGANIZATION worshipfully/O ./O 
He/O was/O so/O gallant/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
The/O way/O he/O had/O rescued/O her/O from/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON and/O the/O Hound/O ,/O why/O ,/O it/O was/O almost/O like/O the/O songs/O ,/O like/O the/O time/O Serwyn/PERSON of/O the/O Mirror/O Shield/O saved/O the/O Princess/O Daeryssa/PERSON from/O the/O giants/O ,/O or/O Prince/O Aemon/PERSON the/O Dragonknight/O championing/O Queen/O Naerys/PERSON 's/O honor/O against/O evil/O Ser/PERSON Morgil/PERSON 's/O slanders/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O touch/O of/O Joffrey/PERSON '/O s/O hand/O on/O her/O sleeve/O made/O her/O heart/O beat/O faster/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O would/O you/O like/O to/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Be/O with/O you/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON thought/O ,/O but/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Whatever/O you/O 'd/O like/O to/O do/O ,/O my/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON reflected/O a/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O could/O go/O riding/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O love/O riding/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON glanced/O back/O at/O Lady/O ,/O who/O was/O following/O at/O their/O heels/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O wolf/O is/O liable/O to/O frighten/O the/O horses/O ,/O and/O my/O dog/O seems/O to/O frighten/O you/O ./O 
Let/O us/O leave/O them/O both/O behind/O and/O set/O off/O on/O our/O own/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O like/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O uncertainly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O I/O could/O tie/O Lady/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O did/O not/O quite/O understand/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O know/O you/O had/O a/O dog/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O my/O mother/O 's/O dog/O ,/O in/O truth/O ./O 
She/O has/O set/O him/O to/O guard/O me/O ,/O and/O so/O he/O does/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O mean/O the/O Hound/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O hit/O herself/O for/O being/O so/O slow/O ./O 
Her/O prince/O would/O never/O love/O her/O if/O she/O seemed/O stupid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O safe/O to/O leave/O him/O behind/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON looked/O annoyed/O that/O she/O would/O even/O ask/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O no/O fear/O ,/O lady/O ./O 
I/O am/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O and/O I/O do/O n't/O fight/O with/O wood/O like/O your/O brothers/O ./O 
All/O I/O need/O is/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O his/O sword/O and/O showed/O it/O to/O her/O ;/O a/O longsword/O adroitly/O shrunken/O to/O suit/O a/O boy/O of/O twelve/O ,/O gleaming/O blue/O steel/O ,/O castle-forged/O and/O double-edged/O ,/O with/O a/O leather/O grip/O and/O a/O lion/O 's/O -/O head/O pommel/O in/O gold/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON exclaimed/O over/O it/O admiringly/O ,/O and/O Joffrey/PERSON looked/O pleased/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O call/O it/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O so/O they/O left/O her/O direwolf/O and/O his/O bodyguard/O behind/O them/O ,/O while/O they/O ranged/O east/O along/O the/O north/O bank/O of/O the/O Trident/O with/O no/O company/O save/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O a/O glorious/O day/O ,/O a/O magical/O day/O ./O 
The/O air/O was/O warm/O and/O heavy/O with/O the/O scent/O of/O flowers/O ,/O and/O the/O woods/O here/O had/O a/O gentle/O beauty/O that/O Sansa/PERSON had/O never/O seen/O in/O the/O north/O ./O 
Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON 's/O mount/O was/O a/O blood/O bay/O courser/O ,/O swift/O as/O the/O wind/O ,/O and/O he/O rode/O it/O with/O reckless/O abandon/O ,/O so/O fast/O that/O Sansa/PERSON was/O hard-pressed/O to/O keep/O up/O on/O her/O mare/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O day/O for/O adventures/O ./O 
They/O explored/O the/O caves/O by/O the/O riverbank/O ,/O and/O tracked/O a/O shadowcat/O to/O its/O lair/O ,/O and/O when/O they/O grew/O hungry/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON found/O a/O holdfast/O by/O its/O smoke/O and/O told/O them/O to/O fetch/O food/O and/O wine/O for/O their/O prince/O and/O his/O lady/O ./O 
They/O dined/O on/O trout/O fresh/O from/O the/O river/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON drank/O more/O wine/O than/O she/O had/O ever/O drunk/O before/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O only/O lets/O us/O have/O one/O cup/O ,/O and/O only/O at/O feasts/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O confessed/O to/O her/O prince/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O betrothed/O can/O drink/O as/O much/O as/O she/O wants/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ,/O refilling/O her/O cup/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O went/O more/O slowly/O after/O they/O had/O eaten/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON sang/O for/O her/O as/O they/O rode/O ,/O his/O voice/O high/O and/O sweet/O and/O pure/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O a/O little/O dizzy/O from/O the/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Should/O n't/O we/O be/O starting/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Soon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O battleground/O is/O right/O up/O ahead/O ,/O where/O the/O river/O bends/O ./O 
That/O was/O where/O my/O father/O killed/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ,/O you/O know/O ./O 
He/O smashed/O in/O his/O chest/O ,/O crunch/O ,/O right/O through/O the/O armor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON swung/O an/O imaginary/O warhammer/O to/O show/O her/O how/O it/O was/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O my/O uncle/O Jaime/PERSON killed/O old/O Aerys/PERSON ,/O and/O my/O father/O was/O king/O ./O 
What/O 's/O that/O sound/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O heard/O it/O too/O ,/O floating/O through/O the/O woods/O ,/O a/O kind/O of/O wooden/O clattering/O ,/O snack/O snack/O snack/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
It/O made/O her/O nervous/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O let/O 's/O go/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O see/O what/O it/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON turned/O his/O horse/O in/O the/O direction/O of/O the/O sounds/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O follow/O ./O 
The/O noises/O grew/O louder/O and/O more/O distinct/O ,/O the/O clack/O of/O wood/O on/O wood/O ,/O and/O as/O they/O grew/O closer/O they/O heard/O heavy/O breathing/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O now/O and/O then/O a/O grunt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Someone/O 's/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O anxiously/O ./O 
She/O found/O herself/O thinking/O of/O Lady/O ,/O wishing/O the/O direwolf/O was/O with/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O safe/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON drew/O his/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O from/O its/O sheath/O ./O 
The/O sound/O of/O steel/O on/O leather/O made/O her/O tremble/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O way/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O riding/O through/O a/O stand/O of/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Beyond/O ,/O in/O a/O clearing/O overlooking/O the/O river/O ,/O they/O came/O upon/O a/O boy/O and/O a/O girl/O playing/O at/O knights/O ./O 
Their/O swords/O were/O wooden/O sticks/O ,/O broom/O handles/O from/O the/O look/O of/O them/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O rushing/O across/O the/O grass/O ,/O swinging/O at/O each/O other/O lustily/O ./O 
The/O boy/O was/O years/O older/O ,/O a/O head/O taller/O ,/O and/O much/O stronger/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O pressing/O the/O attack/O ./O 
The/O girl/O ,/O a/O scrawny/O thing/O in/O soiled/O leathers/O ,/O was/O dodging/O and/O managing/O to/O get/O her/O stick/O in/O the/O way/O of/O most/O of/O the/O boy/O 's/O blows/O ,/O but/O not/O all/O ./O 
When/O she/O tried/O to/O lunge/O at/O him/O ,/O he/O caught/O her/O stick/O with/O his/O own/O ,/O swept/O it/O aside/O ,/O and/O slid/O his/O wood/O down/O hard/O on/O her/O fingers/O ./O 
She/O cried/O out/O and/O lost/O her/O weapon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
The/O boy/O looked/O around/O ,/O wide-eyed/O and/O startled/O ,/O and/O dropped/O his/O stick/O in/O the/O grass/O ./O 
The/O girl/O glared/O at/O them/O ,/O sucking/O on/O her/O knuckles/O to/O take/O the/O sting/O out/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON was/O horrified/O ./O 
`/O Arya/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O incredulously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O away/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON shouted/O back/O at/O them/O ,/O angry/O tears/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O doing/O here/O ?/O 
Leave/O us/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON glanced/O from/O Arya/PERSON to/O Sansa/LOCATION and/O back/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O sister/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O nodded/O ,/O blushing/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON examined/O the/O boy/O ,/O an/O ungainly/O lad/O with/O a/O coarse/O ,/O freckled/O face/O and/O thick/O red/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O who/O are/O you/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O in/O a/O commanding/O tone/O that/O took/O no/O notice/O of/O the/O fact/O that/O the/O other/O was/O a/O year/O his/O senior/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mycah/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O muttered/O ./O 
He/O recognized/O the/O prince/O and/O averted/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O MTord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O the/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O my/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O leave/O him/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O who/O wants/O to/O be/O a/O knight/O ,/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON swung/O down/O from/O his/O mount/O ,/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pick/O up/O your/O sword/O ,/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O eyes/O bright/O with/O amusement/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O us/O see/O how/O good/O you/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mycah/PERSON stood/O there/O ,/O frozen/O with/O fear/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON walked/O toward/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O on/O ,/O pick/O it/O up/O ./O 
Or/O do/O you/O only/O fight/O little/O girls/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O ast/O me/O to/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mycah/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O ast/O me/O to/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O only/O to/O glance/O at/O Arya/PERSON and/O see/O the/O flush/O on/O her/O sister/O 's/O face/O to/O know/O the/O boy/O was/O telling/O the/O truth/O ,/O but/O Joffrey/PERSON was/O in/O no/O mood/O to/O listen/O ./O 
The/O wine/O had/O made/O him/O wild/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O going/O to/O pick/O up/O your/O sword/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mycah/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O only/O a/O stick/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O no/O sword/O ,/O it/O 's/O only/O a/O stick/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O 're/O only/O a/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ,/O and/O no/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON lifted/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O and/O laid/O its/O point/O on/O Mycah/PERSON 's/O cheek/O below/O the/O eye/O ,/O as/O the/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O stood/O trembling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O my/O lady/O 's/O sister/O you/O were/O hitting/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O A/O bright/O bud/O of/O blood/O blossomed/O where/O his/O sword/O pressed/O into/O Mycah/PERSON 's/O flesh/O ,/O and/O a/O slow/O red/O line/O trickled/O down/O the/O boy/O 's/O cheek/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON screamed/O ./O 
She/O grabbed/O up/O her/O fallen/O stick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O was/O afraid/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O you/O stay/O out/O of/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O hurt/O him/O .../O much/O ,/O \/O ''/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON told/O Arya/PERSON ,/O never/O taking/O his/O eyes/O off/O the/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON went/O for/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O slid/O off/O her/O mare/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O too/O slow/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON swung/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O loud/O crack/O as/O the/O wood/O split/O against/O the/O back/O of/O the/O prince/O 's/O head/O ,/O and/O then/O everything/O happened/O at/O once/O before/O Sansa/O 's/O horrified/O eyes/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON staggered/O and/O whirled/O around/O ,/O roaring/O curses/O ./O 
Mycah/PERSON ran/O for/O the/O trees/O as/O fast/O as/O his/O legs/O would/O take/O him/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON swung/O at/O the/O prince/O again/O ,/O but/O this/O time/O Joffrey/PERSON caught/O the/O blow/O on/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O and/O sent/O her/O broken/O stick/O flying/O from/O her/O hands/O ./O 
The/O back/O of/O his/O head/O was/O all/O bloody/O and/O his/O eyes/O were/O on/O fire/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O shrieking/O ,/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O no/O ,/O stop/O it/O ,/O stop/O it/O ,/O both/O of/O you/O ,/O you/O 're/O spoiling/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O but/O no/O one/O was/O listening/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON scooped/O up/O a/O rock/O and/O hurled/O it/O at/O Joffrey/ORGANIZATION '/O s/O head/O ./O 
She/O hit/O his/O horse/O instead/O ,/O and/O the/O blood/O bay/O reared/O and/O went/O galloping/O off/O after/O Mycah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O it/O ,/O do/O n't/O ,/O stop/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON screamed/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON slashed/O at/O Arya/PERSON with/O his/O sword/O ,/O screaming/O obscenities/O ,/O terrible/O words/O ,/O filthy/O words/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON darted/O back/O ,/O frightened/O now/O ,/O but/O Joffrey/PERSON followed/O ,/O hounding/O her/O toward/O the/O woods/O ,/O backing/O her/O up/O against/O a/O tree/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON did/O n't/O know/O what/O to/O do/O ./O 
She/O watched/O helplessly/O ,/O almost/O blind/O from/O her/O tears/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O a/O grey/O blur/O flashed/O past/O her/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O Nymeria/PERSON was/O there/O ,/O leaping/O ,/O jaws/O closing/O around/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O sword/O arm/O ./O 
The/O steel/O fell/O from/O his/O fingers/O as/O the/O wolf/O knocked/O him/O off/O his/O feet/O ,/O and/O they/O rolled/O in/O the/O grass/O ,/O the/O wolf/O snarling/O and/O ripping/O at/O him/O ,/O the/O prince/O shrieking/O in/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O it/O off/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O it/O off/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON 's/O voice/O cracked/O like/O a/O whip/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nymeria/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O direwolf/O let/O go/O of/O Joffrey/LOCATION and/O moved/O to/O Arya/PERSON 's/O side/O ./O 
The/O prince/O lay/O in/O the/O grass/O ,/O whimpering/O ,/O cradling/O his/O mangled/O arm/O ./O 
His/O shirt/O was/O soaked/O in/O blood/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O She/O did/O n't/O hurt/O you/O .../O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O picked/O up/O Lion/O 's/O Tooth/O where/O it/O had/O fallen/O ,/O and/O stood/O over/O him/O ,/O holding/O the/O sword/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON made/O a/O scared/O whimpery/O sound/O as/O he/O looked/O up/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O do/O n't/O hurt/O me/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O tell/O my/O mother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O leave/O him/O alone/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON screamed/O at/O her/O sister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON whirled/O and/O heaved/O the/O sword/O into/O the/O air/O ,/O putting/O her/O whole/O body/O into/O the/O throw/O ./O 
The/O blue/O steel/O flashed/O in/O the/O sun/O as/O the/O sword/O spun/O out/O over/O the/O river/O ./O 
It/O hit/O the/O water/O and/O vanished/O with/O a/O splash/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON moaned/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON ran/O off/O to/O her/O horse/O ,/O Nymeria/PERSON loping/O at/O her/O heels/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O they/O had/O gone/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON went/O to/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O closed/O in/O pain/O ,/O his/O breath/O ragged/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON knelt/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O sobbed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O look/O what/O they/O did/O ,/O look/O what/O they/O did/O ./O 
My/O poor/O prince/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O ride/O to/O the/O holdfast/O and/O bring/O help/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tenderly/O she/O reached/O out/O and/O brushed/O back/O his/O soft/O blond/O hair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O snapped/O open/O and/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O nothing/O but/O loathing/O there/O ,/O nothing/O but/O the/O vilest/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O go/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O spit/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O do/O n't/O touch/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
