-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O the/O host/O trooped/O down/O the/O causeway/O through/O the/O black/O bogs/O of/O the/O Neck/O and/O spilled/O out/O into/O the/O riverlands/O beyond/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON 's/O apprehensions/O grew/O ./O 
She/O masked/O her/O fears/O behind/O a/O face/O kept/O still/O and/O stern/O ,/O yet/O they/O were/O there/O all/O the/O same/O ,/O growing/O with/O every/O league/O they/O crossed/O ./O 
Her/O days/O were/O anxious/O ,/O her/O nights/O restless/O ,/O and/O every/O raven/O that/O flew/O overhead/O made/O her/O clench/O her/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O feared/O for/O her/O lord/O father/O ,/O and/O wondered/O at/O his/O ominous/O silence/O ./O 
She/O feared/O for/O her/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON ,/O and/O prayed/O that/O the/O gods/O would/O watch/O over/O him/O if/O he/O must/O face/O the/O Kingslayer/O in/O battle/O ./O 
She/O feared/O for/O Ned/PERSON and/O her/O girls/O ,/O and/O for/O the/O sweet/O sons/O she/O had/O left/O behind/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
And/O yet/O there/O was/O nothing/O she/O could/O do/O for/O any/O of/O them/O ,/O and/O so/O she/O made/O herself/O put/O all/O thought/O of/O them/O aside/O ./O 
You/O must/O save/O your/O strength/O for/O Robb/PERSON ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
He/O is/O the/O only/O one/O you/O can/O help/O ./O 
You/O must/O be/O as/O fierce/O and/O hard/O as/O the/O north/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON Tully/PERSON ./O 
You/O must/O be/O a/O Stark/O for/O true/O now/O ,/O like/O your/O son/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON rode/O at/O the/O front/O of/O the/O column/O ,/O beneath/O the/O flapping/O white/O banner/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Each/O day/O he/O would/O ask/O one/O of/O his/O lords/O to/O join/O him/O ,/O so/O they/O might/O confer/O as/O they/O marched/O ;/O he/O honored/O every/O man/O in/O turn/O ,/O showing/O no/O favorites/O ,/O listening/O as/O his/O lord/O father/O had/O listened/O ,/O weighing/O the/O words/O of/O one/O against/O the/O other/O ./O 
He/O has/O learned/O so/O much/O from/O Ned/PERSON ,/O she/O thought/O as/O she/O watched/O him/O ,/O but/O has/O he/O learned/O enough/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Blackfish/O had/O taken/O a/O hundred/O picked/O men/O and/O a/O hundred/O swift/O horses/O and/O raced/O ahead/O to/O screen/O their/O movements/O and/O scout/O the/O way/O ./O 
The/O reports/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON 's/O riders/O brought/O back/O did/O little/O to/O reassure/O her/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O host/O was/O still/O many/O days/O to/O the/O south/O .../O but/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Crossing/O ,/O had/O assembled/O a/O force/O of/O near/O four/O thousand/O men/O at/O his/O castles/O on/O the/O Green/O Fork/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Late/O again/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON murmured/O when/O she/O heard/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O Trident/O all/O over/O ,/O damn/O the/O man/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON had/O called/O the/O banners/O ;/O by/O rights/O ,/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON should/O have/O gone/O to/O join/O the/O Tully/PERSON host/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O yet/O here/O he/O sat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Four/O thousand/O men/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON repeated/O ,/O more/O perplexed/O than/O angry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON can/O not/O hope/O to/O fight/O the/O Lannisters/O by/O himself/O ./O 
Surely/O he/O means/O to/O join/O his/O power/O to/O ours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Does/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON asked/O ./O 
She/O had/O ridden/O forward/O to/O join/O Robb/PERSON and/O Robett/PERSON Glover/PERSON ,/O his/O companion/O of/O the/O day/O ./O 
The/O vanguard/O spread/O out/O behind/O them/O ,/O a/O slow-moving/O forest/O of/O lances/O and/O banners/O and/O spears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O ./O 
Expect/O nothing/O of/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O will/O never/O be/O surprised/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O your/O father/O 's/O bannerman/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O men/O take/O their/O oaths/O more/O seriously/O than/O others/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
And/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON was/O always/O friendlier/O with/O Casterly/O Rock/O than/O my/O father/O would/O have/O liked/O ./O 
One/O of/O his/O sons/O is/O wed/O to/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O sister/O ./O 
That/O means/O little/O of/O itself/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O ./O 
Lord/O Walder/PERSON has/O sired/O a/O great/O many/O children/O over/O the/O years/O ,/O and/O they/O must/O needs/O marry/O someone/O ./O 
Still/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O he/O means/O to/O betray/O us/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robett/PERSON Glover/PERSON asked/O gravely/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O I/O doubt/O even/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON knows/O what/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON intends/O to/O do/O ./O 
He/O has/O an/O old/O man/O 's/O caution/O and/O a/O young/O man/O 's/O ambition/O ,/O and/O has/O never/O lacked/O for/O cunning/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O must/O have/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O heatedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O other/O way/O across/O the/O river/O ./O 
You/O know/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
And/O so/O does/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O you/O can/O be/O sure/O of/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O night/O they/O made/O camp/O on/O the/O southern/O edge/O of/O the/O bogs/O ,/O halfway/O between/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O the/O river/O ./O 
It/O was/O there/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON brought/O them/O further/O word/O from/O her/O uncle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Brynden/O says/O to/O tell/O you/O he/O 's/O crossed/O swords/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
There/O are/O a/O dozen/O scouts/O who/O wo/O n't/O be/O reporting/O back/O to/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON anytime/O soon/O ./O 
Or/O ever/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Addam/O Marbrand/O commands/O their/O outriders/O ,/O and/O he/O 's/O pulling/O back/O south/O ,/O burning/O as/O he/O goes/O ./O 
He/O knows/O where/O we/O are/O ,/O more/O or/O less/O ,/O but/O the/O Blackfish/O vows/O he/O will/O not/O know/O when/O we/O split/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unless/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON tells/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Theon/O ,/O when/O you/O return/O to/O my/O uncle/O ,/O tell/O him/O he/O is/O to/O place/O his/O best/O bowmen/O around/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O day/O and/O night/O ,/O with/O orders/O to/O bring/O down/O any/O raven/O they/O see/O leaving/O the/O battlements/O ./O 
I/O want/O no/O birds/O bringing/O word/O of/O my/O son/O 's/O movements/O to/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Brynden/O has/O seen/O to/O it/O already/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O cocky/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O few/O more/O blackbirds/O ,/O and/O we/O should/O have/O enough/O to/O bake/O a/O pie/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O save/O you/O their/O feathers/O for/O a/O hat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O ought/O to/O have/O known/O that/O Brynden/O Blackfish/O would/O be/O well/O ahead/O of/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O have/O the/O Freys/O been/O doing/O while/O the/O Lannisters/O ;/O burn/O their/O fields/O and/O plunder/O their/O holdfasts/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O 's/O been/O some/O fighting/O between/O Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON 's/O men/O and/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O a/O day/O 's/O ride/O from/O here/O ,/O we/O found/O two/O Lannister/O scouts/O feeding/O the/O crows/O where/O the/O Freys/ORGANIZATION had/O strung/O them/O up/O ./O 
Most/O of/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O strength/O remains/O massed/O at/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O bore/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON 's/O seal/O beyond/O a/O doubt/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O bitterly/O ;/O hold/O back/O ,/O wait/O ,/O watch/O ,/O take/O no/O risk/O unless/O forced/O to/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O 's/O been/O fighting/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O perhaps/O he/O does/O mean/O to/O hold/O to/O his/O vows/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O less/O encouraged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Defending/O his/O own/O lands/O is/O one/O thing/O ,/O open/O battle/O against/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON quite/O another/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Has/O the/O Blackfish/O found/O any/O other/O way/O across/O the/O Green/ORGANIZATION Fork/ORGANIZATION ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O river/O 's/O running/O high/O and/O fast/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON says/O it/O ca/O n't/O be/O forded/O ,/O not/O this/O far/O north/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O must/O have/O that/O crossing/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON declared/O ,/O fuming/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O our/O horses/O might/O be/O able/O to/O swim/O the/O river/O ,/O I/O suppose/O ,/O but/O not/O with/O armored/O men/O on/O their/O backs/O ./O 
We/O 'd/O need/O to/O build/O rafts/O to/O pole/O our/O steel/O across/O ,/O helms/O and/O mail/O and/O lances/O ,/O and/O we/O do/O n't/O have/O the/O trees/O for/O that/O ./O 
Or/O the/O time/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON is/O marching/O north/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O balled/O his/O hand/O into/O a/O fist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON would/O be/O a/O fool/O to/O try/O and/O bar/O our/O way/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON said/O with/O his/O customary/O easy/O confidence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O five/O times/O his/O numbers/O ./O 
You/O can/O take/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION if/O you/O need/O to/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O easily/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON warned/O them/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O not/O in/O time/O ./O 
While/O you/O were/O mounting/O your/O siege/O ,/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON would/O bring/O up/O his/O host/O and/O assault/O you/O from/O the/O rear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON glanced/O from/O her/O to/O Greyjoy/LOCATION ,/O searching/O for/O an/O answer/O and/O finding/O none/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O he/O looked/O even/O younger/O than/O his/O fifteen/O years/O ,/O despite/O his/O mail/O and/O sword/O and/O the/O stubble/O on/O his/O cheeks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O would/O my/O lord/O father/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Find/O a/O way/O across/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Whatever/O it/O took/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O next/O morning/O it/O was/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON himself/O who/O rode/O back/O to/O them/O ./O 
He/O had/O put/O aside/O the/O heavy/O plate/O and/O helm/O he/O 'd/O worn/O as/O the/O Knight/O of/O the/O Gate/O for/O the/O lighter/O leather-and-mail/O of/O an/O outrider/O ,/O but/O his/O obsidian/O fish/O still/O fastened/O his/O cloak/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O 's/O face/O was/O grave/O as/O he/O swung/O down/O off/O his/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O has/O been/O a/O battle/O under/O the/O walls/O of/O Riverrun/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O mouth/O grim/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O had/O it/O from/O a/O Lannister/O outrider/O we/O took/O captive/O ./O 
The/O Kingslayer/PERSON has/O destroyed/O Edmure/PERSON 's/O host/O and/O sent/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O Trident/O reeling/O in/O flight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O cold/O hand/O clutched/O at/O Catelyn/LOCATION 's/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O my/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wounded/O and/O taken/O prisoner/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON and/O the/O other/O survivors/O are/O under/O siege/O inside/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O surrounded/O by/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O host/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON looked/O fretful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O get/O across/O this/O accursed/O river/O if/O we/O 're/O to/O have/O any/O hope/O of/O relieving/O them/O in/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O will/O not/O be/O easily/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O uncle/O cautioned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON has/O pulled/O his/O whole/O strength/O back/O inside/O his/O castles/O ,/O and/O his/O gates/O are/O closed/O and/O barred/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Damn/O the/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON swore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O old/O fool/O does/O not/O relent/O and/O let/O me/O cross/O ,/O he/O 'll/O leave/O me/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O storm/O his/O walls/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O pull/O the/O Twins/O down/O around/O his/O ears/O if/O I/O have/O to/O ,/O we/O 'll/O see/O how/O well/O he/O likes/O that/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O sound/O like/O a/O sulky/O boy/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O child/O sees/O an/O obstacle/O ,/O and/O his/O first/O thought/O is/O to/O run/O around/O it/O or/O knock/O it/O down/O ./O 
A/O lord/O must/O learn/O that/O sometimes/O words/O can/O accomplish/O what/O swords/O can/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON 's/O neck/O reddened/O at/O the/O rebuke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O what/O you/O mean/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O meekly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Freys/O have/O held/O the/O crossing/O for/O six/O hundred/O years/O ,/O and/O for/O six/O hundred/O years/O they/O have/O never/O failed/O to/O exact/O their/O toll/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O toll/O ?/O 
What/O does/O he/O want/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O what/O we/O must/O discover/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O if/O I/O do/O not/O choose/O to/O pay/O this/O toll/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O you/O had/O best/O retreat/O back/O to/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ,/O deploy/O to/O meet/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON in/O battle/O .../O or/O grow/O wings/O ./O 
I/O see/O no/O other/O choices/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON put/O her/O heels/O to/O her/O horse/O and/O rode/O off/O ,/O leaving/O her/O son/O to/O ponder/O her/O words/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O do/O to/O make/O him/O feel/O as/O if/O his/O mother/O were/O usurping/O his/O place/O ./O 
Did/O you/O teach/O him/O wisdom/O as/O well/O as/O valor/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ?/O 
she/O wondered/O ./O 
Did/O you/O teach/O him/O how/O to/O kneel/O ?/O 
The/O graveyards/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O were/O full/O of/O brave/O men/O who/O had/O never/O learned/O that/O lesson/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O near/O midday/O when/O their/O vanguard/O came/O in/O sight/O of/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O where/O the/O Lords/O of/O the/O Crossing/O had/O their/O seat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Green/O Fork/O ran/O swift/O and/O deep/O here/O ,/O but/O the/O Freys/ORGANIZATION had/O spanned/O it/O many/O centuries/O past/O and/O grown/O rich/O off/O the/O coin/O men/O paid/O them/O to/O cross/O ./O 
Their/O bridge/O was/O a/O massive/O arch/O of/O smooth/O grey/O ''/O ,/O ``/O rock/O ,/O wide/O enough/O for/O two/O wagons/O to/O pass/O abreast/O ;/O the/O Water/O Tower/O rose/O from/O the/O center/O of/O the/O span/O ,/O commanding/O both/O road/O and/O river/O with/O its/O arrow/O slits/O ,/O murder/O holes/O ,/O and/O portcullises/O ./O 
It/O had/O taken/O the/O Freys/O three/O generations/O to/O complete/O their/O bridge/O ;/O when/O they/O were/O done/O they/O 'd/O thrown/O up/O stout/O timber/O keeps/O on/O either/O bank/O ,/O so/O no/O one/O might/O cross/O without/O their/O leave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O timber/O had/O long/O since/O given/O way/O to/O stone/O ./O 
The/O Twins-two/O squat/O ,/O ugly/O ,/O formidable/O castles/O ,/O identical/O in/O every/O respect/O ,/O with/O the/O bridge/O arching/O between-had/O guarded/O the/O crossing/O for/O centuries/O ./O 
High/O curtain/O walls/O ,/O deep/O moats/O ,/O and/O heavy/O oak-and-iron/O gates/O protected/O the/O approaches/O ,/O the/O bridge/O footings/O rose/O from/O within/O stout/O inner/O keeps/O ,/O there/O was/O a/O barbican/O and/O portcullis/O on/O either/O bank/O ,/O and/O the/O Water/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION defended/O the/O span/O itself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O One/O glance/O was/O sufficient/O to/O tell/O Catelyn/PERSON that/O the/O castle/O would/O not/O be/O taken/O by/O storm/O ./O 
The/O battlements/O bristled/O with/O spears/O and/O swords/O and/O scorpions/O ,/O there/O was/O an/O archer/O at/O every/O crenel/O and/O arrow/O slit/O ,/O the/O drawbridge/O was/O up/O ,/O the/O portcullis/O down/O ,/O the/O gates/O closed/O and/O barred/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Greatjon/O began/O to/O curse/O and/O swear/O as/O soon/O as/O he/O saw/O what/O awaited/O them/O ./O 
Lord/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON glowered/O in/O silence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O can/O not/O be/O assaulted/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O can/O we/O take/O it/O by/O siege/O ,/O without/O an/O army/O on/O the/O far/O bank/O to/O invest/O the/O other/O castle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Helman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON said/O gloomily/O ./O 
Across/O the/O deep-running/O green/O waters/O ,/O the/O western/O twin/O stood/O like/O a/O reflection/O of/O its/O eastern/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O if/O we/O had/O the/O time/O ./O 
Which/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O ,/O we/O do/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O As/O the/O northern/O lords/O studied/O the/O castle/O ,/O a/O sally/O port/O opened/O ,/O a/O plank/O bridge/O slid/O across/O the/O moat/O ,/O and/O a/O dozen/O knights/O rode/O forth/O to/O confront/O them/O ,/O led/O by/O four/O of/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O many/O sons/O ./O 
Their/O banner/O bore/O twin/O towers/O ,/O dark/O blue/O on/O a/O field/O of/O pale/O silver-grey/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O heir/O ,/O spoke/O for/O them/O ./O 
The/O Freys/ORGANIZATION all/O looked/O like/O weasels/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON ,/O past/O sixty/O with/O grandchildren/O of/O his/O own/O ,/O looked/O like/O an/O especially/O old/O and/O tired/O weasel/O ,/O yet/O he/O was/O polite/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O has/O sent/O me/O to/O greet/O you/O ,/O and/O inquire/O as/O to/O who/O leads/O this/O mighty/O host/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON spurred/O his/O horse/O forward/O ./O 
He/O was/O in/O his/O armor/O ,/O with/O the/O direwolf/O shield/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION strapped/O to/O his/O saddle/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON padding/O by/O his/O side/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O knight/O looked/O at/O her/O son/O with/O a/O faint/O flicker/O of/O amusement/O in/O his/O watery/O grey/O eyes/O ,/O though/O his/O gelding/O whickered/O uneasily/O and/O sidled/O away/O from/O the/O direwolf/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O would/O be/O most/O honored/O if/O you/O would/O share/O meat/O and/O mead/O with/O him/O in/O the/O castle/O and/O explain/O your/O purpose/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O words/O crashed/O among/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O like/O a/O great/O stone/O from/O a/O catapult/O ./O 
Not/O one/O of/O them/O approved/O ./O 
They/O cursed/O ,/O argued/O ,/O shouted/O down/O each/O other/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O must/O not/O do/O this/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON pleaded/O with/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON is/O not/O to/O be/O trusted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O in/O there/O alone/O and/O you/O 're/O his/O ./O 
He/O can/O sell/O you/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O throw/O you/O in/O a/O dungeon/O ,/O or/O slit/O your/O throat/O ,/O as/O he/O likes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O wants/O to/O talk/O to/O us/O ,/O let/O him/O open/O his/O gates/O ,/O and/O we/O will/O all/O share/O his/O meat/O and/O mead/O ,/O \/O ''/O declared/O Ser/O Wendel/O Manderly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Or/O let/O him/O come/O out/O and/O treat/O with/O Robb/PERSON here/O ,/O in/O plain/O sight/O of/O his/O men/O and/O ours/O ,/O \/O ''/O suggested/O his/O brother/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Wylis/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O shared/O all/O their/O doubts/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O only/O to/O glance/O at/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON to/O see/O that/O he/O was/O not/O pleased/O by/O what/O he/O was/O hearing/O ./O 
A/O few/O more/O words/O and/O the/O chance/O would/O be/O lost/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O act/O ,/O and/O quickly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O go/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O loudly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O Greatjon/PERSON furrowed/O his/O brow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O are/O you/O certain/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Clearly/O ,/O Robb/PERSON was/O not/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Never/O more/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/O lied/O glibly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON is/O my/O father/O 's/O bannerman/O ./O 
I/O have/O known/O him/O since/O I/O was/O a/O girl/O ./O 
He/O would/O never/O offer/O me/O any/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Unless/O he/O saw/O some/O profit/O in/O it/O ,/O she/O added/O silently/O ,/O but/O some/O truths/O did/O not/O bear/O saying/O ,/O and/O some/O lies/O were/O necessary/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O certain/O my/O lord/O father/O would/O be/O pleased/O to/O speak/O to/O the/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O vouchsafe/O for/O our/O good/O intentions/O ,/O my/O brother/O Ser/PERSON Perwyn/PERSON will/O remain/O here/O until/O she/O is/O safely/O returned/O to/O you/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O shall/O be/O our/O honored/O guest/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
Ser/PERSON Perwyn/PERSON ,/O the/O youngest/O of/O the/O four/O Freys/O in/O the/O party/O ,/O dismounted/O and/O handed/O the/O reins/O of/O his/O horse/O to/O a/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O require/O my/O lady/O mother/O 's/O return/O by/O evenfall/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O my/O intent/O to/O linger/O here/O long/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON Frey/PERSON gave/O a/O polite/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON spurred/O her/O horse/O forward/O and/O did/O not/O look/O back/O ./O 
Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O sons/O and/O envoys/O fell/O in/O around/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O father/O had/O once/O said/O of/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON that/O he/O was/O the/O only/O lord/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O who/O could/O field/O an/O army/O out/O of/O his/O breeches/O ./O 
When/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Crossing/O welcomed/O Catelyn/PERSON in/O the/O great/O hall/O of/O the/O east/O castle/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O twenty/O living/O sons/O -LRB-/O minus/O Ser/PERSON Perwyn/PERSON ,/O who/O would/O have/O made/O twenty-one/O -RRB-/O ,/O thirty-six/O grandsons/O ,/O nineteen/O great-grandsons/O ,/O and/O numerous/O daughters/O ,/O granddaughters/O ,/O bastards/O ,/O and/O grandbastards/O ,/O she/O understood/O just/O what/O he/O had/O meant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON was/O ninety/O ,/O a/O wizened/O pink/O weasel/O with/O a/O bald/O spotted/O head/O ,/O too/O gouty/O to/O stand/O unassisted/O ./O 
His/O newest/O wife/O ,/O a/O pale/O frail/O girl/O of/O sixteen/O years/O ,/O walked/O beside/O his/O litter/O when/O they/O carried/O him/O in/O ./O 
She/O was/O the/O eighth/O Lady/PERSON Frey/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O a/O great/O pleasure/O to/O see/O you/O again/O after/O so/O many/O years/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O squinted/O at/O her/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O ?/O 
I/O doubt/O that/O ./O 
Spare/O me/O your/O sweet/O words/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ,/O I/O am/O too/O old/O ./O 
Why/O are/O you/O here/O ?/O 
Is/O your/O boy/O too/O proud/O to/O come/O before/O me/O himself/O ?/O 
What/O am/O I/O to/O do/O with/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O been/O a/O girl/O the/O last/O time/O she/O had/O visited/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O but/O even/O then/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON had/O been/O irascible/O ,/O sharp/O of/O tongue/O ,/O and/O blunt/O of/O manner/O ./O 
Age/O had/O made/O him/O worse/O than/O ever/O ,/O it/O would/O seem/O ./O 
She/O would/O need/O to/O choose/O her/O words/O with/O care/O ,/O and/O do/O her/O best/O to/O take/O no/O offense/O from/O his/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON said/O reproachfully/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O forget/O yourself/O ./O 
Lady/O Stark/O is/O here/O at/O your/O invitation/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O I/O ask/O you/O ?/O 
You/O are/O not/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON yet/O ,/O not/O until/O I/O die/O ./O 
Do/O I/O look/O dead/O ?/O 
I/O 'll/O hear/O no/O instructions/O from/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O way/O to/O speak/O in/O front/O of/O our/O noble/O guest/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O his/O younger/O sons/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O my/O bastards/O presume/O to/O teach/O me/O courtesy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON complained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O speak/O any/O way/O I/O like/O ,/O damn/O you/O ./O 
I/O 've/O had/O three/O kings/O to/O guest/O in/O my/O life/O ,/O and/O queens/O as/O well/O ,/O do/O you/O think/O I/O require/O lessons/O from/O the/O likes/O of/O you/O ,/O Ryger/PERSON ?/O 
Your/O mother/O was/O milking/O goats/O the/O first/O time/O I/O gave/O ''/O ,/O ``/O her/O my/O seed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O dismissed/O the/O red/O -/O faced/O youth/O with/O a/O flick/O of/O his/O fingers/O and/O gestured/O to/O two/O of/O his/O other/O sons/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Danwell/O ,/O Whalen/PERSON ,/O help/O me/O to/O my/O chair/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O shifted/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON from/O his/O litter/O and/O carried/O him/O to/O the/O high/O seat/O of/O the/O Freys/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O tall/O chair/O of/O black/O oak/O whose/O back/O was/O carved/O in/O the/O shape/O of/O two/O towers/O linked/O by/O a/O bridge/O ./O 
His/O young/O wife/O crept/O up/O timidly/O and/O covered/O his/O legs/O with/O a/O blanket/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O settled/O ,/O the/O old/O man/O beckoned/O Catelyn/PERSON forward/O and/O planted/O a/O papery/O dry/O kiss/O on/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O that/O I/O have/O observed/O the/O courtesies/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O perhaps/O my/O sons/O will/O do/O me/O the/O honor/O of/O shutting/O their/O mouths/O ./O 
Why/O are/O you/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O ask/O you/O to/O open/O your/O gates/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O politely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O son/O and/O his/O lords/O bannermen/O are/O most/O anxious/O to/O cross/O the/O river/O and/O be/O on/O their/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O Riverrun/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O sniggered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O no/O need/O to/O tell/O me/O ,/O no/O need/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O blind/O yet/O ./O 
The/O old/O man/O can/O still/O read/O a/O map/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O Riverrun/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON confirmed/O ./O 
She/O saw/O no/O reason/O to/O deny/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O I/O might/O have/O expected/O to/O find/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
You/O are/O still/O my/O father/O 's/O bannerman/O ,/O are/O you/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Heh/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON ,/O a/O noise/O halfway/O between/O a/O laugh/O and/O a/O grunt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O called/O my/O swords/O ,/O yes/O I/O did/O ,/O here/O they/O are/O ,/O you/O saw/O them/O on/O the/O walls/O ./O 
It/O was/O my/O intent/O to/O march/O as/O soon/O as/O all/O my/O strength/O was/O assembled/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O to/O send/O my/O sons/O ./O 
I/O am/O well/O past/O marching/O myself/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O around/O for/O likely/O confirmation/O and/O pointed/O to/O a/O tall/O ,/O stooped/O man/O of/O fifty/O years/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O her/O ,/O Jared/PERSON ./O 
Tell/O her/O that/O was/O my/O intent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Jared/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O one/O of/O his/O sons/O by/O his/O second/O wife/O ./O 
\/O ``/O On/O my/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O it/O my/O fault/O that/O your/O fool/O brother/O lost/O his/O battle/O before/O we/O could/O march/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O back/O against/O his/O cushions/O and/O scowled/O at/O her/O ,/O as/O if/O challenging/O her/O to/O dispute/O his/O version/O of/O events/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O told/O the/O Kingslayer/O went/O through/O him/O like/O an/O axe/O through/O ripe/O cheese/O ./O 
Why/O should/O my/O boys/O hurry/O south/O to/O die/O ?/O 
All/O those/O who/O did/O go/O south/O are/O running/O north/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O gladly/O have/O spitted/O the/O querulous/O old/O man/O and/O roasted/O him/O over/O a/O fire/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O only/O till/O evenfall/O to/O open/O the/O bridge/O ./O 
Calmly/O ,/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O All/O the/O more/O reason/O that/O we/O must/O reach/O Riverrun/O ,/O and/O soon/O ./O 
Where/O can/O we/O go/O to/O talk/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 're/O talking/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON complained/O ./O 
The/O spotted/O pink/O head/O snapped/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O all/O looking/O at/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O at/O his/O kin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O out/O of/O here/O ./O 
Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON wants/O to/O speak/O to/O me/O in/O private/O ./O 
Might/O be/O she/O has/O designs/O on/O my/O fidelity/O ,/O heh/O ./O 
Go/O ,/O all/O of/O you/O ,/O find/O something/O useful/O to/O do/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O you/O too/O ,/O woman/O ./O 
Out/O ,/O out/O ,/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O As/O his/O sons/O and/O grandsons/O and/O daughters/O and/O bastards/O and/O nieces/O and/O nephews/O streamed/O from/O the/O hall/O ,/O he/O leaned/O close/O to/O Catelyn/LOCATION and/O confessed/O ,/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O all/O waiting/O for/O me/O to/O die/O ./O 
Stevron/PERSON 's/O been/O waiting/O for/O forty/O years/O ,/O but/O I/O keep/O disappointing/O him/O ./O 
Heh/O ./O 
Why/O should/O I/O die/O just/O so/O he/O can/O be/O a/O lord/O ?/O 
I/O ask/O you/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O do/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O every/O hope/O that/O you/O will/O live/O to/O be/O a/O hundred/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O would/O boil/O them/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O to/O be/O sure/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O want/O to/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O want/O to/O cross/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
That/O 's/O blunt/O ./O 
Why/O should/O I/O let/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O her/O anger/O flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O were/O strong/O enough/O to/O climb/O your/O own/O battlements/O ,/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON ,/O you/O would/O see/O that/O my/O son/O has/O twenty/O thousand/O men/O outside/O your/O walls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 'll/O be/O twenty/O thousand/O fresh/O corpses/O when/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON gets/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O shot/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O you/O try/O and/O frighten/O me/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Your/O husband/O 's/O in/O some/O traitor/O 's/O cell/O under/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O your/O father/O 's/O sick/O ,/O might/O be/O dying/O ,/O and/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O got/O your/O brother/O in/O chains/O ./O 
What/O do/O you/O have/O that/O I/O should/O fear/O ?/O 
That/O son/O of/O yours/O ?/O 
I/O 'll/O match/O you/O son/O for/O son/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O still/O have/O eighteen/O when/O yours/O are/O all/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O swore/O an/O oath/O to/O my/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O bobbed/O his/O head/O side/O to/O side/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ,/O I/O said/O some/O words/O ,/O but/O I/O swore/O oaths/O to/O the/O crown/O too/O ,/O it/O seems/O to/O me/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON 's/O the/O king/O now/O ,/O and/O that/O makes/O you/O and/O your/O boy/O and/O all/O those/O fools/O out/O there/O no/O better/O than/O rebels/O ./O 
If/O I/O had/O the/O sense/O the/O gods/O gave/O a/O fish/O ,/O I/O 'd/O help/O the/O Lannisters/O boil/O you/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O do/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O challenged/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON snorted/O with/O disdain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON the/O proud/O and/O splendid/O ,/O Warden/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O oh/O ,/O what/O a/O great/O man/O that/O one/O is/O ,/O him/O and/O his/O gold/O this/O and/O gold/O that/O and/O lions/O here/O and/O lions/O there/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O wager/O you/O ,/O he/O cats/O too/O many/O beans/O ,/O he/O breaks/O wind/O just/O like/O me/O ,/O but/O you/O 'll/O never/O hear/O him/O admit/O it/O ,/O oh/O ,/O no/O ./O 
What/O 's/O he/O got/O to/O be/O so/O puffed/O up/O about/O anyway/O ?/O 
Only/O two/O sons/O ,/O and/O one/O of/O them/O 's/O a/O twisted/O little/O monster/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O match/O him/O son/O for/O son/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O still/O have/O nineteen/O and/O a/O half/O left/O when/O all/O of/O his/O are/O dead/O !/O 
\/O ''/O He/O cackled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON wants/O my/O help/O ,/O he/O can/O bloody/O well/O ask/O for/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O was/O all/O Catelyn/PERSON needed/O to/O hear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O asking/O for/O your/O help/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O humbly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O my/O father/O and/O my/O brother/O and/O my/O lord/O husband/O and/O my/O sons/O are/O asking/O with/O my/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON jabbed/O a/O bony/O finger/O at/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Save/O your/O sweet/O words/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Sweet/O words/O I/O get/O from/O my/O wife/O ./O 
Did/O you/O see/O her/O ?/O 
Sixteen/O she/O is/O ,/O a/O little/O flower/O ,/O and/O her/O honey/O 's/O only/O for/O me/O ./O 
I/O wager/O she/O gives/O me/O a/O son/O by/O this/O time/O next/O year/O ./O 
Perhaps/O I/O 'll/O make/O him/O heir/O ,/O would/O n't/O that/O boil/O the/O rest/O of/O them/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O certain/O she/O will/O give/O you/O many/O sons/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O head/O bobbed/O up/O and/O down/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O lord/O father/O did/O not/O come/O to/O the/O wedding/O ./O 
An/O insult/O ,/O as/O I/O see/O it/O ./O 
Even/O if/O he/O is/O dying/O ./O 
He/O never/O came/O to/O my/O last/O wedding/O either/O ./O 
He/O calls/O me/O the/O Late/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON ,/O you/O know/O ./O 
Does/O he/O think/O I/O 'm/O dead/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O not/O dead/O ,/O and/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O I/O 'll/O outlive/O him/O as/O I/O outlived/O his/O father/O ./O 
Your/O family/O has/O always/O pissed/O on/O me/O ,/O do/O n't/O deny/O it/O ,/O do/O n't/O lie/O ,/O you/O know/O it/O 's/O true/O ./O 
Years/O ago/O ,/O I/O went/O to/O your/O father/O and/O suggested/O a/O match/O between/O his/O son/O and/O my/O daughter/O ./O 
Why/O not/O ?/O 
I/O had/O a/O daughter/O in/O mind/O ,/O sweet/O girl/O ,/O only/O a/O few/O years/O older/O than/O Edmure/PERSON ,/O but/O if/O your/O brother/O did/O n't/O warm/O to/O her/O ,/O I/O had/O others/O he/O might/O have/O had/O ,/O young/O ones/O ,/O old/O ones/O ,/O virgins/O ,/O widows/O ,/O whatever/O he/O wanted/O ./O 
No/O ,/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON would/O not/O hear/O of/O it/O ./O 
Sweet/O words/O he/O gave/O me/O ,/O excuses/O ,/O but/O what/O I/O wanted/O was/O to/O get/O rid/O of/O a/O daughter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O your/O sister/O ,/O that/O one/O ,/O she/O 's/O full/O as/O bad/O ./O 
It/O was/O ,/O oh/O ,/O a/O year/O ago/O ,/O no/O more/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON was/O still/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ,/O and/O I/O went/O to/O the/O city/O to/O see/O my/O sons/O ride/O in/O the/O tourney/O ./O 
Stevron/PERSON and/O Jared/PERSON are/O too/O old/O for/O the/O lists/O now/O ,/O but/O Danwell/PERSON and/O Hosteen/PERSON rode/O ,/O Perwyn/PERSON as/O well/O ,/O and/O a/O couple/O of/O my/O bastards/O tried/O the/O melee/O ./O 
If/O I/O 'd/O known/O how/O they/O 'd/O shame/O me/O ,/O I/O would/O never/O have/O troubled/O myself/O to/O make/O the/O journey/O ./O 
Why/O did/O I/O need/O to/O ride/O all/O that/O way/O to/O see/O Hosteen/PERSON knocked/O off/O his/O horse/O by/O that/O Tyrell/PERSON whelp/O ?/O 
I/O ask/O you/O ./O 
The/O boy/O 's/O half/O his/O age/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Daisy/PERSON they/O call/O him/O ,/O something/O like/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O Danwell/PERSON was/O unhorsed/O by/O a/O hedge/O knight/O !/O 
Some/O days/O I/O wonder/O if/O those/O two/O are/O truly/O mine/O ./O 
My/O third/O wife/O was/O a/O Crakehall/PERSON ,/O all/O of/O the/O Crakehall/O women/O are/O sluts/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O never/O mind/O about/O that/O ,/O she/O died/O before/O you/O were/O born/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O care/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O speaking/O of/O your/O sister/O ./O 
I/O proposed/O that/O Lord/O and/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON foster/O two/O of/O my/O grandsons/O at/O court/O ,/O and/O offered/O to/O take/O their/O own/O son/O to/O ward/O here/O at/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Are/O my/O grandsons/O unworthy/O to/O be/O seen/O at/O the/O king/O 's/O court/O ?/O 
They/O are/O sweet/O boys/O ,/O quiet/O and/O mannerly/O ./O 
Walder/PERSON is/O Merrett/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O named/O after/O me/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O one/O .../O heh/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O recall/O .../O he/O might/O have/O been/O another/O Walder/PERSON ,/O they/O 're/O always/O naming/O them/O Walder/PERSON so/O I/O 'll/O favor/O them/O ,/O but/O his/O father/O .../O which/O one/O was/O his/O father/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O His/O face/O wrinkled/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O whoever/O he/O was/O ,/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON would/O n't/O have/O him/O ,/O or/O the/O other/O one/O ,/O and/O I/O blame/O your/O lady/O sister/O for/O that/O ./O 
She/O frosted/O up/O as/O if/O I/O 'd/O suggested/O selling/O her/O boy/O to/O a/O mummer/O 's/O show/O or/O making/O a/O eunuch/O out/O of/O him/O ,/O and/O when/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON said/O the/O child/O was/O going/O to/O Dragonstone/LOCATION to/O foster/O with/O Stannis/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O she/O stormed/O off/O without/O a/O word/O of/O regrets/O and/O all/O the/O Hand/O could/O give/O me/O was/O apologies/O ./O 
What/O good/O are/O apologies/O ?/O 
I/O ask/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O frowned/O ,/O disquieted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O understood/O that/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O boy/O was/O to/O be/O fostered/O with/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O it/O was/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON said/O irritably/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O I/O ca/O n't/O tell/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON from/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ?/O 
They/O 're/O both/O bungholes/O who/O think/O they/O 're/O too/O noble/O to/O shit/O ,/O but/O never/O mind/O about/O that/O ,/O I/O know/O the/O difference/O ./O 
Or/O do/O you/O think/O I/O 'm/O so/O old/O I/O ca/O n't/O remember/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O ninety/O and/O I/O remember/O very/O well/O ./O 
I/O remember/O what/O to/O do/O with/O a/O woman/O too/O ./O 
That/O wife/O of/O mine/O will/O give/O me/O a/O son/O before/O this/O time/O next/O year/O ,/O I/O 'll/O wager/O ./O 
Or/O a/O daughter/O ,/O that/O ca/O n't/O be/O helped/O ./O 
Boy/O or/O girl/O ,/O it/O will/O be/O red/O ,/O wrinkled/O ,/O and/O squalling/O ,/O and/O like/O as/O not/O she/O 'll/O want/O to/O name/O it/O Walder/PERSON or/O Walda/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O not/O concerned/O with/O what/O Lady/PERSON Frey/PERSON might/O choose/O to/O name/O her/O child/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON was/O going/O to/O foster/O his/O son/O with/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O you/O are/O quite/O certain/O of/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O yes/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O he/O died/O ,/O so/O what/O does/O it/O matter/O ?/O 
You/O say/O you/O want/O to/O cross/O the/O river/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O do./O ,/O '/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON announced/O crisply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O unless/O I/O allow/O it/O ,/O and/O why/O should/O I/O ?/O 
The/O Tullys/O and/O the/O Starks/PERSON have/O never/O been/O friends/O of/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pushed/O himself/O back/O in/O his/O chair/O and/O crossed/O his/O arms/O ,/O smirking/O ,/O waiting/O for/O her/O answer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rest/O was/O only/O haggling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O swollen/O red/O sun/O hung/O low/O against/O the/O western/O hills/O when/O the/O gates/O of/O the/O castle/O opened/O ./O 
The/O drawbridge/O creaked/O down/O ,/O the/O portcullis/O winched/O up/O ,/O and/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON rode/O forth/O to/O rejoin/O her/O son/O and/O his/O lords/O bannermen/O ./O 
Behind/O her/O came/O Ser/PERSON Jared/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Hosteen/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Danwell/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O and/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O bastard/O son/O Ronel/PERSON Rivers/PERSON ,/O leading/O a/O long/O column/O of/O pikemen/O ,/O rank/O on/O rank/O of/O shuffling/O men/O in/O blue/O steel/O ringmail/O and/O silvery/O grey/O cloaks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON galloped/O out/O to/O meet/O her/O ,/O with/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON racing/O beside/O his/O stallion/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON will/O grant/O you/O your/O crossing/O ./O 
His/O swords/O are/O yours/O as/O well/O ,/O less/O four/O hundred/O he/O means/O to/O keep/O back/O to/O hold/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
I/O suggest/O that/O you/O leave/O four/O hundred/O of/O your/O own/O ,/O a/O mixed/O force/O of/O archers/O and/O swordsmen/O ./O 
He/O can/O scarcely/O object/O to/O an/O offer/O to/O augment/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O garrison/O .../O but/O make/O certain/O you/O give/O the/O command/O to/O a/O man/O you/O can/O trust/O ./O 
Lord/O Walder/PERSON may/O need/O help/O keeping/O faith/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Mother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON answered/O ,/O gazing/O at/O the/O ranks/O of/O pikemen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O .../O Ser/PERSON Helman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON ,/O do/O you/O think/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O fine/O choice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O .../O what/O did/O he/O want/O of/O us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O can/O spare/O a/O few/O of/O your/O swords/O ,/O I/O need/O some/O men/O to/O escort/O two/O of/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON 's/O grandsons/O north/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O agreed/O to/O take/O them/O as/O wards/O ./O 
They/O are/O young/O boys/O ,/O aged/O eight/O years/O and/O seven/O ./O 
It/O would/O seem/O they/O are/O both/O named/O Walder/PERSON ./O 
Your/O brother/O Bran/PERSON will/O welcome/O the/O companionship/O of/O lads/O near/O his/O own/O age/O ,/O I/O should/O think/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O all/O ?/O 
Two/O fosterlings/O ?/O 
That/O 's/O a/O small/O enough/O price/O to/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON 's/O son/O Olyvar/PERSON will/O be/O coming/O with/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O to/O serve/O as/O your/O personal/O squire/O ./O 
His/O father/O would/O like/O to/O see/O him/O knighted/O ,/O in/O good/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O squire/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fine/O ,/O that/O 's/O fine/O ,/O if/O he/O 's/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Also/O ,/O if/O your/O sister/O Arya/PERSON is/O returned/O to/O us/O safely/O ,/O it/O is/O agreed/O that/O she/O will/O marry/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O youngest/O son/O ,/O Elmar/PERSON ,/O when/O the/O two/O of/O them/O come/O of/O age/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON looked/O nonplussed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON wo/O n't/O like/O that/O one/O bit/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O are/O to/O wed/O one/O of/O his/O daughters/O ,/O once/O the/O fighting/O is/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O finished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O lordship/O has/O graciously/O consented/O to/O allow/O you/O to/O choose/O whichever/O girl/O you/O prefer/O ./O 
He/O has/O a/O number/O he/O thinks/O might/O be/O suitable/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O To/O his/O credit/O ,/O Robb/PERSON did/O not/O flinch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O consent/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O I/O refuse/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O if/O you/O wish/O to/O cross/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O consent/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O solemnly/O ./O 
He/O had/O never/O seemed/O more/O manly/O to/O her/O than/O he/O did/O in/O that/O moment/O ./O 
Boys/O might/O play/O with/O swords/O ,/O but/O it/O took/O a/O lord/O to/O make/O a/O marriage/O pact/O ,/O knowing/O what/O it/O meant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O crossed/O at/O evenfall/O as/O a/O horned/O moon/O floated/O upon/O the/O river/O ./O 
The/O double/O column/O wound/O its/O way/O through/O the/O gate/O of/O the/O eastern/O twin/O like/O a/O great/O steel/O snake/O ,/O slithering/O across/O the/O courtyard/O ,/O into/O the/O keep/O and/O over/O the/O bridge/O ,/O to/O issue/O forth/O once/O more/O from/O the/O second/O castle/O on/O the/O west/O bank/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON rode/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O serpent/O ,/O with/O her/O son/O and/O her/O uncle/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON Frey/PERSON ./O 
Behind/O followed/O nine/O tenths/O of/O their/O horse/O ;/O knights/O ,/O lancers/O ,/O freeriders/O ,/O and/O mounted/O bowmen/O ./O 
It/O took/O hours/O for/O them/O all/O to/O cross/O ./O 
Afterward/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O remember/O the/O clatter/O of/O countless/O hooves/O on/O the/O drawbridge/O ,/O the/O sight/O of/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON in/O his/O litter/O watching/O them/O pass/O ,/O the/O glitter/O of/O eyes/O peering/O down/O through/O the/O slats/O of/O the/O murder/O holes/O in/O the/O ceiling/O as/O they/O rode/O through/O the/O Water/O Tower/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O larger/O part/O of/O the/O northern/O host/O ,/O pikes/O and/O archers/O and/O great/O masses/O of/O men-at-arms/O on/O foot/O ,/O remained/O upon/O the/O east/O bank/O under/O the/O command/O of/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON ./O 
Robb/PERSON had/O commanded/O him/O to/O continue/O the/O march/O south/O ,/O to/O confront/O the/O huge/O Lannister/O army/O coming/O north/O under/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O good/O or/O ill/O ,/O her/O son/O had/O thrown/O the/O dice/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
