-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O visitors/O poured/O through/O the/O castle/O gates/O in/O a/O river/O of/O gold/O and/O silver/O and/O polished/O steel/O ,/O three/O hundred/O strong/O ,/O a/O pride/O of/O bannermen/O and/O knights/O ,/O of/O sworn/O swords/O and/O freeriders/O ./O 
Over/O their/O heads/O a/O dozen/O golden/O banners/O whipped/O back/O and/O forth/O in/O the/O northern/O wind/O ,/O emblazoned/O with/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O Baratheon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O knew/O many/O of/O the/O riders/O ./O 
There/O came/O Ser/O Jaime/O Lannister/O with/O hair/O as/O bright/O as/O beaten/O gold/O ,/O and/O there/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON with/O his/O terrible/O burned/O face/O ./O 
The/O tall/O boy/O beside/O him/O could/O only/O be/O the/O crown/O prince/O ,/O and/O that/O stunted/O little/O man/O behind/O them/O was/O surely/O the/O Imp/O ,/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O the/O huge/O man/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O column/O ,/O flanked/O by/O two/O knights/O in/O the/O snow-white/O cloaks/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O seemed/O almost/O a/O stranger/O to/O Ned/O .../O until/O he/O vaulted/O off/O the/O back/O of/O his/O warhorse/O with/O a/O familiar/O roar/O ,/O and/O crushed/O him/O in/O a/O bone-crunching/O hug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ned/O !/O 
Ah/O ,/O but/O it/O is/O good/O to/O see/O that/O frozen/O face/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O looked/O him/O over/O top/O to/O bottom/O ,/O and/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O not/O changed/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Would/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O been/O able/O to/O say/O the/O same/O ./O 
Fifteen/O years/O past/O ,/O when/O they/O had/O ridden/O forth/O to/O win/O a/O throne/O ,/O the/O Lord/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O had/O been/O clean-shaven/O ,/O clear-eyed/O ,/O and/O muscled/O like/O a/O maiden/O 's/O fantasy/O ./O 
Six/O and/O a/O half/O feet/O tall/O ,/O he/O towered/O over/O lesser/O men/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O donned/O his/O armor/O and/O the/O great/O antlered/O helmet/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O he/O became/O a/O veritable/O giant/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O had/O a/O giant/O 's/O strength/O too/O ,/O his/O weapon/O of/O choice/O a/O spiked/O iron/O warhammer/O that/O Ned/PERSON could/O scarcely/O lift/O ./O 
In/O those/O days/O ,/O the/O smell/O of/O leather/O and/O blood/O had/O clung/O to/O him/O like/O perfume/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O it/O was/O perfume/O that/O clung/O to/O him/O like/O perfume/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O a/O girth/O to/O match/O his/O height/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O last/O seen/O the/O king/O nine/O years/O before/O during/O Balon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON 's/O rebellion/O ,/O when/O the/O stag/O and/O the/O direwolf/O had/O joined/O to/O end/O the/O pretensions/O of/O the/O self-proclaimed/O King/O of/O the/O Iron/O Islands/O ./O 
Since/O the/O night/O they/O had/O stood/O side/O by/O side/O in/O Greyjoy/LOCATION 's/O fallen/O stronghold/O ,/O where/O Robert/PERSON had/O accepted/O the/O rebel/O lord/O 's/O surrender/O and/O Ned/PERSON had/O taken/O his/O son/O Theon/PERSON as/O hostage/O and/O ward/O ,/O the/O king/O had/O gained/O at/O least/O eight/O stone/O ./O 
A/O beard/O as/O coarse/O and/O black/O as/O iron/O wire/O covered/O his/O jaw/O to/O hide/O his/O double/O chin/O and/O the/O sag/O of/O the/O royal/O jowls/O ,/O but/O nothing/O could/O hide/O his/O stomach/O or/O the/O dark/O circles/O under/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O Robert/PERSON was/O Ned/PERSON 's/O king/O now/O ,/O and/O not/O just/O a/O friend/O ,/O so/O he/O said/O only/O ,/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
Winterfell/O is/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O then/O the/O others/O were/O dismounting/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O grooms/O were/O coming/O forward/O for/O their/O mounts/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON 's/O queen/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O entered/O on/O foot/O with/O her/O younger/O children/O ./O 
The/O wheelhouse/O in/O which/O they/O had/O ridden/O ,/O a/O huge/O double-decked/O carriage/O of/O oiled/O oak/O and/O gilded/O metal/O pulled/O by/O forty/O heavy/O draft/O horses/O ,/O was/O too/O wide/O to/O pass/O through/O the/O castle/O gate/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON knelt/O in/O the/O snow/O to/O kiss/O the/O queen/O 's/O ring/O ,/O while/O Robert/PERSON embraced/O Catelyn/PERSON like/O a/O long-lost/O sister/O ./O 
Then/O the/O children/O had/O been/O brought/O forward/O ,/O introduced/O ,/O and/O approved/O of/O by/O both/O sides/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O sooner/O had/O those/O formalities/O of/O greeting/O been/O completed/O than/O the/O king/O had/O said/O to/O his/O host/O ,/O \/O ``/O Take/O me/O down/O to/O your/O crypt/O ,/O Eddard/O ./O 
I/O would/O pay/O my/O respects/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON loved/O him/O for/O that/O ,/O for/O remembering/O her/O still/O after/O all/O these/O years/O ./O 
He/O called/O for/O a/O lantern/O ./O 
No/O other/O words/O were/O needed/O ./O 
The/O queen/O had/O begun/O to/O protest/O ./O 
They/O had/O been/O riding/O since/O dawn/O ,/O everyone/O was/O tired/O and/O cold/O ,/O surely/O they/O should/O refresh/O themselves/O first/O ./O 
The/O dead/O would/O wait/O ./O 
She/O had/O said/O no/O more/O than/O that/O ;/O Robert/PERSON had/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O and/O her/O twin/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON had/O taken/O her/O quietly/O by/O the/O arm/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O said/O no/O more/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O went/O down/O to/O the/O crypt/O together/O ,/O Ned/PERSON and/O this/O king/O he/O scarcely/O recognized/O ./O 
The/O winding/O stone/O steps/O were/O narrow/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON went/O first/O with/O the/O lantern/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O starting/O to/O think/O we/O would/O never/O reach/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON complained/O as/O they/O descended/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O the/O south/O ,/O the/O way/O they/O talk/O about/O my/O Seven/ORGANIZATION Kingdoms/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O man/O forgets/O that/O your/O part/O is/O as/O big/O as/O the/O other/O six/O combined/O ./O 
\/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O trust/O you/O enjoyed/O the/O journey/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bogs/O and/O forests/O and/O fields/O ,/O and/O scarcely/O a/O decent/O inn/O north/O of/O the/O Neck/O ./O 
I/O 've/O never/O seen/O such/O a/O vast/O emptiness/O ./O 
Where/O are/O all/O your/O people/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Likely/O they/O were/O too/O shy/O to/O come/O out/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON jested/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O the/O chill/O coming/O up/O the/O stairs/O ,/O a/O cold/O breath/O from/O deep/O within/O the/O earth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kings/O are/O a/O rare/O sight/O in/O the/O north/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O More/O likely/O they/O were/O hiding/O under/O the/O snow/O ./O 
Snow/O ,/O Ned/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O put/O one/O hand/O on/O the/O wall/O to/O steady/O himself/O as/O they/O descended/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Late/O summer/O snows/O are/O common/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O they/O did/O not/O trouble/O you/O ./O 
They/O are/O usually/O mild/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O take/O your/O mild/O snows/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON swore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O will/O this/O place/O be/O like/O in/O winter/O ?/O 
I/O shudder/O to/O think/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O winters/O are/O hard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O the/O Starks/PERSON will/O endure/O ./O 
We/O always/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O need/O to/O come/O south/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O need/O a/O taste/O of/O summer/O before/O it/O flees/O ./O 
In/O Highgarden/LOCATION there/O are/O fields/O of/O golden/O roses/O that/O stretch/O away/O as/O far/O as/O the/O eye/O can/O see/O ./O 
The/O fruits/O are/O so/O ripe/O they/O explode/O in/O your/O mouth-melons/O ,/O peaches/O ,/O fireplums/O ,/O you/O 've/O never/O tasted/O such/O sweetness/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O see/O ,/O I/O brought/O you/O some/O ./O 
Even/O at/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ,/O with/O that/O good/O wind/O off/O the/O bay/O ,/O the/O days/O are/O so/O hot/O you/O can/O barely/O move/O ./O 
And/O you/O ought/O to/O see/O the/O towns/O ,/O Ned/PERSON !/O 
Flowers/O everywhere/O ,/O the/O markets/O bursting/O with/O food/O ,/O the/O summerwines/O so/O cheap/O and/O so/O good/O that/O you/O can/O get/O drunk/O just/O breathing/O the/O air/O ./O 
Everyone/O is/O fat/O and/O drunk/O and/O rich/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O and/O slapped/O his/O own/O ample/O stomach/O a/O thump/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O the/O girls/O ,/O Ned/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O exclaimed/O ,/O his/O eyes/O sparkling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O swear/O ,/O women/O lose/O all/O modesty/O in/O the/O heat/O ./O 
They/O swim/O naked/O in/O the/O river/O ,/O right/O beneath/O the/O castle/O ./O 
Even/O in/O the/O streets/O ,/O it/O 's/O too/O damn/O hot/O for/O wool/O or/O fur/O ,/O so/O they/O go/O around/O in/O these/O short/O gowns/O ,/O silk/O if/O they/O have/O the/O silver/O and/O cotton/O if/O not/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O all/O the/O same/O when/O they/O start/O sweating/O and/O the/O cloth/O sticks/O to/O their/O skin/O ,/O they/O might/O as/O well/O be/O naked/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O laughed/O happily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON had/O always/O been/O a/O man/O of/O huge/O appetites/O ,/O a/O man/O who/O knew/O how/O to/O take/O his/O pleasures/O ./O 
That/O was/O not/O a/O charge/O anyone/O could/O lay/O at/O the/O door/O of/O Eddard/O Stark/O ./O 
Yet/O Ned/PERSON could/O not/O help/O but/O notice/O that/O those/O pleasures/O were/O taking/O a/O toll/O on/O the/O king/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O breathing/O heavily/O by/O the/O time/O they/O reached/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O stairs/O ,/O his/O face/O red/O in/O the/O lantern/O light/O as/O they/O stepped/O out/O into/O the/O darkness/O of/O the/O crypt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O respectfully/O ./O 
He/O swept/O the/O lantern/O in/O a/O wide/O semicircle/O ./O 
Shadows/O moved/O and/O lurched/O ./O 
Flickering/O light/O touched/O the/O stones/O underfoot/O and/O brushed/O against/O a/O long/O ''/O ,/O ``/O procession/O of/O granite/O pillars/O that/O marched/O ahead/O ,/O two/O by/O two/O ,/O into/O the/O dark/O ./O 
Between/O the/O pillars/O ,/O the/O dead/O sat/O on/O their/O stone/O thrones/O against/O the/O walls/O ,/O backs/O against/O the/O sepulchres/O that/O contained/O their/O mortal/O remains/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O is/O down/O at/O the/O end/O ,/O with/O Father/O and/O Brandon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O led/O the/O way/O between/O the/O pillars/O and/O Robert/PERSON followed/O wordlessly/O ,/O shivering/O in/O the/O subterranean/O chill/O ./O 
It/O was/O always/O cold/O down/O here/O ./O 
Their/O footsteps/O rang/O off/O the/O stones/O and/O echoed/O in/O the/O vault/O overhead/O as/O they/O walked/O among/O the/O dead/O of/O House/O Stark/O ./O 
The/O Lords/O of/O Winterfell/PERSON watched/O them/O pass/O ./O 
Their/O likenesses/O were/O carved/O into/O the/O stones/O that/O sealed/O the/O tombs/O ./O 
In/O long/O rows/O they/O sat/O ,/O blind/O eyes/O staring/O out/O into/O eternal/O darkness/O ,/O while/O great/O stone/O direwolves/O curled/O round/O their/O feet/O ./O 
The/O shifting/O shadows/O made/O the/O stone/O figures/O seem/O to/O stir/O as/O the/O living/O passed/O by/O ./O 
By/O ancient/O custom/O an/O iron/O longsword/O had/O been/O laid/O across/O the/O lap/O of/O each/O who/O had/O been/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O to/O keep/O the/O vengeful/O spirits/O in/O their/O crypts/O ./O 
The/O oldest/O had/O long/O ago/O rusted/O away/O to/O nothing/O ,/O leaving/O only/O a/O few/O red/O stains/O where/O the/O metal/O had/O rested/O on/O stone/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON wondered/O if/O that/O meant/O those/O ghosts/O were/O free/O to/O roam/O the/O castle/O now/O ./O 
He/O hoped/O not/O ./O 
The/O first/O Lords/O of/O Winterfell/PERSON had/O been/O men/O hard/O as/O the/O land/O they/O ruled/O ./O 
In/O the/O centuries/O before/O the/O Dragonlords/O came/O over/O the/O sea/O ,/O they/O had/O sworn/O allegiance/O to/O no/O man/O ,/O styling/O themselves/O the/O Kings/ORGANIZATION in/O the/O North/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON stopped/O at/O last/O and/O lifted/O the/O oil/O lantern/O ./O 
The/O crypt/O continued/O on/O into/O darkness/O ahead/O of/O them/O ,/O but/O beyond/O this/O point/O the/O tombs/O were/O empty/O and/O unsealed/O ;/O black/O holes/O waiting/O for/O their/O dead/O ,/O waiting/O for/O him/O and/O his/O children/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON did/O not/O like/O to/O think/O on/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O his/O king/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON nodded/O silently/O ,/O knelt/O ,/O and/O bowed/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O were/O three/O tombs/O ,/O side/O by/O side/O ./O 
Lord/O Rickard/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O Ned/PERSON 's/O father/O ,/O had/O a/O long/O ,/O stern/O face/O ./O 
The/O stonemason/O had/O known/O him/O well/O ./O 
He/O sat/O with/O quiet/O dignity/O ,/O stone/O fingers/O holding/O tight/O to/O the/O sword/O across/O his/O lap/O ,/O but/O in/O life/O all/O swords/O had/O failed/O him/O ./O 
In/O two/O smaller/O sepulchres/O on/O either/O side/O were/O his/O children/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Brandon/PERSON had/O been/O twenty/O when/O he/O died/O ,/O strangled/O by/O order/O of/O the/O Mad/O King/O Aerys/O Targaryen/O only/O a/O few/O short/O days/O before/O he/O was/O to/O wed/O Catelyn/PERSON Tully/PERSON of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
His/O father/O had/O been/O forced/O to/O watch/O him/O die/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O true/O heir/O ,/O the/O eldest/O ,/O born/O to/O rule/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lyanna/PERSON had/O only/O been/O sixteen/O ,/O a/O child/O -/O woman/O of/O surpassing/O loveliness/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O loved/O her/O with/O all/O his/O heart/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON had/O loved/O her/O even/O more/O ./O 
She/O was/O to/O have/O been/O his/O bride/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O more/O beautiful/O than/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O after/O a/O silence/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O lingered/O on/O Lyanna/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O could/O will/O her/O back/O to/O life/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O rose/O ,/O made/O awkward/O by/O his/O weight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O damn/O it/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O did/O you/O have/O to/O bury/O her/O in/O a/O place/O like/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O was/O hoarse/O with/O remembered/O grief/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O deserved/O more/O than/O darkness/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O a/O Stark/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O quietly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O her/O place/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O should/O be/O on/O a/O hill/O somewhere/O ,/O under/O a/O fruit/O tree/O ,/O with/O the/O sun/O and/O clouds/O above/O her/O and/O the/O rain/O to/O wash/O her/O clean/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O with/O her/O when/O she/O died/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON reminded/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O wanted/O to/O come/O home/O ,/O to/O rest/O beside/O Brandon/PERSON and/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O could/O hear/O her/O still/O at/O times/O ./O 
Promise/O me/O ,/O she/O had/O cried/O ,/O in/O a/O room/O that/O smelled/O of/O blood/O and/O roses/O ./O 
Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
The/O fever/O had/O taken/O her/O strength/O and/O her/O voice/O had/O been/O faint/O as/O a/O whisper/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O gave/O her/O his/O word/O ,/O the/O fear/O had/O gone/O out/O of/O his/O sister/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON remembered/O the/O way/O she/O had/O smiled/O then/O ,/O how/O tightly/O her/O fingers/O had/O clutched/O ''/O ,/O ``/O his/O as/O she/O gave/O up/O her/O hold/O on/O life/O ,/O the/O rose/O petals/O spilling/O from/O her/O palm/O ,/O dead/O and/O black/O ./O 
After/O that/O he/O remembered/O nothing/O ./O 
They/O had/O found/O him/O still/O holding/O her/O body/O ,/O silent/O with/O grief/O ./O 
The/O little/O crannogman/O ,/O Howland/PERSON Reed/PERSON ,/O had/O taken/O her/O hand/O from/O his/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON could/O recall/O none/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O bring/O her/O flowers/O when/O I/O can/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lyanna/PERSON was/O .../O fond/O of/O flowers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O touched/O her/O cheek/O ,/O his/O fingers/O brushing/O across/O the/O rough/O stone/O as/O gently/O as/O if/O it/O were/O living/O flesh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O vowed/O to/O kill/O Rhaegar/PERSON for/O what/O he/O did/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O did/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O once/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O bitterly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O come/O together/O at/O the/O ford/O of/O the/O Trident/O while/O the/O battle/O crashed/O around/O them/O ,/O Robert/PERSON with/O his/O warhammer/O and/O his/O great/O antlered/O helm/O ,/O the/O Targaryen/LOCATION prince/O armored/O all/O in/O black/O ./O 
On/O his/O breastplate/O was/O the/O three-headed/O dragon/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O wrought/O all/O in/O rubies/O that/O flashed/O like/O fire/O in/O the/O sunlight/O ./O 
The/O waters/O of/O the/O Trident/O ran/O red/O around/O the/O hooves/O of/O their/O destriers/O as/O they/O circled/O and/O clashed/O ,/O again/O and/O again/O ,/O until/O at/O last/O a/O crushing/O blow/O from/O Robert/PERSON 's/O hammer/O stove/O in/O the/O dragon/O and/O the/O chest/O beneath/O it/O ./O 
When/O Ned/PERSON had/O finally/O come/O on/O the/O scene/O ,/O Rhaegar/PERSON lay/O dead/O in/O the/O stream/O ,/O while/O men/O of/O both/O armies/O scrabbled/O in/O the/O swirling/O waters/O for/O rubies/O knocked/O free/O of/O his/O armor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O my/O dreams/O ,/O I/O kill/O him/O every/O night/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O thousand/O deaths/O will/O still/O be/O less/O than/O he/O deserves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O nothing/O Ned/PERSON could/O say/O to/O that/O ./O 
After/O a/O quiet/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O We/O should/O return/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
Your/O wife/O will/O be/O waiting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O take/O my/O wife/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON muttered/O sourly/O ,/O but/O he/O started/O back/O the/O way/O they/O had/O come/O ,/O his/O footsteps/O falling/O heavily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O I/O hear/O `/O Your/O Grace/O '/O once/O more/O ,/O I/O 'll/O have/O your/O head/O on/O a/O spike/O ./O 
We/O are/O more/O to/O each/O other/O than/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O not/O forgotten/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O quietly/O ./O 
When/O the/O king/O did/O not/O answer/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O about/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O never/O seen/O a/O man/O sicken/O so/O quickly/O ./O 
We/O gave/O a/O tourney/O on/O my/O son/O 's/O name/O day/O ./O 
If/O you/O had/O seen/O Jon/PERSON then/O ,/O you/O would/O have/O sworn/O he/O would/O live/O forever/O ./O 
A/O fortnight/O later/O he/O was/O dead/O ./O 
The/O sickness/O was/O like/O a/O fire/O in/O his/O gut/O ./O 
It/O burned/O right/O through/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O paused/O beside/O a/O pillar/O ,/O before/O the/O tomb/O of/O a/O long-dead/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O loved/O that/O old/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O both/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON paused/O a/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Catelyn/O fears/O for/O her/O sister/O ./O 
How/O does/O Lysa/PERSON bear/O her/O grief/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON 's/O mouth/O gave/O a/O bitter/O twist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O well/O ,/O in/O truth/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O losing/O Jon/PERSON has/O driven/O the/O woman/O mad/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
She/O has/O taken/O the/O boy/O back/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
Against/O my/O wishes/O ./O 
I/O had/O hoped/O to/O foster/O him/O with/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O no/O brothers/O ,/O no/O other/O sons/O ./O 
Was/O I/O supposed/O to/O leave/O him/O to/O be/O raised/O by/O women/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O would/O sooner/O entrust/O a/O child/O to/O a/O pit/O viper/O than/O to/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ,/O but/O he/O left/O his/O doubts/O unspoken/O ./O 
Some/O old/O wounds/O never/O truly/O heal/O ,/O and/O bleed/O again/O at/O the/O slightest/O word/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wife/O has/O lost/O the/O husband/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O carefully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps-the/O mother/O feared/O to/O lose/O the/O son/O ./O 
The/O boy/O is/O very/O young/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Six/O ,/O and/O sickly/O ,/O and/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O swore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON had/O never/O taken/O a/O ward/O before/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON ought/O to/O have/O been/O honored/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O are/O a/O great/O and/O noble/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
She/O refused/O to/O even/O hear/O of/O it/O ./O 
Then/O she/O left/O in/O the/O dead/O of/O night/O ,/O without/O so/O much/O as/O a/O by-your-leave/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON was/O furious/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O deeply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O is/O my/O namesake/O ,/O did/O you/O know/O that/O ?/O 
Robert/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O 
I/O am/O sworn/O to/O protect/O him/O ./O 
How/O can/O I/O do/O that/O if/O his/O mother/O steals/O him/O away/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O take/O him/O as/O ward/O ,/O if/O you/O wish/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON should/O consent/O to/O that/O ./O 
She/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON were/O close/O as/O girls/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O be/O welcome/O here/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O generous/O offer/O ,/O my/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O too/O late/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON has/O already/O given/O his/O consent/O ./O 
Fostering/O the/O boy/O elsewhere/O would/O be/O a/O grievous/O affront/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O more/O concern/O for/O my/O nephew/O 's/O welfare/O than/O I/O do/O for/O Lannister/O pride/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON declared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O because/O you/O do/O not/O sleep/O with/O a/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON laughed/O ,/O the/O sound/O rattling/O among/O the/O tombs/O and/O bouncing/O from/O the/O vaulted/O ceiling/O ./O 
His/O smile/O was/O a/O flash/O of/O white/O teeth/O in/O the/O thicket/O of/O the/O huge/O black/O beard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O are/O still/O too/O serious/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O put/O a/O massive/O arm/O around/O Ned/PERSON 's/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O planned/O to/O wait/O a/O few/O days/O to/O speak/O to/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O see/O now/O there/O 's/O no/O need/O for/O it/O ./O 
Come/O ,/O walk/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O started/O back/O down/O between/O the/O pillars/O ./O 
Blind/O stone/O eyes/O seemed/O to/O follow/O them/O as/O they/O passed/O ./O 
The/O king/O kept/O his/O arm/O around/O Ned/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O have/O wondered/O why/O I/O finally/O came/O north/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O after/O so/O long/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O his/O suspicions/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O give/O them/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O the/O joy/O of/O my/O company/O ,/O surely/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O lightly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O there/O is/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
You/O need/O to/O see/O it/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O to/O walk/O along/O its/O battlements/O and/O talk/O to/O those/O who/O man/O it/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O a/O shadow/O of/O what/O it/O once/O was/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON says/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O doubt/O I/O will/O hear/O what/O your/O brother/O says/O soon/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Wall/O has/O stood/O for/O what/O ,/O eight/O thousand/O years/O ?/O 
It/O can/O keep/O a/O few/O days/O more/O ./O 
I/O have/O more/O pressing/O concerns/O ./O 
These/O are/O difficult/O times/O ./O 
I/O need/O good/O men/O about/O me/O ./O 
Men/O like/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O 
He/O served/O as/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O as/O Warden/O of/O the/O East/LOCATION ,/O as/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
He/O will/O not/O be/O easy/O to/O replace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O son/O .../O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O son/O will/O succeed/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O all/O its/O incomes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O brusquely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O more/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O took/O Ned/PERSON by/O surprise/O ./O 
He/O stopped/O ,/O startled/O ,/O and/O turned/O to/O look/O at/O his/O king/O ./O 
The/O words/O came/O unbidden/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Arryns/O have/O always/O been/O Wardens/O of/O the/O East/LOCATION ./O 
The/O title/O goes/O with/O the/O domain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O when/O he/O comes/O of/O age/O ,/O the/O honor/O can/O be/O restored/O to/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O this/O year/O to/O think/O of/O ,/O and/O next/O ./O 
A/O six/O -/O year-old/O boy/O is/O no/O war/O leader/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O peace/O ,/O the/O title/O is/O only/O an/O honor/O ./O 
Let/O the/O boy/O keep/O it/O ./O 
For/O his/O father/O 's/O sake/O if/O not/O his/O own/O ./O 
Surely/O you/O owe/O ,/O Jon/PERSON that/O much/O for/O his/O service/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O was/O not/O pleased/O ./O 
He/O took/O his/O arm/O from/O around/O Ned/PERSON 's/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O service/O was/O the/O duty/O he/O owed/O his/O liege/O lord/O ./O 
I/O am/O not/O ungrateful/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
You/O of/O all/O men/O ought/O to/O know/O that/O ./O 
But/O the/O son/O is/O not/O the/O father/O ./O 
A/O mere/O boy/O can/O not/O hold/O the/O east/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Then/O his/O tone/O softened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Enough/O of/O this/O ./O 
There/O is/O a/O more/O important/O office/O to/O discuss/O ,/O and/O I/O would/O not/O argue/O with/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON grasped/O Ned/PERSON by/O the/O elbow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O need/O of/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O yours/O to/O command/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
Always/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O were/O words/O he/O had/O to/O say/O ,/O and/O so/O he/O said/O them/O ,/O apprehensive/O about/O what/O might/O come/O next/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON scarcely/O seemed/O to/O hear/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Those/O years/O we/O spent/O in/O the/O Eyrie/O .../O gods/O ,/O those/O were/O good/O years/O ./O 
I/O want/O you/O at/O my/O side/O again/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
I/O want/O you/O down/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O not/O up/O here/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O where/O you/O are/O no/O damned/O use/O to/O anybody/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON looked/O off/O into/O the/O darkness/O ,/O for/O a/O moment/O as/O melancholy/O as/O a/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O sitting/O a/O throne/O is/O a/O thousand/O times/O harder/O than/O winning/O one/O ./O 
Laws/O are/O a/O tedious/O business/O and/O counting/O coppers/O is/O worse/O ./O 
And/O the/O people/O .../O there/O is/O no/O end/O of/O them/O ./O 
I/O sit/O on/O that/O damnable/O iron/O chair/O and/O listen/O to/O them/O complain/O until/O my/O mind/O is/O numb/O and/O my/O ass/O is/O raw/O ./O 
They/O all/O want/O something/O ,/O money/O or/O land/O or/O justice/O ./O 
The/O lies/O they/O tell/O .../O and/O my/O lords/O and/O ladies/O are/O no/O better/O ./O 
I/O am/O surrounded/O by/O flatterers/O and/O fools/O ./O 
It/O can/O drive/O a/O man/O to/O madness/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Half/O of/O them/O do/O n't/O dare/O tell/O me/O the/O truth/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O half/O ca/O n't/O find/O it/O ./O 
There/O are/O nights/O I/O wish/O we/O had/O lost/O at/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
Ah/O ,/O no/O ,/O not/O truly/O ,/O but/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O understand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O softly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON looked/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O you/O do/O ./O 
If/O so/O ,/O you/O are/O the/O only/O one/O ,/O my/O old/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O I/O would/O name/O you/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O dropped/O to/O one/O knee/O ./O 
The/O offer/O did/O not/O surprise/O him/O ;/O what/O other/O reason/O could/O Robert/PERSON have/O had/O for/O coming/O so/O far/O ?/O 
The/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O was/O the/O second/O -/O most/O powerful/O man/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
He/O spoke/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O voice/O ,/O commanded/O the/O king/O 's/O armies/O ,/O drafted/O the/O king/O 's/O laws/O ./O 
At/O times/O he/O even/O sat/O upon/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O to/O dispense/O king/O 's/O justice/O ,/O when/O the/O king/O was/O absent/O ,/O or/O sick/O ,/O or/O otherwise/O indisposed/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O offering/O him/O a/O responsibility/O as/O large/O as/O the/O realm/O itself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O last/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O he/O wanted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O worthy/O of/O the/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON groaned/O with/O good-humored/O impatience/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O wanted/O to/O honor/O you/O ,/O I/O 'd/O let/O you/O retire/O ./O 
I/O am/O planning/O to/O make/O you/O run/O the/O kingdom/O and/O fight/O the/O wars/O while/O I/O eat/O and/O drink/O and/O wench/O myself/O into/O an/O early/O grave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slapped/O his/O gut/O and/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O the/O saying/O ,/O about/O the/O king/O and/O his/O Hand/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O knew/O the/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O the/O king/O dreams/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O Hand/O builds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O bedded/O a/O fishmaid/O once/O who/O told/O me/O the/O lowborn/O have/O a/O choicer/O way/O to/O put/O it/O ./O 
The/O king/O eats/O ,/O they/O say/O ,/O and/O the/O Hand/O takes/O the/O shit/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O threw/O back/O his/O head/O and/O roared/O his/O laughter/O ./O 
The/O echoes/O rang/O through/O the/O darkness/O ,/O and/O all/O around/O them/O the/O dead/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION seemed/O to/O watch/O with/O cold/O and/O disapproving/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Finally/O the/O laughter/O dwindled/O and/O stopped/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON was/O still/O on/O one/O knee/O ,/O his/O eyes/O upraised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O it/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O complained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O might/O at/O least/O humor/O me/O with/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O say/O it/O grows/O so/O cold/O up/O here/O in/O winter/O that/O a/O man/O 's/O laughter/O freezes/O in/O his/O throat/O and/O chokes/O him/O to/O death/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O evenly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O that/O is/O why/O the/O Starks/PERSON have/O so/O little/O humor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Come/O south/O with/O me/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O teach/O you/O how/O to/O laugh/O again/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O helped/O me/O win/O this/O damnable/O throne/O ,/O now/O help/O me/O hold/O it/O ./O 
We/O were/O meant/O to/O rule/O together/O ./O 
If/O Lyanna/PERSON had/O lived/O ,/O we/O should/O have/O been/O brothers/O ,/O bound/O by/O blood/O as/O well/O as/O affection/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O it/O is/O not/O too/O ''/O ,/O ``/O late/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O son/O ./O 
You/O have/O a/O daughter/O ./O 
My/O Joff/PERSON and/O your/O Sansa/O shall/O join/O our/O houses/O ,/O as/O Lyanna/PERSON and/O I/O might/O once/O have/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O This/O offer/O did/O surprise/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O is/O only/O eleven/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON waved/O an/O impatient/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Old/O enough/O for/O betrothal/O ./O 
The/O marriage/O can/O wait/O a/O few/O years/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O stand/O up/O and/O say/O yes/O ,/O curse/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O would/O give/O me/O greater/O pleasure/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON answered/O ./O 
He/O hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O honors/O are/O all/O so/O unexpected/O ./O 
May/O I/O have/O some/O time/O to/O consider/O ?/O 
I/O need/O to/O tell/O my/O wife/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O yes/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O tell/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O sleep/O on/O it/O if/O you/O must/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O reached/O down/O ,/O clasped/O Ned/PERSON by/O the/O hand/O ,/O and/O pulled/O him/O roughly/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O do/O n't/O keep/O me/O waiting/O too/O long/O ./O 
I/O am/O not/O the/O most/O patient/O of/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Eddard/O Stark/O was/O filled/O with/O a/O terrible/O sense/O of/O foreboding/O ./O 
This/O was/O his/O place/O ,/O here/O in/O the/O north/O ./O 
He/O looked/O at/O the/O stone/O figures/O all/O around/O them/O ,/O breathed/O deep/O in/O the/O chill/O silence/O of/O the/O crypt/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O dead/O ./O 
They/O were/O all/O listening/O ,/O he/O knew/O ./O 
And/O winter/O was/O coming/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
