-LSB-/O ``/O BRAN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Karstarks/O came/O in/O on/O a/O cold/O windy/O morning/O ,/O bringing/O three/O hundred/O horsemen/O and/O near/O two/O thousand/O foot/O from/O their/O castle/O at/O Karhold/O ./O 
The/O steel/O points/O of/O their/O pikes/O winked/O in/O the/O pale/O sunlight/O as/O the/O column/O approached/O ./O 
A/O man/O went/O before/O them/O ,/O pounding/O out/O a/O slow/O ,/O deep/O -/O throated/O marching/O rhythm/O on/O a/O drum/O that/O was/O bigger/O than/O he/O was/O ,/O boom/O ,/O boom/O ,/O boom/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O watched/O them/O come/O from/O a/O guard/O turret/O atop/O the/O outer/O wall/O ,/O peering/O through/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON 's/O bronze/O far-eye/O while/O perched/O on/O Hodor/PERSON 's/O shoulders/O ./O 
Lord/O Rickard/PERSON himself/O led/O them/O ,/O his/O sons/O Harrion/O and/O Eddard/O and/O Torrhen/PERSON riding/O beside/O him/O beneath/O night-black/O banners/O emblazoned/O with/O the/O white/O sunburst/O of/O their/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O they/O had/O Stark/O blood/O in/O them/O ,/O going/O back/O hundreds/O of/O years/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O not/O look/O like/O Starks/PERSON to/O Bran/O ./O 
They/O were/O big/O men/O ,/O and/O fierce/O ,/O faces/O covered/O with/O thick/O beards/O ,/O hair/O worn/O loose/O past/O the/O shoulders/O ./O 
Their/O cloaks/O were/O made/O of/O skins/O ,/O the/O pelts/O of/O bear/O and/O sea/O -RSB-/O and/O wolf/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O were/O the/O last/O ,/O he/O knew/O ./O 
The/O other/O lords/O were/O already/O here/O ,/O with/O their/O hosts/O ./O 
Bran/O yearned/O to/O ride/O out/O among/O them/O ,/O to/O see/O the/O winter/O houses/O full/O to/O bursting/O ,/O the/O jostling/O crowds/O in/O the/O market/O square/O every/O morning/O ,/O the/O streets/O rutted/O and/O torn/O by/O wheel/O and/O hoof/O ./O 
But/O Robb/PERSON had/O forbidden/O him/O to/O leave/O the/O castle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O no/O men/O to/O spare/O to/O guard/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O brother/O had/O explained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O take/O Summer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O argued/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O act/O the/O boy/O with/O me/O ,/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O better/O than/O that/O ./O 
Only/O two/O days/O ago/O one/O of/O Lord/O Bolton/PERSON 's/O men/O knifed/O one/O of/O Lord/O Cerwyn/PERSON 's/O at/O the/O Smoking/O Log/O ./O 
Our/O lady/O mother/O would/O skin/O me/O for/O a/O pelt/O if/O I/O let/O you/O put/O yourself/O at/O risk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O using/O the/O voice/O of/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O when/O he/O said/O it/O ;/O Bran/O knew/O that/O meant/O there/O was/O no/O appeal/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O because/O of/O what/O had/O happened/O in/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O he/O knew/O ./O 
The/O memory/O still/O gave/O him/O bad/O dreams/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O as/O helpless/O as/O a/O baby/O ,/O no/O more/O able/O to/O defend/O himself/O than/O Rickon/PERSON would/O have/O been/O ./O 
Less/O ,/O even/O .../O Rickon/PERSON would/O have/O kicked/O them/O ,/O at/O the/O least/O ./O 
It/O shamed/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O only/O a/O few/O years/O younger/O than/O Robb/PERSON ;/O if/O his/O brother/O was/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O so/O was/O he/O ./O 
He/O should/O have/O been/O able/O to/O protect/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O year/O ago/O ,/O before/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O visited/O the/O town/O even/O if/O it/O meant/O climbing/O over/O the/O walls/O by/O himself/O ./O 
In/O those/O days/O he/O could/O run/O down/O stairs/O ,/O get/O on/O and/O off/O his/O pony/O by/O himself/O ,/O and/O wield/O a/O wooden/O sword/O good/O enough/O to/O knock/O Prince/PERSON Tommen/PERSON in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
Now/O he/O could/O only/O watch/O ,/O peering/O out/O through/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON 's/O lens/O tube/O ./O 
The/O maester/O had/O taught/O him/O all/O the/O banners/O :/O the/O mailed/O fist/O of/O the/O Glovers/O ,/O silver/O on/O scarlet/O ;/O Lady/PERSON Mormont/PERSON 's/O black/O bear/O ;/O the/O hideous/O flayed/O man/O that/O went/O before/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON of/O the/O Dreadfort/O ;/O a/O bull/O moose/O for/O the/O Hornwoods/O ;/O a/O battle-axe/O for/O the/O Cerwyns/O ;/O three/O sentinel/O trees/O for/O the/O Tallharts/O ;/O and/O the/O fearsome/O sigil/O of/O House/O Umber/O ,/O a/O roaring/O giant/O in/O shattered/O chains/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O soon/O enough/O he/O learned/O the/O faces/O too/O ,/O when/O the/O lords/O and/O their/O sons/O and/O knights/O retainer/O came/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION to/O feast/O ./O 
Even/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION was/O not/O large/O enough/O to/O seat/O all/O of/O them/O at/O once/O ,/O so/O Robb/PERSON hosted/O each/O of/O the/O principal/O bannermen/O in/O turn/O ./O 
Bran/O was/O always/O given/O the/O place/O of/O honor/O at/O his/O brother/O 's/O right/O hand/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O gave/O him/O queer/O hard/O stares/O as/O he/O ''/O ,/O ``/O sat/O there/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O wondered/O by/O what/O right/O a/O green/O boy/O should/O be/O placed/O above/O them/O ,/O and/O him/O a/O cripple/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O many/O is/O it/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O asked/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON as/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON and/O his/O sons/O rode/O through/O the/O gates/O in/O the/O outer/O wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Twelve/O thousand/O men/O ,/O or/O near/O enough/O as/O makes/O no/O matter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O many/O knights/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Few/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O with/O a/O touch/O of/O impatience/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O be/O a/O knight/O ,/O you/O must/O stand/O your/O vigil/O in/O a/O sept/O ,/O and/O be/O anointed/O with/O the/O seven/O oils/O to/O consecrate/O your/O vows/O ./O 
In/O the/O north/O ,/O only/O a/O few/O of/O the/O great/O houses/O worship/O the/O Seven/O ./O 
The/O rest/O honor/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O and/O name/O no/O knights/O .../O but/O those/O lords/O and/O their/O sons/O and/O sworn/O swords/O are/O no/O less/O fierce/O or/O loyal/O or/O honorable/O ./O 
A/O man/O 's/O worth/O is/O not/O marked/O by/O a/O ser/O before/O his/O name/O ./O 
As/O I/O have/O told/O you/O a/O hundred/O times/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Still/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ``/O how/O many/O knights/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O hundred/O ,/O perhaps/O four/O .../O among/O three/O thousand/O armored/O lances/O who/O are/O not/O knights/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON is/O the/O last/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON will/O feast/O him/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O doubt/O he/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O long/O before/O .../O before/O they/O go/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O must/O march/O soon/O ,/O or/O not/O at/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O winter/O town/O is/O full/O to/O bursting/O ,/O and/O this/O army/O of/O his/O will/O eat/O the/O countryside/O clean/O if/O it/O camps/O here/O much/O longer/O ./O 
Others/O are/O waiting/O to/O join/O him/O all/O along/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O barrow/O knights/O and/O crannogmen/O and/O the/O Lords/O Manderly/O and/O Flint/LOCATION ./O 
The/O fighting/O has/O begun/O in/O the/O riverlands/O ,/O and/O your/O brother/O has/O many/O leagues/O to/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O felt/O as/O miserable/O as/O he/O sounded/O ./O 
He/O handed/O the/O bronze/O tube/O back/O to/O the/O maester/O ,/O and/O noticed/O how/O thin/O Luwin/PERSON '/O s/O hair/O had/O grown/O on/O top/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O the/O pink/O of/O scalp/O showing/O through/O ./O 
It/O felt/O queer/O to/O look/O down/O on/O him/O this/O way/O ,/O when/O he/O 'd/O spent/O his/O whole/O life/O looking/O up/O at/O him/O ,/O but/O when/O you/O sat/O on/O Hodor/PERSON 's/O back/O you/O looked/O down/O on/O everyone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O watch/O anymore/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON ,/O take/O me/O back/O to/O the/O keep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Hodor/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON tucked/O the/O tube/O up/O his/O sleeve/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O your/O lord/O brother/O will/O not/O have/O time/O to/O see/O you/O now/O ./O 
He/O must/O greet/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON and/O his/O sons/O and/O make/O them/O welcome/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O trouble/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
I/O want/O to/O visit/O the/O godswood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O put/O his/O hand/O on/O Hodor/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O series/O of/O chisel-cut/O handholds/O made/O a/O ladder/O in/O the/O granite/O of/O the/O tower/O 's/O inner/O wall/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON hummed/O tunelessly/O as/O he/O went/O down/O hand/O under/O hand/O ,/O Bran/O bouncing/O against/O his/O back/O in/O the/O wicker/O seat/O that/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON had/O fashioned/O for/O him/O ./O 
Luwin/PERSON had/O gotten/O the/O idea/O from/O the/O baskets/O the/O women/O used/O to/O carry/O firewood/O on/O their/O backs/O ;/O after/O that/O it/O had/O been/O a/O simple/O matter/O of/O cutting/O legholes/O and/O attaching/O some/O new/O straps/O to/O spread/O Bran/O 's/O weight/O more/O evenly/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O as/O good/O as/O riding/O Dancer/O ,/O but/O there/O were/O places/O Dancer/O could/O not/O go/O ,/O and/O this/O did/O not/O shame/O Bran/O the/O way/O it/O did/O when/O Hodor/PERSON carried/O him/O in/O his/O arms/O like/O a/O baby/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON seemed/O to/O like/O it/O too/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O though/O with/O Hodor/O it/O was/O hard/O to/O tell/O ./O 
The/O only/O tricky/O part/O was/O doors/O ./O 
Sometimes/O Hodor/PERSON forgot/O that/O he/O had/O Bran/O on/O his/O back/O ,/O and/O that/O could/O be/O painful/O when/O he/O went/O through/O a/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O near/O a/O fortnight/O there/O had/O been/O so/O many/O comings/O and/O goings/O that/O Robb/PERSON ordered/O both/O portcullises/O kept/O up/O and/O the/O drawbridge/O down/O between/O them/O ,/O even/O in/O the/O dead/O of/O night/O ./O 
A/O long/O column/O of/O armored/O lancers/O was/O crossing/O the/O moat/O between/O the/O walls/O when/O Bran/O emerged/O from/O the/O tower/O ;/O Karstark/O men/O ,/O following/O their/O lords/O into/O the/O castle/O ./O 
They/O wore/O black/O iron/O halfhelms/O and/O black/O woolen/O cloaks/O patterned/O with/O the/O white/O sunburst/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON trotted/O along/O beside/O them/O ,/O smiling/O to/O himself/O ,/O his/O boots/O thudding/O against/O the/O wood/O of/O the/O drawbridge/O ./O 
The/O riders/O gave/O them/O queer/O looks/O as/O they/O went/O by/O ,/O and/O once/O Bran/O heard/O someone/O guffaw/O ./O 
He/O refused/O to/O let/O it/O trouble/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Men/O will/O look/O at/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON had/O warned/O him/O the/O first/O time/O they/O had/O strapped/O the/O wicker/O basket/O around/O Hodor/LOCATION 's/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O will/O look/O ,/O and/O they/O will/O talk/O ,/O and/O some/O will/O mock/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Let/O them/O mock/O ,/O Bran/O thought/O ./O 
No/O one/O mocked/O him/O in/O his/O bedchamber/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O not/O live/O his/O life/O in/O bed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O they/O passed/O beneath/O the/O gatehouse/O portcullis/O ,/O Bran/O put/O two/O fingers/O into/O his/O mouth/O and/O whistled/O ./O 
Summer/O came/O loping/O across/O the/O yard/O ./O 
Suddenly/O the/O Karstark/O lancers/O were/O fighting/O for/O control/O ,/O as/O their/O horses/O rolled/O their/O eyes/O and/O whickered/O in/O dismay/O ./O 
One/O stallion/O reared/O ,/O screaming/O ,/O his/O rider/O cursing/O and/O hanging/O on/O desperately/O ./O 
The/O scent/O of/O the/O direwolves/O sent/O horses/O into/O a/O frenzy/O of/O fear/O if/O they/O were/O not/O accustomed/O to/O it/O ,/O but/O they/O 'd/O quiet/O soon/O enough/O once/O Summer/O was/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O godswood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O reminded/O Hodor/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O Winterfell/O itself/O was/O crowded/O ./O 
The/O yard/O rang/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O sword/O and/O axe/O ,/O the/O rumble/O of/O wagons/O ,/O and/O the/O barking/O of/O dogs/O ./O 
The/O armory/O doors/O were/O open/O ,/O and/O Bran/O glimpsed/O Mikken/PERSON at/O his/O forge/O ,/O his/O hammer/O ringing/O as/O sweat/O dripped/O off/O his/O bare/O chest/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O never/O seen/O as/O many/O strangers/O in/O all/O his/O years/O ,/O not/O even/O when/O King/O Robert/PERSON had/O come/O to/O visit/O Father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O tried/O not/O to/O flinch/O as/O Hodor/PERSON ducked/O through/O a/O low/O door/O ./O 
They/O walked/O down/O a/O long/O dim/O hallway/O ,/O Summer/O padding/O easily/O beside/O them/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O glanced/O up/O from/O time/O to/O time/O ,/O eyes/O smoldering/O like/O liquid/O gold/O ./O 
Bran/O would/O have/O liked/O to/O touch/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O riding/O too/O high/O for/O his/O hand/O to/O reach/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O godswood/O was/O an/O island/O of/O peace/O in/O the/O sea/O of/O chaos/O that/O Winterfell/PERSON had/O become/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON made/O his/O way/O through/O the/O dense/O stands/O of/O oak/O and/O ironwood/O and/O sentinels/O ,/O to/O the/O still/O pool/O beside/O the/O heart/O tree/O ./O 
He/O stopped/O under/O the/O gnarled/O limbs/O of/O the/O weirwood/O ,/O humming/O ./O 
Bran/O reached/O up/O over/O his/O head/O and/O pulled/O himself/O out/O of/O his/O seat/O ,/O drawing/O the/O dead/O weight/O of/O his/O legs/O up/O through/O the/O holes/O in/O the/O wicker/O basket/O ./O 
He/O hung/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O dangling/O ,/O the/O dark/O red/O leaves/O brushing/O against/O his/O face/O ,/O until/O Hodor/PERSON lifted/O him/O and/O lowered/O him/O to/O the/O smooth/O stone/O beside/O the/O water/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O be/O by/O myself/O for/O a/O while/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O go/O soak/O ./O 
Go/O to/O the/O pools/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Hodor/PERSON stomped/O through/O the/O trees/O and/O vanished/O ./O 
Across/O the/O godswood/O ,/O beneath/O the/O windows/O of/O the/O Guest/ORGANIZATION House/ORGANIZATION ,/O an/O underground/O hot/O spring/O fed/O three/O small/O ponds/O ./O 
Steam/O rose/O from/O the/O water/O day/O and/O night/O ,/O and/O the/O wall/O that/O loomed/O above/O was/O thick/O with/O moss/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON hated/O cold/O water/O ,/O and/O would/O fight/O like/O a/O treed/O wildcat/O when/O threatened/O with/O soap/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O happily/O immerse/O himself/O in/O the/O hottest/O pool/O and/O sit/O for/O hours/O ,/O giving/O a/O loud/O burp/O to/O echo/O the/O spring/O whenever/O a/O bubble/O rose/O from/O the/O murky/O green/O depths/O to/O break/O upon/O the/O surface/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Summer/O lapped/O at/O the/O water/O and/O settled/O down/O at/O Bran/O 's/O side/O ./O 
He/O rubbed/O the/O wolf/O under/O the/O jaw/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O moment/O boy/O and/O beast/O both/O felt/O at/O peace/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O always/O liked/O the/O godswood/O ,/O even/O before/O ,/O but/O of/O late/O he/O found/O himself/O drawn/O to/O it/O more/O and/O more/O ./O 
Even/O the/O heart/O tree/O no/O longer/O scared/O him/O the/O way/O it/O used/O to/O ./O 
The/O deep/O red/O eyes/O carved/O into/O the/O pale/O trunk/O still/O watched/O him/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O he/O took/O comfort/O from/O that/O now/O ./O 
The/O gods/O were/O looking/O over/O him/O ,/O he/O told/O himself/O ;/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O gods/O of/O the/O Starks/PERSON and/O the/O First/O Men/O and/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ,/O his/O father/O 's/O gods/O ./O 
He/O felt/O safe/O in/O their/O sight/O ,/O and/O the/O deep/O silence/O of/O the/O trees/O helped/O him/O think/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O been/O thinking/O a/O lot/O since/O his/O fall/O ;/O thinking/O ,/O and/O dreaming/O ,/O and/O talking/O with/O the/O gods/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O make/O it/O so/O Robb/PERSON wo/O n't/O go/O away/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O prayed/O softly/O ./O 
He/O moved/O his/O hand/O through/O the/O cold/O water/O ,/O sending/O ripples/O across/O the/O pool/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O make/O him/O stay/O ./O 
Or/O if/O he/O has/O to/O go/O ,/O bring/O him/O home/O safe/O ,/O with/O Mother/O and/O Father/O and/O the/O girls/O ./O 
And/O make/O it/O .../O make/O it/O so/O Rickon/PERSON understands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O baby/O brother/O had/O been/O wild/O as/O a/O winter/O storm/O since/O he/O learned/O Robb/PERSON was/O riding/O off/O to/O war/O ,/O weeping/O and/O angry/O by/O turns/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O refused/O to/O eat/O ,/O cried/O and/O screamed/O for/O most/O of/O a/O night/O ,/O even/O punched/O Old/O Nan/PERSON when/O she/O tried/O to/O sing/O him/O to/O sleep/O ,/O and/O the/O next/O day/O he/O 'd/O vanished/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON had/O set/O half/O the/O castle/O searching/O for/O him/O ,/O and/O when/O at/O last/O they/O 'd/O found/O him/O down/O in/O the/O crypts/O ,/O Rickon/PERSON had/O slashed/O at/O them/O with/O a/O rusted/O iron/O sword/O he/O 'd/O snatched/O from/O a/O dead/O king/O 's/O hand/O ,/O and/O Shaggydog/PERSON had/O come/O slavering/O out/O of/O the/O darkness/O like/O a/O green-eyed/O demon/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O was/O near/O as/O wild/O as/O Rickon/PERSON ;/O he/O 'd/O bitten/O Gage/PERSON on/O the/O arm/O and/O torn/O a/O chunk/O of/O flesh/O from/O Mikken/PERSON 's/O thigh/O ./O 
It/O had/O taken/O Robb/PERSON himself/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON to/O bring/O him/O to/O bay/O ./O 
Farlen/PERSON had/O the/O black/O wolf/O chained/O up/O in/O the/O kennels/O now/O ,/O and/O Rickon/PERSON cried/O all/O the/O more/O for/O being/O without/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON counseled/O Robb/PERSON to/O remain/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O Bran/O pleaded/O with/O him/O too/O ,/O for/O his/O own/O sake/O as/O much/O as/O Rickon/PERSON 's/O ,/O but/O his/O brother/O only/O shook/O his/O head/O stubbornly/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O go/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O only/O half/O a/O lie/O ./O 
Someone/O had/O to/O go/O ,/O to/O hold/O the/O Neck/O and/O help/O the/O Tullys/O against/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O Bran/O could/O understand/O that/O ,/O but/O it/O did/O not/O have/O to/O be/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
His/O brother/O might/O have/O given/O the/O command/O to/O Hal/PERSON Mollen/PERSON or/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O or/O to/O one/O of/O his/O lords/O bannermen/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON urged/O him/O to/O do/O just/O that/O ,/O but/O Robb/PERSON would/O not/O hear/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O would/O never/O have/O sent/O men/O off/O to/O die/O while/O he/O huddled/O like/O a/O craven/O behind/O the/O walls/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O all/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON seemed/O half/O a/O stranger/O to/O Bran/O now/O ,/O transformed/O ,/O a/O lord/O in/O truth/O ,/O though/O he/O had/O not/O yet/O seen/O his/O sixteenth/O name/O day/O ./O 
Even/O their/O father/O 's/O bannermen/O seemed/O to/O sense/O it/O ./O 
Many/O tried/O to/O test/O him/O ,/O each/O in/O his/O own/O way/O ./O 
Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON and/O Robert/PERSON Glover/PERSON both/O demanded/O the/O honor/O of/O battle/O command/O ,/O the/O first/O brusquely/O ,/O the/O second/O with/O a/O smile/O and/O a/O jest/O ./O 
Stout/O ,/O grey-haired/O Maege/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ,/O dressed/O in/O mail/O like/O a/O man/O ,/O told/O Robb/PERSON bluntly/O that/O he/O was/O young/O enough/O to/O be/O her/O grandson/O ,/O and/O had/O no/O business/O giving/O her/O commands/O .../O but/O as/O it/O happened/O ,/O she/O had/O a/O granddaughter/O she/O would/O be/O willing/O to/O have/O him/O marry/O ./O 
Softspoken/O Lord/O Cerwyn/PERSON had/O actually/O brought/O his/O daughter/O with/O him/O ,/O a/O plump/O ,/O homely/O maid/O of/O thirty/O years/O who/O sat/O at/O her/O father/O 's/O left/O hand/O and/O never/O lifted/O her/O eyes/O from/O her/O plate/O ./O 
Jovial/O Lord/O Hornwood/PERSON had/O no/O daughters/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O bring/O gifts/O ,/O a/O horse/O one/O day/O ,/O a/O haunch/O of/O venison/O the/O next/O ,/O a/O silver-chased/O hunting/O horn/O the/O day/O after/O ,/O and/O he/O asked/O nothing/O in/O return/O .../O nothing/O but/O a/O certain/O holdfast/O taken/O from/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O grandfather/O ,/O and/O hunting/O rights/O north/O of/O a/O certain/O ridge/O ,/O and/O leave/O to/O dam/O the/O White/LOCATION Knife/LOCATION ,/O if/O it/O please/O the/O lord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON answered/O each/O of/O them/O with/O cool/O courtesy/O ,/O much/O as/O Father/O might/O have/O ,/O and/O somehow/O he/O bent/O them/O to/O his/O will/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O when/O Lord/O Umber/O ,/O who/O was/O called/O the/O Greatjon/O by/O his/O men/O and/O stood/O as/O tall/O as/O Hodor/PERSON and/O twice/O as/O wide/O ,/O threatened/O to/O take/O his/O forces/O home/O if/O he/O was/O placed/O behind/O the/O Hornwoods/O or/O the/O Cerwyns/O in/O the/O order/O of/O march/O ,/O Robb/PERSON told/O him/O he/O was/O welcome/O to/O do/O so/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O when/O we/O are/O done/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O promised/O ,/O scratching/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON behind/O the/O ear/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O will/O march/O back/O north/O ,/O root/O you/O out/O of/O your/O keep/O ,/O and/O hang/O you/O for/O an/O oathbreaker/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Cursing/O ,/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON flung/O a/O flagon/O of/O ale/O into/O the/O fire/O and/O bellowed/O that/O Robb/PERSON was/O so/O green/O he/O must/O piss/O grass/O ./O 
When/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON moved/O to/O restrain/O him/O ,/O he/O knocked/O him/O to/O the/O floor/O ,/O kicked/O over/O a/O table/O ,/O and/O unsheathed/O the/O biggest/O ,/O ugliest/O greatsword/O that/O Bran/O had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
All/O along/O the/O benches/O ,/O his/O sons/O and/O brothers/O and/O sworn/O swords/O leapt/O to/O their/O feet/O ,/O grabbing/O for/O their/O steel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O Robb/PERSON only/O said/O a/O quiet/O word/O ,/O and/O in/O a/O snarl/O and/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O Lord/O Umber/O was/O on/O his/O back/O ,/O his/O sword/O spinning/O on/O the/O floor/O three/O feet/O away/O and/O his/O hand/O dripping/O blood/O where/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON had/O bitten/O off/O two/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O taught/O me/O that/O it/O was/O death/O to/O bare/O steel/O against/O your/O liege/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O doubtless/O you/O only/O meant/O to/O cut/O my/O meat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O 's/O bowels/O went/O to/O water/O as/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON struggled/O to/O rise/O ,/O sucking/O at/O the/O red/O stumps/O of/O fingers/O .../O but/O then/O ,/O astonishingly/O ,/O the/O huge/O man/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O meat/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O roared/O ,/O \/O ``/O is/O bloody/O tough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O somehow/O after/O that/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON became/O Robb/PERSON 's/O right/O hand/O ,/O his/O staunchest/O champion/O ,/O loudly/O telling/O all/O and/O sundry/O that/O the/O boy/O lord/O was/O a/O Stark/O after/O all/O ,/O and/O they/O 'd/O damn/O well/O better/O bend/O their/O knees/O if/O they/O did/O n't/O fancy/O having/O them/O chewed/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O that/O very/O night/O ,/O his/O brother/O came/O to/O Bran/O 's/O bedchamber/O pale/O and/O shaken/O ,/O after/O the/O fires/O had/O burned/O low/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thought/O he/O was/O going/O to/O kill/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON confessed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O you/O see/O the/O way/O he/O threw/O down/O Hal/PERSON ,/O like/O he/O was/O no/O bigger/O than/O Rickon/PERSON ?/O 
Gods/O ,/O I/O was/O so/O scared/O ./O 
And/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON 's/O not/O the/O worst/O of/O them/O ,/O only/O the/O loudest/O ./O 
Lord/O Roose/PERSON never/O says/O a/O word/O ,/O he/O only/O looks/O at/O me/O ,/O and/O all/O I/O can/O think/O of/O is/O that/O room/O they/O have/O in/O the/O Dreadfort/O ,/O where/O the/O Boltons/ORGANIZATION hang/O the/O skins/O of/O their/O enemies/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O just/O one/O of/O Old/O Nan/PERSON 's/O stories/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
A/O note/O of/O doubt/O crept/O into/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O a/O weary/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Cerwyn/PERSON means/O to/O take/O his/O daughter/O south/O with/O us/O ./O 
To/O cook/O for/O him/O ,/O he/O says/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON is/O certain/O I/O 'll/O find/O the/O girl/O in/O my/O bedroll/O one/O night/O ./O 
I/O wish/O .../O I/O wish/O Father/O was/O here/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O one/O thing/O they/O could/O agree/O on/O ,/O Bran/O and/O Rickon/PERSON and/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ;/O they/O all/O wished/O Father/O was/O here/O ./O 
But/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON was/O a/O thousand/O leagues/O away/O ,/O a/O captive/O in/O some/O dungeon/O ,/O a/O hunted/O fugitive/O running/O for/O his/O life/O ,/O or/O even/O dead/O ./O 
No/O one/O seemed/O to/O know/O for/O certain/O ;/O every/O traveler/O told/O a/O different/O tale/O ,/O each/O more/O terrifying/O than/O the/O last/O ./O 
The/O heads/O of/O Father/O 's/O guardsmen/O were/O rotting/O on/O the/O walls/O of/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O impaled/O on/O spikes/O ./O 
King/O Robert/PERSON was/O dead/O at/O Father/O 's/O hands/O ./O 
The/O Baratheons/PERSON had/O laid/O siege/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
Lord/O Eddard/PERSON had/O fled/O south/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O wicked/O brother/O Renly/PERSON ./O 
Arya/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON had/O been/O murdered/O by/O the/O Hound/O ./O 
Mother/O ''/O ,/O ``/O had/O killed/O Tyrion/O the/O Imp/O and/O hung/O his/O body/O from/O the/O walls/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O marching/O on/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O burning/O and/O slaughtering/O as/O he/O went/O ./O 
One/O winesodden/O taleteller/O even/O claimed/O that/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON had/O returned/O from/O the/O dead/O and/O was/O marshaling/O a/O vast/O host/O of/O ancient/O heroes/O on/O Dragonstone/O to/O reclaim/O his/O father/O 's/O throne/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O raven/O came/O ,/O bearing/O a/O letter/O marked/O with/O Father/O 's/O own/O seal/O and/O written/O in/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O hand/O ,/O the/O cruel/O truth/O seemed/O no/O less/O incredible/O ./O 
Bran/O would/O never/O forget/O the/O look/O on/O Robb/PERSON 's/O face/O as/O he/O stared/O at/O their/O sister/O 's/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O says/O Father/O conspired/O at/O treason/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O brothers/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O read/O ./O 
\/O ``/O King/O Robert/PERSON is/O dead/O ,/O and/O Mother/PERSON and/O I/O are/O summoned/O to/O the/O Red/O Keep/O to/O swear/O fealty/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
She/O says/O we/O must/O be/O loyal/O ,/O and/O when/O she/O marries/O Joffrey/PERSON she/O will/O plead/O with/O him/O to/O spare/O our/O lord/O father/O 's/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O fingers/O closed/O into/O a/O fist/O ,/O crushing/O Sansa/O 's/O letter/O between/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O she/O says/O nothing/O of/O Arya/PERSON ,/O nothing/O ,/O not/O so/O much/O as/O a/O word/O ./O 
Damn/O her/O !/O 
What/O 's/O wrong/O with/O the/O girl/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O felt/O all/O cold/O inside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O lost/O her/O wolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O weakly/O ,/O remembering/O the/O day/O when/O four/O of/O his/O father/O 's/O guardsmen/O had/O returned/O from/O the/O south/O with/O Lady/O 's/O bones/O ./O 
Summer/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON and/O Shaggydog/PERSON had/O begun/O to/O howl/O before/O they/O crossed/O the/O drawbridge/O ,/O in/O voices/O drawn/O and/O desolate/O ./O 
Beneath/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O First/O Keep/O was/O an/O ancient/O lichyard/O ,/O its/O headstones/O spotted/O with/O pale/O lichen/O ,/O where/O the/O old/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O had/O laid/O their/O faithful/O servants/O ./O 
It/O was/O there/O they/O buried/O Lady/O ,/O while/O her/O brothers/O stalked/O between/O the/O graves/O like/O restless/O shadows/O ./O 
She/O had/O gone/O south/O ,/O and/O only/O her/O bones/O had/O returned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Their/O grandfather/O ,/O old/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON ,/O had/O gone/O as/O well/O ,/O with/O his/O son/O Brandon/PERSON who/O was/O Father/O 's/O brother/O ,/O and/O two/O hundred/O of/O his/O best/O men/O ./O 
None/O had/O ever/O returned/O ./O 
And/O Father/O had/O gone/O south/O ,/O with/O Arya/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O and/O Jory/PERSON and/O Hullen/PERSON and/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON and/O the/O rest/O ,/O and/O later/O Mother/O and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON had/O gone/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O n't/O come/O back/O either/O ./O 
And/O now/O Robb/PERSON meant/O to/O go/O ./O 
Not/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O not/O to/O swear/O fealty/O ,/O but/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O with/O a/O sword/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
And/O if/O their/O lord/O father/O were/O truly/O a/O prisoner/O ,/O that/O could/O mean/O his/O death/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
It/O frightened/O Bran/O more/O than/O he/O could/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O Robb/PERSON has/O to/O go/O ,/O watch/O over/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O entreated/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O as/O they/O watched/O him/O with/O the/O heart/O tree/O 's/O red/O eyes/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O watch/O over/O his/O men/O ,/O Hal/PERSON and/O Quent/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O rest/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Umber/O and/O Lady/PERSON Mormont/PERSON and/O the/O other/O lords/O ./O 
And/O Theon/PERSON too/O ,/O I/O suppose/O ./O 
Watch/O them/O and/O keep/O them/O safe/O ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O gods/O ./O 
Help/O them/O defeat/O the/O Lannisters/O and/O save/O Father/O and/O bring/O them/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O faint/O wind/O sighed/O through/O the/O godswood/O and/O the/O red/O leaves/O stirred/O and/O whispered/O ./O 
Summer/O bared/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O hear/O them/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O a/O voice/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O lifted/O his/O head/O ./O 
Osha/ORGANIZATION stood/O across/O the/O pool/O ,/O beneath/O an/O ancient/O oak/O ,/O her/O face/O shadowed/O by/O leaves/O ./O 
Even/O in/O irons/O ,/O the/O wildling/O moved/O quiet/O as/O a/O cat/O ./O 
Summer/O circled/O the/O pool/O ,/O sniffed/O at/O her/O ./O 
The/O tall/O woman/O flinched/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Summer/O ,/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O called/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O took/O one/O final/O sniff/O ,/O spun/O ,/O and/O bounded/O back/O ./O 
Bran/O wrapped/O his/O arms/O around/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O doing/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O not/O seen/O Osha/O since/O they/O 'd/O taken/O her/O captive/O in/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O though/O he/O knew/O she/O 'd/O been/O set/O to/O working/O in/O the/O kitchens/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O are/O my/O gods/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O they/O are/O the/O only/O gods/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O hair/O was/O growing/O out/O ,/O brown/O and/O shaggy/O ./O 
It/O made/O her/O look/O more/O womanly/O ,/O that/O and/O the/O simple/O dress/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O brown/O roughspun/O they/O 'd/O given/O her/O when/O they/O took/O her/O mail/O and/O leather/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gage/PERSON lets/O me/O have/O my/O prayers/O from/O time/O to/O time/O ,/O when/O I/O feel/O the/O need/O ,/O and/O I/O let/O him/O do/O as/O he/O likes/O under/O my/O skirt/O ,/O when/O he/O feels/O the/O need/O ./O 
It/O 's/O nothing/O to/O me/O ./O 
I/O like/O the/O smell/O of/O flour/O on/O his/O hands/O ,/O and/O he/O 's/O gentler/O than/O Stiv/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O gave/O an/O awkward/O bow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O leave/O you/O ./O 
There/O 's/O pots/O that/O want/O scouring/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O stay/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O commanded/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O what/O you/O meant/O ,/O about/O hearing/O the/O gods/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Osha/O studied/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O asked/O them/O and/O they/O 're/O answering/O ./O 
Open/O your/O ears/O ,/O listen/O ,/O you/O 'll/O hear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O listened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O only/O the/O wind/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O after/O a/O moment/O ,/O uncertain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O leaves/O are/O rustling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O do/O you/O think/O sends/O the/O wind/O ,/O if/O not/O the/O gods/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O seated/O herself/O across/O the/O pool/O from/O him/O ,/O clinking/O faintly/O as/O she/O moved/O ./O 
Mikken/PERSON had/O fixed/O iron/O manacles/O to/O her/O ankles/O ,/O with/O a/O heavy/O chain/O between/O them/O ;/O she/O could/O walk/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O she/O kept/O her/O strides/O small/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O way/O for/O her/O to/O run/O ,/O or/O climb/O ,/O or/O mount/O a/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O see/O you/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
They/O hear/O you/O talking/O ./O 
That/O rustling/O ,/O that/O 's/O them/O talking/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O are/O they/O saying/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O sad/O ./O 
Your/O lord/O brother/O will/O get/O no/O help/O from/O them/O ,/O not/O where/O he/O 's/O going/O ./O 
The/O old/O gods/O have/O no/O power/O in/O the/O south/O ./O 
The/O weirwoods/O there/O were/O all/O cut/O down/O ,/O thousands/O of/O years/O ago/O ./O 
How/O can/O they/O watch/O your/O brother/O when/O they/O have/O no/O eyes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O had/O not/O thought/O of/O that/O ./O 
It/O frightened/O him/O ./O 
If/O even/O the/O gods/O could/O not/O help/O his/O brother/O ,/O what/O hope/O was/O there/O ?/O 
Maybe/O Osha/ORGANIZATION was/O n't/O hearing/O them/O right/O ./O 
He/O cocked/O his/O head/O and/O tried/O to/O listen/O again/O ./O 
He/O thought/O he/O could/O hear/O the/O sadness/O now/O ,/O but/O nothing/O more/O than/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rustling/O grew/O louder/O ./O 
Bran/O heard/O muffled/O footfalls/O and/O a/O low/O humming/O ,/O and/O Hodor/PERSON came/O blundering/O out/O of/O the/O trees/O ,/O naked/O and/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O must/O have/O heard/O our/O voices/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O you/O forgot/O your/O clothes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hodor/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
He/O was/O dripping/O wet/O from/O the/O neck/O down/O ,/O steaming/O in/O the/O chill/O air/O ./O 
His/O body/O was/O covered/O with/O brown/O hair/O ,/O thick/O as/O a/O pelt/O ./O 
Between/O his/O legs/O ,/O his/O manhood/O swung/O long/O and/O heavy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION eyed/O him/O with/O a/O sour/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O there/O 's/O a/O big/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O giant/O 's/O blood/O in/O him/O ,/O or/O I/O 'm/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON says/O there/O are/O no/O more/O giants/O ./O 
He/O says/O they/O 're/O all/O dead/O ,/O like/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ./O 
All/O that/O 's/O left/O of/O them/O are/O old/O bones/O in/O the/O earth/O that/O men/O turn/O up/O with/O plows/O from/O time/O to/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O Maester/O Luwin/O ride/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O \/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 'll/O find/O giants/O then/O ,/O or/O they/O 'll/O find/O him/O ./O 
My/O brother/O killed/O one/O ./O 
Ten/O foot/O tall/O she/O was/O ,/O and/O stunted/O at/O that/O ./O 
They/O 've/O been/O known/O to/O grow/O big/O as/O twelve/O and/O thirteen/O feet/O ./O 
Fierce/O things/O they/O are/O too/O ,/O all/O hair/O and/O teeth/O ,/O and/O the/O wives/O have/O beards/O like/O their/O husbands/O ,/O so/O there/O 's/O no/O telling/O them/O apart/O ./O 
The/O women/O take/O human/O men/O for/O lovers/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O from/O them/O the/O half/O bloods/O come/O ./O 
It/O goes/O harder/O on/O the/O women/O they/O catch/O ./O 
The/O men/O are/O so/O big/O they/O 'll/O rip/O a/O maid/O apart/O before/O they/O get/O her/O with/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O grinned/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O you/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O I/O mean/O ,/O do/O you/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O I/O do/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O insisted/O ./O 
He/O understood/O about/O mating/O ;/O he/O had/O seen/O dogs/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O and/O watched/O a/O stallion/O mount/O a/O mare/O ./O 
But/O talking/O about/O it/O made/O him/O uncomfortable/O ./O 
He/O looked/O at/O Hodor/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O back/O and/O bring/O your/O clothes/O ,/O Hodor/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O dress/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O back/O the/O way/O he/O had/O come/O ,/O ducking/O under/O a/O low-hanging/O tree/O limb/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O awfully/O big/O ,/O Bran/O thought/O as/O he/O watched/O him/O go/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O there/O truly/O giants/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O uncertainly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Giants/ORGANIZATION and/O worse/O than/O giants/O ,/O Lordling/O ./O 
I/O tried/O to/O tell/O your/O brother/O when/O he/O asked/O his/O questions/O ,/O him/O and/O your/O maester/O and/O that/O smiley/O boy/O Greyjoy/PERSON ./O 
The/O cold/O winds/O are/O rising/O ,/O and/O men/O go/O out/O from/O their/O fires/O and/O never/O come/O back/O .../O or/O if/O they/O do/O ,/O they/O 're/O not/O men/O no/O more/O ,/O but/O only/O wights/O ,/O with/O blue/O eyes/O and/O cold/O black/O hands/O ./O 
Why/O do/O you/O think/O I/O run/O south/O with/O Stiv/PERSON and/O Hali/PERSON and/O the/O rest/O of/O them/O fools/O ?/O 
Mance/PERSON thinks/O he/O 'll/O fight/O ,/O the/O brave/O sweet/O stubborn/O man/O ,/O like/O the/O white/O walkers/O were/O no/O more/O than/O rangers/O ,/O but/O what/O does/O he/O know/O ?/O 
He/O can/O call/O himself/O King/PERSON -/PERSON beyond-the-Wall/PERSON all/O he/O likes/O ,/O but/O he/O 's/O still/O just/O another/O old/O black/O crow/O who/O flew/O down/O from/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
He/O 's/O never/O tasted/O winter/O ./O 
I/O was/O born/O up/O there/O ,/O child/O ,/O like/O my/O mother/O and/O her/O mother/O before/O her/O and/O her/O mother/O before/O her/O ,/O born/O of/O the/O Free/O Folk/O ./O 
We/O remember/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION stood/O ,/O her/O chains/O rattling/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O tried/O to/O tell/O your/O lordling/O brother/O ./O 
Only/O yesterday/O ,/O when/O I/O saw/O him/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
`/O MTord/O Stark/O ,/O '/O I/O called/O to/O him/O ,/O respectful/O as/O you/O please/O ,/O but/O he/O looked/O through/O me/O ,/O and/O that/O sweaty/O oaf/O Greatjon/O Umber/O shoves/O me/O out/O of/O the/O path/O ./O 
So/O be/O it/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O wear/O my/O irons/O and/O hold/O my/O tongue/O ./O 
A/O man/O who/O wo/O n't/O listen/O ca/O n't/O hear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON will/O listen/O to/O me/O ,/O I/O know/O he/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O he/O now/O ?/O 
We/O 'll/O see/O ./O 
You/O tell/O him/O this/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
You/O tell/O him/O he/O 's/O bound/O on/O marching/O the/O wrong/O way/O ./O 
It/O 's/O north/O he/O should/O be/O taking/O his/O swords/O ./O 
North/O ,/O not/O south/O ./O 
You/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O tell/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O But/O that/O night/O ,/O when/O they/O feasted/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O Robb/PERSON was/O not/O with/O them/O ./O 
He/O took/O his/O meal/O in/O the/O solar/O instead/O ,/O with/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON and/O the/O Greatjon/LOCATION and/O the/O other/O lords/O bannermen/O ,/O to/O make/O the/O final/O plans/O for/O the/O long/O march/O to/O come/O ./O 
It/O was/O left/O to/O Bran/O to/O fill/O his/O place/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O table/O ,/O and/O act/O the/O host/O to/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON 's/O sons/O and/O honored/O friends/O ./O 
They/O were/O already/O at/O their/O places/O when/O Hodor/PERSON carried/O Bran/O into/O the/O hall/O on/O his/O back/O ,/O and/O knelt/O beside/O the/O high/O seat/O ./O 
Two/O of/O the/O serving/O men/O helped/O lift/O him/O from/O his/O basket/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O feel/O the/O eyes/O of/O every/O stranger/O in/O the/O hall/O ./O 
It/O had/O grown/O quiet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON announced/O ,/O \/O ``/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O of/O Winterfell/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O welcome/O you/O to/O our/O fires/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O stiffly/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O offer/O you/O meat/O and/O mead/O in/O honor/O of/O our/O friendship/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Harrion/O Karstark/O ,/O the/O oldest/O of/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON '/O s/O sons/O ,/O bowed/O ,/O and/O his/O brothers/O after/O him/O ,/O yet/O as/O they/O settled/O back/O in/O their/O places/O he/O heard/O the/O younger/O two/O talking/O in/O low/O voices/O ,/O over/O the/O clatter/O of/O wine/O cups/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O .../O sooner/O die/O than/O live/O like/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O muttered/O one/O ,/O his/O father/O 's/O namesake/O Eddard/O ,/O and/O his/O brother/O Torrhen/PERSON said/O likely/O the/O boy/O was/O broken/O inside/O as/O well/O as/O out/O ,/O too/O craven/O to/O take/O his/O own/O life/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Broken/O ,/O Bran/O thought/O bitterly/O as/O he/O clutched/O his/O knife/O ./O 
Is/O that/O what/O he/O was/O now/O ?/O 
Bran/O the/O Broken/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O be/O broken/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O fiercely/O to/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O who/O 'd/O been/O seated/O to/O his/O right/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O be/O a/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O some/O who/O call/O my/O order/O the/O knights/O of/O the/O mind/O ,/O \/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O surpassing/O clever/O boy/O when/O you/O work/O at/O it/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
Have/O you/O ever/O thought/O that/O you/O might/O wear/O a/O maester/O 's/O chain/O ?/O 
There/O is/O no/O limit/O to/O what/O you/O might/O learn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O learn/O magic/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O crow/O promised/O that/O I/O would/O fly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O teach/O you/O history/O ,/O healing/O ,/O herblore/O ./O 
I/O can/O teach/O you/O the/O speech/O of/O ravens/O ,/O and/O how/O to/O build/O a/O castle/O ,/O and/O the/O way/O a/O sailor/O steers/O his/O ship/O by/O the/O stars/O ./O 
I/O can/O teach/O you/O to/O measure/O the/O days/O and/O mark/O the/O seasons/O ,/O and/O at/O the/O Citadel/LOCATION in/O Oldtown/LOCATION they/O can/O teach/O you/O a/O thousand/O things/O more/O ./O 
But/O ,/O Bran/O ,/O no/O man/O can/O teach/O you/O magic/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O children/O could/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O That/O reminded/O him/O of/O the/O promise/O he/O had/O made/O to/O Osha/ORGANIZATION in/O the/O godswood/O ,/O so/O he/O told/O Luwin/PERSON what/O she/O had/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O maester/O listened/O politely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wildling/O woman/O could/O give/O Old/O Nan/PERSON lessons/O in/O telling/O tales/O ,/O I/O think/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O when/O Bran/O was/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O talk/O with/O her/O again/O if/O you/O like/O ,/O but/O it/O would/O be/O best/O if/O you/O did/O not/O trouble/O your/O brother/O with/O this/O folly/O ./O 
He/O has/O more/O than/O enough/O to/O concern/O him/O without/O fretting/O over/O giants/O and/O dead/O men/O in/O the/O woods/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O Lannisters/O who/O hold/O your/O lord/O father/O ,/O Bran/O ,/O not/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O put/O a/O gentle/O hand/O on/O Bran/O 's/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Think/O on/O what/O I/O said/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O two/O days/O later/O ,/O as/O a/O red/O dawn/O broke/O across/O a/O windswept/O sky/O ,/O Bran/O found/O himself/O in/O the/O yard/O beneath/O the/O gatehouse/O ,/O strapped/O atop/O Dancer/O as/O he/O said/O his/O farewells/O to/O his/O brother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O lord/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O mounted/O on/O a/O shaggy/O grey/O stallion/O ,/O his/O shield/O hung/O from/O the/O horse/O 's/O side/O ;/O wood/O banded/O with/O iron/O ,/O white/O and/O grey/O ,/O and/O on/O it/O the/O snarling/O face/O of/O a/O direwolf/O His/O brother/O wore/O grey/O chainmail/O over/O bleached/O leathers/O ,/O sword/O and/O dagger/O at/O his/O waist/O ,/O a/O fur-trimmed/O cloak/O across/O his/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O take/O my/O place/O ,/O as/O I/O took/O Father/O 's/O ,/O until/O we/O come/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O replied/O miserably/O ./O 
He/O had/O never/O felt/O so/O little/O or/O alone/O or/O scared/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O know/O how/O to/O be/O a/O lord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Listen/O to/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON 's/O counsel/O ,/O and/O take/O care/O of/O Rickon/LOCATION ./O 
Tell/O him/O that/O I/O 'll/O be/O back/O as/O soon/O as/O the/O fighting/O is/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON had/O refused/O to/O come/O down/O ./O 
He/O was/O up/O in/O his/O chamber/O ,/O redeyed/O and/O defiant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O 'd/O screamed/O when/O Bran/ORGANIZATION had/O asked/O if/O he/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O say/O farewell/O to/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O NO/O farewell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O told/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O says/O no/O one/O ever/O comes/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O ca/O n't/O be/O a/O baby/O forever/O ./O 
He/O 's/O a/O Stark/O ,/O and/O near/O four/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O Mother/PERSON will/O be/O home/O soon/O ./O 
And/O I/O 'll/O bring/O back/O Father/O ,/O I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O wheeled/O his/O courser/O around/O and/O trotted/O away/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON followed/O ,/O loping/O beside/O the/O warhorse/O ,/O lean/O and/O swift/O ./O 
Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON went/O before/O them/O through/O the/O gate/O ,/O carrying/O the/O rippling/O white/O banner/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Stark/O atop/O a/O high/O standard/O of/O grey/O ash/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON and/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON fell/O in/O on/O either/O side/O of/O Robb/LOCATION ,/O and/O their/O knights/O formed/O up/O in/O a/O double/O column/O behind/O them/O ,/O steel/O -/O tipped/O lances/O glinting/O in/O the/O sun/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Uncomfortably/O ,/O he/O remembered/O Osha/ORGANIZATION 's/O words/O ./O 
He/O 's/O marching/O the/O wrong/O way/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
For/O an/O instant/O he/O wanted/O to/O gallop/O after/O him/O and/O shout/O a/O warning/O ,/O but/O when/O Robb/PERSON vanished/O beneath/O the/O portcullis/O ,/O the/O moment/O was/O gone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O castle/O walls/O ,/O a/O roar/O of/O sound/O went/O up/O ./O 
The/O foot/O soldiers/O and/O townsfolk/O were/O cheering/O Robb/PERSON as/O he/O rode/O past/O ,/O Bran/O knew/O ;/O cheering/O for/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ,/O for/O the/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/O on/O his/O great/O stallion/O ,/O with/O his/O cloak/O streaming/O and/O Grey/O Wind/O racing/O beside/O him/O ./O 
They/O would/O never/O ''/O ,/O ``/O cheer/O for/O him/O that/O way/O ,/O he/O realized/O with/O a/O dull/O ache/O ./O 
He/O might/O be/O the/O lord/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION while/O his/O brother/O and/O father/O were/O gone/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O still/O Bran/O the/O Broken/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O even/O get/O off/O his/O own/O horse/O ,/O except/O to/O fall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O distant/O cheers/O had/O faded/O to/O silence/O and/O the/O yard/O was/O empty/O at/O last/O ,/O Winterfell/PERSON seemed/O deserted/O and/O dead/O ./O 
Bran/O looked/O around/O at/O the/O faces/O of/O those/O who/O remained/O ,/O women/O and/O children/O and/O old/O men/O .../O and/O Hodor/LOCATION ./O 
The/O huge/O stableboy/O had/O a/O lost/O and/O frightened/O look/O to/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O sadly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O agreed/O ,/O wondering/O what/O it/O meant/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
