-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O On/O a/O hill/O overlooking/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O a/O long/O trestle/O table/O of/O rough-hewn/O pine/O had/O been/O erected/O beneath/O an/O elm/O tree/O and/O covered/O with/O a/O golden/O cloth/O ./O 
There/O ,/O beside/O his/O pavilion/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON took/O his/O evening/O meal/O with/O his/O chief/O knights/O and/O lords/O bannermen/O ,/O his/O great/O crimson/O -/O and/O -/O gold/O standard/O waving/O overhead/O from/O a/O lofty/O pike/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O arrived/O late/O ,/O saddlesore/O ,/O and/O sour/O ,/O all/O too/O vividly/O aware/O of/O how/O amusing/O he/O must/O look/O as/O he/O waddled/O up/O the/O slope/O to/O his/O father/O ./O 
The/O day/O 's/O march/O had/O been/O long/O and/O tiring/O ./O 
He/O thought/O he/O might/O get/O quite/O drunk/O tonight/O ./O 
It/O was/O twilight/O ,/O and/O the/O air/O was/O alive/O with/O drifting/O fireflies/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O cooks/O were/O serving/O the/O meat/O course/O :/O five/O suckling/O pigs/O ,/O skin/O seared/O and/O crackling/O ,/O a/O different/O fruit/O in/O every/O mouth/O ./O 
The/O smell/O made/O his/O mouth/O water/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O pardons/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O began/O ,/O taking/O his/O place/O on/O the/O bench/O beside/O his/O uncle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O I/O 'd/O best/O charge/O you/O with/O burying/O our/O dead/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O are/O as/O late/O to/O battle/O as/O you/O are/O to/O table/O ,/O the/O fighting/O will/O all/O be/O done/O by/O the/O time/O you/O arrive/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O surely/O you/O can/O save/O me/O a/O peasant/O or/O two/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O too/O many/O ,/O I/O would/O n't/O want/O to/O be/O greedy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O filled/O his/O wine/O cup/O and/O watched/O a/O serving/O man/O carve/O into/O the/O pig/O ./O 
The/O crisp/O skin/O crackled/O under/O his/O knife/O ,/O and/O hot/O juice/O ran/O from/O the/O meat/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O loveliest/O sight/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O seen/O in/O ages/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Addam/O 's/O outriders/O say/O the/O Stark/O host/O has/O moved/O south/O from/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O reported/O as/O his/O trencher/O was/O filled/O with/O slices/O of/O pork/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON 's/O levies/O have/O joined/O them/O ./O 
They/O are/O likely/O no/O more/O than/O a/O day/O 's/O march/O north/O of/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O about/O to/O eat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Does/O the/O thought/O of/O facing/O the/O Stark/O boy/O unman/O you/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON ?/O 
Your/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON would/O be/O eager/O to/O come/O to/O grips/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O sooner/O come/O to/O grips/O with/O that/O pig/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON is/O not/O half/O so/O tender/O ,/O and/O he/O never/O smelled/O as/O good/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON ,/O the/O sour/O bird/O who/O had/O charge/O of/O their/O stores/O and/O supplies/O ,/O leaned/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O your/O savages/O do/O not/O share/O your/O reluctance/O ,/O else/O we/O 've/O wasted/O our/O good/O steel/O on/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O savages/O will/O put/O your/O steel/O to/O excellent/O use/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ./O 
When/O he/O had/O told/O Lefford/PERSON he/O needed/O arms/O and/O armor/O to/O equip/O the/O three/O hundred/O men/O Ulf/PERSON had/O fetched/O down/O out/O of/O the/O foothills/O ,/O you/O would/O have/O thought/O he/O 'd/O asked/O the/O man/O to/O turn/O his/O virgin/O daughters/O over/O to/O their/O pleasure/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O that/O great/O hairy/O one/O today/O ,/O the/O one/O who/O insisted/O that/O he/O must/O have/O two/O battle-axes/O ,/O the/O heavy/O black/O steel/O ones/O with/O twin/O crescent/O blades/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shagga/O likes/O to/O kill/O with/O either/O hand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O as/O a/O trencher/O of/O steaming/O pork/O was/O laid/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O still/O had/O that/O wood-axe/O of/O his/O strapped/O to/O his/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shagga/O is/O of/O the/O opinion/O that/O three/O axes/O are/O even/O better/O than/O two/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O reached/O a/O thumb/O and/O forefinger/O into/O the/O salt/O dish/O ,/O and/O sprinkled/O a/O healthy/O pinch/O over/O his/O meat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON leaned/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O had/O a/O thought/O to/O put/O you/O and/O your/O wildlings/O in/O the/O vanguard/O when/O we/O come/O to/O battle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Kevan/PERSON seldom/O \/O ``/O had/O a/O thought/O \/O ''/O that/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON had/O not/O had/O first/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O skewered/O a/O chunk/O of/O meat/O on/O the/O point/O of/O his/O dagger/O and/O brought/O it/O to/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
Now/O he/O lowered/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O vanguard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O repeated/O dubiously/O ./O 
Either/O his/O lord/O father/O had/O a/O new/O respect/O for/O Tyrion/O '/O s/O abilities/O ,/O or/O he/O 'd/O decided/O to/O rid/O himself/O of/O his/O embarrassing/O get/O for/O good/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O the/O gloomy/O feeling/O he/O knew/O which/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O seem/O ferocious/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ferocious/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON realized/O he/O was/O echoing/O his/O uncle/O like/O a/O trained/O bird/O ./O 
His/O father/O watched/O ,/O judging/O him/O ,/O weighing/O every/O word/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O tell/O you/O how/O ferocious/O they/O are/O ./O 
Last/O night/O ,/O a/O Moon/O Brother/O stabbed/O a/O Stone/O Crow/O over/O a/O sausage/O ./O 
So/O today/O as/O we/O made/O camp/O three/O Stone/O Crows/O seized/O the/O man/O and/O opened/O his/O throat/O for/O him/O ./O 
Perhaps/O they/O were/O hoping/O to/O get/O the/O sausage/O back/O ,/O I/O could/O n't/O say/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON managed/O to/O keep/O Shagga/PERSON from/O chopping/O off/O the/O dead/O man/O 's/O cock/O ,/O which/O was/O fortunate/O ,/O but/O even/O so/O Ulf/PERSON is/O demanding/O blood/O money/O ,/O which/O Conn/LOCATION and/O Shagga/PERSON refuse/O to/O pay/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O soldiers/O lack/O discipline/O ,/O the/O fault/O lies/O with/O their/O lord/O commander/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON had/O always/O been/O able/O to/O make/O men/O follow/O him/O eagerly/O ,/O and/O die/O for/O him/O if/O need/O be/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON lacked/O that/O gift/O ./O 
He/O bought/O loyalty/O with/O gold/O ,/O and/O compelled/O obedience/O with/O his/O name/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O bigger/O man/O would/O be/O able/O to/O put/O the/O fear/O in/O them/O ,/O is/O that/O what/O you/O 're/O saying/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON turned/O to/O his/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O my/O son/O 's/O men/O will/O not/O obey/O his/O commands/O ,/O perhaps/O the/O vanguard/O is/O not/O the/O place/O for/O him/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O he/O would/O be/O more/O comfortable/O in/O the/O rear/O ,/O guarding/O our/O baggage/O train/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O me/O no/O kindnesses/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O angrily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O have/O no/O other/O command/O to/O offer/O me/O ,/O I/O 'll/O lead/O your/O van/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON studied/O his/O dwarf/O son/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O said/O nothing/O about/O command/O ./O 
You/O will/O serve/O under/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O took/O one/O bite/O of/O pork/O ,/O chewed/O a/O moment/O ,/O and/O spit/O it/O out/O angrily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O find/O I/O am/O not/O hungry/O after/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O climbing/O awkwardly/O off/O the/O bench/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pray/O excuse/O me/O ,/O my/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON inclined/O his/O head/O ,/O dismissing/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON turned/O and/O walked/O away/O ./O 
He/O was/O conscious/O of/O their/O eyes/O on/O his/O back/O as/O he/O waddled/O down/O the/O hill/O ./O 
A/O great/O gust/O of/O laughter/O went/O up/O from/O behind/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O look/O back/O ./O 
He/O hoped/O they/O all/O choked/O on/O their/O suckling/O pigs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dusk/O had/O settled/O ,/O turning/O all/O the/O banners/O black/O ./O 
The/O Lannister/O camp/O sprawled/O for/O miles/O between/O the/O river/O and/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
In/O amongst/O the/O men/O and/O the/O horses/O and/O the/O trees/O ,/O it/O was/O easy/O to/O get/O lost/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON did/O ./O 
He/O passed/O a/O dozen/O great/O pavilions/O and/O a/O hundred/O cookfires/O ./O 
Fireflies/O drifted/O amongst/O the/O tents/O like/O wandering/O stars/O ./O 
He/O caught/O the/O scent/O of/O garlic/O sausage/O ,/O spiced/O and/O savory/O ,/O so/O tempting/O it/O made/O his/O empty/O stomach/O growl/O ./O 
Away/O in/O the/O distance/O ,/O he/O heard/O voices/O raised/O in/O some/O bawdy/O song/O ./O 
A/O giggling/O woman/O raced/O past/O him/O ,/O naked/O beneath/O a/O dark/O cloak/O ,/O her/O drunken/O pursuer/O stumbling/O over/O tree/O roots/O ./O 
Farther/O on/O ,/O two/O spearmen/O faced/O each/O other/O across/O a/O little/O trickle/O of/O a/O stream/O ,/O practicing/O their/O thrust/O -/O and-parry/O in/O the/O fading/O light/O ,/O their/O chests/O bare/O and/O slick/O with/O sweat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O one/O looked/O at/O him/O ./O 
No/O one/O spoke/O to/O him/O ./O 
No/O one/O paid/O him/O any/O mind/O ./O 
He/O was/O surrounded/O by/O men/O sworn/O to/O House/ORGANIZATION Lannister/O ,/O a/O vast/O host/O twenty/O thousand/O strong/O ,/O and/O yet/O he/O was/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O heard/O the/O deep/O rumble/O of/O Shagga/PERSON 's/O laughter/O booming/O through/O the/O dark/O ,/O he/O followed/O it/O to/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O in/O their/O small/O corner/O of/O the/O night/O ./O 
Conn/PERSON son/O of/O Coratt/PERSON waved/O a/O tankard/O of/O ale/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O Halfman/O !/O 
Come/O ,/O sit/O by/O our/O fire/O ,/O share/O meat/O with/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O ./O 
We/O have/O an/O ox/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O see/O that/O ,/O Conn/PERSON son/O of/O Coratt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O huge/O red/O carcass/O was/O suspended/O over/O a/O roaring/O fire/O ,/O skewered/O on/O a/O spit/O the/O size/O of/O a/O small/O tree/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O it/O was/O a/O small/O tree/O ./O 
Blood/O and/O grease/O dripped/O down/O into/O the/O flames/O as/O two/O Stone/O Crows/O turned/O the/O meat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O ./O 
Send/O for/O me/O when/O the/O ox/O is/O cooked/O ./O 
\/O ''/O From/O the/O look/O of/O it/O ,/O that/O might/O even/O be/O before/O the/O battle/O ./O 
He/O walked/O on/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Each/O clan/O had/O its/O own/O cookfire/O ;/O Black/ORGANIZATION Ears/ORGANIZATION did/O not/O eat/O with/O Stone/O Crows/O ,/O Stone/O Crows/O did/O not/O eat/O with/O Moon/PERSON Brothers/PERSON ,/O and/O no/O one/O ate/O with/O Burned/O Men/O ./O 
The/O modest/O tent/O he/O had/O coaxed/O out/O of/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON 's/O stores/O had/O been/O erected/O in/O the/O center/O of/O the/O four/O fires/O ./O 
Tyrion/O found/O Bronn/PERSON sharing/O a/O skin/O of/O wine/O with/O the/O new/O servants/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON had/O sent/O him/O a/O groom/O and/O a/O body/O servant/O to/O see/O to/O his/O needs/O ,/O and/O even/O insisted/O he/O take/O a/O squire/O ./O 
They/O were/O seated/O around/O the/O embers/O of/O a/O small/O cookfire/O ./O 
A/O girl/O was/O with/O them/O ;/O slim/O ,/O dark-haired/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O eighteen/O by/O the/O look/O of/O her/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON studied/O her/O face/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O before/O he/O spied/O fishbones/O in/O the/O ashes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O did/O you/O eat/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Trout/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O his/O groom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON caught/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Trout/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
Suckling/O pig/O ./O 
Damn/O my/O father/O ./O 
He/O stared/O mournfully/O at/O the/O bones/O ,/O his/O belly/O rumbling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O squire/O ,/O a/O boy/O with/O the/O unfortunate/O name/O of/O Podrick/PERSON Payne/PERSON ,/O swallowed/O whatever/O he/O had/O been/O about/O to/O say/O ./O 
The/O lad/O was/O a/O distant/O cousin/O to/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON ,/O the/O king/O 's/O headsman/O .../O and/O almost/O as/O quiet/O ,/O although/O not/O for/O want/O of/O a/O tongue/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O made/O him/O stick/O it/O out/O once/O ,/O just/O to/O be/O certain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Definitely/O a/O tongue/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O had/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Someday/O you/O must/O learn/O to/O use/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O At/O the/O moment/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O have/O the/O patience/O to/O try/O and/O coax/O a/O thought/O out/O of/O the/O lad/O ,/O whom/O he/O suspected/O had/O been/O inflicted/O on/O him/O as/O a/O cruel/O jape/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON turned/O his/O attention/O back/O to/O the/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O Bronn/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O rose/O gracefully/O and/O looked/O down/O at/O him/O from/O the/O lofty/O height/O of/O five/O feet/O or/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O and/O she/O can/O speak/O for/O herself/O ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O cocked/O his/O head/O to/O one/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O Tyrion/PERSON ,/O of/O House/O Lannister/O ./O 
Men/O call/O me/O the/O Imp/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O mother/O named/O me/O Shae/PERSON ./O 
Men/O call/O me/O .../O often/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON laughed/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/LOCATION had/O to/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Into/O the/O tent/O ,/O Shae/PERSON ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O lifted/O the/O flap/O and/O held/O it/O for/O her/O ./O 
Inside/O ,/O he/O knelt/O to/O light/O a/O candle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O life/O of/O a/O soldier/O was/O not/O without/O certain/O compensations/O ./O 
Wherever/O you/O have/O a/O camp/O ,/O you/O are/O certain/O to/O have/O camp/O followers/O ./O 
At/O the/O end/O of/O the/O day/O 's/O march/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O sent/O Bronn/PERSON back/O to/O find/O him/O a/O likely/O whore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O prefer/O one/O who/O is/O reasonably/O young/O ,/O with/O as/O pretty/O a/O face/O as/O you/O can/O find/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O had/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O she/O has/O washed/O sometime/O this/O year/O ,/O I/O shall/O be/O glad/O ./O 
If/O she/O has/O n't/O ,/O wash/O her/O ./O 
Be/O certain/O that/O you/O tell/O her/O who/O I/O am/O ,/O and/O warn/O her/O of/O what/O I/O am/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jyck/PERSON had/O not/O always/O troubled/O to/O do/O that/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O look/O the/O girls/O got/O in/O their/O eyes/O sometimes/O when/O they/O first/O beheld/O ''/O ,/O ``/O the/O lordling/O they/O 'd/O been/O hired/O to/O pleasure/O .../O a/O took/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON did/O not/O ever/O care/O to/O see/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O lifted/O the/O candle/O and/O looked/O her/O over/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON had/O done/O well/O enough/O ;/O she/O was/O doe-eyed/O and/O slim/O ,/O with/O small/O firm/O breasts/O and/O a/O smile/O that/O was/O by/O turns/O shy/O ,/O insolent/O ,/O and/O wicked/O ./O 
He/O liked/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shall/O I/O take/O my/O gown/O off/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O good/O time/O ./O 
Are/O you/O a/O maiden/O ,/O Shae/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O demurely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O would/O please/O me/O would/O be/O the/O truth/O of/O you/O ,/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aye/O ,/O but/O that/O will/O cost/O you/O double/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O decided/O they/O would/O get/O along/O splendidly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O a/O Lannister/O ./O 
Gold/O I/O have/O in/O plenty/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O find/O me/O generous/O .../O but/O I/O 'll/O want/O more/O from/O you/O than/O what/O you/O 've/O got/O between/O your/O legs/O ,/O though/O I/O 'll/O want/O that/O too/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O share/O my/O tent/O ,/O pour/O my/O wine/O ,/O laugh/O at/O my/O jests/O ,/O rub/O the/O ache/O from/O my/O legs/O after/O each/O day/O 's/O ride/O .../O and/O whether/O I/O keep/O you/O a/O day/O or/O a/O year/O ,/O for/O so/O long/O as/O we/O are/O together/O you/O will/O take/O no/O other/O men/O into/O your/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fair/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O reached/O down/O to/O the/O hem/O of/O her/O thin/O roughspun/O gown/O and/O pulled/O it/O up/O over/O her/O head/O in/O one/O smooth/O motion/O ,/O tossing/O it/O aside/O ./O 
There/O was/O nothing/O underneath/O but/O Shae/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O he/O do/O n't/O put/O down/O that/O candle/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O will/O burn/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O put/O down/O the/O candle/O ,/O took/O her/O hand/O in/O his/O ,/O and/O pulled/O her/O gently/O to/O him/O ./O 
She/O bent/O to/O kiss/O him/O ./O 
Her/O mouth/O tasted/O of/O honey/O and/O cloves/O ,/O and/O her/O fingers/O were/O deft/O and/O practiced/O as/O they/O found/O the/O fastenings/O of/O his/O clothes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O entered/O her/O ,/O she/O welcomed/O him/O with/O whispered/O endearments/O and/O small/O ,/O shuddering/O gasps/O of/O pleasure/O ./O 
Tyrion/O suspected/O her/O delight/O was/O feigned/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O it/O so/O well/O that/O it/O did/O not/O matter/O ./O 
That/O much/O truth/O he/O did/O not/O crave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O needed/O her/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON realized/O afterward/O ,/O as/O she/O lay/O quietly/O in/O his/O arms/O ./O 
Her/O or/O someone/O like/O her/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O nigh/O on/O a/O year/O since/O he/O 'd/O lain/O with/O a/O woman/O ,/O since/O before/O he/O had/O set/O out/O for/O Winterfell/O in/O company/O with/O his/O brother/O and/O King/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
He/O could/O well/O die/O on/O the/O morrow/O or/O the/O day/O after/O ,/O and/O if/O he/O did/O ,/O he/O would/O sooner/O go/O to/O his/O grave/O thinking/O of/O Shae/PERSON than/O of/O his/O lord/O father/O ,/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O or/O the/O Lady/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O could/O feel/O the/O softness/O of/O her/O breasts/O pressed/O against/O his/O arm/O as/O she/O lay/O beside/O him/O ./O 
That/O was/O a/O good/O feeling/O ./O 
A/O song/O filled/O his/O head/O ./O 
Softly/O ,/O quietly/O ,/O he/O began/O to/O whistle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O 's/O that/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Shae/PERSON murmured/O against/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O song/O I/O learned/O as/O a/O boy/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O ./O 
Go/O to/O sleep/O ,/O sweetling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O her/O eyes/O were/O closed/O and/O her/O breathing/O deep/O and/O steady/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON slid/O out/O from/O beneath/O her/O ,/O gently/O ,/O so/O as/O not/O to/O disturb/O her/O sleep/O ./O 
Naked/O ,/O he/O crawled/O outside/O ,/O stepped/O over/O his/O squire/O ,/O and/O walked/O around/O behind/O his/O tent/O to/O make/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON was/O seated/O cross-legged/O under/O a/O chestnut/O tree/O ,/O near/O where/O they/O 'd/O tied/O the/O horses/O ./O 
He/O was/O honing/O the/O edge/O of/O his/O sword/O ,/O wide/O awake/O ;/O the/O sellsword/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O sleep/O like/O other/O men/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O did/O you/O find/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O him/O as/O he/O pissed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O took/O her/O from/O a/O knight/O ./O 
The/O man/O was/O loath/O to/O give/O her/O up/O ,/O but/O your/O name/O changed/O his/O thinking/O somewhat/O .../O that/O ,/O and/O my/O dirk/O at/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Splendid/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O dryly/O ,/O shaking/O off/O the/O last/O drops/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O seem/O to/O recall/O saying/O find/O me/O a/O whore/O ,/O not/O make/O me/O an/O enemy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O pretty/O ones/O were/O all/O claimed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O be/O pleased/O to/O take/O her/O back/O if/O you/O 'd/O prefer/O a/O toothless/O drab/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O limped/O closer/O to/O where/O he/O sat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O would/O call/O that/O insolence/O ,/O and/O send/O you/O to/O the/O mines/O for/O impertinence/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O for/O me/O you/O 're/O not/O your/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O one/O with/O boils/O all/O over/O her/O nose/O ./O 
Would/O you/O like/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O ,/O and/O break/O your/O heart/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O shot/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O keep/O Shae/PERSON ./O 
Did/O you/O perchance/O note/O the/O name/O of/O this/O knight/O you/O took/O her/O from/O ?/O 
I/O 'd/O rather/O not/O have/O him/O beside/O me/O in/O the/O battle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/O rose/O ,/O cat-quick/O and/O cat-graceful/O ,/O turning/O his/O sword/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O have/O me/O beside/O you/O in/O the/O battle/O ,/O dwarf/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O nodded/O ./O 
The/O night/O air/O was/O warm/O on/O his/O bare/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O that/O I/O survive/O this/O battle/O ,/O and/O you/O can/O name/O your/O reward/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON tossed/O the/O longsword/O from/O his/O right/O hand/O to/O his/O left/O ,/O and/O tried/O a/O cut/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O 'd/O want/O to/O kill/O the/O likes/O of/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O ,/O for/O one/O ./O 
He/O 's/O put/O me/O in/O the/O van/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O do/O the/O same/O ./O 
A/O small/O man/O with/O a/O big/O shield/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O give/O the/O archers/O fits/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O find/O you/O oddly/O cheering/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O must/O be/O mad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON sheathed/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Beyond/O a/O doubt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O Tyrion/PERSON returned/O to/O his/O tent/O ,/O Shae/PERSON rolled/O onto/O her/O elbow/O and/O murmured/O sleepily/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O woke/O and/O m/O `/O lord/O was/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O MTord/O is/O back/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slid/O in/O beside/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O hand/O went/O between/O his/O stunted/O legs/O ,/O and/O found/O him/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O he/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ,/O stroking/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O asked/O her/O about/O the/O man/O Bronn/PERSON had/O taken/O her/O from/O ,/O and/O she/O named/O the/O minor/O retainer/O of/O an/O insignificant/O lordling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O need/O not/O fear/O his/O like/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O girl/O said/O ,/O her/O fingers/O busy/O at/O his/O cock/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O a/O small/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O am/O I/O ,/O pray/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O giant/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O purred/O ,/O \/O ``/O my/O giant/O of/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O mounted/O him/O then/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O time/O ,/O she/O almost/O made/O him/O believe/O it/O ./O 
Tyrion/O went/O to/O sleep/O smiling/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O .../O and/O woke/O in/O darkness/O to/O the/O blare/O of/O trumpets/O ./O 
Shae/PERSON was/O shaking/O him/O by/O the/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O MTord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wake/O up/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O frightened/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Groggy/O ,/O he/O sat/O up/O and/O threw/O back/O the/O blanket/O ./O 
The/O horns/O called/O through/O the/O night/O ,/O wild/O and/O urgent/O ,/O a/O cry/O that/O said/O huny/O huny/O huny/O ./O 
He/O heard/O shouts/O ,/O the/O clatter/O of/O spears/O ,/O the/O whicker/O of/O horses/O ,/O though/O nothing/O yet/O that/O spoke/O to/O him/O of/O fighting/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O 's/O trumpets/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Battle/O assembly/O ./O 
I/O thought/O Stark/O was/O yet/O a/O day/O 's/O march/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Shae/PERSON shook/O her/O head/O ,/O lost/O ./O 
Her/O eyes/O were/O wide/O and/O white/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Groaning/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON lurched/O to/O his/O feet/O and/O pushed/O his/O way/O outside/O ,/O shouting/O for/O his/O squire/O ./O 
Wisps/O of/O pale/O fog/O drifted/O through/O the/O night/O ,/O long/O white/O fingers/O off/O the/O river/O ./O 
Men/O and/O horses/O blundered/O ''/O ,/O ``/O through/O the/O predawn/O chill/O ;/O saddles/O were/O being/O cinched/O ,/O wagons/O loaded/O ,/O fires/O extinguished/O ./O 
The/O trumpets/O blew/O again/O :/O huny/O huny/O huny/O ./O 
Knights/O vaulted/O onto/O snorting/O coursers/O while/O men-at-arms/O buckled/O their/O sword/O belts/O as/O they/O ran/O ./O 
When/O he/O found/O Pod/O ,/O the/O boy/O was/O snoring/O softly/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON gave/O him/O a/O sharp/O poke/O in/O the/O ribs/O with/O his/O toe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O armor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O be/O quick/O about/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON came/O trotting/O out/O of/O the/O mists/O ,/O already/O armored/O and/O ahorse/O ,/O wearing/O his/O battered/O halfhelm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O know/O what/O 's/O happened/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Stark/O boy/O stole/O a/O march/O on/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O crept/O down/O the/O kingsroad/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O and/O now/O his/O host/O is/O less/O than/O a/O mile/O north/O of/O here/O ,/O forming/O up/O in/O battle/O array/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Huny/PERSON ,/O the/O trumpets/O called/O ,/O huny/O huny/O huny/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O See/O that/O the/O clansmen/O are/O ready/O to/O ride/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON ducked/O back/O inside/O his/O tent/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O my/O clothes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O barked/O at/O Shae/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ./O 
No/O ,/O the/O leather/O ,/O damn/O it/O ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
Bring/O me/O my/O boots/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O he/O was/O dressed/O ,/O his/O squire/O had/O laid/O out/O his/O armor/O ,/O such/O that/O it/O was/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON owned/O a/O fine/O suit/O of/O heavy/O plate/O ,/O expertly/O crafted/O to/O fit/O his/O misshapen/O body/O ./O 
Alas/O ,/O it/O was/O safe/O at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O he/O was/O not/O ./O 
He/O had/O to/O make/O do/O with/O oddments/O assembled/O from/O Lord/O Lefford/PERSON 's/O wagons/O :/O mail/O hauberk/O and/O coif/O ,/O a/O dead/O knight/O 's/O gorget/O ,/O lobstered/O greaves/O and/O gauntlets/O and/O pointed/O steel/O boots/O ./O 
Some/O of/O it/O was/O ornate/O ,/O some/O plain/O ;/O not/O a/O bit/O of/O it/O matched/O ,/O or/O fit/O as/O it/O should/O ./O 
His/O breastplate/O was/O meant/O for/O a/O bigger/O man/O ;/O for/O his/O oversize/O head/O ,/O they/O found/O a/O huge/O bucket/O -/O shaped/O greathelm/O topped/O with/O a/O foot/O -/O long/O triangular/O spike/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Shae/PERSON helped/O Pod/O with/O the/O buckles/O and/O clasps/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O die/O ,/O weep/O for/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O the/O whore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O will/O you/O know/O ?/O 
You/O 'll/O be/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O believe/O you/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Shae/PERSON lowered/O the/O greathelm/O down/O over/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O Pod/PERSON fastened/O it/O to/O his/O gorget/O ./O 
Tyrion/O buckled/O on/O his/O belt/O ,/O heavy/O with/O the/O weight/O of/O shortsword/O and/O dirk/O ./O 
By/O then/O his/O groom/O had/O brought/O up/O his/O mount/O ,/O a/O formidable/O brown/O courser/O armored/O as/O heavily/O as/O he/O was/O ./O 
He/O needed/O help/O to/O mount/O ;/O he/O felt/O as/O though/O he/O weighed/O a/O thousand/O stone/O ./O 
Pod/O handed/O him/O up/O his/O shield/O ,/O a/O massive/O slab/O of/O heavy/O ironwood/O banded/O with/O steel/O ./O 
Lastly/O they/O gave/O him/O his/O battle-axe/O ./O 
Shae/PERSON stepped/O back/O and/O looked/O him/O over/O ./O 
\/O ``/O MTord/O looks/O fearsome/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O MTord/O looks/O a/O dwarf/O in/O mismatched/O armor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON answered/O sourly/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O thank/O you/O for/O the/O kindness/O ./O 
Podrick/PERSON ,/O should/O the/O battle/O go/O against/O us/O ,/O see/O the/O lady/O safely/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O saluted/O her/O with/O his/O axe/O ,/O wheeled/O his/O horse/O about/O ,/O and/O trotted/O off/O ./O 
His/O stomach/O was/O a/O hard/O knot/O ,/O so/O tight/O it/O pained/O him/O ./O 
Behind/O ,/O his/O servants/O hurriedly/O began/O to/O strike/O his/O tent/O ./O 
Pale/O crimson/O fingers/O fanned/O out/O to/O the/O east/O as/O the/O first/O rays/O of/O the/O sun/O broke/O over/O the/O horizon/O ./O 
The/O western/O sky/O was/O a/O deep/O purple/O ,/O speckled/O with/O stars/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON wondered/O whether/O this/O was/O the/O last/O sunrise/O he/O would/O ever/O see/O .../O and/O whether/O wondering/O was/O a/O mark/O of/O cowardice/O ./O 
Did/O his/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON ever/O contemplate/O death/O before/O a/O battle/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O warhorn/O sounded/O in/O the/O far/O distance/O ,/O a/O deep/O mournful/O note/O that/O chilled/O the/O soul/O ./O 
The/O clansmen/O climbed/O onto/O their/O scrawny/O mountain/O horses/O ,/O shouting/O curses/O and/O rude/O jokes/O ./O 
Several/O appeared/O to/O be/O drunk/O ./O 
The/O rising/O sun/O was/O burning/O off/O the/O drifting/O tendrils/O of/O fog/O as/O Tyrion/PERSON led/O them/O off/O ./O 
What/O grass/O the/O horses/O had/O left/O was/O heavy/O with/O dew/O ,/O as/O if/O some/O passing/O god/O had/O scattered/O a/O bag/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O diamonds/O over/O the/O earth/O ./O 
The/O mountain/O men/O fell/O in/O behind/O him/O ,/O each/O clan/O arrayed/O behind/O its/O own/O leaders/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O dawn/O light/O ,/O the/O army/O of/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON unfolded/O like/O an/O iron/O rose/O ,/O thorns/O gleaming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O uncle/O would/O lead/O the/O center/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON had/O raised/O his/O standards/O above/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
Quivers/O hanging/O from/O their/O belts/O ,/O the/O foot/O archers/O arrayed/O themselves/O into/O three/O long/O lines/O ,/O to/O east/O and/O west/O of/O the/O road/O ,/O and/O stood/O calmly/O stringing/O their/O bows/O ./O 
Between/O them/O ,/O pikemen/O formed/O squares/O ;/O behind/O were/O rank/O on/O rank/O of/O men-at-arms/O with/O spear/O and/O sword/O and/O axe/O ./O 
Three/O hundred/O heavy/O horse/O surrounded/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON and/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O Lefford/LOCATION ,/O Lydden/PERSON ,/O and/O Serrett/PERSON with/O all/O their/O sworn/O retainers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O right/O wing/O was/O all/O cavalry/O ,/O some/O four/O thousand/O men/O ,/O heavy/O with/O the/O weight/O of/O their/O armor/O ./O 
More/O than/O three/O quarters/O of/O the/O knights/O were/O there/O ,/O massed/O together/O like/O a/O great/O steel/O fist/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON Marbrand/PERSON had/O the/O command/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON saw/O his/O banner/O unfurl/O as/O his/O standardbearer/O shook/O it/O out/O ;/O a/O burning/O tree/O ,/O orange/O and/O smoke/O ./O 
Behind/O him/O flew/O Ser/O Flement/O 's/O purple/O unicorn/O ,/O the/O brindled/O boar/O of/O Crakehall/LOCATION ,/O the/O bantam/O rooster/O of/O Swyft/LOCATION ,/O and/O more/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O lord/O father/O took/O his/O place/O on/O the/O hill/O where/O he/O had/O slept/O ./O 
Around/O him/O ,/O the/O reserve/O assembled/O ;/O a/O huge/O force/O ,/O half/O mounted/O and/O half/O foot/O ,/O five/O thousand/O strong/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON almost/O always/O chose/O to/O command/O the/O reserve/O ;/O he/O would/O take/O the/O high/O ground/O and/O watch/O the/O battle/O unfold/O below/O him/O ,/O committing/O his/O forces/O when/O and/O where/O they/O were/O needed/O most/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O from/O afar/O ,/O his/O lord/O father/O was/O resplendent/O ./O 
Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O battle/O armor/O put/O his/O son/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O gilded/O suit/O to/O shame/O ./O 
His/O greatcloak/O was/O sewn/O from/O countless/O layers/O of/O cloth-of-gold/O ,/O so/O heavy/O that/O it/O barely/O stirred/O even/O when/O he/O charged/O ,/O so/O large/O that/O its/O drape/O covered/O most/O of/O his/O stallion/O 's/O hindquarters/O when/O he/O took/O the/O saddle/O ./O 
No/O ordinary/O clasp/O would/O suffice/O for/O such/O a/O weight/O ,/O so/O the/O greatcloak/O was/O held/O in/O place/O by/O a/O matched/O pair/O of/O miniature/O lionesses/O crouching/O on/O his/O shoulders/O ,/O as/O if/O poised/O to/O spring/O ./O 
Their/O mate/O ,/O a/O male/O with/O a/O magnificent/O mane/O ,/O reclined/O atop/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON '/O s/O greathelm/O ,/O one/O paw/O raking/O the/O air/O as/O he/O roared/O ./O 
All/O three/O lions/O were/O wrought/O in/O gold/O ,/O with/O ruby/O eyes/O ./O 
His/O armor/O was/O heavy/O steel/O plate/O ,/O enameled/O in/O a/O dark/O crimson/O ,/O greaves/O and/O gauntlets/O inlaid/O with/O ornate/O gold/O scrollwork/O ./O 
His/O rondels/O were/O golden/O sunbursts/O ,/O all/O his/O fastenings/O were/O gilded/O ,/O and/O the/O red/O steel/O was/O burnished/O to/O such/O a/O high/O sheen/O that/O it/O shone/O like/O fire/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O rising/O sun/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O could/O hear/O the/O rumble/O of/O the/O foemen/O 's/O drums/O now/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON as/O he/O had/O last/O seen/O him/O ,/O in/O his/O father/O 's/O high/O seat/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION of/LOCATION Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O a/O sword/O naked/O and/O shining/O in/O his/O hands/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O how/O the/O direwolves/O had/O come/O at/O him/O out/O of/O the/O shadows/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O he/O could/O see/O them/O again/O ,/O snarling/O and/O snapping/O ,/O teeth/O bared/O in/O his/O face/O ./O 
Would/O the/O boy/O bring/O his/O wolves/O to/O war/O with/O him/O ?/O 
The/O thought/O made/O him/O uneasy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O northerners/O would/O be/O exhausted/O after/O their/O long/O sleepless/O march/O ./O 
Tyrion/O wondered/O what/O the/O boy/O had/O been/O thinking/O ./O 
Did/O he/O think/O to/O take/O them/O unawares/O while/O they/O slept/O ?/O 
Small/O chance/O of/O that/O ;/O whatever/O else/O might/O be/O said/O of/O him/O ,/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O no/O man/O 's/O fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O van/O was/O massing/O on/O the/O left/O ./O 
He/O saw/O the/O standard/O first/O ,/O three/O black/O dogs/O on/O a/O yellow/O field/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON sat/O beneath/O it/O ,/O mounted/O on/O the/O biggest/O horse/O Tyrion/O had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON took/O one/O look/O at/O him/O and/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Always/O follow/O a/O big/O man/O into/O battle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O threw/O him/O a/O hard/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O why/O is/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O make/O such/O splendid/O targets/O ./O 
That/O one/O ,/O he/O 'll/O draw/O the/O eyes/O of/O every/O bowman/O on/O the/O field/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Laughing/O ,/O Tyrion/O regarded/O the/O Mountain/O with/O fresh/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O confess/O ,/O I/O had/O not/O considered/O it/O in/O that/O light/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Clegane/PERSON had/O no/O splendor/O about/O him/O ;/O his/O armor/O was/O steel/O plate/O ,/O dull/O grey/O ,/O scarred/O by/O hard/O use/O and/O showing/O neither/O sigil/O nor/O ornament/O ./O 
He/O was/O pointing/O men/O into/O position/O with/O his/O blade/O ,/O a/O two/O -/O handed/O greatsword/O that/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON waved/O about/O with/O one/O hand/O as/O a/O lesser/O man/O might/O wave/O a/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Any/O man/O runs/O ,/O I/O 'll/O cut/O him/O down/O myself/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O was/O roaring/O when/O he/O caught/O sight/O of/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Imp/O !/O 
Take/O the/O left/O ./O 
Hold/O the/O river/O ./O 
If/O you/O can/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O left/O of/O the/O left/O ./O 
To/O turn/O their/O flank/O ,/O the/O Starks/PERSON would/O need/O horses/O that/O could/O run/O on/O water/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON led/O his/O men/O toward/O the/O riverbank/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ,/O pointing/O with/O his/O axe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O river/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O blanket/O of/O pale/O mist/O still/O clung/O to/O the/O surface/O of/O the/O water/O ,/O the/O murky/O green/O current/O swirling/O past/O underneath/O ./O 
The/O shallows/O were/O muddy/O and/O choked/O with/O reeds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O river/O is/O ours/O ./O 
Whatever/O happens/O ,/O keep/O close/O to/O the/O water/O ./O 
Never/O lose/O sight/O of/O it/O ./O 
Let/O no/O enemy/O come/O between/O us/O and/O our/O river/O ./O 
If/O they/O dirty/O our/O waters/O ,/O hack/O off/O their/O cocks/O and/O feed/O them/O to/O the/O fishes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Shagga/PERSON had/O an/O axe/O in/O either/O hand/O ./O 
He/O smashed/O them/O together/O and/O made/O them/O ring/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Halfman/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O 
Other/O Stone/O Crows/O picked/O up/O the/O cry/O ,/O and/O the/O Black/O Ears/O and/O Moon/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION as/O well/O ./O 
The/O Burned/O Men/O did/O not/O shout/O ,/O but/O they/O rattled/O their/O swords/O and/O spears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Halfman/O !/O 
Halfman/O !/O 
Halfman/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O turned/O his/O courser/O in/O a/O circle/O to/O look/O over/O the/O field/O ./O 
The/O ground/O was/O rolling/O and/O uneven/O here/O ;/O soft/O and/O muddy/O near/O the/O river/O ,/O rising/O in/O a/O gentle/O slope/O toward/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O stony/O and/O broken/O beyond/O it/O ,/O to/O the/O cast/O ./O 
A/O few/O trees/O spotted/O the/O hillsides/O ,/O but/O most/O of/O the/O land/O had/O been/O cleared/O and/O planted/O ./O 
His/O heart/O pounded/O in/O his/O chest/O in/O time/O to/O the/O drums/O ,/O and/O under/O his/O layers/O of/O leather/O and/O steel/O his/O brow/O was/O cold/O with/O sweat/O ./O 
He/O watched/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON as/O the/O Mountain/O rode/O up/O and/O down/O the/O line/O ,/O shouting/O and/O gesticulating/O ./O 
This/O wing/O too/O was/O all/O cavalry/O ,/O but/O where/O the/O right/O was/O a/O mailed/O fist/O of/O knights/O and/O heavy/O lancers/O ,/O the/O vanguard/O was/O made/O up/O of/O the/O sweepings/O of/O the/O west/O :/O mounted/O archers/O in/O leather/O jerkins/O ,/O a/O swarming/O mass/O of/O undisciplined/O freeriders/O and/O sellswords/O ,/O fieldhands/O on/O plow/O horses/O armed/O with/O scythes/O and/O their/O fathers/O '/O rusted/O swords/O ,/O half/O -/O trained/O boys/O from/O the/O stews/O of/O Lannisport/LOCATION and/O Tyrion/LOCATION and/O his/O mountain/O clansmen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Crow/O food/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON muttered/O beside/O him/O ,/O giving/O voice/O to/O what/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O left/O unsaid/O ./O 
He/O could/O only/O nod/O ./O 
Had/O his/O lord/O father/O taken/O leave/O of/O his/O senses/O ?/O 
No/O pikes/O ,/O too/O few/O bowmen/O ,/O a/O bare/O handful/O of/O knights/O ,/O the/O ill-armed/O and/O unarmored/O ,/O commanded/O by/O an/O unthinking/O brute/O who/O led/O with/O his/O rage/O .../O how/O could/O his/O father/O expect/O this/O travesty/O of/O a/O battle/O to/O hold/O his/O left/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O no/O time/O to/O think/O about/O it/O ./O 
The/O drums/O were/O so/O near/O that/O the/O beat/O crept/O under/O his/O skin/O and/O set/O his/O hands/O to/O twitching/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON drew/O his/O longsword/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O the/O enemy/O was/O there/O before/O them/O ,/O boiling/O over/O the/O tops/O of/O the/O hills/O ,/O advancing/O with/O measured/O tread/O behind/O a/O wall/O of/O shields/O and/O pikes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Gods/O be/O damned/O ,/O look/O at/O them/O all/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O though/O he/O knew/O his/O father/O had/O more/O men/O on/O the/O field/O ./O 
Their/O captains/O led/O them/O on/O armored/O warhorses/O ,/O standard-bearers/O riding/O alongside/O with/O their/O banners/O ./O 
He/O glimpsed/O the/O bull/O moose/O of/O the/O Hornwoods/O ,/O the/O Karstark/O sunburst/O ,/O Lord/O Cerwyn/PERSON 's/O battle-axe/O ,/O and/O the/O mailed/O fist/O of/O the/O Glovers/O .../O and/O the/O twin/O towers/O of/O Frey/PERSON ,/O blue/O on/O grey/O ./O 
So/O much/O for/O his/O father/O 's/O certainty/O that/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON would/O not/O bestir/O himself/O ./O 
The/O white/O of/O House/O Stark/O was/O seen/O everywhere/O ,/O the/O grey/O direwolves/O seeming/O to/O run/O and/O leap/O as/O the/O banners/O swirled/O and/O streamed/O from/O the/O high/O staffs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O is/O the/O boy/O ?/O 
Tyrion/O wondered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O warhorn/O blew/O ./O 
Haroooooooooooooooooooooooo/O ,/O it/O cried/O ,/O its/O voice/O as/O long/O and/O low/O and/O chilling/O as/O a/O cold/O wind/O from/O the/O north/O ./O 
The/O Lannister/O trumpets/O answered/O ,/O da-DA/O da-DA/O da/O -/O DAAAAAAAAA/LOCATION ,/O brazen/O and/O defiant/O ,/O yet/O it/O seemed/O to/O Tyrion/LOCATION that/O they/O sounded/O somehow/O smaller/O ,/O more/O anxious/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O a/O fluttering/O in/O his/O bowels/O ,/O a/O queasy/O liquid/O feeling/O ;/O he/O hoped/O he/O was/O not/O going/O to/O die/O sick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O the/O horns/O died/O away/O ,/O a/O hissing/O filled/O the/O air/O ;/O a/O vast/O flight/O of/O arrows/O arched/O up/O from/O his/O right/O ,/O where/O the/O archers/O stood/O flanking/O the/O road/O ./O 
The/O northerners/O broke/O into/O a/O run/O ,/O shouting/O as/O they/O came/O ,/O but/O the/O Lannister/O arrows/O fell/O on/O them/O like/O hail/O ,/O hundreds/O of/O arrows/O ,/O thousands/O ,/O and/O shouts/O turned/O to/O screams/O as/O men/O stumbled/O and/O went/O down/O ./O 
By/O then/O a/O second/O flight/O was/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O and/O the/O archers/O were/O fitting/O a/O third/O arrow/O to/O their/O bowstrings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O trumpets/O blared/O again/O ,/O da-DAAA/O da-DAAA/O da-DA/O da-DA/O daDAAAAAAA/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON waved/O his/O huge/O sword/O and/O bellowed/O a/O command/O ,/O and/O a/O thousand/O other/O voices/O screamed/O back/O at/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON put/O his/O spurs/O to/O his/O horse/O and/O added/O one/O more/O voice/O to/O the/O cacophony/O ,/O and/O the/O van/O surged/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O river/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O at/O his/O clansmen/O as/O they/O rode/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O ,/O hew/O to/O the/O river/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O still/O leading/O when/O they/O broke/O a/O canter/O ,/O until/O Chella/PERSON gave/O a/O bloodcurdling/O shriek/O and/O galloped/O past/O him/O ,/O and/O Shagga/PERSON howled/O and/O followed/O ./O 
The/O clansmen/O charged/O after/O them/O ,/O leaving/O Tyrion/O in/O their/O dust/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O crescent/O of/O enemy/O spearmen/O had/O formed/O ahead/O ,/O a/O double/O hedgehog/O bristling/O with/O steel/O ,/O waiting/O behind/O tall/O oaken/O shields/O marked/O with/O the/O sunburst/O of/O Karstark/LOCATION ./O 
Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON was/O the/O first/O to/O reach/O them/O ,/O leading/O a/O wedge/O of/O armored/O veterans/O ./O 
Half/O the/O horses/O shied/O at/O the/O last/O second/O ,/O breaking/O their/O charge/O before/O the/O row/O of/O spears/O ./O 
The/O others/O died/O ,/O sharp/O steel/O points/O ripping/O through/O their/O chests/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON saw/O a/O dozen/O men/O go/O down/O ./O 
The/O Mountain/O 's/O stallion/O reared/O ,/O lashing/O out/O with/O iron-shod/O hooves/O as/O a/O barbed/O spearhead/O raked/O across/O his/O neck/O ./O 
Maddened/O ,/O the/O beast/O lunged/O into/O the/O ranks/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON thrust/O at/O him/O from/O every/O side/O ,/O but/O the/O shield/O wall/O broke/O beneath/O his/O weight/O ./O 
The/O northerners/O stumbled/O away/O from/O the/O animal/O 's/O death/O throes/O ./O 
As/O his/O horse/O fell/O ,/O snorting/O blood/O and/O biting/O with/O his/O last/O red/O breath/O ,/O the/O Mountain/O rose/O untouched/O ,/O laying/O about/O him/O with/O his/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Shagga/O went/O bursting/O through/O the/O gap/O before/O the/O shields/O could/O close/O ,/O other/O Stone/O Crows/O hard/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON shouted/O ,/O \/O ``/O Burned/O Men/O !/O 
Moon/O Brothers/O !/O 
After/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O but/O most/O of/O them/O were/O ahead/O of/O him/O ./O 
He/O glimpsed/O Timett/O son/O of/O Timett/PERSON vault/O free/O as/O his/O mount/O died/O under/O him/O in/O full/O stride/O ,/O saw/O a/O Moon/O Brother/O impaled/O on/O a/O Karstark/O spear/O ,/O watched/O Conn/PERSON 's/O horse/O shatter/O a/O man/O 's/O ribs/O with/O a/O kick/O ./O 
A/O flight/O of/O arrows/O descended/O on/O them/O ;/O where/O they/O came/O from/O he/O could/O not/O say/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O but/O they/O fell/O on/O Stark/O and/O Lannister/O alike/O ,/O rattling/O off/O armor/O or/O finding/O flesh/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON lifted/O his/O shield/O and/O hid/O beneath/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O hedgehog/O was/O crumbling/O ,/O the/O northerners/O reeling/O back/O under/O the/O impact/O of/O the/O mounted/O assault/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON saw/O Shagga/PERSON catch/O a/O spearman/O full/O in/O the/O chest/O as/O the/O fool/O came/O on/O at/O a/O run/O ,/O saw/O his/O axe/O shear/O through/O mail/O and/O leather/O and/O muscle/O and/O lungs/O ./O 
The/O man/O was/O dead/O on/O his/O feet/O ,/O the/O axehead/O lodged/O in/O his/O breast/O ,/O yet/O Shagga/PERSON rode/O on/O ,/O cleaving/O a/O shield/O in/O two/O with/O his/O left-hand/O battle-axe/O while/O the/O corpse/O was/O bouncing/O and/O stumbling/O bonelessly/O along/O on/O his/O right/O ./O 
Finally/O the/O dead/O man/O slid/O off/O ./O 
Shagga/PERSON smashed/O the/O two/O axes/O together/O and/O roared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O then/O the/O enemy/O was/O on/O him/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O battle/O shrunk/O to/O the/O few/O feet/O of/O ground/O around/O his/O horse/O ./O 
A/O man-at-arms/O thrust/O at/O his/O chest/O and/O his/O axe/O lashed/O out/O ,/O knocking/O the/O spear/O aside/O ./O 
The/O man/O danced/O back/O for/O another/O try/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON spurred/O his/O horse/O and/O rode/O right/O over/O him/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON was/O surrounded/O by/O three/O foes/O ,/O but/O he/O lopped/O the/O head/O off/O the/O first/O spear/O that/O came/O at/O him/O ,/O and/O raked/O his/O blade/O across/O a/O second/O man/O 's/O face/O on/O his/O backslash/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O thrown/O spear/O came/O hurtling/O at/O Tyrion/LOCATION from/O the/O left/O and/O lodged/O in/O his/O shield/O with/O a/O woody/O chunk/O ./O 
He/O wheeled/O and/O raced/O after/O the/O thrower/O ,/O but/O the/O man/O raised/O his/O own/O shield/O over/O his/O head/O ./O 
Tyrion/O circled/O around/O him/O ,/O raining/O axe/O blows/O down/O on/O the/O wood/O ./O 
Chips/O of/O oak/O went/O flying/O ,/O until/O the/O northerner/O lost/O his/O feet/O and/O slipped/O ,/O failing/O flat/O on/O his/O back/O with/O his/O shield/O on/O top/O of/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O below/O the/O reach/O of/O Tyrion/O 's/O axe/O and/O it/O was/O too/O much/O bother/O to/O dismount/O ,/O so/O he/O left/O him/O there/O and/O rode/O after/O another/O man/O ,/O taking/O him/O from/O behind/O with/O a/O sweeping/O downcut/O that/O sent/O a/O jolt/O of/O impact/O up/O his/O arm/O ./O 
That/O won/O him/O a/O moment/O 's/O respite/O ./O 
Reining/O up/O ,/O he/O looked/O for/O the/O river/O ./O 
There/O it/O was/O ,/O off/O to/O the/O right/O ./O 
Somehow/O he/O had/O gotten/O turned/O around/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O Burned/O Man/O rode/O past/O ,/O slumped/O against/O his/O horse/O ./O 
A/O spear/O had/O entered/O his/O belly/O and/O come/O out/O through/O his/O back/O ./O 
He/O was/O past/O any/O help/O ,/O but/O when/O Tyrion/PERSON saw/O one/O of/O the/O northerners/O run/O up/O and/O make/O a/O grab/O for/O his/O reins/O ,/O he/O charged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O quarry/O met/O him/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
He/O was/O tall/O and/O spare/O ,/O wearing/O a/O long/O chainmail/O hauberk/O and/O gauntlets/O of/O lobstered/O steel/O ,/O but/O he/O 'd/O lost/O his/O helm/O and/O blood/O ran/O down/O into/O his/O eyes/O from/O a/O gash/O across/O his/O forehead/O ./O 
Tyrion/O aimed/O a/O swipe/O at/O his/O face/O ,/O but/O the/O tall/O man/O slammed/O it/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O in/O a/O circle/O as/O Tyrion/O rode/O around/O him/O ,/O hacking/O at/O his/O head/O and/O shoulders/O ./O 
Steel/O rang/O on/O steel/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/LOCATION soon/O realized/O that/O the/O tall/O man/O was/O quicker/O and/O stronger/O than/O he/O was/O ./O 
Where/O in/O the/O seven/O hells/O was/O Bronn/LOCATION ?/O 
\/O ``/O Die/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O grunted/O ,/O chopping/O at/O him/O savagely/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON barely/O got/O his/O shield/O up/O in/O time/O ,/O and/O the/O wood/O seemed/O to/O explode/O inward/O under/O the/O force/O of/O the/O blow/O ./O 
The/O shattered/O pieces/O fell/O away/O from/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Die/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O swordsman/O bellowed/O ,/O shoving/O in/O close/O and/O whanging/O Tyrion/O across/O the/O temple/O so/O hard/O his/O head/O rang/O ./O 
The/O blade/O made/O a/O hideous/O scraping/O sound/O as/O he/O drew/O it/O back/O over/O the/O steel/O ./O 
The/O tall/O man/O grinned/O .../O until/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O destrier/O bit/O ,/O quick/O as/O a/O snake/O ,/O laying/O his/O cheek/O bare/O to/O the/O bone/O ./O 
Then/O he/O screamed/O ./O 
Tyrion/O buried/O his/O axe/O in/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O did/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O he/O wrenched/O the/O blade/O free/O ,/O he/O heard/O a/O shout/O ./O 
`/O Eddard/O !/O 
\/O ''/O a/O voice/O rang/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O Eddard/O and/O Winterfell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O came/O thundering/O down/O on/O him/O ,/O swinging/O the/O spiked/O ball/O of/O a/O morningstar/O around/O his/O head/O ./O 
Their/O warhorses/O slammed/O together/O before/O Tyrion/O could/O so/O much/O as/O open/O his/O mouth/O to/O shout/O for/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
His/O right/O elbow/O exploded/O with/O pain/O as/O the/O spikes/O punched/O ''/O ,/O ``/O through/O the/O thin/O metal/O around/O the/O joint/O ./O 
His/O axe/O was/O gone/O ,/O as/O fast/O as/O that/O ./O 
He/O clawed/O for/O his/O sword/O ,/O but/O the/O morningstar/O was/O circling/O again/O ,/O coming/O at/O his/O face/O ./O 
A/O sickening/O crunch/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O falling/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O recall/O hitting/O the/O ground/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O looked/O up/O there/O was/O only/O sky/O above/O him/O ./O 
He/O rolled/O onto/O his/O side/O and/O tried/O to/O find/O his/O feet/O ,/O but/O pain/O shuddered/O through/O him/O and/O the/O world/O throbbed/O ./O 
The/O knight/O who/O had/O felled/O him/O drew/O up/O above/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O the/O Imp/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O boomed/O down/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O mine/O ./O 
Do/O you/O yield/O ,/O Lannister/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Tyrion/O thought/O ,/O but/O the/O word/O caught/O in/O his/O throat/O ./O 
He/O made/O a/O croaking/O sound/O and/O fought/O his/O way/O to/O his/O knees/O ,/O fumbling/O for/O a/O weapon/O ./O 
His/O sword/O ,/O his/O dirk/O ,/O anything/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O yield/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O loomed/O overhead/O on/O his/O armored/O warhorse/O ./O 
Man/O and/O horse/O both/O seemed/O immense/O ./O 
The/O spiked/O ball/O swung/O in/O a/O lazy/O circle/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON 's/O hands/O were/O numb/O ,/O his/O vision/O blurred/O ,/O his/O scabbard/O empty/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yield/O or/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O knight/O declared/O ,/O his/O flail/O whirling/O faster/O and/O faster/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O lurched/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O driving/O his/O head/O into/O the/O horse/O 's/O belly/O ./O 
The/O animal/O gave/O a/O hideous/O scream/O and/O reared/O ./O 
It/O tried/O to/O twist/O away/O from/O the/O agony/O ,/O a/O shower/O of/O blood/O and/O viscera/O poured/O down/O over/O Tyrion/ORGANIZATION 's/O face/O ,/O and/O the/O horse/O fell/O like/O an/O avalanche/O ./O 
The/O next/O he/O knew/O ,/O his/O visor/O was/O packed/O with/O mud/O and/O something/O was/O crushing/O his/O foot/O ./O 
He/O wriggled/O free/O ,/O his/O throat/O so/O tight/O he/O could/O scarce/O talk/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O yield/O .../O \/O ''/O he/O managed/O to/O croak/O faintly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O moaned/O ,/O thick/O with/O pain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O scraped/O the/O mud/O off/O his/O helm/O so/O he/O could/O see/O again/O ./O 
The/O horse/O had/O fallen/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O onto/O its/O rider/O ./O 
The/O knight/O 's/O leg/O was/O trapped/O ,/O the/O arm/O he/O 'd/O used/O to/O break/O his/O fall/O twisted/O at/O a/O grotesque/O angle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yield/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O repeated/O ./O 
Fumbling/O at/O his/O belt/O with/O his/O good/O hand/O ,/O he/O drew/O a/O sword/O and/O flung/O it/O at/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O yield/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dazed/O ,/O the/O dwarf/O knelt/O and/O lifted/O the/O blade/O ./O 
Pain/O hammered/O through/O his/O elbow/O when/O he/O moved/O his/O arm/O ./O 
The/O battle/O seemed/O to/O have/O moved/O beyond/O him/O ./O 
No/O one/O remained/O on/O his/O part/O of/O the/O field/O save/O a/O large/O number/O of/O corpses/O ./O 
Ravens/O were/O already/O circling/O and/O landing/O to/O feed/O ./O 
He/O saw/O that/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON had/O brought/O up/O his/O center/O in/O support/O of/O the/O van/O ;/O his/O huge/O mass/O of/O pikemen/O had/O pushed/O the/O northerners/O back/O against/O the/O hills/O ./O 
They/O were/O struggling/O on/O the/O slopes/O ,/O pikes/O thrusting/O against/O another/O wall/O of/O shields/O ,/O these/O oval/O and/O reinforced/O with/O iron/O studs/O ./O 
As/O he/O watched/O ,/O the/O air/O filled/O with/O arrows/O again/O ,/O and/O the/O men/O behind/O the/O oak/O wall/O crumbled/O beneath/O the/O murderous/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O believe/O you/O are/O losing/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O knight/O under/O the/O horse/O ./O 
The/O man/O made/O no/O reply/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sound/O of/O hooves/O coming/O up/O behind/O him/O made/O him/O whirl/O ,/O though/O he/O could/O scarcely/O lift/O the/O sword/O he/O held/O for/O the/O agony/O in/O his/O elbow/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON reined/O up/O and/O looked/O down/O on/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Small/O use/O you/O turned/O out/O to/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O you/O did/O well/O enough/O on/O your/O own/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O lost/O the/O spike/O off/O your/O helm/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O groped/O at/O the/O top/O of/O the/O greathelm/O ./O 
The/O spike/O had/O snapped/O off/O clean/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O n't/O lost/O it/O ./O 
I/O know/O just/O where/O it/O is/O ./O 
Do/O you/O see/O my/O horse/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O they/O found/O it/O ,/O the/O trumpets/O had/O sounded/O again/O and/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O reserve/O came/O sweeping/O up/O along/O the/O river/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON watched/O his/O father/O fly/O past/O ,/O the/O crimson/O -/O and-go/O Id/O banner/O of/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lannister/O rippling/O over/O his/O head/O as/O he/O thundered/O across/O the/O field/O ./O 
Five/O hundred/O knights/O surrounded/O him/O ,/O sunlight/O flashing/O off/O the/O points/O of/O their/O lances/O ./O 
The/O remnants/O of/O the/O Stark/O lines/O shattered/O like/O glass/O beneath/O the/O hammer/O of/O their/O charge/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O With/O his/O elbow/O swollen/O and/O throbbing/O inside/O his/O armor/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON made/O no/O attempt/O to/O join/O the/O slaughter/O ./O 
He/O and/O Bronn/LOCATION went/O looking/O for/O his/O men/O ./O 
Many/O he/O found/O among/O the/O dead/O ./O 
Ulf/PERSON son/PERSON of/PERSON Umar/PERSON lay/O in/O a/O pool/O of/O congealing/O blood/O ,/O his/O arm/O gone/O at/O the/O elbow/O ,/O a/O dozen/O of/O his/O Moon/O Brothers/O sprawled/O around/O him/O ./O 
Shagga/PERSON was/O slumped/O beneath/O a/O tree/O ,/O riddled/O with/O arrows/O ,/O Conn/PERSON 's/O head/O in/O his/O lap/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON thought/O they/O were/O both/O dead/O ,/O but/O as/O he/O dismounted/O ,/O Shagga/PERSON opened/O his/O eyes/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O They/O have/O killed/O Conn/PERSON son/O of/O Coratt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Handsome/O Conn/O had/O no/O mark/O but/O for/O the/O red/O stain/O over/O his/O breast/O ,/O where/O the/O spear/O thrust/O had/O killed/O him/O ./O 
When/O Bronn/PERSON pulled/O Shagga/PERSON to/O his/O feet/O ,/O the/O big/O man/O seemed/O to/O notice/O the/O arrows/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
He/O plucked/O them/O out/O one/O by/O one/O ,/O cursing/O the/O holes/O they/O had/O made/O in/O his/O layers/O of/O mail/O and/O leather/O ,/O and/O yowling/O like/O a/O babe/O at/O the/O few/O that/O had/O buried/O themselves/O in/O his/O flesh/O ./O 
Chella/PERSON daughter/PERSON of/PERSON Cheyk/PERSON rode/O up/O as/O they/O were/O yanking/O arrows/O out/O of/O Shagga/LOCATION ,/O and/O showed/O them/O four/O ears/O she/O had/O taken/O ./O 
Timett/O they/O discovered/O looting/O the/O bodies/O of/O the/O slain/O with/O his/O Burned/O Men/O ./O 
Of/O the/O three/O hundred/O clansmen/O who/O had/O ridden/O to/O battle/O behind/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O perhaps/O half/O had/O survived/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O left/O the/O living/O to/O look/O after/O the/O dead/O ,/O sent/O Bronn/PERSON to/O take/O charge/O of/O his/O captive/O knight/O ,/O and/O went/O alone/O in/O search/O of/O his/O father/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON was/O seated/O by/O the/O river/O ,/O sipping/O wine/O from/O a/O jeweled/O cup/O as/O his/O squire/O undid/O the/O fastenings/O on/O his/O breastplate/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O fine/O victory/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O when/O he/O saw/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O wild/O men/O fought/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O father/O 's/O eyes/O were/O on/O him/O ,/O pale/O green/O flecked/O with/O gold/O ,/O so/O cool/O they/O gave/O Tyrion/PERSON a/O chill/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O that/O surprise/O you/O ,/O Father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O it/O upset/O your/O plans/O ?/O 
We/O were/O supposed/O to/O be/O butchered/O ,/O were/O we/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON drained/O his/O cup/O ,/O his/O face/O expressionless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O put/O the/O least/O disciplined/O men/O on/O the/O left/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
I/O anticipated/O that/O they/O would/O break/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON is/O a/O green/O boy/O ,/O more/O like/O to/O be/O brave/O than/O wise/O ./O 
I/O 'd/O hoped/O that/O if/O he/O saw/O our/O left/O collapse/O ,/O he/O might/O plunge/O into/O the/O gap/O ,/O eager/O for/O a/O rout/O ./O 
Once/O he/O was/O fully/O committed/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON 's/O pikes/O would/O wheel/O and/O take/O him/O in/O the/O flank/O ,/O driving/O him/O into/O the/O river/O while/O I/O brought/O up/O the/O reserve/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O thought/O it/O best/O to/O place/O me/O in/O the/O midst/O of/O this/O carnage/O ,/O yet/O keep/O me/O ignorant/O of/O your/O plans/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O feigned/O rout/O is/O less/O convincing/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O am/O not/O inclined/O to/O trust/O my/O plans/O to/O a/O man/O who/O consorts/O with/O sellswords/O and/O savages/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O pity/O my/O savages/O ruined/O your/O dance/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O pulled/O off/O his/O steel/O gauntlet/O and/O let/O it/O fall/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O wincing/O at/O the/O pain/O that/O stabbed/O up/O his/O arm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Stark/O boy/O proved/O more/O cautious/O than/O I/O expected/O for/O one/O of/O his/O years/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON admitted/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O a/O victory/O is/O a/O victory/O ./O 
You/O appear/O to/O be/O wounded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O 's/O right/O arm/O was/O soaked/O with/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Good/O of/O you/O to/O notice/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O through/O clenched/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Might/O I/O trouble/O you/O to/O send/O for/O your/O maesters/O ?/O 
Unless/O you/O relish/O the/O notion/O of/O having/O a/O one-armed/O dwarf/O for/O a/O son/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O An/O urgent/O shout/O of/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O turned/O his/O father/O 's/O head/O before/O he/O could/O reply/O ./O 
Tywin/O Lannister/O rose/O to/O his/O feet/O as/O Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON Marbrand/PERSON leapt/O down/O off/O his/O courser/O ./O 
The/O horse/O was/O lathered/O and/O bleeding/O from/O the/O mouth/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON dropped/O to/O one/O knee/O ,/O a/O rangy/O man/O with/O dark/O copper/O hair/O that/O fell/O to/O his/O shoulders/O ,/O armored/O in/O burnished/O bronzed/O steel/O with/O the/O fiery/O tree/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION etched/O black/O on/O his/O breastplate/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O liege/O ,/O we/O have/O taken/O some/O of/O their/O commanders/O ./O 
Lord/O Cerwyn/PERSON ,/O Ser/O Wylis/O Manderly/O ,/O Harrion/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ,/O four/O Freys/O ./O 
Lord/O Hornwood/PERSON is/O dead/O ,/O and/O I/O fear/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON has/O escaped/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O the/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Addam/O hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Stark/O boy/O was/O not/O with/O them/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
They/O say/O he/O crossed/O at/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION with/O the/O great/O part/O of/O his/O horse/O ,/O riding/O hard/O for/O Riverrun/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O green/O boy/O ,/O Tyrion/O remembered/O ,/O more/O like/O to/O be/O brave/O than/O wise/O ./O 
He/O would/O have/O laughed/O ,/O if/O he/O had/O n't/O hurt/O so/O much/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
