-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O the/O battle/O was/O done/O ,/O Dany/PERSON rode/O her/O silver/O through/O the/O fields/O of/O the/O dead/O ./O 
Her/O handmaids/O and/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O came/O after/O ,/O smiling/O and/O jesting/O among/O themselves/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dothraki/O hooves/O had/O torn/O the/O earth/O and/O trampled/O the/O rye/O and/O lentils/O into/O the/O ground/O ,/O while/O arakhs/O and/O arrows/O had/O sown/O a/O terrible/O new/O crop/O and/O watered/O it/O with/O blood/O ./O 
Dying/O horses/O lifted/O their/O heads/O and/O screamed/O at/O her/O as/O she/O rode/O past/O ./O 
Wounded/O men/O moaned/O and/O prayed/O ./O 
Jaqqa/O rhan/O moved/O among/O them/O ,/O the/O mercy/O men/O with/O their/O heavy/O axes/O ,/O taking/O a/O harvest/O of/O heads/O from/O the/O dead/O and/O dying/O alike/O ./O 
After/O them/O would/O scurry/O a/O flock/O of/O small/O girls/O ,/O pulling/O arrows/O from/O the/O corpses/O to/O fill/O their/O baskets/O ./O 
Last/O of/O all/O the/O dogs/O would/O come/O sniffing/O ,/O lean/O and/O hungry/O ,/O the/O feral/O pack/O that/O was/O never/O far/O behind/O the/O khalasar/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sheep/O had/O been/O dead/O longest/O ./O 
There/O seemed/O to/O be/O thousands/O of/O them/O ,/O black/O with/O flies/O ,/O arrow/O shafts/O bristling/O from/O each/O carcass/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON 's/O riders/O had/O done/O that/O ,/O Dany/PERSON knew/O ;/O no/O man/O of/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O khalasar/O would/O be/O such/O a/O fool/O as/O to/O waste/O his/O arrows/O on/O sheep/O when/O there/O were/O shepherds/O yet/O to/O kill/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O town/O was/O afire/O ,/O black/O plumes/O of/O smoke/O roiling/O and/O tumbling/O as/O they/O rose/O into/O a/O hard/O blue/O sky/O ./O 
Beneath/O broken/O walls/O of/O dried/O mud/O ,/O riders/O galloped/O back/O and/O forth/O ,/O swinging/O their/O long/O whips/O as/O they/O herded/O the/O survivors/O from/O the/O smoking/O rubble/O ./O 
The/O women/O and/O children/O of/O Ogo/ORGANIZATION 's/O khalasar/O walked/O with/O a/O sullen/O pride/O ,/O even/O in/O defeat/O and/O bondage/O ;/O they/O were/O slaves/O now/O ,/O but/O they/O seemed/O not/O to/O fear/O it/O ./O 
It/O was/O different/O with/O the/O townsfolk/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON pitied/O them/O ;/O she/O remembered/O what/O terror/O felt/O like/O ./O 
Mothers/O stumbled/O along/O with/O blank/O ,/O dead/O faces/O ,/O pulling/O sobbing/O children/O by/O the/O hand/O ./O 
There/O were/O only/O a/O few/O men/O among/O them/O ,/O cripples/O and/O cowards/O and/O grandfathers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O the/O people/O of/O this/O country/O named/O themselves/O the/O Lhazareen/PERSON ,/O but/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON called/O them/O haesh/O rakhi/O ,/O the/O Lamb/O Men/O ./O 
Once/O Dany/PERSON might/O have/O taken/O them/O for/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O for/O they/O had/O the/O same/O copper/O skin/O and/O almond-shaped/O eyes/O ./O 
Now/O they/O looked/O alien/O to/O her/O ,/O squat/O and/O flat-faced/O ,/O their/O black/O hair/O cropped/O unnaturally/O short/O ./O 
They/O were/O herders/O of/O sheep/O and/O eaters/O of/O vegetables/O ,/O and/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON said/O they/O belonged/O south/O of/O the/O river/O bend/O ./O 
The/O grass/O of/O the/O Dothraki/O sea/O was/O not/O meant/O for/O sheep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON saw/O one/O boy/O bolt/O and/O run/O for/O the/O river/O ./O 
A/O rider/O cut/O him/O off/O and/O turned/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O others/O boxed/O him/O in/O ,/O cracking/O their/O whips/O in/O his/O face/O ,/O running/O him/O this/O way/O and/O that/O ./O 
One/O galloped/O behind/O him/O ,/O lashing/O him/O across/O the/O buttocks/O until/O his/O thighs/O ran/O red/O with/O blood/O ./O 
Another/O snared/O his/O ankle/O with/O a/O lash/O and/O sent/O him/O sprawling/O ./O 
Finally/O ,/O when/O the/O boy/O could/O only/O crawl/O ,/O they/O grew/O bored/O of/O the/O sport/O and/O put/O an/O arrow/O through/O his/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON met/O her/O outside/O the/O shattered/O gate/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O dark/O green/O surcoat/O over/O his/O mail/O ./O 
His/O gauntlets/O ,/O greaves/O ,/O and/O greathelm/O were/O dark/O grey/O steel/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON had/O mocked/O him/O for/O a/O coward/O when/O he/O donned/O his/O armor/O ,/O but/O the/O knight/O had/O spit/O insults/O right/O back/O in/O their/O teeth/O ,/O tempers/O had/O flared/O ,/O longsword/O had/O clashed/O with/O arakh/O ,/O and/O the/O rider/O whose/O taunts/O had/O been/O loudest/O had/O been/O left/O behind/O to/O bleed/O to/O death/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON lifted/O the/O visor/O of/O his/O flat-topped/O greathelm/O as/O he/O rode/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O lord/O husband/O awaits/O you/O within/O the/O town/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON took/O no/O harm/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O few/O cuts/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON answered/O ,/O \/O ``/O nothing/O of/O consequence/O ./O 
He/O slew/O two/O khals/O this/O day/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON first/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O son/O ,/O Fogo/PERSON ,/O who/O became/O khal/O when/O Ogo/ORGANIZATION fell/O ./O 
His/O bloodriders/O cut/O the/O bells/O from/O their/O hair/O ,/O and/O now/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O every/O step/O rings/O louder/O than/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ogo/O and/O his/O son/O had/O shared/O the/O high/O bench/O with/O her/O lord/O husband/O at/O the/O naming/O feast/O where/O Viserys/PERSON had/O been/O crowned/O ,/O but/O that/O was/O in/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O beneath/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION ,/O where/O every/O rider/O was/O a/O brother/O and/O all/O quarrels/O were/O put/O aside/O ./O 
It/O was/O different/O out/O in/O the/O grass/O ./O 
Ogo/ORGANIZATION 's/O khalasar/O had/O been/O attacking/O the/O town/O when/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON caught/O him/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O what/O the/O Lamb/O Men/O had/O thought/O ,/O when/O they/O first/O saw/O the/O dust/O of/O their/O horses/O from/O atop/O those/O cracked/O -/O mud/O walls/O ./O 
Perhaps/O a/O few/O ,/O the/O younger/O and/O more/O foolish/O who/O still/O believed/O that/O the/O gods/O heard/O the/O prayers/O of/O desperate/O men/O ,/O took/O it/O for/O deliverance/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Across/O the/O road/O ,/O a/O girl/O no/O older/O than/O Dany/PERSON was/O sobbing/O in/O a/O high/O thin/O voice/O as/O a/O rider/O shoved/O her/O over/O a/O pile/O of/O corpses/O ,/O facedown/O ,/O and/O thrust/O himself/O inside/O her/O ./O 
Other/O riders/O dismounted/O to/O take/O their/O turns/O ./O 
That/O was/O the/O sort/O of/O deliverance/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON brought/O the/O Lamb/O Men/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O Daenerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON reminded/O herself/O as/O she/O turned/O her/O face/O away/O ./O 
She/O pressed/O her/O lips/O together/O and/O hardened/O her/O heart/O and/O rode/O on/O toward/O the/O gate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Most/O of/O Ogo/ORGANIZATION 's/O riders/O fled/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON was/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Still/O ,/O there/O may/O be/O as/O many/O as/O ten/O thousand/O captives/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Slaves/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON would/O drive/O them/O downriver/O to/O one/O of/O the/O towns/O on/O Slaver/O 's/O Bay/LOCATION ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O cry/O ,/O but/O she/O told/O herself/O that/O she/O must/O be/O strong/O ./O 
This/O is/O war/O ,/O this/O is/O what/O it/O looks/O like/O ,/O this/O is/O the/O price/O of/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O told/O the/O khal/O he/O ought/O to/O make/O for/O Meereen/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 'll/O pay/O a/O better/O price/O than/O he/O 'd/O get/O from/O a/O slaving/O caravan/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON writes/O that/O they/O had/O a/O plague/O last/O year/O ,/O so/O the/O brothels/O are/O paying/O double/O for/O healthy/O young/O girls/O ,/O and/O triple/O for/O boys/O under/O ten/O ./O 
If/O enough/O children/O survive/O the/O journey/O ,/O the/O gold/O will/O buy/O us/O all/O the/O ships/O we/O need/O ,/O and/O hire/O men/O to/O sail/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Behind/O them/O ,/O the/O girl/O being/O raped/O made/O a/O heartrending/O sound/O ,/O a/O long/O sobbing/O wail/O that/O went/O on/O and/O on/O and/O on/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON 's/O hand/O clenched/O hard/O around/O the/O reins/O ,/O and/O she/O turned/O the/O silver/O 's/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Make/O them/O stop/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O sounded/O perplexed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O heard/O my/O words/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O spoke/O to/O her/O khas/O in/O the/O harsh/O accents/O of/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhogo/O ,/O Quaro/O ,/O you/O will/O aid/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
I/O want/O no/O rape/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O warriors/O exchanged/O a/O baffled/O look/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON spurred/O his/O horse/O closer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O have/O a/O gentle/O heart/O ,/O but/O you/O do/O not/O understand/O ./O 
This/O is/O how/O it/O has/O always/O been/O ./O 
Those/O men/O have/O shed/O blood/O for/O the/O khal/O ./O 
Now/O they/O claim/O their/O reward/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Across/O the/O road/O ,/O the/O girl/O was/O still/O crying/O ,/O her/O high/O singsong/O tongue/O strange/O to/O Dany/PERSON 's/O ears/O ./O 
The/O first/O man/O was/O done/O with/O her/O now/O ,/O and/O a/O second/O had/O taken/O his/O place/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O is/O a/O lamb/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Quaro/PERSON said/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O is/O nothing/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
The/O riders/O do/O her/O honor/O ./O 
The/O Lamb/O Men/O lay/O with/O sheep/O ,/O it/O is/O known/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O known/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O handmaid/O Irri/O echoed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O known/O ,/O \/O ''/O agreed/O Jhogo/PERSON ,/O astride/O the/O tall/O grey/O stallion/O that/O Drogo/PERSON had/O given/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O her/O wailing/O offends/O your/O ears/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O Jhogo/PERSON will/O bring/O you/O her/O tongue/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O his/O arakh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O have/O her/O harmed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O claim/O her/O ./O 
Do/O as/O I/O command/O you/O ,/O or/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON will/O know/O the/O reason/O why/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ai/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Jhogo/PERSON replied/O ,/O kicking/O his/O horse/O ./O 
Quaro/PERSON and/O the/O others/O followed/O his/O lead/O ,/O the/O bells/O in/O their/O hair/O chiming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O with/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O gave/O her/O a/O curious/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O your/O brother/O 's/O sister/O ,/O in/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Viserys/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O did/O not/O understand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaegar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O galloped/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON heard/O Jhogo/PERSON shout/O ./O 
The/O rapers/O laughed/O at/O him/O ./O 
One/O man/O shouted/O back/O ./O 
Jhogo/PERSON 's/O arakh/O flashed/O ,/O and/O the/O man/O 's/O head/O went/O tumbling/O from/O his/O shoulders/O ./O 
Laughter/O turned/O to/O curses/O as/O the/O horsemen/O reached/O for/O weapons/O ,/O but/O by/O then/O Quaro/PERSON and/O Aggo/LOCATION and/O Rakharo/PERSON were/O there/O ./O 
She/O saw/O Aggo/PERSON point/O across/O the/O road/O to/O where/O she/O sat/O upon/O her/O silver/O ./O 
The/O riders/O looked/O at/O her/O with/O cold/O black/O eyes/O ./O 
One/O spat/O ./O 
The/O others/O scattered/O to/O their/O mounts/O ,/O muttering/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O All/O the/O while/O the/O man/O atop/O the/O lamb/O girl/O continued/O to/O plunge/O in/O and/O out/O of/O her/O ,/O so/O intent/O on/O his/O pleasure/O that/O he/O seemed/O unaware/O of/O what/O was/O going/O on/O around/O him/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON dismounted/O and/O wrenched/O him/O off/O with/O a/O mailed/O hand/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON went/O sprawling/O in/O the/O mud/O ,/O bounced/O up/O with/O a/O knife/O in/O hand/O ,/O and/O died/O with/O Aggo/PERSON 's/O arrow/O through/O his/O throat/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON pulled/O the/O girl/O off/O the/O pile/O of/O corpses/O and/O wrapped/O her/O in/O his/O blood-spattered/O cloak/O ./O 
He/O led/O her/O across/O the/O road/O to/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O want/O done/O with/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O girl/O was/O trembling/O ,/O her/O eyes/O wide/O and/O vague/O ./O 
Her/O hair/O was/O matted/O with/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Doreah/O ,/O see/O to/O her/O hurts/O ./O 
You/O do/O not/O have/O a/O rider/O 's/O look/O ,/O perhaps/O she/O will/O not/O fear/O you/O ./O 
The/O rest/O ,/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O urged/O the/O silver/O through/O the/O broken/O wooden/O gate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O worse/O inside/O the/O town/O ./O 
Many/O of/O the/O houses/O were/O afire/O ,/O and/O the/O jaqqa/O rhan/O had/O been/O about/O their/O grisly/O work/O ./O 
Headless/O corpses/O filled/O the/O narrow/O ,/O twisty/O lanes/O ./O 
They/O passed/O other/O women/O being/O raped/O ./O 
Each/O time/O Dany/PERSON reined/O up/O ,/O sent/O her/O khas/O to/O make/O an/O end/O to/O it/O ,/O and/O claimed/O the/O victim/O as/O slave/O ./O 
One/O of/O them/O ,/O a/O thick-bodied/O ,/O flat-nosed/O woman/O of/O forty/O years/O ,/O blessed/O Dany/PERSON haltingly/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ,/O but/O from/O the/O others/O she/O got/O only/O flat/O black/O stares/O ./O 
They/O were/O suspicious/O of/O her/O ,/O she/O realized/O with/O sadness/O ;/O afraid/O that/O she/O had/O saved/O them/O for/O some/O worse/O fate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O can/O not/O claim/O them/O all/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O the/O fourth/O time/O they/O stopped/O ,/O while/O the/O warriors/O of/O her/O khas/O herded/O her/O new/O slaves/O behind/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O khaleesi/O ,/O heir/O to/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O for/O you/O to/O tell/O me/O what/O I/O can/O not/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Across/O the/O city/O ,/O a/O building/O collapsed/O in/O a/O great/O gout/O of/O fire/O and/O smoke/O ,/O and/O she/O heard/O distant/O screams/O and/O the/O wailing/O of/O frightened/O children/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O found/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON seated/O before/O a/O square/O windowless/O temple/O with/O thick/O mud/O walls/O and/O a/O bulbous/O dome/O like/O some/O immense/O brown/O onion/O ./O 
Beside/O him/O was/O a/O pile/O of/O heads/O taller/O than/O he/O was/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O short/O arrows/O of/O the/O Lamb/O Men/O stuck/O through/O the/O meat/O of/O his/O upper/O arm/O ,/O and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O blood/O covered/O the/O left/O side/O of/O his/O bare/O chest/O like/O a/O splash/O of/O paint/O ./O 
His/O three/O bloodriders/O were/O with/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jhiqui/PERSON helped/O Dany/PERSON dismount/O ;/O she/O had/O grown/O clumsy/O as/O her/O belly/O grew/O larger/O and/O heavier/O ./O 
She/O knelt/O before/O the/O khal/O \/O ``/O My/O sun-and-stars/O is/O wounded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O arakh/O cut/O was/O wide/O but/O shallow/O ;/O his/O left/O nipple/O was/O gone/O ,/O and/O a/O flap/O of/O bloody/O flesh/O and/O skin/O dangled/O from/O his/O chest/O like/O a/O wet/O rag/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O scratch/O ,/O moon/O of/O life/O ,/O from/O arakh/O of/O one/O bloodrider/O to/O Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON said/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O kill/O him/O for/O it/O ,/O and/O Ogo/ORGANIZATION too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O his/O head/O ,/O the/O bells/O in/O his/O braid/O ringing/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O Ogo/O you/O hear/O ,/O and/O Fogo/PERSON his/O khalakka/O ,/O who/O was/O khal/O when/O I/O slew/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O man/O can/O stand/O before/O the/O sun/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O father/O of/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O mounted/O warrior/O rode/O up/O and/O vaulted/O from/O his/O saddle/O ./O 
He/O spoke/O to/O Haggo/LOCATION ,/O a/O stream/O of/O angry/O Dothraki/PERSON too/O fast/O for/O Dany/PERSON to/O understand/O ./O 
The/O huge/O bloodrider/O gave/O her/O a/O heavy/O look/O before/O he/O turned/O to/O his/O khal/O \/O ``/O This/O one/O is/O Mago/PERSON ,/O who/O rides/O in/O the/O khas/O of/O Ko/O Jhaqo/O ./O 
He/O says/O the/O khaleesi/O has/O taken/O his/O spoils/O ,/O a/O daughter/O of/O the/O lambs/O who/O was/O his/O to/O mount/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O face/O was/O still/O and/O hard/O ,/O but/O his/O black/O eyes/O were/O curious/O as/O they/O went/O to/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O the/O truth/O of/O this/O ,/O moon/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O commanded/O in/O Dothraki/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O what/O she/O had/O done/O ,/O in/O his/O own/O tongue/O so/O the/O khal/O would/O understand/O her/O better/O ,/O her/O words/O simple/O and/O direct/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O was/O done/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON was/O frowning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O way/O of/O war/O ./O 
These/O women/O are/O our/O slaves/O now/O ,/O to/O do/O with/O as/O we/O please/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O pleases/O me/O to/O hold/O them/O safe/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O wondering/O if/O she/O had/O dared/O too/O much/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O your/O warriors/O would/O mount/O these/O women/O ,/O let/O them/O take/O them/O gently/O and/O keep/O them/O for/O wives/O ./O 
Give/O them/O places/O in/O the/O khalasar/O and/O let/O them/O bear/O you/O sons/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Qotho/O was/O ever/O the/O crudest/O of/O the/O bloodriders/O ./O 
It/O was/O he/O who/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O the/O horse/O breed/O with/O the/O sheep/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Something/O in/O his/O tone/O reminded/O her/O of/O Viserys/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON turned/O on/O him/O angrily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O dragon/O feeds/O on/O horse/O and/O sheep/O alike/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O how/O fierce/O she/O grows/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O my/O son/O inside/O her/O ,/O the/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O ,/O filling/O her/O with/O his/O fire/O ./O 
Ride/O slowly/O ,/O Ootho/O .../O if/O the/O mother/O does/O not/O burn/O you/O where/O you/O sit/O ,/O the/O son/O will/O trample/O you/O into/O the/O mud/O ./O 
And/O you/O ,/O Mago/PERSON ,/O hold/O your/O tongue/O and/O find/O another/O lamb/O to/O mount/O ./O 
These/O belong/O to/O my/O khaleesi/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O started/O to/O reach/O out/O a/O hand/O to/O Daenerys/PERSON ,/O but/O as/O he/O lifted/O his/O arm/O Drogo/PERSON grimaced/O in/O sudden/O pain/O and/O turned/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON could/O almost/O feel/O his/O agony/O ./O 
The/O wounds/O were/O worse/O than/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O led/O her/O to/O believe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O the/O healers/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O demanded/O ./O 
The/O khalasar/O had/O two/O sorts/O :/O barren/O women/O and/O eunuch/O slaves/O ./O 
The/O herbwomen/O dealt/O in/O potions/O and/O spells/O ,/O the/O eunuchs/O in/O knife/O ,/O needle/O ,/O and/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O do/O they/O not/O attend/O the/O khal/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O khal/O sent/O the/O hairless/O men/O away/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O old/O Cohollo/PERSON assured/O her/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON saw/O the/O bloodrider/O had/O taken/O a/O wound/O himself/O ;/O a/O deep/O gash/O in/O his/O left/O shoulder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Many/O riders/O are/O hurt/O ,/O \/O ''/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON said/O stubbornly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O them/O be/O healed/O first/O ./O 
This/O arrow/O is/O no/O more/O than/O the/O bite/O of/O a/O fly/O ,/O this/O little/O cut/O only/O a/O new/O scar/O to/O boast/O of/O to/O my/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON could/O see/O the/O muscles/O in/O his/O chest/O where/O the/O skin/O had/O been/O cut/O away/O ./O 
A/O trickle/O of/O blood/O ran/O from/O the/O arrow/O that/O pierced/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O for/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON to/O wait/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O proclaimed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhogo/O ,/O seek/O out/O these/O eunuchs/O and/O bring/O them/O here/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Silver/O Lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O woman/O 's/O voice/O said/O behind/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O help/O the/O Great/O Rider/O with/O his/O hurts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON turned/O her/O head/O ./O 
The/O speaker/O was/O one/O of/O the/O slaves/O she/O had/O claimed/O ,/O the/O heavy/O ,/O flat-nosed/O woman/O who/O had/O blessed/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O khal/O needs/O no/O help/O from/O women/O who/O lie/O with/O sheep/O ,/O \/O ''/O barked/O Qotho/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Aggo/O ,/O cut/O out/O her/O tongue/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Aggo/PERSON grabbed/O her/O hair/O and/O pressed/O a/O knife/O to/O her/O throat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON lifted/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
She/O is/O mine/O ./O 
Let/O her/O speak/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Aggo/O looked/O from/O her/O to/O Qotho/LOCATION ./O 
He/O lowered/O his/O knife/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O meant/O no/O wrong/O ,/O fierce/O riders/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O woman/O spoke/O Dothraki/PERSON well/O ./O 
The/O robes/O she/O wore/O had/O once/O been/O the/O lightest/O and/O finest/O of/O woolens/O ,/O rich/O with/O embroidery/O ,/O but/O now/O they/O were/O mud/O -/O caked/O and/O bloody/O and/O ripped/O ./O 
She/O clutched/O the/O torn/O cloth/O of/O her/O bodice/O to/O her/O heavy/O breasts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O some/O small/O skill/O in/O the/O healing/O arts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON asked/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O named/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
I/O am/O godswife/O of/O this/O temple/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maegi/O ,/O \/O ''/O grunted/O Haggo/PERSON ,/O fingering/O his/O arakh/O ./O 
His/O look/O was/O dark/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON remembered/O the/O word/O from/O a/O terrifying/O story/O that/O Jhiqui/PERSON had/O told/O her/O one/O night/O by/O the/O cookfire/O ./O 
A/O maegi/O was/O a/O woman/O who/O lay/O with/O demons/O and/O practiced/O the/O blackest/O of/O sorceries/O ,/O a/O vile/O thing/O ,/O evil/O and/O soulless/O ,/O who/O came/O to/O men/O in/O the/O dark/O of/O night/O and/O sucked/O life/O and/O strength/O from/O their/O bodies/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O a/O healer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O healer/O of/O sheeps/O ,/O \/O ''/O sneered/O Qotho/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O I/O say/O kill/O this/O maegi/O and/O wait/O for/O the/O hairless/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON ignored/O the/O bloodrider/O 's/O outburst/O ./O 
This/O old/O ,/O homely/O ,/O thickbodied/O woman/O did/O not/O look/O like/O a/O maegi/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O did/O you/O learn/O your/O healing/O ,/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O mother/O was/O godswife/O before/O me/O ,/O and/O taught/O me/O all/O the/O songs/O and/O spells/O most/O pleasing/O to/O the/O Great/O Shepherd/O ,/O and/O how/O to/O make/O the/O sacred/O smokes/O and/O ointments/O from/O leaf/O and/O root/O and/O berry/O ./O 
When/O I/O was/O younger/O and/O more/O fair/O ,/O I/O went/O in/O caravan/O to/O Asshai/LOCATION by/O the/O Shadow/O ,/O to/O learn/O from/O their/O mages/O ./O 
Ships/O from/O many/O lands/O come/O to/O Asshai/LOCATION ,/O so/O I/O lingered/O long/O to/O study/O the/O healing/O ways/O of/O distant/O peoples/O ./O 
A/O moonsinger/O of/O the/O Jogos/O Nhai/O gifted/O me/O with/O her/O birthing/O songs/O ,/O a/O woman/O of/O your/O own/O riding/O people/O taught/O me/O the/O magics/O of/O grass/O and/O corn/O and/O horse/O ,/O and/O a/O maester/O from/O the/O Sunset/O Lands/O opened/O a/O body/O for/O me/O and/O showed/O me/O all/O the/O secrets/O that/O hide/O beneath/O the/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O Mormont/O spoke/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O maester/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Marwyn/PERSON ,/O he/O named/O himself/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O woman/O replied/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ./O 
\/O ``/O From/O the/O sea/O ./O 
Beyond/O the/O sea/O ./O 
The/O Seven/O Lands/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
Sunset/O Lands/O ./O 
Where/O men/O are/O iron/O and/O dragons/O rule/O ./O 
He/O taught/O me/O this/O speech/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O maester/O in/O Asshai/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON mused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O Godswife/O ,/O what/O did/O this/O Marwyn/PERSON wear/O about/O his/O neck/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O chain/O so/O tight/O it/O was/O like/O to/O choke/O him/O ,/O Iron/O Lord/O ,/O with/O links/O of/O many/O metals/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O knight/O looked/O at/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O a/O man/O trained/O in/O the/O Citadel/O of/O Oldtown/LOCATION wears/O such/O a/O chain/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O such/O men/O do/O know/O much/O of/O healing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O should/O you/O want/O to/O help/O my/O khal/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O men/O are/O one/O flock/O ,/O or/O so/O we/O are/O taught/O ,/O \/O ''/O replied/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Great/O Shepherd/O sent/O me/O to/O earth/O to/O heal/O his/O lambs/O ,/O wherever/O I/O might/O find/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Qotho/O gave/O her/O a/O stinging/O slap/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O no/O sheep/O ,/O maegi/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O angrily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O is/O mine/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O have/O her/O harmed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON grunted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O arrow/O must/O come/O out/O ,/O Qotho/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Great/O Rider/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON answered/O ,/O touching/O her/O bruised/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O your/O breast/O must/O be/O washed/O and/O sewn/O ,/O lest/O the/O wound/O fester/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O it/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON commanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Great/O Rider/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O woman/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O my/O tools/O and/O potions/O are/O inside/O the/O god/O 's/O house/O ,/O where/O the/O healing/O powers/O are/O strongest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O carry/O you/O ,/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Haggo/PERSON offered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON waved/O him/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O need/O no/O man/O 's/O help/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O in/O a/O voice/O proud/O and/O hard/O ./O 
He/O stood/O ,/O unaided/O ,/O towering/O over/O them/O all/O ./O 
A/O fresh/O wave/O of/O blood/O ran/O down/O his/O breast/O ,/O from/O where/O Ogo/ORGANIZATION 's/O arakh/O had/O cut/O off/O his/O nipple/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON moved/O quickly/O to/O his/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O no/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ,/O \/O ``/O so/O you/O may/O lean/O on/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON put/O a/O huge/O hand/O on/O her/O shoulder/O ./O 
She/O took/O some/O of/O his/O weight/O as/O they/O walked/O toward/O the/O great/O mud/O temple/O ./O 
The/O three/O bloodriders/O followed/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jo/PERSON rah/O and/O the/O warriors/O of/O her/O khas/O to/O guard/O the/O entrance/O and/O make/O certain/O no/O one/O set/O the/O building/O afire/O while/O they/O were/O still/O inside/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O passed/O through/O a/O series/O of/O anterooms/O ,/O into/O the/O high/O central/O chamber/O under/O the/O onion/O ./O 
Faint/O light/O shone/O down/O through/O hidden/O windows/O above/O ./O 
A/O few/O torches/O burnt/O smokily/O from/O sconces/O on/O the/O walls/O ./O 
Sheepskins/O were/O scattered/O across/O the/O mud/O floor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON said/O ,/O pointing/O to/O the/O altar/O ,/O a/O massive/O blue-veined/O stone/O carved/O with/O images/O of/O shepherds/O and/O their/O flocks/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON lay/O upon/O it/O ./O 
The/O old/O woman/O threw/O a/O handful/O of/O dried/O leaves/O onto/O a/O brazier/O ,/O filling/O the/O chamber/O with/O fragrant/O smoke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Best/O if/O you/O wait/O outside/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O the/O rest/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O are/O blood/O of/O his/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cohollo/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O we/O wait/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Qotho/O stepped/O close/O to/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Know/O this/O ,/O wife/O of/O the/O Lamb/O God/O ./O 
Harm/O the/O khal/O and/O you/O suffer/O the/O same/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O his/O skinning/O knife/O and/O showed/O her/O the/O blade/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O will/O do/O no/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON felt/O she/O could/O trust/O this/O old/O ,/O plainfaced/O woman/O with/O her/O flat/O nose/O ;/O she/O had/O saved/O her/O from/O the/O hard/O hands/O of/O her/O rapers/O ,/O after/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O must/O stay/O ,/O then/O help/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON told/O the/O bloodriders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Great/O Rider/O is/O too/O strong/O for/O me/O ./O 
Hold/O him/O still/O while/O I/O draw/O the/O arrow/O from/O his/O flesh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O let/O the/O rags/O of/O her/O gown/O fall/O to/O her/O waist/O as/O she/O opened/O a/O carved/O chest/O ,/O and/O busied/O herself/O with/O bottles/O and/O boxes/O ,/O knives/O and/O needles/O ./O 
When/O she/O was/O ready/O ,/O she/O broke/O off/O the/O barbed/O arrowhead/O and/O pulled/O out/O the/O shaft/O ,/O chanting/O in/O the/O singsong/O tongue/O of/O the/O Lhazareen/O ./O 
She/O heated/O a/O flagon/O of/O wine/O to/O boiling/O on/O the/O brazier/O ,/O and/O poured/O it/O over/O his/O wounds/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON cursed/O her/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O move/O ./O 
She/O bound/O the/O arrow/O wound/O with/O a/O plaster/O of/O wet/O leaves/O and/O turned/O to/O the/O gash/O on/O his/O breast/O ,/O smearing/O it/O ''/O ,/O ``/O with/O a/O pale/O green/O paste/O before/O she/O pulled/O the/O flap/O of/O skin/O back/O in/O place/O ./O 
The/O khal/O ground/O his/O teeth/O together/O and/O swallowed/O a/O scream/O ./O 
The/O godswife/O took/O out/O a/O silver/O needle/O and/O a/O bobbin/O of/O silk/O thread/O and/O began/O to/O close/O the/O flesh/O ./O 
When/O she/O was/O done/O she/O painted/O the/O skin/O with/O red/O ointment/O ,/O covered/O it/O with/O more/O leaves/O ,/O and/O bound/O the/O breast/O in/O a/O ragged/O piece/O of/O lambskin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O say/O the/O prayers/O I/O give/O you/O and/O keep/O the/O lambskin/O in/O place/O for/O ten/O days/O and/O ten/O nights/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O will/O be/O fever/O ,/O and/O itching/O ,/O and/O a/O great/O scar/O when/O the/O healing/O is/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON sat/O ,/O bells/O ringing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O sing/O of/O my/O scars/O ,/O sheep/O woman/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O flexed/O his/O arm/O and/O scowled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Drink/O neither/O wine/O nor/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O cautioned/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pain/O you/O will/O have/O ,/O but/O you/O must/O keep/O your/O body/O strong/O to/O fight/O the/O poison/O spirits/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O khal/O ,/O \/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O spit/O on/O pain/O and/O drink/O what/O I/O like/O ./O 
Cohollo/O ,/O bring/O my/O vest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O older/O man/O hastened/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Before/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O to/O the/O ugly/O Lhazareen/O woman/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O heard/O you/O speak/O of/O birthing/O songs/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O every/O secret/O of/O the/O bloody/O bed/O ,/O Silver/O Lady/O ,/O nor/O have/O I/O ever/O lost/O a/O babe/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O time/O is/O near/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O have/O you/O attend/O me/O when/O he/O comes/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Moon/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O you/O do/O not/O ask/O a/O slave/O ,/O you/O tell/O her/O ./O 
She/O will/O do/O as/O you/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O jumped/O down/O from/O the/O altar/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O my/O blood/O ./O 
The/O stallions/O call/O ,/O this/O place/O is/O ashes/O ./O 
It/O is/O time/O to/O ride/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Haggo/PERSON followed/O the/O khal/O from/O the/O temple/O ,/O but/O Qotho/PERSON lingered/O long/O enough/O to/O favor/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON with/O a/O stare/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O ,/O maegi/O ,/O as/O the/O khal/O fares/O ,/O so/O shall/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O rider/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O woman/O answered/O him/O ,/O gathering/O up/O her/O jars/O and/O bottles/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Great/O Shepherd/O guards/O the/O flock/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
