-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O dreamt/O an/O old/O dream/O ,/O of/O three/O knights/O in/O white/O cloaks/O ,/O and/O a/O tower/O long/O fallen/O ,/O and/O Lyanna/PERSON in/O her/O bed/O of/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O dream/O his/O friends/O rode/O with/O him/O ,/O as/O they/O had/O in/O life/O ./O 
Proud/O Martyn/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ,/O Jory/PERSON 's/O father/O ;/O faithful/O Theo/PERSON Wull/PERSON ;/O Ethan/PERSON Glover/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O been/O Brandon/PERSON 's/O squire/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Mark/PERSON Ryswell/PERSON ,/O soft/O of/O speech/O and/O gentle/O of/O heart/O ;/O the/O crannogman/O ,/O Howland/PERSON Reed/PERSON ;/O Lord/O Dustin/PERSON on/O his/O great/O red/O stallion/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O known/O their/O faces/O as/O well/O as/O he/O knew/O his/O own/O once/O ,/O but/O the/O years/O leech/O at/O a/O man/O 's/O memories/O ,/O even/O those/O he/O has/O vowed/O never/O to/O forget/O ./O 
In/O the/O dream/O they/O were/O only/O shadows/O ,/O grey/O wraiths/O on/O horses/O made/O of/O mist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O were/O seven/O ,/O facing/O three/O ./O 
In/O the/O dream/O as/O it/O had/O been/O in/O life/O ./O 
Yet/O these/O were/O no/O ordinary/O three/O ./O 
They/O waited/O before/O the/O round/O tower/O ,/O the/O red/O mountains/O of/O Dome/LOCATION at/O their/O backs/O ,/O their/O white/O cloaks/O blowing/O in/O the/O wind/O ./O 
And/O these/O were/O no/O shadows/O ;/O their/O faces/O burned/O clear/O ,/O even/O now/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O the/O Sword/O of/O the/O Morning/O ,/O had/O a/O sad/O smile/O on/O his/O lips/O ./O 
The/O hilt/O of/O the/O greatsword/O Dawn/PERSON poked/O up/O over/O his/O right/O shoulder/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Oswell/PERSON Whent/PERSON was/O on/O one/O knee/O ,/O sharpening/O his/O blade/O with/O a/O whetstone/O ./O 
Across/O his/O white-enameled/O helm/O ,/O the/O black/O bat/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION spread/O its/O wings/O ./O 
Between/O them/O stood/O fierce/O old/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON Hightower/PERSON ,/O the/O White/ORGANIZATION Bull/ORGANIZATION ,/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O looked/O for/O you/O on/O the/O Trident/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O to/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O were/O not/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON answered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Woe/O to/O the/O Usurper/O if/O we/O had/O been/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Oswell/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O King/O 's/O Landing/O fell/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON slew/O your/O king/O with/O a/O golden/O sword/O ,/O and/O I/O wondered/O where/O you/O were/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Far/O away/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O or/O Aerys/O would/O yet/O sit/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O and/O our/O false/O brother/O would/O burn/O in/O seven/O hells/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O came/O down/O on/O Storm/O 's/O End/O to/O lift/O the/O siege/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O them/O .../O and/O the/O Lords/ORGANIZATION Tyrell/ORGANIZATION and/O Redwyne/O dipped/O their/O banners/O ,/O and/O all/O their/O knights/O bent/O the/O knee/O to/O pledge/O us/O fealty/O ./O 
I/O was/O certain/O you/O would/O be/O among/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Our/O knees/O do/O not/O bend/O easily/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Willem/PERSON Darry/PERSON is/O fled/O to/O Dragonstone/LOCATION ,/O with/O your/O queen/O and/O Prince/PERSON Viserys/PERSON ./O 
I/O thought/O you/O might/O have/O sailed/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Willem/O is/O a/O good/O man/O and/O true/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Oswell/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O not/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Kingsguard/O does/O not/O flee/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O or/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON ./O 
He/O donned/O his/O helm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O swore/O a/O vow/O ,/O \/O ''/O explained/O old/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O wraiths/O moved/O up/O beside/O him/O ,/O with/O shadow/O swords/O in/O hand/O ./O 
They/O were/O seven/O against/O three/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O now/O it/O begins/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O the/O Sword/O of/O the/O Morning/O ./O 
He/O unsheathed/O Dawn/PERSON and/O held/O it/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
The/O blade/O was/O pale/O as/O milkglass/O ,/O alive/O with/O light/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O with/O sadness/O in/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O it/O ends/O ./O 
\/O ''/O As/O they/O came/O together/O in/O a/O rush/O of/O steel/O and/O shadow/O ,/O he/O could/O hear/O Lyanna/PERSON screaming/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Eddard/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O called/O ./O 
A/O storm/O of/O rose/O petals/O blew/O across/O a/O blood-streaked/O sky/O ,/O as/O blue/O as/O the/O eyes/O of/O death/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lyanna/PERSON called/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O promise/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lya/PERSON ,/O I/O promise/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O man/O echoed/O from/O the/O dark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Groaning/O ,/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON opened/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Moonlight/PERSON streamed/O through/O the/O tall/O windows/O of/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O A/O shadow/O stood/O over/O the/O bed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O .../O how/O long/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O sheets/O were/O tangled/O ,/O his/O leg/O splinted/O and/O plastered/O ./O 
A/O dull/O throb/O of/O pain/O shot/O up/O his/O side/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Six/O days/O and/O seven/O nights/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O voice/O was/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON 's/O ./O 
The/O steward/O held/O a/O cup/O to/O Ned/PERSON 's/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O .../O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O water/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON said/O you/O would/O be/O thirsty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON drank/O ./O 
His/O lips/O were/O parched/O and/O cracked/O ./O 
The/O water/O tasted/O sweet/O as/O honey/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O left/O orders/O ,/O \/O ''/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON told/O him/O when/O the/O cup/O was/O empty/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O speak/O with/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O On/O the/O morrow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O am/O stronger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O could/O not/O face/O Robert/PERSON now/O ./O 
The/O dream/O had/O left/O him/O weak/O as/O a/O kitten/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Poole/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O he/O commanded/O us/O to/O send/O you/O to/O him/O the/O moment/O you/O opened/O your/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O steward/O busied/O himself/O lighting/O a/O bedside/O candle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON cursed/O softly/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O never/O known/O for/O his/O patience/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O him/O I/O 'm/O too/O weak/O to/O come/O to/O him/O ./O 
If/O he/O wishes/O to/O speak/O with/O me/O ,/O I/O should/O be/O pleased/O to/O receive/O him/O here/O ./O 
I/O hope/O you/O wake/O him/O from/O a/O sound/O sleep/O ./O 
And/O summon/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O was/O about/O to/O say/O Jory/PERSON when/O he/O remembered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Summon/O the/O captain/O of/O my/O guard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Alyn/PERSON stepped/O into/O the/O bedchamber/O a/O few/O moments/O after/O the/O steward/O had/O taken/O his/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Poole/PERSON tells/O me/O it/O has/O been/O six/O days/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O must/O know/O how/O things/O stand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O is/O fled/O the/O city/O ,/O \/O ''/O Alyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O talk/O is/O he/O 's/O ridden/O back/O to/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION to/O join/O his/O father/O ./O 
The/O story/O of/O how/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON took/O the/O Imp/O is/O on/O every/O lip/O ./O 
I/O have/O put/O on/O extra/O guards/O ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O does/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON assured/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O daughters/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O have/O been/O with/O you/O every/O day/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Sansa/O prays/O quietly/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON .../O \/O ''/O He/O hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O has/O not/O said/O a/O word/O since/O they/O brought/O you/O back/O ./O 
She/O is/O a/O fierce/O little/O thing/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
I/O have/O never/O seen/O such/O anger/O in/O a/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Whatever/O happens/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O my/O daughters/O kept/O safe/O ./O 
I/O fear/O this/O is/O only/O the/O beginning/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O harm/O will/O come/O to/O them/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Alyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O stake/O my/O life/O on/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jory/PERSON and/O the/O others/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O gave/O them/O over/O to/O the/O silent/O sisters/O ,/O to/O be/O sent/O north/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Jory/PERSON would/O want/O to/O lie/O beside/O his/O grandfather/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O would/O have/O to/O be/O his/O grandfather/O ,/O for/O Jory/PERSON 's/O father/O was/O buried/O far/O to/O the/O south/O ./O 
Martyn/PERSON Cassel/PERSON had/O perished/O with/O the/O rest/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O pulled/O the/O tower/O down/O afterward/O ,/O and/O used/O its/O bloody/O stones/O to/O build/O eight/O cairns/O upon/O the/O ridge/O ./O 
It/O was/O said/O that/O Rhaegar/PERSON had/O named/O that/O place/O the/O tower/O of/O joy/O ,/O but/O for/O Ned/PERSON it/O was/O a/O bitter/O memory/O ./O 
They/O had/O been/O seven/O against/O three/O ,/O yet/O only/O two/O had/O lived/O to/O ride/O away/O ;/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON himself/O and/O the/O little/O crannogman/O ,/O Howland/PERSON Reed/PERSON ./O 
He/O did/O not/O think/O it/O omened/O well/O that/O he/O should/O dream/O that/O dream/O again/O after/O so/O many/O years/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 've/O done/O well/O ,/O Alyn/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON was/O saying/O when/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON returned/O ./O 
The/O steward/O bowed/O low/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O Grace/O is/O without/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O and/O the/O queen/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON pushed/O himself/O up/O higher/O ,/O wincing/O as/O his/O leg/O trembled/O with/O pain/O ./O 
He/O had/O not/O expected/O Cersei/PERSON to/O come/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O bode/O well/O that/O she/O had/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O them/O in/O ,/O and/O leave/O us/O ./O 
What/O we/O have/O to/O say/O should/O not/O go/O beyond/O these/O walls/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Poole/PERSON withdrew/O quietly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON had/O taken/O time/O to/O dress/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O black/O velvet/O doublet/O with/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O Baratheon/PERSON worked/O upon/O the/O breast/O in/O golden/O thread/O ,/O and/O a/O golden/O mantle/O with/O a/O cloak/O of/O black/O and/O gold/O squares/O ./O 
A/O flagon/O of/O wine/O was/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O his/O face/O already/O flushed/O from/O drink/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON entered/O behind/O him/O ,/O a/O jeweled/O tiara/O in/O her/O hair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O pardons/O ./O 
I/O can/O not/O rise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O matter/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O gruffly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Some/O wine/O ?/O 
From/O the/O Arbor/PERSON ./O 
A/O good/O vintage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O small/O cup/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O head/O is/O still/O heavy/O from/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O man/O in/O your/O place/O should/O count/O himself/O fortunate/O that/O his/O head/O is/O still/O on/O his/O shoulders/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O declared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Quiet/O ,/O woman/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON snapped/O ./O 
He/O brought/O Ned/O a/O cup/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O the/O leg/O still/O pain/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
His/O head/O was/O swimming/O ,/O but/O it/O would/O not/O do/O to/O admit/O to/O weakness/O in/O front/O of/O the/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pycelle/PERSON swears/O it/O will/O heal/O clean/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O take/O it/O you/O know/O what/O Catelyn/PERSON has/O done/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON took/O a/O small/O swallow/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O wife/O is/O blameless/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
All/O she/O did/O she/O did/O at/O my/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O pleased/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON grumbled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O By/O what/O right/O do/O you/O dare/O lay/O hands/O on/O my/O blood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON demanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O do/O you/O think/O you/O are/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O her/O with/O icy/O courtesy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Charged/O by/O your/O own/O lord/O husband/O to/O keep/O the/O king/O 's/O peace/O and/O enforce/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O were/O the/O Hand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON began/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O now/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Silence/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O king/O roared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O asked/O him/O a/O question/O and/O he/O answered/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON subsided/O ,/O cold/O with/O anger/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O the/O king/O 's/O peace/O ,/O you/O say/O ./O 
Is/O this/O how/O you/O keep/O my/O peace/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ?/O 
Seven/O men/O are/O dead/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Eight/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O corrected/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tregar/O died/O this/O morning/O ,/O of/O the/O blow/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON gave/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Abductions/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O drunken/O slaughter/O in/O my/O streets/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O have/O it/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O good/O reason/O for/O taking/O the/O Imp/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O said/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O have/O it/O !/O 
To/O hell/O with/O her/O reasons/O ./O 
You/O will/O command/O her/O to/O release/O the/O dwarf/O at/O once/O ,/O and/O you/O will/O make/O your/O peace/O with/O Jaime/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Three/O of/O my/O men/O were/O butchered/O before/O my/O eyes/O ,/O because/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON wished/O to/O chasten/O me/O ./O 
Am/O I/O to/O forget/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O was/O not/O the/O cause/O of/O this/O quarrel/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON told/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON was/O returning/O drunk/O from/O a/O brothel/O ./O 
His/O men/O attacked/O Jaime/PERSON and/O his/O guards/O ,/O even/O as/O his/O wife/O attacked/O Tyrion/LOCATION on/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O know/O me/O better/O than/O that/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ask/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON if/O you/O doubt/O me/O ./O 
He/O was/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O talked/O to/O Little/O finger/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O claims/O he/O rode/O off/O to/O bring/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O before/O the/O fighting/O began/O ,/O but/O he/O admits/O you/O were/O returning/O from/O some/O whorehouse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O whorehouse/O ?/O 
Damn/O your/O eyes/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O I/O went/O there/O to/O have/O a/O look/O at/O your/O daughter/O !/O 
Her/O mother/O has/O named/O her/O Barra/ORGANIZATION ./O 
She/O looks/O like/O that/O first/O girl/O you/O fathered/O ,/O when/O we/O were/O boys/O together/O in/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O watched/O the/O queen/O as/O he/O spoke/O ;/O her/O face/O was/O a/O mask/O ,/O still/O and/O pale/O ,/O betraying/O nothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON flushed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Barra/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O supposed/O to/O please/O me/O ?/O 
Damn/O the/O girl/O ./O 
I/O thought/O she/O had/O more/O sense/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O can/O not/O be/O more/O than/O fifteen/O ,/O and/O a/O whore/O ,/O and/O you/O thought/O she/O had/O sense/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O incredulous/O ./O 
His/O leg/O was/O beginning/O to/O pain/O him/O sorely/O ./O 
It/O was/O hard/O to/O keep/O his/O temper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O fool/O child/O is/O in/O love/O with/O you/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O glanced/O at/O Cersei/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O fit/O subject/O for/O the/O queen/O 's/O ears/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Her/O Grace/O will/O have/O no/O liking/O for/O anything/O I/O have/O to/O say/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O told/O the/O Kingslayer/O has/O fled/O the/O city/O ./O 
Give/O me/O leave/O to/O bring/O him/O back/O to/O justice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O swirled/O the/O wine/O in/O his/O cup/O ,/O brooding/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O swallow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O no/O more/O of/O this/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON slew/O three/O of/O your/O men/O ,/O and/O you/O five/O of/O his/O ./O 
Now/O it/O ends/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O your/O notion/O of/O justice/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O so/O ,/O I/O am/O pleased/O that/O I/O am/O no/O longer/O your/O Hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O looked/O to/O her/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O any/O man/O had/O dared/O speak/O to/O a/O Targaryen/O as/O he/O has/O spoken/O to/O you/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O take/O me/O for/O Aerys/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON interrupted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O took/O you/O for/O a/O king/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON and/O Tyrion/O are/O your/O own/O brothers/O ,/O by/O all/O the/O laws/O of/O marriage/O and/O the/O bonds/O we/O share/O ./O 
The/O Starks/PERSON have/O driven/O off/O the/O one/O and/O seized/O the/O other/O ./O 
This/O man/O dishonors/O you/O with/O every/O breath/O he/O takes/O ,/O and/O yet/O you/O stand/O there/O meekly/O ,/O asking/O if/O his/O leg/O pains/O him/O and/O would/O he/O like/O some/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON 's/O face/O was/O dark/O with/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O many/O times/O must/O I/O tell/O you/O to/O hold/O your/O tongue/O ,/O woman/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cersei/O 's/O face/O was/O a/O study/O in/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O a/O jape/O the/O gods/O have/O made/O of/O us/O two/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O all/O rights/O ,/O you/O ought/O to/O be/O in/O skirts/O and/O me/O in/O mail/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Purple/O with/O rage/O ,/O the/O king/O lashed/O out/O ,/O a/O vicious/O backhand/O blow/O to/O the/O side/O of/O the/O head/O ./O 
She/O stumbled/O against/O the/O table/O and/O fell/O hard/O ,/O yet/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON did/O not/O cry/O out/O ./O 
Her/O slender/O fingers/O brushed/O her/O cheek/O ,/O where/O the/O pale/O smooth/O skin/O was/O already/O reddening/O ./O 
On/O the/O morrow/O the/O bruise/O would/O cover/O half/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O wear/O this/O as/O a/O badge/O of/O honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wear/O it/O in/O silence/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O honor/O you/O again/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON vowed/O ./O 
He/O shouted/O for/O a/O guard/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON stepped/O into/O the/O room/O ,/O tall/O and/O somber/O in/O his/O white/O armor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O queen/O is/O tired/O ./O 
See/O her/O to/O her/O bedchamber/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O helped/O Cersei/PERSON to/O her/O feet/O and/O led/O her/O out/O without/O a/O word/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON reached/O for/O the/O flagon/O and/O refilled/O his/O cup/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O see/O what/O she/O does/O to/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O seated/O himself/O ,/O cradling/O his/O wine/O cup/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O loving/O wife/O ./O 
The/O mother/O of/O my/O children/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O rage/O was/O gone/O from/O him/O now/O ;/O in/O his/O eyes/O Ned/PERSON saw/O something/O sad/O and/O scared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O not/O have/O hit/O her/O ./O 
That/O was/O not/O .../O that/O was/O not/O kingly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stared/O down/O at/O his/O hands/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O did/O not/O quite/O know/O what/O they/O were/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O always/O strong/O .../O no/O one/O could/O stand/O before/O me/O ,/O no/O one/O ./O 
How/O do/O you/O fight/O someone/O if/O you/O ca/O n't/O hit/O them/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Confused/O ,/O the/O king/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaegar/O .../O Rhaegar/PERSON won/O ,/O damn/O him/O ./O 
I/O killed/O him/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O I/O drove/O the/O spike/O right/O through/O that/O black/O armor/O into/O his/O black/O heart/O ,/O and/O he/O died/O at/O my/O feet/O ./O 
They/O made/O up/O songs/O about/O it/O ./O 
Yet/O somehow/O he/O still/O won/O ./O 
He/O has/O Lyanna/PERSON now/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O drained/O his/O cup/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O must/O talk/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON pressed/O his/O fingertips/O against/O his/O temples/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O sick/O unto/O death/O of/O talk/O ./O 
On/O the/O morrow/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O the/O kingswood/O to/O hunt/O ./O 
Whatever/O you/O have/O to/O say/O can/O wait/O until/O I/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O the/O gods/O are/O good/O ,/O I/O shall/O not/O be/O here/O on/O your/O return/O ./O 
You/O commanded/O me/O to/O return/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O remember/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON stood/O up/O ,/O grasping/O one/O of/O the/O bedposts/O to/O steady/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O are/O seldom/O good/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Here/O ,/O this/O is/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pulled/O the/O heavy/O silver/O hand/O clasp/O from/O a/O pocket/O in/O the/O lining/O of/O his/O cloak/O and/O tossed/O it/O on/O the/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Like/O it/O or/O not/O ,/O you/O are/O my/O Hand/O ,/O damn/O you/O ./O 
I/O forbid/O you/O to/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O picked/O up/O the/O silver/O clasp/O ./O 
He/O was/O being/O given/O no/O choice/O ,/O it/O seemed/O ./O 
His/O leg/O throbbed/O ,/O and/O he/O felt/O as/O helpless/O as/O a/O child/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Targaryen/O girl/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O groaned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O ,/O do/O n't/O start/O with/O her/O again/O ./O 
That/O 's/O done/O ,/O I/O 'll/O hear/O no/O more/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O you/O want/O me/O as/O your/O Hand/O ,/O if/O you/O refuse/O to/O listen/O to/O my/O counsel/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O not/O ?/O 
Someone/O has/O to/O rule/O this/O damnable/O kingdom/O ./O 
Put/O on/O the/O badge/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
It/O suits/O you/O ./O 
And/O if/O you/O ever/O throw/O it/O in/O my/O face/O again/O ,/O I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O I/O 'll/O pin/O the/O damned/O thing/O on/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
