-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Wings/O shadowed/O her/O fever/O dreams/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O was/O walking/O down/O a/O long/O hall/O beneath/O high/O stone/O arches/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O look/O behind/O her/O ,/O must/O not/O look/O behind/O her/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O door/O ahead/O of/O her/O ,/O tiny/O with/O distance/O ,/O but/O even/O from/O afar/O ,/O she/O saw/O that/O it/O was/O painted/O red/O ./O 
She/O walked/O faster/O ,/O and/O her/O bare/O feet/O left/O bloody/O footprints/O on/O the/O stone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O saw/O sunlight/O on/O the/O Dothraki/O sea/O ,/O the/O living/O plain/O ,/O rich/O with/O the/O smells/O of/O earth/O and/O death/O ./O 
Wind/O stirred/O the/O grasses/O ,/O and/O they/O rippled/O like/O water/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON held/O her/O in/O strong/O arms/O ,/O and/O his/O hand/O stroked/O her/O sex/O and/O opened/O her/O and/O woke/O that/O sweet/O wetness/O that/O was/O his/O alone/O ,/O and/O the/O stars/O smiled/O down/O on/O them/O ,/O stars/O in/O a/O daylight/O sky/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Home/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O as/O he/O entered/O her/O and/O filled/O her/O with/O his/O seed/O ,/O but/O suddenly/O the/O stars/O were/O gone/O ,/O and/O across/O the/O blue/O sky/O swept/O the/O great/O wings/O ,/O and/O the/O world/O took/O flame/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON 's/O face/O was/O drawn/O and/O sorrowful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rhaegar/PERSON was/O the/O last/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
He/O warmed/O translucent/O hands/O over/O a/O glowing/O brazier/O where/O stone/O eggs/O smouldered/O red/O as/O coals/O ./O 
One/O moment/O he/O was/O there/O and/O the/O next/O he/O was/O fading/O ,/O his/O flesh/O colorless/O ,/O less/O substantial/O than/O the/O wind/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O last/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ,/O thin/O as/O a/O wisp/O ,/O and/O was/O gone/O ./O 
She/O felt/O the/O dark/O behind/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O red/O door/O seemed/O farther/O away/O than/O ever/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O stood/O before/O her/O ,/O screaming/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O dragon/O does/O not/O beg/O ,/O slut/O ./O 
You/O do/O not/O command/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O dragon/O ,/O and/O I/O will/O be/O crowned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O molten/O gold/O trickled/O down/O his/O face/O like/O wax/O ,/O burning/O deep/O channels/O in/O his/O flesh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O dragon/O and/O I/O will/O be/O crowned/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shrieked/O ,/O and/O his/O fingers/O snapped/O like/O snakes/O ,/O biting/O at/O her/O nipples/O ,/O pinching/O ,/O twisting/O ,/O even/O as/O his/O eyes/O burst/O and/O ran/O like/O jelly/O down/O seared/O and/O blackened/O cheeks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O red/O door/O was/O so/O far/O ahead/O of/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O feel/O the/O icy/O breath/O behind/O ,/O sweeping/O up/O on/O her/O ./O 
If/O it/O caught/O her/O she/O would/O die/O a/O death/O that/O was/O more/O than/O death/O ,/O howling/O forever/O alone/O in/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
She/O began/O to/O run/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O do/O n't/O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O could/O feel/O the/O heat/O inside/O her/O ,/O a/O terrible/O burning/O in/O her/O womb/O ./O 
Her/O son/O was/O tall/O and/O proud/O ,/O with/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O copper/O skin/O and/O her/O own/O silver-gold/O hair/O ,/O violet/O eyes/O shaped/O like/O almonds/O ./O 
And/O he/O smiled/O for/O her/O and/O began/O to/O lift/O his/O hand/O toward/O hers/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O opened/O his/O mouth/O the/O fire/O poured/O out/O ./O 
She/O saw/O his/O heart/O burning/O through/O his/O chest/O ,/O and/O in/O an/O instant/O he/O was/O gone/O ,/O consumed/O like/O a/O moth/O by/O a/O candle/O ,/O turned/O to/O ash/O ./O 
She/O wept/O for/O her/O child/O ,/O the/O promise/O of/O a/O sweet/O mouth/O on/O her/O breast/O ,/O but/O her/O tears/O turned/O to/O steam/O as/O they/O touched/O her/O skin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O want/O to/O wake/O the/O dragon/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ghosts/O lined/O the/O hallway/O ,/O dressed/O in/O the/O faded/O raiment/O of/O kings/O ./O 
In/O their/O hands/O were/O swords/O of/O pale/O fire/O ./O 
They/O had/O hair/O of/O silver/O and/O hair/O of/O gold/O and/O hair/O of/O platinum/O white/O ,/O and/O their/O eyes/O were/O ''/O ,/O ``/O opal/O and/O amethyst/O ,/O tourmaline/O and/O jade/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Faster/O ,/O \/O ''/O they/O cried/O ,/O \/O ``/O faster/O ,/O faster/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O raced/O ,/O her/O feet/O melting/O the/O stone/O wherever/O they/O touched/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Faster/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O ghosts/O cried/O as/O one/O ,/O and/O she/O screamed/O and/O threw/O herself/O forward/O ./O 
A/O great/O knife/O of/O pain/O ripped/O down/O her/O back/O ,/O and/O she/O felt/O her/O skin/O tear/O open/O and/O smelled/O the/O stench/O of/O burning/O blood/O and/O saw/O the/O shadow/O of/O wings/O ./O 
And/O Daenerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON flew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O door/O loomed/O before/O her/O ,/O the/O red/O door/O ,/O so/O close/O ,/O so/O close/O ,/O the/O hall/O was/O a/O blur/O around/O her/O ,/O the/O cold/O receding/O behind/O ./O 
And/O now/O the/O stone/O was/O gone/O and/O she/O flew/O across/O the/O Dothraki/LOCATION sea/LOCATION ,/O high/O and/O higher/O ,/O the/O green/O rippling/O beneath/O ,/O and/O all/O that/O lived/O and/O breathed/O fled/O in/O terror/O from/O the/O shadow/O of/O her/O wings/O ./O 
She/O could/O smell/O home/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O it/O ,/O there/O ,/O just/O beyond/O that/O door/O ,/O green/O fields/O and/O great/O stone/O houses/O and/O arms/O to/O keep/O her/O warm/O ,/O there/O ./O 
She/O threw/O open/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O the/O dragon/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O saw/O her/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON ,/O mounted/O on/O a/O stallion/O as/O black/O as/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Fire/O glimmered/O red/O through/O the/O narrow/O eye/O slit/O of/O his/O helm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O last/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON 's/O voice/O whispered/O faintly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O last/O ,/O the/O last/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON lifted/O his/O polished/O black/O visor/O ./O 
The/O face/O within/O was/O her/O own/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O that/O ,/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O there/O was/O only/O the/O pain/O ,/O the/O fire/O within/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O whisperings/O of/O stars/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O woke/O to/O the/O taste/O of/O ashes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O moaned/O ,/O \/O ``/O no/O ,/O please/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jhiqui/PERSON hovered/O over/O her/O ,/O a/O frightened/O doe/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O tent/O was/O drenched/O in/O shadow/O ,/O still/O and/O close/O ./O 
Flakes/O of/O ash/O drifted/O upward/O from/O a/O brazier/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON followed/O them/O with/O her/O eyes/O through/O the/O smoke/O hole/O above/O ./O 
Flying/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
I/O had/O wings/O ,/O I/O was/O flying/O ./O 
But/O it/O was/O only/O a/O dream/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Help/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ,/O struggling/O to/O rise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O Her/O voice/O was/O raw/O as/O a/O wound/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O not/O think/O what/O she/O wanted/O ./O 
Why/O did/O she/O hurt/O so/O much/O ?/O 
It/O was/O as/O if/O her/O body/O had/O been/O torn/O to/O pieces/O and/O remade/O from/O the/O scraps/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Quick/O as/O that/O Jhiqui/PERSON was/O gone/O ,/O bolting/O from/O the/O tent/O ,/O shouting/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON needed/O .../O something/O .../O someone/O .../O what/O ?/O 
It/O was/O important/O ,/O she/O knew/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O only/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O that/O mattered/O ./O 
She/O rolled/O onto/O her/O side/O and/O got/O an/O elbow/O under/O her/O ,/O fighting/O the/O blanket/O tangled/O about/O her/O legs/O ./O 
It/O was/O so/O hard/O to/O move/O ./O 
The/O world/O swam/O dizzily/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O found/O her/O on/O the/O carpet/O ,/O crawling/O toward/O her/O dragon/O eggs/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON lifted/O her/O in/O his/O arms/O and/O carried/O her/O back/O to/O her/O sleeping/O silks/O ,/O while/O she/O struggled/O feebly/O against/O him/O ./O 
Over/O his/O shoulder/O she/O saw/O her/O three/O handmaids/O ,/O Jhogo/PERSON with/O his/O little/O wisp/O of/O mustache/O ,/O and/O the/O flat/O broad/O face/O of/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O must/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O tried/O to/O tell/O them/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O to/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O sleep/O ,/O Princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ./O 
No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ./O 
Please/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O covered/O her/O with/O silk/O ,/O though/O she/O was/O burning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sleep/O and/O grow/O strong/O again/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
Come/O back/O to/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O then/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON was/O there/O ,/O the/O maegi/O ,/O tipping/O a/O cup/O against/O her/O lips/O ./O 
She/O tasted/O sour/O milk/O ,/O and/O something/O else/O ,/O something/O thick/O and/O bitter/O ./O 
Warm/O liquid/O ran/O down/O her/O chin/O ./O 
Somehow/O she/O swallowed/O ./O 
The/O tent/O grew/O dimmer/O ,/O and/O sleep/O took/O her/O ''/O ,/O ``/O again/O ./O 
This/O time/O she/O did/O not/O dream/O ./O 
She/O floated/O ,/O serene/O and/O at/O peace/O ,/O on/O a/O black/O sea/O that/O knew/O no/O shore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O a/O time-a/O night/O ,/O a/O day/O ,/O a/O year/O ,/O she/O could/O not/O say-she/O woke/O again/O ./O 
The/O tent/O was/O dark/O ,/O its/O silken/O walls/O flapping/O like/O wings/O when/O the/O wind/O gusted/O outside/O ./O 
This/O time/O Dany/PERSON did/O not/O attempt/O to/O rise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Irri/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O ,/O \/O ``/O Jhiqui/O ./O 
Doreah/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O were/O there/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O throat/O is/O dry/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O so/O dry/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O they/O brought/O her/O water/O ./O 
It/O was/O warm/O and/O flat/O ,/O yet/O Dany/PERSON drank/O it/O eagerly/O ,/O and/O sent/O Jhiqui/PERSON for/O more/O ./O 
Irri/ORGANIZATION dampened/O a/O soft/O cloth/O and/O stroked/O her/O brow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O been/O sick/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O girl/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O long/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O cloth/O was/O soothing/O ,/O but/O Irri/ORGANIZATION seemed/O so/O sad/O ,/O it/O frightened/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Long/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
When/O Jhiqui/PERSON returned/O with/O more/O water/O ,/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON came/O with/O her/O ,/O eyes/O heavy/O from/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O lifting/O Dany/PERSON 's/O head/O to/O the/O cup/O once/O more/O ,/O but/O this/O time/O it/O was/O only/O wine/O ./O 
Sweet/O ,/O sweet/O wine/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON drank/O ,/O and/O lay/O back/O ,/O listening/O to/O the/O soft/O sound/O of/O her/O own/O breathing/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O heaviness/O in/O her/O limbs/O ,/O as/O sleep/O crept/O in/O to/O fill/O her/O up/O once/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O she/O murmured/O ,/O her/O voice/O slurred/O and/O drowsy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O .../O I/O want/O to/O hold/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O maegi/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O you/O wish/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bring/O me/O .../O egg/O .../O dragon/O 's/O egg/O .../O please/O .../O \/O ''/O Her/O lashes/O turned/O to/O lead/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O too/O weary/O to/O hold/O them/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O woke/O the/O third/O time/O ,/O a/O shaft/O of/O golden/O sunlight/O was/O pouring/O through/O the/O smoke/O hole/O of/O the/O tent/O ,/O and/O her/O arms/O were/O wrapped/O around/O a/O dragon/O 's/O egg/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O pale/O one/O ,/O its/O scales/O the/O color/O of/O butter/O cream/O ,/O veined/O with/O whorls/O of/O gold/O and/O bronze/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON could/O feel/O the/O heat/O of/O it/O ./O 
Beneath/O her/O bedsilks/O ,/O a/O fine/O sheen/O of/O perspiration/O covered/O her/O bare/O skin/O ./O 
Dragondew/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
Her/O fingers/O trailed/O lightly/O across/O the/O surface/O of/O the/O shell/O ,/O tracing/O the/O wisps/O of/O gold/O ,/O and/O deep/O in/O the/O stone/O she/O felt/O something/O twist/O and/O stretch/O in/O response/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O frighten/O her/O ./O 
All/O her/O fear/O was/O gone/O ,/O burned/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON touched/O her/O brow/O ./O 
Under/O the/O film/O of/O sweat/O ,/O her/O skin/O was/O cool/O to/O the/O touch/O ,/O her/O fever/O gone/O ./O 
She/O made/O herself/O sit/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O moment/O of/O dizziness/O ,/O and/O the/O deep/O ache/O between/O her/O thighs/O ./O 
Yet/O she/O felt/O strong/O ./O 
Her/O maids/O came/O running/O at/O the/O sound/O of/O her/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Water/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ,/O \/O ``/O a/O flagon/O of/O water/O ,/O cold/O as/O you/O can/O find/O it/O ./O 
And/O fruit/O ,/O I/O think/O ./O 
Dates/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O standing/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON brought/O a/O sandsilk/O robe/O and/O draped/O it/O over/O her/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O a/O warm/O bath/O ,/O and/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ,/O and/O .../O \/O ''/O Memory/O came/O back/O to/O her/O all/O at/O once/O ,/O and/O she/O faltered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O forced/O herself/O to/O say/O ,/O watching/O their/O faces/O with/O dread/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O khal/O lives/O ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON answered/O quietly/O .../O yet/O Dany/PERSON saw/O a/O darkness/O in/O her/O eyes/O when/O she/O said/O the/O words/O ,/O and/O no/O sooner/O had/O she/O spoken/O than/O she/O rushed/O away/O to/O fetch/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O turned/O to/O Doreah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A./O ./O 
./O 
I/O shall/O bring/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lysene/PERSON girl/O said/O ,/O bowing/O her/O head/O and/O fleeing/O the/O tent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jhiqui/PERSON would/O have/O run/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON caught/O her/O by/O the/O wrist/O and/O held/O her/O captive/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
I/O must/O know/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON .../O and/O my/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Why/O had/O she/O not/O remembered/O the/O child/O until/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O My/O son/O .../O Rhaego/O .../O where/O is/O he/O ?/O 
I/O want/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O handmaid/O lowered/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O .../O he/O did/O not/O live/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O voice/O was/O a/O frightened/O whisper/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON released/O her/O wrist/O ./O 
My/O son/O is/O dead/O ,/O she/O thought/O as/O Jhiqui/PERSON left/O the/O tent/O ./O 
She/O had/O known/O somehow/O ./O 
She/O had/O known/O since/O she/O woke/O the/O first/O time/O to/O Jhiqui/PERSON 's/O tears/O ./O 
No/O ,/O she/O had/O known/O before/O she/O woke/O ./O 
Her/O dream/O came/O back/O to/O her/O ,/O sudden/O and/O vivid/O ,/O and/O she/O remembered/O the/O tall/O man/O with/O the/O copper/O skin/O and/O long/O silver-gold/O braid/O ,/O bursting/O into/O flame/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O should/O weep/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O yet/O her/O eyes/O were/O dry/O as/O ash/O ./O 
She/O had/O wept/O in/O her/O dream/O ,/O and/O the/O tears/O had/O turned/O to/O steam/O on/O her/O cheeks/O ./O 
All/O the/O grief/O has/O been/O burned/O out/O of/O me/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
She/O felt/O sad/O ,/O and/O yet/O .../O she/O could/O feel/O Rhaego/O receding/O from/O her/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O never/O been/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O and/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON entered/O a/O few/O moments/O later/O ,/O and/O found/O Dany/PERSON standing/O over/O the/O other/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O ,/O the/O two/O still/O in/O their/O chest/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O to/O her/O that/O they/O felt/O as/O hot/O as/O the/O one/O she/O had/O slept/O with/O ,/O which/O was/O passing/O strange/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O ,/O come/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O took/O his/O hand/O and/O placed/O it/O on/O the/O black/O egg/O with/O the/O scarlet/O swirls/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O feel/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shell/ORGANIZATION ,/O hard/O as/O rock/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O knight/O was/O wary/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Scales/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Heat/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
Cold/O stone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O his/O hand/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Princess/O ,/O are/O you/O well/O ?/O 
Should/O you/O be/O up/O ,/O weak/O as/O you/O are/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Weak/O ?/O 
I/O am/O strong/O ,/O Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O To/O please/O him/O ,/O she/O reclined/O on/O a/O pile/O of/O cushions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O how/O my/O child/O died/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O never/O lived/O ,/O my/O princess/O ./O 
The/O women/O say/O He/O faltered/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON saw/O how/O the/O flesh/O hung/O loose/O on/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O way/O he/O limped/O when/O he/O moved/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ./O 
Tell/O me/O what/O the/O women/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O turned/O his/O face/O away/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O haunted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O say/O the/O child/O was/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O waited/O ,/O but/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON could/O not/O say/O it/O ./O 
His/O face/O grew/O dark/O with/O shame/O ./O 
He/O looked/O half/O a/O corpse/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Monstrous/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON finished/O for/O him/O ./O 
The/O knight/O was/O a/O powerful/O man/O ,/O yet/O Dany/PERSON understood/O in/O that/O moment/O that/O the/O maegi/O was/O stronger/O ,/O and/O crueler/O ,/O and/O infinitely/O more/O dangerous/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Twisted/O ./O 
I/O drew/O him/O forth/O myself/O ./O 
He/O was/O scaled/O like/O a/O lizard/O ,/O blind/O ,/O with/O the/O stub/O of/O a/O tail/O and/O small/O leather/O wings/O like/O the/O wings/O of/O a/O bat/O ./O 
When/O I/O touched/O him/O ,/O the/O flesh/O sloughed/O off/O the/O bone/O ,/O and/O inside/O he/O was/O full/O of/O graveworms/O and/O the/O stink/O of/O corruption/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O dead/O for/O years/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Darkness/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O ./O 
The/O terrible/O darkness/O sweeping/O up/O behind/O to/O devour/O her/O ./O 
If/O she/O looked/O back/O she/O was/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O son/O was/O alive/O and/O strong/O when/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON carried/O me/O into/O this/O tent/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O could/O feel/O him/O kicking/O ,/O fighting/O to/O be/O born/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O may/O be/O as/O it/O may/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O answered/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O the/O creature/O that/O came/O forth/O from/O your/O womb/O was/O as/O I/O said/O ./O 
Death/O was/O in/O that/O tent/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O shadows/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON husked/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON could/O hear/O the/O doubt/O in/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O ,/O maegi/O ./O 
I/O saw/O you/O ,/O alone/O ,/O dancing/O with/O the/O shadows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O grave/O casts/O long/O shadows/O ,/O Iron/O Lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Long/O and/O dark/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O end/O no/O light/O can/O hold/O them/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O killed/O her/O son/O ,/O Dany/PERSON knew/O ./O 
He/O had/O done/O what/O he/O did/O for/O love/O and/O loyalty/O ,/O yet/O he/O had/O carried/O her/O into/O a/O place/O no/O living/O man/O should/O go/O and/O fed/O her/O baby/O to/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
He/O knew/O it/O too/O ;/O the/O grey/O face/O ,/O the/O hollow/O eyes/O ,/O the/O limp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O shadows/O have/O touched/O you/O too/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
The/O knight/O made/O no/O reply/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON turned/O to/O the/O godswife/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O warned/O me/O that/O only/O death/O could/O pay/O for/O life/O ./O 
I/O thought/O you/O meant/O the/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O a/O lie/O you/O told/O yourself/O ./O 
You/O knew/O the/O price/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Had/O she/O ?/O 
Had/O she/O ?/O 
If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O price/O was/O paid/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O horse/O ,/O my/O child/O ,/O Quaro/PERSON and/O Qotho/PERSON ,/O Haggo/PERSON and/O Cohollo/O ./O 
The/O price/O was/O paid/O and/O paid/O and/O paid/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O rose/O from/O her/O cushions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O is/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ?/O 
Show/O him/O to/O me/O ,/O godswife/O ,/O maegi/O ,/O bloodmage/O ,/O whatever/O you/O are/O ./O 
Show/O me/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ./O 
Show/O me/O what/O I/O bought/O with/O my/O son/O 's/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O woman/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O I/O will/O take/O you/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON was/O weaker/O than/O she/O knew/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON slipped/O an/O arm/O around/O her/O and/O helped/O her/O stand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Time/O enough/O for/O this/O later/O ,/O my/O princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O quietly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O see/O him/O now/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O After/O the/O dimness/O of/O the/O tent/O ,/O the/O world/O outside/O was/O blinding/O bright/O ./O 
The/O sun/O burned/O like/O molten/O gold/O ,/O and/O the/O land/O was/O seared/O and/O empty/O ./O 
Her/O handmaids/O waited/O with/O fruit/O and/O wine/O and/O water/O ,/O and/O Jhogo/PERSON moved/O close/O to/O help/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON support/O her/O ./O 
Aggo/PERSON and/O Rakharo/PERSON stood/O behind/O ./O 
The/O glare/O of/O sun/O on/O sand/O made/O it/O hard/O to/O see/O more/O ,/O until/O Dany/PERSON raised/O her/O hand/O to/O shade/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O saw/O the/O ashes/O of/O a/O fire/O ,/O a/O few/O score/O horses/O milling/O listlessly/O and/O searching/O for/O a/O bite/O of/O grass/O ,/O a/O scattering/O of/O tents/O and/O bedrolls/O ./O 
A/O small/O crowd/O of/O children/O had/O gathered/O to/O watch/O her/O ,/O and/O beyond/O she/O glimpsed/O women/O going/O about/O their/O work/O ,/O and/O withered/O old/O men/O staring/O at/O the/O flat/O blue/O sky/O with/O tired/O eyes/O ,/O swatting/O feebly/O at/O bloodflies/O ./O 
A/O count/O might/O show/O a/O hundred/O people/O ,/O no/O more/O ./O 
Where/O the/O other/O forty/O thousand/O had/O made/O their/O camp/O ,/O only/O the/O wind/O and/O dust/O lived/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O khalasar/O is/O gone/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O khal/O who/O can/O not/O ride/O is/O no/O khal/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Jhogo/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O follow/O only/O the/O strong/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O sorry/O ,/O my/O princess/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O way/O to/O hold/O them/O ./O 
Ko/PERSON Pono/PERSON left/O first/O ,/O naming/O himself/O Khal/PERSON Pono/PERSON ,/O and/O many/O followed/O him/O ./O 
Jhaqo/PERSON was/O not/O long/O to/O do/O the/O same/O ./O 
The/O rest/O slipped/O away/O night/O by/O night/O ,/O in/O large/O bands/O and/O small/O ./O 
There/O are/O a/O dozen/O new/O khalasars/O on/O the/O Dothraki/LOCATION sea/LOCATION ,/O where/O once/O there/O was/O only/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O old/O remain/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Aggo/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O frightened/O ,/O the/O weak/O ,/O and/O the/O sick/O ./O 
And/O we/O who/O swore/O ./O 
We/O remain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O took/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O herds/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Rakharo/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O were/O too/O few/O to/O stop/O them/O ./O 
It/O is/O the/O right/O of/O the/O strong/O to/O take/O from/O the/O weak/O ./O 
They/O took/O many/O slaves/O as/O well/O ,/O the/O khal/O 's/O and/O yours/O ,/O yet/O they/O left/O some/O few/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Eroeh/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Dany/PERSON ,/O remembering/O the/O frightened/O child/O she/O had/O saved/O outside/O the/O city/O of/O the/O Lamb/O Men/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mago/PERSON seized/O her/O ,/O who/O is/O Khal/PERSON Jhaqo/PERSON 's/O bloodrider/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Jhogo/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O mounted/O her/O high/O and/O low/O and/O gave/O her/O to/O his/O khal/O ,/O and/O Jhaqo/PERSON gave/O her/O to/O his/O other/O bloodriders/O ./O 
They/O were/O six/O ./O 
When/O they/O were/O done/O with/O her/O ,/O they/O cut/O her/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O her/O fate/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Aggo/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O a/O cruel/O fate/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O not/O so/O cruel/O as/O Mago/PERSON 's/O will/O be/O ./O 
I/O promise/O you/O that/O ,/O by/O the/O old/O gods/O and/O the/O new/O ,/O by/O the/O lamb/O god/O and/O the/O horse/O god/O and/O every/O god/O that/O lives/O ./O 
I/O swear/O it/O by/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION and/O the/O Womb/O of/O the/O World/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Before/O I/O am/O done/O with/O them/O ,/O Mago/PERSON and/O Ko/PERSON Jhaqo/PERSON will/O plead/O for/O the/O mercy/O they/O showed/O Eroeh/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O exchanged/O uncertain/O glances/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O handmaid/O Irri/PERSON explained/O ,/O as/O if/O to/O a/O child/O ,/O \/O ``/O Jhaqo/O is/O a/O khal/O now/O ,/O with/O twenty/O thousand/O riders/O at/O his/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O lifted/O her/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O I/O am/O Daenerys/PERSON Stormhorn/PERSON ,/O Daenerys/PERSON of/O House/O Targaryen/O ,/O of/O the/O blood/O of/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O and/O Maegor/O the/O Cruel/O and/O old/O Valyria/LOCATION before/O them/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O dragon/O 's/O daughter/O ,/O and/O I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O these/O men/O will/O die/O screaming/O ./O 
Now/O bring/O me/O to/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O lying/O on/O the/O bare/O red/O earth/O ,/O staring/O up/O at/O the/O sun/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O dozen/O bloodflies/O had/O settled/O on/O his/O body/O ,/O though/O he/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O feel/O them/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON brushed/O them/O away/O and/O knelt/O beside/O him/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O wide/O open/O but/O did/O not/O see/O ,/O and/O she/O knew/O at/O once/O that/O he/O was/O blind/O ./O 
When/O she/O whispered/O his/O name/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O hear/O ./O 
The/O wound/O on/O his/O breast/O was/O as/O healed/O as/O it/O would/O ever/O be/O ,/O the/O scar/O that/O covered/O it/O grey/O and/O red/O and/O hideous/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O is/O he/O out/O here/O alone/O ,/O in/O the/O sun/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O seems/O to/O like/O the/O warmth/O ,/O Princess/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O eyes/O follow/O the/O sun/O ,/O though/O he/O does/O not/O see/O it/O ./O 
He/O can/O walk/O after/O a/O fashion/O ./O 
He/O will/O go/O where/O you/O lead/O him/O ,/O but/O no/O farther/O ./O 
He/O will/O eat/O if/O you/O put/O food/O in/O his/O mouth/O ,/O drink/O if/O you/O dribble/O water/O on/O his/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON kissed/O her/O sun-and-stars/O gently/O on/O the/O brow/O ,/O and/O stood/O to/O face/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O spells/O are/O costly/O ,/O maegi/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O lives/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O asked/O for/O life/O ./O 
You/O paid/O for/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O not/O life/O ,/O for/O one/O who/O was/O as/O Drogo/PERSON was/O ./O 
His/O life/O was/O laughter/O ,/O and/O meat/O roasting/O over/O a/O firepit/O ,/O and/O a/O horse/O between/O his/O legs/O ./O 
His/O life/O was/O an/O arakh/O in/O his/O hand/O and/O his/O bells/O ringing/O in/O his/O hair/O as/O he/O rode/O to/O meet/O an/O enemy/O ./O 
His/O life/O was/O his/O bloodriders/O ,/O and/O me/O ,/O and/O the/O son/O I/O was/O to/O give/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON made/O no/O reply/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O will/O he/O be/O as/O he/O was/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON demanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O the/O sun/O rises/O in/O the/O west/O and/O sets/O in/O the/O east/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O the/O seas/O go/O dry/O and/O mountains/O blow/O in/O the/O wind/O like/O leaves/O ./O 
When/O your/O womb/O quickens/O again/O ,/O and/O you/O bear/O a/O living/O child/O ./O 
Then/O he/O will/O return/O ,/O and/O not/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON gestured/O at/O Ser/ORGANIZATION Jorah/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Leave/O us/O ./O 
I/O would/O speak/O with/O this/O maegi/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON and/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON withdrew/O ./O 
`/O You/O knew/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O when/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O 
She/O ached/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O inside/O and/O out/O ,/O but/O her/O fury/O gave/O her/O strength/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O knew/O what/O I/O was/O buying/O ,/O and/O you/O knew/O the/O price/O ,/O and/O yet/O you/O let/O me/O pay/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O wrong/O of/O them/O to/O burn/O my/O temple/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O heavy/O ,/O flat-nosed/O woman/O said/O placidly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O angered/O the/O Great/O Shepherd/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O was/O no/O god/O 's/O work/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O coldly/O ./O 
If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O cheated/O me/O ./O 
You/O murdered/O my/O child/O within/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O stallion/O who/O mounts/O the/O world/O will/O burn/O no/O cities/O now/O ./O 
His/O khalasar/O shall/O trample/O no/O nations/O into/O dust/O ,/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O spoke/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O anguished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saved/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Saved/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O Lhazareen/O woman/O spat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O riders/O had/O taken/O me/O ,/O not/O as/O a/O man/O takes/O a/O woman/O but/O from/O behind/O ,/O as/O a/O dog/O takes/O a/O bitch/O ./O 
The/O fourth/O was/O in/O me/O when/O you/O rode/O past/O ./O 
How/O then/O did/O you/O save/O me/O ?/O 
I/O saw/O my/O god/O 's/O house/O burn/O ,/O where/O I/O had/O healed/O good/O men/O beyond/O counting/O ./O 
My/O home/O they/O burned/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O street/O I/O saw/O piles/O of/O heads/O ./O 
I/O saw/O the/O head/O of/O a/O baker/O who/O made/O my/O bread/O ./O 
I/O saw/O the/O head/O of/O a/O boy/O I/O had/O saved/O from/O deadeye/O fever/O ,/O only/O three/O moons/O past/O ./O 
I/O heard/O children/O crying/O as/O the/O riders/O drove/O them/O off/O with/O their/O whips/O ./O 
Tell/O me/O again/O what/O you/O saved/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON laughed/O cruelly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O to/O your/O khal/O and/O see/O what/O life/O is/O worth/O ,/O when/O all/O the/O rest/O is/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON called/O out/O for/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O and/O bid/O them/O take/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON and/O bind/O her/O hand/O and/O foot/O ,/O but/O the/O maegi/O smiled/O at/O her/O as/O they/O carried/O her/O off/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O shared/O a/O secret/O ./O 
A/O word/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON could/O have/O her/O head/O off/O .../O yet/O then/O what/O would/O she/O have/O ?/O 
A/O head/O ?/O 
If/O life/O was/O worthless/O ,/O what/O was/O death/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O led/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON back/O to/O her/O tent/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON commanded/O them/O to/O fill/O a/O tub/O ,/O and/O this/O time/O there/O was/O no/O blood/O in/O the/O water/O ./O 
She/O bathed/O him/O herself/O ,/O washing/O the/O dirt/O and/O the/O dust/O from/O his/O arms/O and/O chest/O ,/O cleaning/O his/O face/O with/O a/O soft/O cloth/O ,/O soaping/O his/O long/O black/O hair/O and/O combing/O the/O knots/O and/O tangles/O from/O it/O till/O it/O shone/O again/O as/O she/O remembered/O ./O 
It/O was/O well/O past/O dark/O before/O she/O was/O done/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON was/O exhausted/O ./O 
She/O stopped/O for/O drink/O and/O food/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O all/O she/O could/O do/O to/O nibble/O at/O a/O fig/O and/O keep/O down/O a/O mouthful/O of/O water/O ./O 
Sleep/O would/O have/O been/O a/O release/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O slept/O enough/O .../O too/O long/O ,/O in/O truth/O ./O 
She/O owed/O this/O night/O to/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O for/O all/O the/O nights/O that/O had/O been/O ,/O and/O yet/O might/O be/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O memory/O of/O their/O first/O ride/O was/O with/O her/O when/O she/O led/O him/O out/O into/O the/O darkness/O ,/O for/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON believed/O that/O all/O things/O of/O importance/O in/O a/O man/O 's/O life/O must/O be/O done/O beneath/O the/O open/O sky/O ./O 
She/O told/O herself/O that/O there/O were/O powers/O stronger/O than/O hatred/O ,/O and/O spells/O older/O and/O truer/O than/O any/O the/O maegi/O had/O learned/O in/O Asshai/LOCATION ./O 
The/O night/O was/O black/O and/O moonless/O ,/O but/O overhead/O a/O million/O stars/O burned/O bright/O ./O 
She/O took/O that/O for/O an/O omen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O soft/O blanket/O of/O grass/O welcomed/O them/O here/O ,/O only/O the/O hard/O dusty/O ground/O ,/O bare/O and/O strewn/O with/O stones/O ./O 
No/O trees/O stirred/O in/O the/O wind/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O no/O stream/O to/O soothe/O her/O fears/O with/O the/O gentle/O music/O of/O water/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON told/O herself/O that/O the/O stars/O would/O be/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O our/O first/O ride/O together/O ,/O the/O day/O we/O wed./O ./O 
Remember/O the/O night/O we/O made/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Rhaego/O ,/O with/O the/O khalasar/O all/O around/O us/O and/O your/O eyes/O on/O my/O face/O ./O 
Remember/O how/O cool/O and/O clean/O the/O water/O was/O in/O the/O Womb/O of/O the/O World/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Remember/O ,/O my/O sun-andstars/O ./O 
Remember/O ,/O and/O come/O back/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O birth/O had/O left/O her/O too/O raw/O and/O torn/O to/O take/O him/O inside/O of/O her/O ,/O as/O she/O would/O have/O wanted/O ,/O but/O Doreah/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O other/O ways/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON used/O her/O hands/O ,/O her/O mouth/O ,/O her/O breasts/O ./O 
She/O raked/O him/O with/O her/O nails/O and/O covered/O him/O with/O kisses/O and/O whispered/O and/O prayed/O and/O told/O him/O stories/O ,/O and/O by/O the/O end/O she/O had/O bathed/O him/O with/O her/O tears/O ./O 
Yet/O Drogo/PERSON did/O not/O feel/O ,/O or/O speak/O ,/O or/O rise/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O when/O the/O bleak/O dawn/O broke/O over/O an/O empty/O horizon/O ,/O Dany/PERSON knew/O that/O he/O was/O truly/O lost/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O the/O sun/O rises/O in/O the/O west/O and/O sets/O in/O the/O east/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O sadly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O the/O seas/O go/O dry/O and/O mountains/O blow/O in/O the/O wind/O like/O leaves/O ./O 
When/O my/O womb/O quickens/O again/O ,/O and/O I/O bear/O a/O living/O child/O ./O 
Then/O you/O will/O return/O ,/O my/O sun-and-stars/O ,/O and/O not/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Never/O ,/O the/O darkness/O cried/O ,/O never/O never/O never/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O the/O tent/O Dany/PERSON found/O a/O cushion/O ,/O soft/O silk/O stuffed/O with/O feathers/O ./O 
She/O clutched/O it/O to/O her/O breasts/O as/O she/O walked/O back/O out/O to/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O to/O her/O sun-and-stars/O ./O 
If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O 
It/O hurt/O even/O to/O walk/O ,/O and/O she/O wanted/O to/O sleep/O ,/O to/O sleep/O and/O not/O to/O dream/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O knelt/O ,/O kissed/O Drogo/PERSON on/O the/O lips/O ,/O and/O pressed/O the/O cushion/O down/O across/O his/O face/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
