-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O came/O for/O Sansa/O on/O the/O third/O day/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O chose/O a/O simple/O dress/O of/O dark/O grey/O wool/O ,/O plainly/O cut/O but/O richly/O embroidered/O around/O the/O collar/O and/O sleeves/O ./O 
Her/O fingers/O felt/O thick/O and/O clumsy/O as/O she/O struggled/O with/O the/O silver/O fastenings/O without/O the/O benefit/O of/O servants/O ./O 
Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON had/O been/O confined/O with/O her/O ,/O but/O Jeyne/PERSON was/O useless/O ./O 
Her/O face/O was/O puffy/O from/O all/O her/O crying/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O not/O seem/O to/O stop/O sobbing/O about/O her/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O certain/O your/O father/O is/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O her/O when/O she/O had/O finally/O gotten/O the/O dress/O buttoned/O right/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O ask/O the/O queen/O to/O let/O you/O see/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O thought/O that/O kindness/O might/O lift/O Jeyne/PERSON 's/O spirits/O ,/O but/O the/O other/O girl/O just/O looked/O at/O her/O with/O red/O ,/O swollen/O eyes/O and/O began/O to/O cry/O all/O the/O harder/O ./O 
She/O was/O such/O a/O child/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O wept/O too/O ,/O the/O first/O day/O ./O 
Even/O within/O the/O stout/O walls/O of/O Maegor/PERSON 's/O Holdfast/O ,/O with/O her/O door/O closed/O and/O barred/O ,/O it/O was/O hard/O not/O to/O be/O terrified/O when/O the/O killing/O began/O ./O 
She/O had/O grown/O up/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O steel/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O and/O scarcely/O a/O day/O of/O her/O life/O had/O passed/O without/O hearing/O the/O clash/O of/O sword/O on/O sword/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O knowing/O that/O the/O fighting/O was/O real/O made/O all/O the/O difference/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
She/O heard/O it/O as/O she/O had/O never/O heard/O it/O before/O ,/O and/O there/O were/O other/O sounds/O as/O well/O ,/O grunts/O of/O pain/O ,/O angry/O curses/O ,/O shouts/O for/O help/O ,/O and/O the/O moans/O of/O wounded/O and/O dying/O men/O ./O 
In/O the/O songs/O ,/O the/O knights/O never/O screamed/O nor/O begged/O for/O mercy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O So/O she/O wept/O ,/O pleading/O through/O her/O door/O for/O them/O to/O tell/O her/O what/O was/O happening/O ,/O calling/O for/O her/O father/O ,/O for/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON ,/O for/O the/O king/O ,/O for/O her/O gallant/O prince/O ./O 
If/O the/O men/O guarding/O her/O heard/O her/O pleas/O ,/O they/O gave/O no/O answer/O ./O 
The/O only/O time/O the/O door/O opened/O was/O late/O that/O night/O ,/O when/O they/O thrust/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON inside/O ,/O bruised/O and/O shaking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O killing/O everyone/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O steward/O 's/O daughter/O had/O shrieked/O at/O her/O ./O 
She/O went/O on/O and/O on/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O had/O broken/O down/O her/O door/O with/O a/O warhammer/O ,/O she/O said/O ./O 
There/O were/O bodies/O on/O the/O stair/O of/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O and/O the/O steps/O were/O slick/O with/O blood/O ./O 
Sansa/O dried/O her/O own/O tears/O as/O she/O struggled/O to/O comfort/O her/O friend/O ./O 
They/O went/O to/O sleep/O in/O the/O same/O bed/O ,/O cradled/O in/O each/O other/O 's/O arms/O like/O sisters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O second/O day/O was/O even/O worse/O ./O 
The/O room/O where/O Sansa/PERSON had/O been/O confined/O was/O at/O the/O top/O of/O the/O highest/O tower/O of/O Maegor/PERSON 's/O Holdfast/O ./O 
From/O its/O window/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O that/O the/O heavy/O iron/O portcullis/O in/O the/O gatehouse/O was/O down/O ,/O and/O the/O drawbridge/O drawn/O up/O over/O the/O deep/O dry/O moat/O that/O separated/O the/O keep-within-a-keep/O from/O the/O larger/O castle/O that/O surrounded/O it/O ./O 
Lannister/O guardsmen/O prowled/O the/O walls/O with/O spears/O and/O crossbows/O to/O hand/O ./O 
The/O fighting/O was/O over/O ,/O and/O the/O silence/O of/O the/O grave/O had/O settled/O over/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ./O 
The/O only/O sounds/O were/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON 's/O endless/O whimpers/O and/O sobs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O were/O fed-hard/O cheese/O and/O fresh-baked/O bread/O and/O milk/O to/O break/O their/O fast/O ,/O roast/O chicken/O and/O greens/O at/O midday/O ,/O and/O a/O late/O supper/O of/O beef/O and/O barley/O stew-but/O the/O servants/O who/O brought/O the/O meals/O would/O not/O answer/O Sansa/O '/O s/O questions/O ./O 
That/O evening/O ,/O some/O women/O brought/O her/O clothes/O from/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O and/O some/O of/O Jeyne/PERSON 's/O things/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O they/O seemed/O nearly/O as/O frightened/O as/O Jeyne/PERSON ,/O and/O when/O she/O tried/O to/O talk/O to/O them/O ,/O they/O fled/O from/O her/O as/O if/O she/O had/O the/O grey/O plague/O ./O 
The/O guards/O outside/O the/O door/O still/O refused/O to/O let/O them/O leave/O the/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O I/O need/O to/O speak/O to/O the/O queen/O again/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O them/O ,/O as/O she/O told/O everyone/O she/O saw/O that/O day/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O 'll/O want/O to/O talk/O to/O me/O ,/O I/O know/O she/O will/O ./O 
Tell/O her/O I/O want/O to/O see/O her/O ,/O please/O ./O 
If/O not/O the/O queen/O ,/O then/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ,/O if/O you/O 'd/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
We/O 're/O to/O marry/O when/O we/O 're/O older/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O At/O sunset/O on/O the/O second/O day/O ,/O a/O great/O bell/O began/O to/O ring/O ./O 
Its/O voice/O was/O deep/O and/O sonorous/O ,/O and/O the/O long/O slow/O clanging/O filled/O Sansa/O with/O a/O sense/O of/O dread/O ./O 
The/O ringing/O went/O on/O and/O on/O ,/O and/O after/O a/O while/O they/O heard/O other/O bells/O answering/O from/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION on/O Visenya/PERSON 's/O Hill/PERSON ./O 
The/O sound/O rumbled/O across/O the/O city/O like/O thunder/O ,/O warning/O of/O the/O storm/O to/O come/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON asked/O ,/O covering/O her/O ears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O are/O they/O ringing/O the/O bells/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O is/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON could/O not/O say/O how/O she/O knew/O it/O ,/O yet/O she/O did/O ./O 
The/O slow/O ,/O endless/O clanging/O filled/O their/O room/O ,/O as/O mournful/O as/O a/O dirge/O ./O 
Had/O some/O enemy/O stormed/O the/O castle/O and/O murdered/O King/O Robert/PERSON ?/O 
Was/O that/O the/O meaning/O of/O the/O fighting/O they/O had/O heard/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O went/O to/O sleep/O wondering/O ,/O restless/O ,/O and/O fearful/O ./O 
Was/O her/O beautiful/O Joffrey/O the/O king/O now/O ?/O 
Or/O had/O they/O killed/O him/O too/O ?/O 
She/O was/O afraid/O for/O him/O ,/O and/O for/O her/O father/O ./O 
If/O only/O they/O would/O tell/O her/O what/O was/O happening/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O night/O Sansa/O dreamt/O of/O Joffrey/LOCATION on/O the/O throne/O ,/O with/O herself/O seated/O beside/O him/O in/O a/O gown/O of/O woven/O gold/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O crown/O on/O her/O head/O ,/O and/O everyone/O she/O had/O ever/O known/O came/O before/O her/O ,/O to/O bend/O the/O knee/O and/O say/O their/O courtesies/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O next/O morning/O ,/O the/O morning/O of/O the/O third/O day/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON Blount/PERSON of/O the/O Kingsguard/O came/O to/O escort/O her/O to/O the/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON was/O an/O ugly/O man/O with/O a/O broad/O chest/O and/O short/O ,/O bandy/O legs/O ./O 
His/O nose/O was/O flat/O ,/O his/O cheeks/O baggy/O with/O jowls/O ,/O his/O hair/O grey/O and/O brittle/O ./O 
Today/O he/O wore/O white/O velvet/O ,/O and/O his/O snowy/O cloak/O was/O fastened/O with/O a/O lion/O brooch/O ./O 
The/O beast/O had/O the/O soft/O sheen/O of/O gold/O ,/O and/O his/O eyes/O were/O tiny/O rubies/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O look/O very/O handsome/O and/O splendid/O this/O morning/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
A/O lady/O remembered/O her/O courtesies/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O resolved/O to/O be/O a/O lady/O no/O matter/O what/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON said/O in/O a/O flat/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Her/O Grace/O awaits/O ./O 
Come/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O were/O guards/O outside/O her/O door/O ,/O Lannister/O men-at-arms/O in/O crimson/O cloaks/O and/O lion-crested/O helms/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON made/O herself/O smile/O at/O them/O pleasantly/O and/O bid/O them/O a/O good/O morning/O as/O she/O passed/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O first/O time/O she/O had/O been/O allowed/O outside/O the/O chamber/O since/O Ser/PERSON Arys/PERSON Oakheart/PERSON had/O led/O her/O there/O two/O mornings/O past/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O keep/O you/O safe/O ,/O my/O sweet/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON had/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O never/O forgive/O me/O if/O anything/O happened/O to/O his/O precious/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O expected/O that/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON would/O escort/O her/O to/O the/O royal/O apartments/O ,/O but/O instead/O he/O led/O her/O out/O of/O Maegor/PERSON 's/O Holdfast/LOCATION ./O 
The/O bridge/O was/O down/O again/O ./O 
Some/O workmen/O were/O lowering/O a/O man/O on/O ropes/O into/O the/O depths/O of/O the/O dry/O moat/O ./O 
When/O Sansa/PERSON peered/O down/O ,/O she/O saw/O a/O body/O impaled/O on/O the/O huge/O iron/O spikes/O below/O ./O 
She/O averted/O her/O eyes/O quickly/O ,/O afraid/O to/O ask/O ,/O afraid/O to/O look/O too/O long/O ,/O afraid/O he/O might/O be/O someone/O she/O knew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O found/O Queen/PERSON Cersei/PERSON in/O the/O council/O chambers/O ,/O seated/O at/O the/O head/O of/O a/O long/O table/O littered/O with/O papers/O ,/O candles/O ,/O and/O blocks/O of/O sealing/O wax/O ./O 
The/O room/O was/O as/O splendid/O as/O any/O that/O Sansa/PERSON had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
She/O stared/O in/O awe/O at/O the/O carved/O wooden/O screen/O and/O the/O twin/O sphinxes/O that/O sat/O beside/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON said/O when/O they/O were/O ushered/O inside/O by/O another/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Mandon/PERSON of/O the/O curiously/O dead/O face/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O brought/O the/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O hoped/O Joffrey/PERSON might/O be/O with/O her/O ./O 
Her/O prince/O was/O not/O there/O ,/O but/O three/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O councillors/O were/O ./O 
Lord/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON sat/O on/O the/O queen/O 's/O left/O hand/O ,/O Grand/PERSON Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O table/O ,/O while/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON hovered/O over/O them/O ,/O smelling/O flowery/O ./O 
All/O of/O them/O were/O clad/O in/O black/O ,/O she/O realized/O with/O a/O feeling/O of/O dread/O ./O 
Mourning/O clothes/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O wore/O a/O high-collared/O black/O silk/O gown/O ,/O with/O a/O hundred/O dark/O red/O rubies/O sewn/O into/O her/O bodice/O ,/O covering/O her/O from/O neck/O to/O bosom/O ./O 
They/O were/O cut/O in/O the/O shape/O of/O teardrops/O ,/O as/O if/O the/O queen/O were/O weeping/O blood/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON smiled/O to/O see/O her/O ,/O and/O Sansa/O thought/O it/O was/O the/O sweetest/O and/O saddest/O smile/O she/O had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O my/O sweet/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O you/O 've/O been/O asking/O for/O me/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sorry/O that/O I/O could/O not/O send/O for/O you/O sooner/O ./O 
Matters/O have/O been/O very/O unsettled/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O not/O had/O a/O moment/O ./O 
I/O trust/O my/O people/O have/O been/O taking/O good/O care/O of/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Everyone/O has/O been/O very/O sweet/O and/O pleasant/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O thank/O you/O ever/O so/O much/O for/O asking/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O politely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O ,/O well/O ,/O no/O one/O will/O talk/O to/O us/O or/O tell/O us/O what/O 's/O happened/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON seemed/O puzzled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O put/O the/O steward/O 's/O girl/O in/O with/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O did/O not/O know/O what/O else/O to/O do/O with/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Next/O time/O ,/O you/O will/O ask/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O her/O voice/O sharp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O only/O know/O what/O sort/O of/O tales/O she/O 's/O been/O filling/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O head/O with/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jeyne/O 's/O scared/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O wo/O n't/O stop/O crying/O ./O 
I/O promised/O her/O I/O 'd/O ask/O if/O she/O could/O see/O her/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Old/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O lowered/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Her/O father/O is/O well/O ,/O is/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O anxiously/O ./O 
She/O knew/O there/O had/O been/O fighting/O ,/O but/O surely/O no/O one/O would/O harm/O a/O steward/O ./O 
Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON did/O not/O even/O wear/O a/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON looked/O at/O each/O of/O the/O councillors/O in/O turn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O have/O Sansa/O fretting/O needlessly/O ./O 
What/O shall/O we/O do/O with/O this/O little/O friend/O of/O hers/O ,/O my/O lords/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON leaned/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O find/O a/O place/O for/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O in/O the/O city/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O take/O me/O for/O a/O fool/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O ignored/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Boros/O ,/O escort/O this/O girl/O to/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON '/O s/O apartments/O and/O instruct/O his/O people/O to/O keep/O her/O there/O until/O he/O comes/O for/O her/O ./O 
Tell/O her/O that/O Littlefinger/PERSON will/O be/O taking/O her/O to/O see/O her/O father/O ,/O that/O ought/O to/O calm/O her/O down/O ./O 
I/O want/O her/O gone/O before/O Sansa/O returns/O to/O her/O chamber/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O bowed/O deeply/O ,/O spun/O on/O his/O heel/O ,/O and/O took/O his/O leave/O ,/O his/O long/O white/O cloak/O stirring/O the/O air/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O was/O confused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O understand/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O is/O Jeyne/PERSON 's/O father/O ?/O 
Why/O ca/O n't/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON take/O her/O to/O him/O instead/O of/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON having/O to/O do/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O promised/O herself/O she/O would/O be/O a/O lady/O ,/O gentle/O as/O the/O queen/O and/O as/O strong/O as/O her/O mother/O ,/O the/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ,/O but/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O she/O was/O scared/O again/O ./O 
For/O a/O second/O she/O thought/O she/O might/O cry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O you/O sending/O her/O ?/O 
She/O has/O n't/O done/O anything/O wrong/O ,/O she/O 's/O a/O good/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O upset/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O said/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O ca/O n't/O be/O having/O that/O ./O 
Not/O another/O word/O ,/O now/O ./O 
Lord/O Baelish/PERSON will/O see/O that/O Jeyne/PERSON 's/O well/O taken/O care/O of/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O patted/O the/O chair/O beside/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sit/O down/O ,/O Sansa/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O talk/O to/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O seated/O herself/O beside/O the/O queen/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON smiled/O again/O ,/O but/O that/O did/O not/O make/O her/O feel/O any/O less/O anxious/O ./O 
Varys/PERSON was/O wringing/O his/O soft/O hands/O together/O ,/O Grand/PERSON Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON kept/O his/O sleepy/O eyes/O on/O the/O papers/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ,/O but/O she/O could/O feel/O Little/O finger/O staring/O ./O 
Something/O about/O the/O way/O the/O small/O man/O looked/O at/O her/O made/O Sansa/PERSON feel/O as/O though/O she/O had/O no/O clothes/O on/O ./O 
Goose/O Burnps/O pimpled/O her/O skin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sweet/O Sansa/O ,/O \/O ''/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON said/O ,/O laying/O a/O soft/O hand/O on/O her/O wrist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Such/O a/O beautiful/O child/O ./O 
I/O do/O hope/O you/O know/O how/O much/O Joffrey/PERSON and/O I/O love/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O breathless/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON was/O forgotten/O ./O 
Her/O prince/O loved/O her/O ./O 
Nothing/O else/O mattered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O queen/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O of/O you/O almost/O as/O my/O own/O daughter/O ./O 
And/O I/O know/O the/O love/O you/O bear/O for/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O gave/O a/O weary/O shake/O of/O her/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O afraid/O we/O have/O some/O grave/O news/O about/O your/O lord/O father/O ./O 
You/O must/O be/O brave/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O quiet/O words/O gave/O Sansa/O a/O chill/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O is/O a/O traitor/O ,/O dear/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON lifted/O his/O ancient/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O my/O own/O ears/O ,/O I/O heard/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON swear/O to/O our/O beloved/O King/O Robert/PERSON that/O he/O would/O protect/O the/O young/O princes/O as/O if/O they/O were/O his/O own/O sons/O ./O 
And/O yet/O the/O moment/O the/O king/O was/O dead/O ,/O he/O called/O the/O small/O council/O together/O to/O steal/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON 's/O rightful/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O blurted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O n't/O do/O that/O ./O 
He/O would/O n't/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O picked/O up/O a/O letter/O ./O 
The/O paper/O was/O torn/O and/O stiff/O with/O dried/O blood/O ,/O but/O the/O broken/O seal/O was/O her/O father/O 's/O ,/O the/O direwo/O If/O stamped/O in/O pale/O wax/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O found/O this/O on/O the/O captain/O of/O your/O household/O guard/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ./O 
It/O is/O a/O letter/O to/O my/O late/O husband/O 's/O brother/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O inviting/O him/O to/O take/O the/O crown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O there/O 's/O been/O a/O mistake/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sudden/O panic/O made/O her/O dizzy/O and/O faint/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O send/O for/O my/O father/O ,/O he/O 'll/O tell/O you/O ,/O he/O would/O never/O write/O such/O a/O letter/O ,/O the/O king/O was/O his/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON thought/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O betrayal/O would/O have/O broken/O his/O heart/O ./O 
The/O gods/O are/O kind/O ,/O that/O he/O did/O not/O live/O to/O see/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O sweetling/O ,/O you/O must/O see/O what/O a/O dreadful/O position/O this/O has/O left/O us/O in/O ./O 
You/O are/O innocent/O of/O any/O wrong/O ,/O we/O all/O know/O that/O ,/O and/O yet/O you/O are/O the/O daughter/O of/O a/O traitor/O ./O 
How/O can/O I/O allow/O you/O to/O marry/O my/O son/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O I/O love/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O wailed/O ,/O confused/O and/O frightened/O ./O 
What/O did/O they/O mean/O to/O do/O to/O her/O ?/O 
What/O had/O they/O done/O to/O her/O father/O ?/O 
It/O was/O not/O supposed/O to/O happen/O this/O way/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O wed/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O they/O were/O betrothed/O ,/O he/O was/O promised/O to/O her/O ,/O she/O had/O even/O dreamed/O about/O it/O ./O 
It/O was/O n't/O fair/O to/O take/O him/O away/O from/O her/O on/O account/O of/O whatever/O her/O father/O might/O have/O done/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O well/O I/O know/O that/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON said/O ,/O her/O voice/O so/O kind/O and/O sweet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O else/O should/O you/O have/O come/O to/O me/O and/O told/O me/O of/O your/O father/O 's/O plan/O to/O send/O you/O away/O from/O us/O ,/O if/O not/O for/O love/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O for/O love/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O in/O a/O rush/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O would/O n't/O even/O give/O me/O leave/O to/O say/O farewell/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O was/O the/O good/O girl/O ,/O the/O obedient/O girl/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O felt/O as/O wicked/O as/O Arya/PERSON that/O morning/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O sneaking/O away/O from/O Septa/O Mordane/O ,/O defying/O her/O lord/O father/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O done/O anything/O so/O willful/O before/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O never/O have/O done/O it/O then/O if/O she/O had/O n't/O loved/O Joffrey/PERSON as/O much/O as/O she/O did/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O going/O to/O take/O me/O back/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION and/O marry/O me/O to/O some/O hedge/O knight/O ,/O even/O though/O it/O was/O Joff/PERSON I/O wanted/O ./O 
I/O told/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O n't/O listen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O had/O been/O her/O last/O hope/O ./O 
The/O king/O could/O command/O Father/O to/O let/O her/O stay/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O marry/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ,/O Sansa/PERSON knew/O he/O could/O ,/O but/O the/O king/O had/O always/O frightened/O her/O ./O 
He/O was/O loud/O and/O rough-voiced/O and/O drunk/O as/O often/O as/O not/O ,/O and/O he/O would/O probably/O have/O just/O sent/O her/O back/O to/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O if/O they/O even/O let/O her/O see/O him/O ./O 
So/O she/O went/O to/O the/O queen/O instead/O ,/O and/O poured/O out/O her/O heart/O ,/O and/O Cersei/PERSON had/O listened/O and/O thanked/O her/O sweetly/O .../O only/O then/O Ser/PERSON Arys/PERSON had/O escorted/O her/O to/O the/O high/O room/O in/O Maegor/LOCATION 's/O Holdfast/LOCATION and/O posted/O guards/O ,/O and/O a/O few/O hours/O later/O ,/O the/O fighting/O had/O begun/O outside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O finished/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O have/O to/O let/O me/O marry/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O I/O 'll/O be/O ever/O so/O good/O a/O wife/O to/O him/O ,/O you/O 'll/O see/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O be/O a/O queen/O just/O like/O you/O ,/O I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON looked/O to/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O of/O the/O council/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O say/O to/O her/O plea/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O poor/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O murmured/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O love/O so/O true/O and/O innocent/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O cruel/O to/O deny/O it/O .../O and/O yet/O ,/O what/O can/O we/O do/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O father/O stands/O condemned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O soft/O hands/O washed/O each/O other/O in/O a/O gesture/O of/O helpless/O distress/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O child/O born/O of/O traitor/O 's/O seed/O will/O find/O that/O betrayal/O comes/O naturally/O to/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O is/O a/O sweet/O thing/O now/O ,/O but/O in/O ten/O years/O ,/O who/O can/O say/O what/O treasons/O she/O may/O hatch/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O said/O ,/O horrified/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O ,/O I/O 'd/O never/O .../O I/O would/O n't/O betray/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O I/O love/O him/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ,/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O so/O poignant/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O yet/O ,/O it/O is/O truly/O said/O that/O blood/O runs/O truer/O than/O oaths/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O reminds/O me/O of/O the/O mother/O ,/O not/O the/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON said/O quietly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O at/O her/O ./O 
The/O hair/O ,/O the/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O is/O the/O very/O image/O of/O Cat/O at/O the/O same/O age/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O troubled/O ,/O and/O yet/O Sansa/O could/O see/O kindness/O in/O her/O clear/O green/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Child/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O if/O I/O could/O truly/O believe/O that/O you/O were/O not/O like/O your/O father/O ,/O why/O nothing/O should/O please/O me/O more/O than/O to/O see/O you/O wed/O to/O my/O Joffrey/O ./O 
I/O know/O he/O loves/O you/O with/O all/O his/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O yet/O ,/O I/O fear/O that/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON and/O the/O Grand/O Maester/O have/O the/O right/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O blood/O will/O tell/O ./O 
I/O have/O only/O to/O remember/O how/O your/O sister/O set/O her/O wolf/O on/O my/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O like/O Arya/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O blurted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O has/O the/O traitor/O 's/O blood/O ,/O not/O me/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O good/O ,/O ask/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON ,/O she/O 'll/O tell/O you/O ,/O I/O only/O want/O to/O be/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O loyal/O and/O loving/O wife/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O felt/O the/O weight/O of/O Cersei/PERSON '/O s/O eyes/O as/O the/O queen/O studied/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O believe/O you/O mean/O it/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O turned/O to/O face/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O ,/O it/O seems/O to/O me/O that/O if/O the/O rest/O of/O her/O kin/O were/O to/O remain/O loyal/O in/O this/O terrible/O time/O ,/O that/O would/O go/O a/O long/O way/O toward/O laying/O our/O fears/O to/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON stroked/O his/O huge/O soft/O beard/O ,/O his/O wide/O brow/O furrowed/O in/O thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON has/O three/O sons/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mere/O boys/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON said/O with/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O be/O more/O concerned/O with/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON and/O the/O Tullys/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O took/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O hand/O in/O both/O of/O hers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Child/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O your/O letters/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O nodded/O nervously/O ./O 
She/O could/O read/O and/O write/O better/O than/O any/O of/O her/O brothers/O ,/O although/O she/O was/O hopeless/O at/O sums/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O pleased/O to/O hear/O that/O ./O 
Perhaps/O there/O is/O hope/O for/O you/O and/O Joffrey/PERSON still/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O want/O me/O to/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O must/O write/O your/O lady/O mother/O ,/O and/O your/O brother/O ,/O the/O eldest/O .../O what/O is/O his/O name/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O word/O of/O your/O lord/O father/O 's/O treason/O will/O no/O doubt/O reach/O them/O soon/O ./O 
Better/O that/O it/O should/O come/O from/O you/O ./O 
You/O must/O tell/O them/O how/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON betrayed/O his/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O wanted/O Joffrey/PERSON desperately/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O not/O think/O she/O had/O the/O courage/O to/O do/O as/O the/O queen/O was/O asking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O he/O never/O .../O I/O do/O n't/O .../O Your/O Grace/O ,/O I/O would/O n't/O know/O what/O to/O say/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O queen/O patted/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O will/O tell/O you/O what/O to/O write/O ,/O child/O ./O 
The/O important/O thing/O is/O that/O you/O urge/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON and/O your/O brother/O to/O keep/O the/O king/O 's/O peace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O go/O hard/O for/O them/O if/O they/O do/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O the/O love/O you/O bear/O them/O ,/O you/O must/O urge/O them/O to/O walk/O the/O path/O of/O wisdom/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O lady/O mother/O will/O no/O doubt/O fear/O for/O you/O dreadfully/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O tell/O her/O that/O you/O are/O well/O and/O in/O our/O care/O ,/O that/O we/O are/O treating/O you/O gently/O and/O seeing/O to/O your/O every/O want/O ./O 
Bid/O them/O to/O come/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O pledge/O their/O fealty/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON when/O he/O takes/O his/O throne/O ./O 
If/O they/O do/O that/O .../O why/O ,/O then/O we/O shall/O know/O that/O there/O is/O no/O taint/O in/O your/O blood/O ,/O and/O when/O you/O come/O into/O the/O flower/O of/O your/O womanhood/O ,/O you/O shall/O wed/O the/O king/O in/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION ,/O before/O the/O eyes/O of/O gods/O and/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O .../O wed/O the/O king/O .../O The/O words/O made/O her/O breath/O come/O faster/O ,/O yet/O still/O Sansa/O hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O .../O if/O I/O might/O see/O my/O father/O ,/O talk/O to/O him/O about/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Treason/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON hinted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O disappoint/O me/O ,/O Sansa/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O said/O ,/O with/O eyes/O gone/O hard/O as/O stones/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 've/O told/O you/O of/O your/O father/O 's/O crimes/O ./O 
If/O you/O are/O truly/O as/O loyal/O as/O you/O say/O ,/O why/O should/O you/O want/O to/O see/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O only/O meant/O Sansa/PERSON felt/O her/O eyes/O grow/O wet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O not/O .../O please/O ,/O he/O has/O n't/O been/O .../O hurt/O ,/O or/O .../O or/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON has/O not/O been/O harmed/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O said/O ./O 
But/O .../O what/O 's/O to/O become/O of/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O a/O matter/O for/O the/O king/O to/O decide/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O announced/O ponderously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O king/O !/O 
Sansa/PERSON blinked/O back/O her/O tears/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON was/O the/O king/O now/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
Her/O gallant/O prince/O would/O never/O hurt/O her/O father/O ,/O no/O matter/O what/O he/O might/O have/O done/O ./O 
If/O she/O went/O to/O him/O and/O pleaded/O for/O mercy/O ,/O she/O was/O certain/O he/O 'd/O listen/O ./O 
He/O had/O to/O listen/O ,/O he/O loved/O her/O ,/O even/O the/O queen/O said/O so/O ./O 
Jo/PERSON ff/O would/O need/O to/O punish/O Father/O ,/O the/O lords/O would/O expect/O it/O ,/O but/O perhaps/O he/O could/O send/O him/O back/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O or/O exile/O him/O to/O one/O of/O the/O Free/O Cities/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O 
It/O would/O only/O have/O to/O be/O for/O a/O few/O years/O ./O 
By/O then/O she/O and/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O be/O married/O ./O 
Once/O she/O was/O queen/O ,/O she/O could/O persuade/O Joff/PERSON to/O bring/O Father/O back/O and/O grant/O him/O a/O pardon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Only/O .../O if/O Mother/PERSON or/O Robb/PERSON did/O anything/O treasonous/O ,/O called/O the/O banners/O or/O refused/O to/O swear/O fealty/O or/O anything/O ,/O it/O would/O all/O go/O wrong/O ./O 
Her/O Joffrey/PERSON was/O good/O and/O kind/O ,/O she/O knew/O it/O in/O her/O heart/O ,/O but/O a/O king/O had/O to/O be/O stern/O with/O rebels/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O make/O them/O understand/O ,/O she/O had/O to/O !/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O .../O I/O 'll/O write/O the/O letters/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O With/O a/O smile/O as/O warm/O as/O the/O sunrise/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON leaned/O close/O and/O kissed/O her/O gently/O on/O the/O cheek/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O knew/O you/O would/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON will/O be/O so/O proud/O when/O I/O tell/O him/O what/O courage/O and/O good/O sense/O you/O 've/O shown/O here/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O In/O the/O end/O ,/O she/O wrote/O four/O letters/O ./O 
To/O her/O mother/O ,/O the/O Lady/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O and/O to/O her/O brothers/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O to/O her/O aunt/O and/O her/O grandfather/O as/O well/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
By/O the/O time/O she/O had/O done/O ,/O her/O fingers/O were/O cramped/O and/O stiff/O and/O stained/O with/O ink/O ./O 
Varys/PERSON had/O her/O father/O 's/O seal/O ./O 
She/O warmed/O the/O pale/O white/O beeswax/O over/O a/O candle/O ,/O poured/O it/O carefully/O ,/O and/O watched/O as/O the/O eunuch/O stamped/O each/O letter/O with/O the/O direwolf/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Stark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON and/O all/O her/O things/O were/O gone/O when/O Ser/PERSON Mandon/PERSON Moore/PERSON returned/O Sansa/O to/O the/O high/O tower/O of/O Maegor/PERSON 's/O Holdfast/O ./O 
No/O more/O weeping/O ,/O she/O thought/O gratefully/O ./O 
Yet/O somehow/O it/O seemed/O colder/O with/O Jeyne/PERSON gone/O ,/O even/O after/O she/O 'd/O built/O a/O fire/O ./O 
She/O pulled/O a/O chair/O close/O to/O the/O hearth/O ,/O took/O down/O one/O of/O her/O favorite/O books/O ,/O and/O lost/O herself/O in/O the/O stories/O of/O Florian/PERSON and/O Jonquil/O ,/O of/O Lady/O Sheila/PERSON and/O the/O Rainbow/O Knight/O ,/O of/O valiant/O Prince/PERSON Aemon/PERSON and/O his/O doomed/O love/O for/O his/O brother/O 's/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O until/O later/O that/O night/O ,/O as/O she/O was/O drifting/O off/O to/O sleep/O ,/O that/O Sansa/O realized/O she/O had/O forgotten/O to/O ask/O about/O her/O sister/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
