-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O land/O was/O red/O and/O dead/O and/O parched/O ,/O and/O good/O wood/O was/O hard/O to/O come/O by/O ./O 
Her/O foragers/O returned/O with/O gnarled/O cottonwoods/O ,/O purple/O brush/O ,/O sheaves/O of/O brown/O grass/O ./O 
They/O took/O the/O two/O straightest/O trees/O ,/O hacked/O the/O limbs/O and/O branches/O from/O them/O ,/O skinned/O off/O their/O bark/O ,/O and/O split/O them/O ,/O laying/O the/O logs/O in/O a/O square/O ./O 
Its/O center/O they/O filled/O with/O straw/O ,/O brush/O ,/O bark/O shavings/O ,/O and/O bundles/O of/O dry/O grass/O ./O 
Rakharo/PERSON chose/O a/O stallion/O from/O the/O small/O herd/O that/O remained/O to/O them/O ;/O he/O was/O not/O the/O equal/O of/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O red/O ,/O but/O few/O horses/O were/O ./O 
In/O the/O center/O of/O the/O square/O ,/O Aggo/O fed/O him/O a/O withered/O apple/O and/O dropped/O him/O in/O an/O instant/O with/O an/O axe/O blow/O between/O the/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bound/O hand/O and/O foot/O ,/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON watched/O from/O the/O dust/O with/O disquiet/O in/O her/O black/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O enough/O to/O kill/O a/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O Dany/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O itself/O ,/O the/O blood/O is/O nothing/O ./O 
You/O do/O not/O have/O the/O words/O to/O make/O a/O spell/O ,/O nor/O the/O wisdom/O to/O find/O them/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O bloodmagic/O is/O a/O game/O for/O children/O ?/O 
You/O call/O me/O maegi/O as/O if/O it/O were/O a/O curse/O ,/O but/O all/O it/O means/O is/O wise/O ./O 
You/O are/O a/O child/O ,/O with/O a/O child/O 's/O ignorance/O ./O 
Whatever/O you/O mean/O to/O do/O ,/O it/O will/O not/O work/O ./O 
Loose/O me/O from/O these/O bonds/O and/O I/O will/O help/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O tired/O of/O the/O maegi/O 's/O braying/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O Jhogo/PERSON ./O 
He/O took/O his/O whip/O to/O her/O ,/O and/O after/O that/O the/O godswife/O kept/O silent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Over/O the/O carcass/O of/O the/O horse/O ,/O they/O built/O a/O platform/O of/O hewn/O logs/O ;/O trunks/O of/O smaller/O trees/O and/O limbs/O from/O the/O greater/O ,/O and/O the/O thickest/O straightest/O branches/O they/O could/O find/O ./O 
They/O laid/O the/O wood/O east/O to/O west/O ,/O from/O sunrise/O to/O sunset/O ./O 
On/O the/O platform/O they/O piled/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O treasures/O :/O his/O great/O tent/O ,/O his/O painted/O vests/O ,/O his/O saddles/O and/O harness/O ,/O the/O whip/O his/O father/O had/O given/O him/O when/O he/O came/O to/O manhood/O ,/O the/O arakh/O he/O had/O used/O to/O slay/O Khal/PERSON Ogo/PERSON and/O his/O son/O ,/O a/O mighty/O dragonbone/O bow/O ./O 
Aggo/O would/O have/O added/O the/O weapons/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O bloodriders/O had/O given/O Dany/PERSON for/O bride/O gifts/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O she/O forbade/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Those/O are/O mine/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O mean/O to/O keep/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Another/O layer/O of/O brush/O was/O piled/O about/O the/O khal/O 's/O treasures/O ,/O and/O bundles/O of/O dried/O grass/O scattered/O over/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON drew/O her/O aside/O as/O the/O sun/O was/O creeping/O toward/O its/O zenith/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Princess/O .../O \/O ''/O he/O began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O do/O you/O call/O me/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON challenged/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O Viserys/PERSON was/O your/O king/O ,/O was/O he/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Viserys/O is/O dead/O ./O 
I/O am/O his/O heir/O ,/O the/O last/O blood/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Targaryen/O ./O 
Whatever/O was/O his/O is/O mine/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O .../O queen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O going/O to/O one/O knee/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sword/O that/O was/O his/O is/O yours/O ,/O Daenerys/PERSON ./O 
And/O my/O heart/O as/O well/O ,/O that/O never/O belonged/O to/O your/O brother/O ./O 
I/O am/O only/O a/O knight/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O nothing/O to/O offer/O you/O but/O exile/O ,/O but/O I/O beg/O you/O ,/O hear/O me/O ./O 
Let/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON go/O ./O 
You/O shall/O not/O be/O alone/O ./O 
I/O promise/O you/O ,/O no/O man/O shall/O take/O you/O to/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON unless/O you/O wish/O to/O go/O ./O 
You/O need/O not/O join/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O ./O 
Come/O east/O with/O me/O ./O 
Yi/PERSON Ti/PERSON ,/O Oarth/LOCATION ,/O the/O Jade/O Sea/O ,/O Asshai/PERSON by/O the/O Shadow/O ./O 
We/O will/O see/O all/O the/O wonders/O yet/O unseen/O ,/O and/O drink/O what/O wines/O the/O gods/O see/O fit/O to/O serve/O us/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
I/O know/O what/O you/O intend/O ./O 
Do/O not/O ./O 
Do/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O must/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
She/O touched/O his/O face/O ,/O fondly/O ,/O sadly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O understand/O that/O you/O loved/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O in/O a/O voice/O thick/O with/O despair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O loved/O my/O lady/O wife/O once/O ,/O yet/O I/O did/O not/O die/O with/O her/O ./O 
You/O are/O my/O queen/O ,/O my/O sword/O is/O yours/O ,/O but/O do/O not/O ask/O me/O to/O stand/O aside/O as/O you/O climb/O on/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O pyre/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O watch/O you/O burn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O what/O you/O fear/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON kissed/O him/O lightly/O on/O his/O broad/O forehead/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O such/O a/O child/O as/O that/O ,/O sweet/O ser/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O mean/O to/O die/O with/O him/O ?/O 
You/O swear/O it/O ,/O my/O queen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O swear/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O that/O by/O rights/O were/O hers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O third/O level/O of/O the/O platform/O was/O woven/O of/O branches/O no/O thicker/O than/O a/O finger/O ,/O and/O covered/O with/O dry/O leaves/O and/O twigs/O ./O 
They/O laid/O them/O north/O to/O south/O ,/O from/O ice/O to/O fire/O ,/O and/O piled/O them/O high/O with/O soft/O cushions/O and/O sleeping/O silks/O ./O 
The/O sun/O had/O begun/O to/O lower/O toward/O the/O west/O by/O the/O time/O they/O were/O done/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON called/O the/O Dothraki/O around/O her/O ./O 
Fewer/O than/O a/O hundred/O were/O left/O ./O 
How/O many/O had/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION started/O with/O ?/O 
she/O wondered/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O matter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O be/O my/O khalasar/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O the/O faces/O of/O slaves/O ./O 
I/O free/O you/O ./O 
Take/O off/O your/O collars/O ./O 
Go/O if/O you/O wish/O ,/O no/O one/O shall/O harm/O you/O ./O 
If/O you/O stay/O ,/O it/O will/O be/O as/O brothers/O and/O sisters/O ,/O husbands/O and/O wives/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O black/O eyes/O watched/O her/O ,/O wary/O ,/O expressionless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O the/O children/O ,/O women/O ,/O the/O wrinkled/O faces/O of/O the/O aged/O ./O 
I/O was/O a/O child/O yesterday/O ./O 
Today/O I/O am/O a/O woman/O ./O 
Tomorrow/O I/O will/O be/O old/O ./O 
To/O each/O of/O you/O I/O say/O ,/O give/O me/O your/O hands/O and/O your/O hearts/O ,/O and/O there/O will/O always/O be/O a/O place/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O turned/O to/O the/O three/O young/O warriors/O of/O her/O khas/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhogo/O ,/O to/O you/O I/O give/O the/O silver-handled/O whip/O that/O was/O my/O bride/O gift/O ,/O and/O name/O you/O ko/O ,/O and/O ask/O your/O oath/O ,/O that/O you/O will/O live/O and/O die/O as/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O riding/O at/O my/O side/O to/O keep/O me/O safe/O from/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON took/O the/O whip/O from/O her/O hands/O ,/O but/O his/O face/O was/O confused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O hesitantly/O ,/O \/O ``/O this/O is/O not/O done/O ./O 
It/O would/O shame/O me/O ,/O to/O be/O bloodrider/O to/O a/O woman/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aggo/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON called/O ,/O paying/O no/O heed/O to/O Jhogo/PERSON 's/O words/O ./O 
If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O you/O I/O give/O the/O dragonbone/O bow/O that/O was/O my/O bride/O gift/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O double-curved/O ,/O shiny/O black/O and/O exquisite/O ,/O taller/O than/O she/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O name/O you/O ko/O ,/O and/O ask/O your/O oath/O ,/O that/O you/O should/O live/O and/O die/O as/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O riding/O at/O my/O side/O to/O keep/O me/O safe/O from/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Aggo/PERSON accepted/O the/O bow/O with/O lowered/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O not/O say/O these/O words/O ./O 
Only/O a/O man/O can/O lead/O a/O khalasar/O or/O name/O a/O ko/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rakharo/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O turning/O away/O from/O the/O refusal/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O shall/O have/O the/O great/O arakh/O that/O was/O my/O bride/O gift/O ,/O with/O hilt/O and/O blade/O chased/O in/O gold/O ./O 
And/O you/O too/O I/O name/O my/O ko/O ,/O and/O ask/O that/O you/O live/O and/O die/O as/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O riding/O at/O my/O side/O to/O keep/O me/O safe/O from/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rakharo/PERSON said/O ,/O taking/O the/O arakh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O ride/O at/O your/O side/O to/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON beneath/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION ,/O and/O keep/O you/O safe/O from/O harm/O until/O you/O take/O your/O place/O with/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O ./O 
No/O more/O can/O I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O nodded/O ,/O as/O calmly/O as/O if/O she/O had/O not/O heard/O his/O answer/O ,/O and/O turned/O to/O the/O last/O of/O her/O champions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O first/O and/O greatest/O of/O my/O knights/O ,/O I/O have/O no/O bride/O gift/O to/O give/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O one/O day/O you/O shall/O have/O from/O my/O hands/O a/O longsword/O like/O none/O the/O world/O has/O ever/O seen/O ,/O dragon/O -/O forged/O and/O made/O of/O Valyrian/O steel/O ./O 
And/O I/O would/O ask/O for/O your/O oath/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O it/O ,/O my/O queen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O kneeling/O to/O lay/O his/O sword/O at/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O vow/O to/O serve/O you/O ,/O to/O obey/O you/O ,/O to/O die/O for/O you/O if/O need/O be/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Whatever/O may/O come/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Whatever/O may/O come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O hold/O you/O to/O that/O oath/O ./O 
I/O pray/O you/O never/O regret/O the/O giving/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON lifted/O him/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
Stretching/O on/O her/O toes/O to/O reach/O his/O lips/O ,/O she/O kissed/O the/O knight/O gently/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O first/O of/O my/O Queensguard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O could/O feel/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O khalasar/O on/O her/O as/O she/O entered/O her/O tent/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O were/O muttering/O and/O giving/O her/O strange/O sideways/O looks/O from/O the/O corners/O of/O their/O dark/O almond/O eyes/O ./O 
They/O thought/O her/O mad/O ,/O Dany/PERSON realized/O ./O 
Perhaps/O she/O was/O ./O 
She/O would/O know/O soon/O enough/O ./O 
If/O I/O look/O back/O I/O am/O lost/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O bath/O was/O scalding/O hot/O when/O Irri/PERSON helped/O her/O into/O the/O tub/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON did/O not/O flinch/O or/O cry/O aloud/O ./O 
She/O liked/O the/O heat/O ./O 
It/O made/O her/O feel/O clean/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON had/O scented/O the/O water/O with/O the/O oils/O she/O had/O found/O in/O the/O market/O in/O Vaes/O Dothrak/O ;/O the/O steam/O rose/O moist/O and/O fragrant/O ./O 
Doreah/PERSON washed/O her/O hair/O and/O combed/O it/O out/O ,/O working/O loose/O the/O mats/O and/O tangles/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON scrubbed/O her/O back/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON closed/O her/O eyes/O and/O let/O the/O smell/O and/O the/O warmth/O enfold/O her/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O heat/O soaking/O through/O the/O soreness/O between/O her/O thighs/O ./O 
She/O shuddered/O when/O it/O entered/O her/O ,/O and/O her/O pain/O and/O stiffness/O seemed/O to/O dissolve/O ./O 
She/O floated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O was/O clean/O ,/O her/O handmaids/O helped/O her/O from/O the/O water/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON and/O Jhiqui/PERSON fanned/O her/O dry/O ,/O while/O Doreah/PERSON brushed/O her/O hair/O until/O it/O fell/O like/O a/O river/O of/O liquid/O silver/O down/O her/O back/O ./O 
They/O scented/O her/O with/O spiceflower/O and/O cinnamon/O ;/O a/O touch/O on/O each/O wrist/O ,/O behind/O her/O ears/O ,/O on/O the/O tips/O of/O her/O milk/O -/O heavy/O breasts/O ./O 
The/O last/O dab/O was/O for/O her/O sex/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON 's/O finger/O felt/O as/O light/O and/O cool/O as/O a/O lover/O 's/O kiss/O as/O it/O slid/O softly/O up/O between/O her/O lips/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O ,/O Dany/PERSON sent/O them/O all/O away/O ,/O so/O she/O might/O prepare/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON for/O his/O final/O ride/O into/O the/O night/O lands/O ./O 
She/O washed/O his/O body/O clean/O and/O brushed/O and/O oiled/O his/O hair/O ,/O running/O her/O fingers/O through/O it/O for/O the/O last/O time/O ,/O feeling/O the/O weight/O of/O it/O ,/O remembering/O the/O first/O time/O she/O had/O touched/O it/O ,/O the/O night/O of/O their/O wedding/O ride/O ./O 
His/O hair/O had/O never/O been/O cut/O ./O 
How/O many/O men/O could/O die/O with/O their/O hair/O uncut/O ?/O 
She/O buried/O her/O face/O in/O it/O and/O inhaled/O the/O dark/O fragrance/O of/O the/O oils/O ./O 
He/O smelled/O like/O grass/O and/O warm/O earth/O ,/O like/O smoke/O and/O semen/O and/O horses/O ./O 
He/O smelled/O like/O Drogo/PERSON ./O 
Forgive/O me/O ,/O sun/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
Forgive/O me/O for/O all/O I/O have/O done/O and/O all/O I/O must/O do/O ./O 
I/O paid/O the/O price/O ,/O my/O star/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O too/O high/O ,/O too/O high/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON braided/O his/O hair/O and/O slid/O the/O silver/O rings/O onto/O his/O mustache/O and/O hung/O his/O bells/O one/O by/O one/O ./O 
So/O many/O bells/O ,/O gold/O and/O silver/O and/O bronze/O ./O 
Bells/O so/O his/O enemies/O would/O hear/O him/O coming/O and/O grow/O weak/O with/O fear/O ./O 
She/O dressed/O him/O in/O horsehair/O leggings/O and/O high/O boots/O ,/O buckling/O a/O belt/O heavy/O with/O gold/O and/O silver/O medallions/O about/O his/O waist/O ./O 
Over/O his/O scarred/O chest/O she/O slipped/O a/O painted/O vest/O ,/O old/O and/O faded/O ,/O the/O one/O Drogo/PERSON had/O loved/O best/O ./O 
For/O herself/O she/O chose/O loose/O sandsilk/O trousers/O ,/O sandals/O that/O laced/O halfway/O up/O her/O legs/O ,/O and/O a/O vest/O like/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sun/O was/O going/O down/O when/O she/O called/O them/O back/O to/O carry/O his/O body/O to/O the/O pyre/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON watched/O in/O silence/O as/O Jhogo/PERSON and/O Aggo/PERSON bore/O him/O from/O the/O tent/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON walked/O behind/O them/O ./O 
They/O ''/O ,/O ``/O laid/O him/O down/O on/O his/O cushions/O and/O silks/O ,/O his/O head/O toward/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/O far/O to/O the/O northeast/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oil/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O ,/O and/O they/O brought/O forth/O the/O jars/O and/O poured/O them/O over/O the/O pyre/O ,/O soaking/O the/O silks/O and/O the/O brush/O and/O the/O bundles/O of/O dry/O grass/O ,/O until/O the/O oil/O trickled/O from/O beneath/O the/O logs/O and/O the/O air/O was/O rich/O with/O fragrance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O my/O eggs/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON commanded/O her/O handmaids/O ./O 
Something/O in/O her/O voice/O made/O them/O run/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON took/O her/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O queen/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON will/O have/O no/O use/O for/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O in/O the/O night/O lands/O ./O 
Better/O to/O sell/O them/O in/O Asshai/LOCATION ./O 
Sell/O one/O and/O we/O can/O buy/O a/O ship/O to/O take/O us/O back/O to/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
Sell/O all/O three/O and/O you/O will/O be/O a/O wealthy/O woman/O all/O your/O days/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O were/O not/O given/O to/O me/O to/O sell/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O climbed/O the/O pyre/O herself/O to/O place/O the/O eggs/O around/O her/O sun-andstars/O ./O 
The/O black/O beside/O his/O heart/O ,/O under/O his/O arm/O ./O 
The/O green/O beside/O his/O head/O ,/O his/O braid/O coiled/O around/O it/O ./O 
The/O cream-and-gold/O down/O between/O his/O legs/O ./O 
When/O she/O kissed/O him/O for/O the/O last/O time/O ,/O Dany/PERSON could/O taste/O the/O sweetness/O of/O the/O oil/O on/O his/O lips/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O she/O climbed/O down/O off/O the/O pyre/O ,/O she/O noticed/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON watching/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O mad/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O godswife/O said/O hoarsely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O it/O so/O far/O from/O madness/O to/O wisdom/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O take/O this/O maegi/O and/O bind/O her/O to/O the/O pyre/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O the/O .../O my/O queen/O ,/O no/O ,/O hear/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O as/O I/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Still/O he/O hesitated/O ,/O until/O her/O anger/O flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O swore/O to/O obey/O me/O ,/O whatever/O might/O come/O ./O 
Rakharo/PERSON ,/O help/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O godswife/O did/O not/O cry/O out/O as/O they/O dragged/O her/O to/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O pyre/O and/O staked/O her/O down/O amidst/O his/O treasures/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON poured/O the/O oil/O over/O the/O woman/O 's/O head/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O ,/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O for/O the/O lessons/O you/O have/O taught/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O not/O hear/O me/O scream/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON responded/O as/O the/O oil/O dripped/O from/O her/O hair/O and/O soaked/O her/O clothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O it/O is/O not/O your/O screams/O I/O want/O ,/O only/O your/O life/O ./O 
I/O remember/O what/O you/O told/O me/O ./O 
Only/O death/O can/O pay/O for/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON opened/O her/O mouth/O ,/O but/O made/O no/O reply/O ./O 
As/O she/O stepped/O away/O ,/O Dany/PERSON saw/O that/O the/O contempt/O was/O gone/O from/O the/O maegi/O '/O s/O flat/O black/O eyes/O ;/O in/O its/O place/O was/O something/O that/O might/O have/O been/O fear/O ./O 
Then/O there/O was/O nothing/O to/O be/O done/O but/O watch/O the/O sun/O and/O look/O for/O the/O first/O star/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O a/O horselord/O dies/O ,/O his/O horse/O is/O slain/O with/O him/O ,/O so/O he/O might/O ride/O proud/O into/O the/O night/O lands/O ./O 
The/O bodies/O are/O burned/O beneath/O the/O open/O sky/O ,/O and/O the/O khal/O rises/O on/O his/O fiery/O steed/O to/O take/O his/O place/O among/O the/O stars/O ./O 
The/O more/O fiercely/O the/O man/O burned/O in/O life/O ,/O the/O brighter/O his/O star/O will/O shine/O in/O the/O darkness/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jhogo/PERSON spied/O it/O first/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O hushed/O voice/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON looked/O and/O saw/O it/O ,/O low/O in/O the/O east/O ./O 
The/O first/O star/O was/O a/O comet/O ,/O burning/O red/O ./O 
Bloodred/O ;/O fire/O red/O ;/O the/O dragon/O 's/O tail/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O have/O asked/O for/O a/O stronger/O sign/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON took/O the/O torch/O from/O Aggo/ORGANIZATION 's/O hand/O and/O thrust/O it/O between/O the/O logs/O ./O 
The/O oil/O took/O the/O fire/O at/O once/O ,/O the/O brush/O and/O dried/O grass/O a/O heartbeat/O later/O ./O 
Tiny/O flames/O went/O darting/O up/O the/O wood/O like/O swift/O ''/O ,/O ``/O red/O mice/O ,/O skating/O over/O the/O oil/O and/O leaping/O from/O bark/O to/O branch/O to/O leaf/O ./O 
A/O rising/O heat/O puffed/O at/O her/O face/O ,/O soft/O and/O sudden/O as/O a/O lover/O 's/O breath/O ,/O but/O in/O seconds/O it/O had/O grown/O too/O hot/O to/O bear/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON stepped/O backward/O ./O 
The/O wood/O crackled/O ,/O louder/O and/O louder/O ./O 
Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON began/O to/O sing/O in/O a/O shrill/O ,/O ululating/O voice/O ./O 
The/O flames/O whirled/O and/O writhed/O ,/O racing/O each/O other/O up/O the/O platform/O ./O 
The/O dusk/O shimmered/O as/O the/O air/O itself/O seemed/O to/O liquefy/O from/O the/O heat/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON heard/O logs/O spit/O and/O crack/O ./O 
The/O fires/O swept/O over/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON ./O 
Her/O song/O grew/O louder/O ,/O shriller/O .../O then/O she/O gasped/O ,/O again/O and/O again/O ,/O and/O her/O song/O became/O a/O shuddering/O wail/O ,/O thin/O and/O high/O and/O full/O of/O agony/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O now/O the/O flames/O reached/O her/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O and/O now/O they/O were/O all/O around/O him/O ./O 
His/O clothing/O took/O fire/O ,/O and/O for/O an/O instant/O the/O khal/O was/O clad/O in/O wisps/O of/O floating/O orange/O silk/O and/O tendrils/O of/O curling/O smoke/O ,/O grey/O and/O greasy/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON 's/O lips/O parted/O and/O she/O found/O herself/O holding/O her/O breath/O ./O 
Part/O of/O her/O wanted/O to/O go/O to/O him/O as/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O feared/O ,/O to/O rush/O into/O the/O flames/O to/O beg/O for/O his/O forgiveness/O and/O take/O him/O inside/O her/O one/O last/O time/O ,/O the/O fire/O melting/O the/O flesh/O from/O their/O bones/O until/O they/O were/O as/O one/O ,/O forever/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O could/O smell/O the/O odor/O of/O burning/O flesh/O ,/O no/O different/O than/O horseflesh/O roasting/O in/O a/O firepit/O ./O 
The/O pyre/O roared/O in/O the/O deepening/O dusk/O like/O some/O great/O beast/O ,/O drowning/O out/O the/O fainter/O sound/O of/O Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON 's/O screaming/O and/O sending/O up/O long/O tongues/O of/O flame/O to/O lick/O at/O the/O belly/O of/O the/O night/O ./O 
As/O the/O smoke/O grew/O thicker/O ,/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON backed/O away/O ,/O coughing/O ./O 
Huge/O orange/O gouts/O of/O fire/O unfurled/O their/O banners/O in/O that/O hellish/O wind/O ,/O the/O logs/O hissing/O and/O cracking/O ,/O glowing/O cinders/O rising/O on/O the/O smoke/O to/O float/O away/O into/O the/O dark/O like/O so/O many/O newborn/O fireflies/O ./O 
The/O heat/O beat/O at/O the/O air/O with/O great/O red/O wings/O ,/O driving/O the/O Dothraki/O back/O ,/O driving/O off/O even/O Mormont/PERSON ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON stood/O her/O ground/O ./O 
She/O was/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O and/O the/O fire/O was/O in/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O sensed/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O long/O ago/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O as/O she/O took/O a/O step/O closer/O to/O the/O conflagration/O ,/O but/O the/O brazier/O had/O not/O been/O hot/O enough/O ./O 
The/O flames/O writhed/O before/O her/O like/O the/O women/O who/O had/O danced/O at/O her/O wedding/O ,/O whirling/O and/O singing/O and/O spinning/O their/O yellow/O and/O orange/O and/O crimson/O veils/O ,/O fearsome/O to/O behold/O ,/O yet/O lovely/O ,/O so/O lovely/O ,/O alive/O with/O heat/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON opened/O her/O arms/O to/O them/O ,/O her/O skin/O flushed/O and/O glowing/O ./O 
This/O is/O a/O wedding/O ,/O too/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
Mirri/PERSON Maz/PERSON Duur/PERSON had/O fallen/O silent/O ./O 
The/O godswife/O thought/O her/O a/O child/O ,/O but/O children/O grow/O ,/O and/O children/O learn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Another/O step/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON could/O feel/O the/O heat/O of/O the/O sand/O on/O the/O soles/O of/O her/O feet/O ,/O even/O through/O her/O sandals/O ./O 
Sweat/O ran/O down/O her/O thighs/O and/O between/O her/O breasts/O and/O in/O rivulets/O over/O her/O cheeks/O ,/O where/O tears/O had/O once/O run/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON was/O shouting/O behind/O her/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O matter/O anymore/O ,/O only/O the/O fire/O mattered/O ./O 
The/O flames/O were/O so/O beautiful/O ,/O the/O loveliest/O things/O she/O had/O ever/O seen/O ,/O each/O one/O a/O sorcerer/O robed/O in/O yellow/O and/O orange/O and/O scarlet/O ,/O swirling/O long/O smoky/O cloaks/O ./O 
She/O saw/O crimson/O firelions/O and/O great/O yellow/O serpents/O and/O unicorns/O made/O of/O pale/O blue/O flame/O ;/O she/O saw/O fish/O and/O foxes/O and/O monsters/O ,/O wolves/O and/O bright/O birds/O and/O flowering/O trees/O ,/O each/O more/O beautiful/O than/O the/O last/O ./O 
She/O saw/O a/O horse/O ,/O a/O great/O grey/O stallion/O limned/O in/O smoke/O ,/O its/O flowing/O mane/O a/O nimbus/O of/O blue/O flame/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O my/O love/O ,/O my/O sun-and-stars/O ,/O yes/O ,/O mount/O now/O ,/O tide/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O vest/O had/O begun/O to/O smolder/O ,/O so/O Dany/PERSON shrugged/O it/O off/O and/O let/O it/O fall/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
The/O painted/O leather/O burst/O into/O sudden/O flame/O as/O she/O skipped/O closer/O to/O the/O fire/O ,/O her/O breasts/O bare/O to/O the/O blaze/O ,/O streams/O of/O milk/O flowing/O from/O her/O red/O and/O swollen/O nipples/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O now/O ,/O and/O for/O an/O ''/O ,/O ``/O instant/O she/O glimpsed/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON before/O her/O ,/O mounted/O on/O his/O smoky/O stallion/O ,/O a/O flaming/O lash/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
He/O smiled/O ,/O and/O the/O whip/O snaked/O down/O at/O the/O pyre/O ,/O hissing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O heard/O a/O crack/O ,/O the/O sound/O of/O shattering/O stone/O ./O 
The/O platform/O of/O wood/O and/O brush/O and/O grass/O began/O to/O shift/O and/O collapse/O in/O upon/O itself/O ./O 
Bits/O of/O burning/O wood/O slid/O down/O at/O her/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON was/O showered/O with/O ash/O and/O cinders/O ./O 
And/O something/O else/O came/O crashing/O down/O ,/O bouncing/O and/O rolling/O ,/O to/O land/O at/O her/O feet/O ;/O a/O chunk/O of/O curved/O rock/O ,/O pale/O and/O veined/O with/O gold/O ,/O broken/O and/O smoking/O ./O 
The/O roaring/O filled/O the/O world/O ,/O yet/O dimly/O through/O the/O firefall/O Dany/PERSON heard/O women/O shriek/O and/O children/O cry/O out/O in/O wonder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Only/O death/O can/O pay/O for/O life/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O there/O came/O a/O second/O crack/O ,/O loud/O and/O sharp/O as/O thunder/O ,/O and/O the/O smoke/O stirred/O and/O whirled/O around/O her/O and/O the/O pyre/O shifted/O ,/O the/O logs/O exploding/O as/O the/O fire/O touched/O their/O secret/O hearts/O ./O 
She/O heard/O the/O screams/O of/O frightened/O horses/O ,/O and/O the/O voices/O of/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON raised/O in/O shouts/O of/O fear/O and/O terror/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON calling/O her/O name/O and/O cursing/O ./O 
No/O ,/O she/O wanted/O to/O shout/O to/O him/O ,/O no/O ,/O my/O good/O knight/O ,/O do/O not/O fear.for/O me/O ./O 
The/O fire/O is/O mine/O ./O 
I/O am/O Daenerys/PERSON Stormborn/PERSON ,/O daughter/O of/O dragons/O ,/O bride/O of/O dragons/O ,/O mother/O of/O dragons/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O see/O ?/O 
Do/O n't/O you/O SEE/O ?/O 
With/O a/O belch/O of/O flame/O and/O smoke/O that/O reached/O thirty/O feet/O into/O the/O sky/O ,/O the/O pyre/O collapsed/O and/O came/O down/O around/O her/O ./O 
Unafraid/O ,/O Dany/PERSON stepped/O forward/O into/O the/O firestorm/O ,/O calling/O to/O her/O children/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O third/O crack/O was/O as/O loud/O and/O sharp/O as/O the/O breaking/O of/O the/O world/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O fire/O died/O at/O last/O and/O the/O ground/O became/O cool/O enough/O to/O walk/O upon/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON found/O her/O amidst/O the/O ashes/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O blackened/O logs/O and/O bits/O of/O glowing/O ember/O and/O the/O burnt/O bones/O of/O man/O and/O woman/O and/O stallion/O ./O 
She/O was/O naked/O ,/O covered/O with/O soot/O ,/O her/O clothes/O turned/O to/O ash/O ,/O her/O beautiful/O hair/O all/O crisped/O away/O .../O yet/O she/O was/O unhurt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O cream/O -/O and-go/O Id/O dragon/O was/O suckling/O at/O her/O left/O breast/O ,/O the/O green-and-bronze/O at/O the/O right/O ./O 
Her/O arms/O cradled/O them/O close/O ./O 
The/O black-and-scarlet/O beast/O was/O draped/O across/O her/O shoulders/O ,/O its/O long/O sinuous/O neck/O coiled/O under/O her/O chin/O ./O 
When/O it/O saw/O Jorah/PERSON ,/O it/O raised/O its/O head/O and/O looked/O at/O him/O with/O eyes/O as/O red/O as/O coals/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Wordless/O ,/O the/O knight/O fell/O to/O his/O knees/O ./O 
The/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O came/O up/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Jhogo/PERSON was/O the/O first/O to/O lay/O his/O arakh/O at/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O ,/O pushing/O his/O face/O to/O the/O smoking/O earth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O heard/O Aggo/O echo/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rakharo/PERSON shouted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O after/O them/O came/O her/O handmaids/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O others/O ,/O all/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O men/O and/O women/O and/O children/O ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON had/O only/O to/O look/O at/O their/O eyes/O to/O know/O that/O they/O were/O hers/O now/O ,/O today/O and/O tomorrow/O and/O forever/O ,/O hers/O as/O they/O had/O never/O been/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O Daenerys/O Targaryen/O rose/O to/O her/O feet/O ,/O her/O black/O hissed/O ,/O pale/O smoke/O venting/O from/O its/O mouth/O and/O nostrils/O ./O 
The/O other/O two/O pulled/O away/O from/O her/O breasts/O and/O added/O their/O voices/O to/O the/O call/O ,/O translucent/O wings/O unfolding/O and/O stirring/O the/O air/O ,/O and/O for/O the/O first/O time/O in/O hundreds/O of/O years/O ,/O the/O night/O came/O alive/O with/O the/O music/O of/O dragons/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
