-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O seemed/O a/O thousand/O years/O ago/O that/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O carried/O her/O infant/O son/O out/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O crossing/O the/O Tumblestone/LOCATION in/O a/O small/O boat/O to/O begin/O their/O journey/O north/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
And/O it/O was/O across/O the/O Tumblestone/LOCATION that/O they/O came/O home/O now/O ,/O though/O the/O boy/O wore/O plate/O and/O mail/O in/O place/O of/O swaddling/O clothes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON sat/O in/O the/O bow/O with/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON ,/O his/O hand/O resting/O on/O his/O direwolf/O s/O head/O as/O the/O rowers/O pulled/O at/O their/O oars/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON was/O with/O him/O ./O 
Her/O uncle/O Brynden/PERSON would/O come/O behind/O in/O the/O second/O boat/O ,/O with/O the/O Greatjon/LOCATION and/O Lord/O Karstark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O a/O place/O toward/O the/O stern/O ./O 
They/O shot/O down/O the/O Tumblestone/LOCATION ,/O letting/O the/O strong/O current/O push/O them/O past/O the/O looming/O Wheel/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
The/O splash/O and/O rumble/O of/O the/O great/O waterwheel/O within/O was/O a/O sound/O from/O her/O girlhood/O that/O brought/O a/O sad/O smile/O to/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O face/O ./O 
From/O the/O sandstone/O walls/O of/O the/O castle/O ,/O soldiers/O and/O servants/O shouted/O down/O her/O name/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON 's/O ,/O and/O \/O ``/O Winterfell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O From/O every/O rampart/O waved/O the/O banner/O of/O House/O Tully/O :/O a/O leaping/O trout/O ,/O silver/O ,/O against/O a/O rippling/O blue-and-red/O field/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O stirring/O sight/O ,/O yet/O it/O did/O not/O lift/O her/O heart/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O if/O indeed/O her/O heart/O would/O ever/O lift/O again/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O Ned/PERSON .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Below/O the/O Wheel/O Tower/O ,/O they/O made/O a/O wide/O turn/O and/O knifed/O through/O the/O churning/O water/O ./O 
The/O men/O put/O their/O backs/O into/O it/O ./O 
The/O wide/O arch/O of/O the/O Water/O Gate/O came/O into/O view/O ,/O and/O she/O heard/O the/O creak/O of/O heavy/O chains/O as/O the/O great/O iron/O portcullis/O was/O winched/O upward/O ./O 
It/O rose/O slowly/O as/O they/O approached/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O that/O the/O lower/O half/O of/O it/O was/O red/O with/O rust/O ./O 
The/O bottom/O foot/O dripped/O brown/O mud/O on/O them/O as/O they/O passed/O underneath/O ,/O the/O barbed/O spikes/O mere/O inches/O above/O their/O heads/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON gazed/O up/O at/O the/O bars/O and/O wondered/O how/O deep/O the/O rust/O went/O and/O how/O well/O the/O portcullis/O would/O stand/O up/O to/O a/O ram/O and/O whether/O it/O ought/O to/O be/O replaced/O ./O 
Thoughts/O like/O that/O were/O seldom/O far/O from/O her/O mind/O these/O days/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O passed/O beneath/O the/O arch/O and/O under/O the/O walls/O ,/O moving/O from/O sunlight/O to/O shadow/O and/O back/O into/O sunlight/O ./O 
Boats/O large/O and/O small/O were/O tied/O up/O all/O around/O them/O ,/O secured/O to/O iron/O rings/O set/O in/O the/O stone/O ./O 
Her/O father/O 's/O guards/O waited/O on/O the/O water/O stair/O with/O her/O brother/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Edmure/PERSON Tully/PERSON was/O a/O stocky/O young/O man/O with/O a/O shaggy/O head/O of/O auburn/O hair/O and/O a/O fiery/O beard/O ./O 
His/O breastplate/O was/O scratched/O and/O dented/O from/O battle/O ,/O his/O blue-and-red/O cloak/O stained/O by/O blood/O and/O smoke/O ./O 
At/O his/O side/O stood/O the/O Lord/O Hos/PERSON Blackwood/PERSON ,/O a/O hard/O pike/O of/O a/O man/O with/O close-cropped/O salt-and-pepper/O whiskers/O and/O a/O hook/O nose/O ./O 
His/O bright/O yellow/O armor/O was/O inlaid/O with/O jet/O in/O elaborate/O vine-and-leaf/O patterns/O ,/O and/O a/O cloak/O sewn/O from/O raven/O feathers/O draped/O his/O thin/O shoulders/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O Lord/O Hos/O who/O led/O the/O sortie/O that/O plucked/O her/O brother/O from/O the/O Lannister/O camp/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bring/O them/O in/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/O Edmure/O commanded/O ./O 
Three/O men/O scrambled/O down/O the/O stairs/O knee-deep/O in/O the/O water/O and/O pulled/O the/O boat/O close/O with/O long/O hooks/O ./O 
When/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON bounded/O out/O ,/O one/O of/O them/O dropped/O his/O pole/O and/O lurched/O back/O ,/O stumbling/O and/O sitting/O down/O abruptly/O in/O the/O river/O ./O 
The/O others/O laughed/O ,/O and/O the/O man/O got/O a/O sheepish/O look/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON vaulted/O over/O the/O side/O of/O the/O boat/O and/O lifted/O Catelyn/PERSON by/O the/O waist/O ,/O setting/O her/O on/O a/O dry/O step/O above/O him/O as/O water/O lapped/O around/O his/O boots/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Edmure/O came/O down/O the/O steps/O to/O embrace/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O sister/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O hoarsely/O ./O 
He/O had/O deep/O blue/O eyes/O and/O a/O mouth/O made/O for/O smiles/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O not/O smiling/O now/O ./O 
He/O looked/O worn/O and/O tired/O ,/O battered/O by/O battle/O and/O haggard/O from/O strain/O ./O 
His/O neck/O was/O bandaged/O where/O he/O had/O taken/O a/O wound/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON hugged/O him/O fiercely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O grief/O is/O mine/O ,/O Cat/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O when/O they/O broke/O apart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O we/O heard/O about/O Lord/O Eddard/O .../O the/O Lannisters/O will/O pay/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ,/O you/O will/O have/O your/O vengeance/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O that/O bring/O Ned/PERSON back/O to/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O sharply/O ./O 
The/O wound/O was/O still/O too/O fresh/O for/O softer/O words/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O think/O about/O Ned/PERSON now/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O do/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O be/O strong/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O that/O will/O keep/O ./O 
I/O must/O see/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O awaits/O you/O in/O his/O solar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Edmure/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON is/O bedridden/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O 's/O steward/O explained/O ./O 
When/O had/O that/O good/O man/O grown/O so/O old/O and/O grey/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O He/O instructed/O me/O to/O bring/O you/O to/O him/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O take/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Edmure/PERSON escorted/O her/O up/O the/O water/O stair/O and/O across/O the/O lower/O bailey/O ,/O where/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON and/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O once/O crossed/O swords/O for/O her/O favor/O ./O 
The/O massive/O sandstone/O walls/O of/O the/O keep/O loomed/O above/O them/O ./O 
As/O they/O pushed/O through/O a/O door/O between/O two/O guardsmen/O in/O fish/O -/O crest/O helms/O ,/O she/O asked/O ,/O \/O ``/O How/O bad/O is/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O dreading/O the/O answer/O even/O as/O she/O said/O the/O words/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Edmure/O 's/O look/O was/O somber/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O will/O not/O be/O with/O us/O long/O ,/O the/O maesters/O say/O ./O 
The/O pain/O is/O .../O constant/O ,/O and/O grievous/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O blind/O rage/O filled/O her/O ,/O a/O rage/O at/O all/O the/O world/O ;/O at/O her/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON and/O her/O sister/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O at/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O at/O the/O maesters/O ,/O at/O Ned/PERSON and/O her/O father/O and/O the/O monstrous/O gods/O who/O would/O take/O them/O both/O away/O from/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O should/O have/O told/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O should/O have/O sent/O word/O as/O soon/O as/O you/O knew/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O forbade/O it/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O want/O his/O enemies/O to/O know/O that/O he/O was/O dying/O ./O 
With/O the/O realm/O so/O troubled/O ,/O he/O feared/O that/O if/O the/O Lannisters/O suspected/O how/O frail/O he/O was/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O they/O might/O attack/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON finished/O ,/O hard/O ./O 
It/O was/O your/O doing/O ,/O yours/O ,/O a/O voice/O whispered/O inside/O her/O ./O 
If/O you/O had/O not/O taken/O it/O upon/O yourself/O to/O seize/O the/O dwarf/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O climbed/O the/O spiral/O stair/O in/O silence/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O keep/O was/O three-sided/O ,/O like/O Riverrun/LOCATION itself/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON 's/O solar/O was/O triangular/O as/O well/O ,/O with/O a/O stone/O balcony/O that/O jutted/O out/O to/O the/O east/O like/O the/O prow/O of/O some/O great/O sandstone/O ship/O ./O 
From/O there/O the/O lord/O of/O the/O castle/O could/O look/O down/O on/O his/O walls/O and/O battlements/O ,/O and/O beyond/O ,/O to/O where/O the/O waters/O met/O ./O 
They/O had/O moved/O her/O father/O 's/O bed/O out/O onto/O the/O balcony/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O likes/O to/O sit/O in/O the/O sun/O and/O watch/O the/O rivers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Edmure/PERSON explained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ,/O see/O who/O I/O 've/O brought/O ./O 
Cat/O has/O come/O to/O see/O you/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON had/O always/O been/O a/O big/O man/O ;/O tall/O and/O broad/O in/O his/O youth/O ,/O portly/O as/O he/O grew/O older/O ./O 
Now/O he/O seemed/O shrunken/O ,/O the/O muscle/O and/O meat/O melted/O off/O his/O bones/O ./O 
Even/O his/O face/O sagged/O ./O 
The/O last/O time/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O seen/O him/O ,/O his/O hair/O and/O beard/O had/O been/O brown/O ,/O well/O streaked/O with/O grey/O ./O 
Now/O they/O had/O gone/O white/O as/O snow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O opened/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O Edmure/O 's/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Little/O cat/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O in/O a/O voice/O thin/O and/O wispy/O and/O wracked/O by/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O little/O cat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O tremulous/O smile/O touched/O his/O face/O as/O his/O hand/O groped/O for/O hers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O watched/O for/O you/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O leave/O you/O to/O talk/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O brother/O said/O ,/O kissing/O their/O lord/O father/O gently/O on/O the/O brow/O before/O he/O withdrew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON knelt/O and/O took/O her/O father/O 's/O hand/O in/O hers/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O big/O hand/O ,/O but/O fleshless/O now/O ,/O the/O bones/O moving/O loosely/O under/O the/O skin/O ,/O all/O the/O strength/O gone/O from/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O should/O have/O told/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O rider/O ,/O a/O raven/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Riders/O are/O taken/O ,/O questioned/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ravens/O are/O brought/O down/O .../O \/O ''/O A/O spasm/O of/O pain/O took/O him/O ,/O and/O his/O fingers/O clutched/O hers/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O crabs/O are/O in/O my/O belly/O .../O pinching/O ,/O always/O pinching/O ./O 
Day/O and/O night/O ./O 
They/O have/O fierce/O claws/O ,/O the/O crabs/O ./O 
Maester/O Vyman/O makes/O me/O dreamwine/O ,/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O .../O I/O sleep/O a/O lot/O .../O but/O I/O wanted/O to/O be/O awake/O to/O see/O you/O ,/O when/O you/O came/O ./O 
I/O was/O afraid/O .../O when/O the/O Lannisters/O took/O your/O brother/O ,/O the/O camps/O all/O around/O us/O .../O was/O afraid/O I/O would/O go/O ,/O before/O I/O could/O see/O you/O again/O .../O I/O was/O afraid/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O here/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O Robb/PERSON ,/O my/O son/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O want/O to/O see/O you/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O had/O my/O eyes/O ,/O I/O remember/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O did/O ,/O and/O does/O ./O 
And/O we/O 've/O brought/O you/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O in/O irons/O ./O 
Riverrun/O is/O free/O again/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O ./O 
Last/O night/O ,/O when/O it/O began/O ,/O I/O told/O them/O .../O had/O to/O see/O ./O 
They/O carried/O me/O to/O the/O gatehouse/O .../O watched/O from/O the/O battlements/O ./O 
Ah/O ,/O that/O was/O beautiful/O .../O the/O torches/O came/O in/O a/O wave/O ,/O I/O could/O hear/O the/O cries/O floating/O across/O the/O river/O ./O 
./O '/O 
./O 
sweet/O cries/O .../O when/O that/O siege/O tower/O went/O up/O ,/O gods/O .../O would/O have/O died/O then/O ,/O and/O glad/O ,/O if/O only/O I/O could/O have/O seen/O you/O children/O first/O ./O 
Was/O it/O your/O boy/O who/O did/O it/O ?/O 
Was/O it/O your/O Robb/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O fiercely/O proud/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O Robb/PERSON .../O and/O Brynden/LOCATION ./O 
Your/O brother/O is/O here/O as/O well/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O father/O 's/O voice/O was/O a/O faint/O whisper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Blackfish/O .../O came/O back/O ?/O 
From/O the/O Vale/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O Lysa/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O A/O cool/O wind/O moved/O through/O his/O thin/O white/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O be/O good/O ,/O your/O sister/O .../O did/O she/O come/O as/O well/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O sounded/O so/O full/O of/O hope/O and/O yearning/O that/O it/O was/O hard/O to/O tell/O the/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sorry/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O face/O fell/O ,/O and/O some/O light/O went/O out/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O hoped/O I/O would/O have/O liked/O to/O see/O her/O ,/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O with/O her/O son/O ,/O in/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON gave/O a/O weary/O nod/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON now/O ,/O poor/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O gone/O .../O I/O remember/O .../O why/O did/O she/O not/O come/O with/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O is/O frightened/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
In/O the/O Eyrie/O she/O feels/O safe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O kissed/O his/O wrinkled/O brow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON will/O be/O waiting/O ./O 
Will/O you/O see/O him/O ?/O 
And/O Brynden/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O son/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Cat/O 's/O child/O .../O he/O had/O my/O eyes/O ,/O I/O remember/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O born/O ./O 
Bring/O him/O .../O yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O your/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O father/O glanced/O out/O over/O the/O rivers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blackfish/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Has/O he/O wed/O yet/O ?/O 
Taken/O some/O .../O girl/O to/O wife/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Even/O on/O his/O deathbed/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O sadly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O not/O wed./O ./O 
You/O know/O that/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
Nor/O will/O he/O ever/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O told/O him/O .../O commanded/O him/O ./O 
Marry/O !/O 
I/O was/O his/O lord/O ./O 
He/O knows/O ./O 
My/O right/O ,/O to/O make/O his/O match/O ./O 
A/O good/O match/O ./O 
A/O Redwyne/O ./O 
Old/O House/O ./O 
Sweet/O girl/O ,/O pretty/O .../O freckles/O .../O Bethany/PERSON ,/O yes/O ./O 
Poor/O child/O ./O 
Still/O waiting/O ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
Still/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bethany/PERSON Redwyne/PERSON wed/O Lord/O Rowan/PERSON years/O ago/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O has/O three/O children/O by/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Even/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON muttered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O so/O ./O 
Spit/O on/O the/O girl/O ./O 
The/O Redwynes/O ./O 
Spit/O on/O me/O ./O 
His/O lord/O ,/O his/O brother/O .../O that/O Blackfish/O ./O 
I/O had/O other/O offers/O ./O 
Lord/O Bracken/PERSON 's/O girl/O ./O 
Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON .../O any/O of/O three/O ,/O he/O said/O .../O Has/O he/O wed/O ?/O 
Anyone/O ?/O 
Anyone/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O he/O has/O come/O many/O leagues/O to/O see/O you/O ,/O fighting/O his/O way/O back/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
I/O would/O not/O be/O here/O now/O ,/O if/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON had/O not/O helped/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O ever/O a/O warrior/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O husked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O he/O could/O do/O ./O 
Knight/O of/O the/O Gate/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O back/O and/O closed/O his/O eyes/O ,/O inutterably/O weary/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O him/O ./O 
Later/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O sleep/O now/O ./O 
Too/O sick/O to/O fight/O ./O 
Send/O him/O up/O later/O ,/O the/O Blackfish/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON kissed/O him/O gently/O ,/O smoothed/O his/O hair/O ,/O and/O left/O him/O there/O in/O the/O shade/O of/O his/O keep/O ,/O with/O his/O rivers/O flowing/O beneath/O ./O 
He/O was/O asleep/O before/O she/O left/O the/O solar/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O returned/O to/O the/O lower/O bailey/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON stood/O on/O the/O water/O stairs/O with/O wet/O boots/O ,/O talking/O with/O the/O captain/O of/O Riverrun/PERSON 's/O guards/O ./O 
He/O came/O to/O her/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dying/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O we/O feared/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O 's/O craggy/O face/O showed/O his/O pain/O plain/O ./O 
He/O ran/O his/O fingers/O through/O his/O thick/O grey/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O he/O see/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O says/O he/O is/O too/O sick/O to/O fight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Brynden/O Blackfish/O chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O too/O old/O a/O soldier/O to/O believe/O that/O ./O 
Hoster/PERSON will/O be/O chiding/O me/O about/O the/O Redwyne/O girl/O even/O as/O we/O light/O his/O funeral/O pyre/O ,/O damn/O his/O bones/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON smiled/O ,/O knowing/O it/O was/O true/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O see/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O went/O with/O Greyjoy/PERSON to/O the/O hall/O ,/O I/O believe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON was/O seated/O on/O a/O bench/O in/O Riverrun/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O enjoying/O a/O horn/O of/O ale/O and/O regaling/O her/O father/O 's/O garrison/O with/O an/O account/O of/O the/O slaughter/O in/O the/O Whispering/O Wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Some/O tried/O to/O flee/O ,/O but/O we/O 'd/O pinched/O the/O valley/O shut/O at/O both/O ends/O ,/O and/O we/O rode/O out/O of/O the/O darkness/O with/O sword/O and/O lance/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O must/O have/O thought/O the/O Others/O themselves/O were/O on/O them/O when/O that/O wolf/O of/O Robb/PERSON 's/O got/O in/O among/O them/O ./O 
I/O saw/O him/O tear/O one/O man/O 's/O arm/O from/O his/O shoulder/O ,/O and/O their/O horses/O went/O mad/O at/O the/O scent/O of/O him/O ./O 
I/O could/O n't/O tell/O you/O how/O many/O men/O were/O thrown/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Theon/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O interrupted/O ,/O \/O ``/O where/O might/O I/O find/O my/O son/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Robb/PERSON went/O to/O visit/O the/O godswood/O ,/O my/O lady/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O what/O Ned/PERSON would/O have/O done/O ./O 
He/O is/O his/O father/O 's/O son/O as/O much/O as/O mine/O ,/O I/O must/O remember/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O gods/O ,/O Ned/PERSON .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O found/O Robb/PERSON beneath/O the/O green/O canopy/O of/O leaves/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O tall/O redwoods/O and/O great/O old/O elms/O ,/O kneeling/O before/O the/O heart/O tree/O ,/O a/O slender/O weirwood/O with/O a/O face/O more/O sad/O than/O fierce/O ./O 
His/O longsword/O was/O before/O him/O ,/O the/O point/O thrust/O in/O the/O earth/O ,/O his/O gloved/O hands/O clasped/O around/O the/O hilt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Around/O him/O others/O knelt/O :/O Greatjon/O Umber/O ,/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ,/O Maege/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ,/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON ,/O and/O more/O ./O 
Even/O Tytos/PERSON Blackwood/PERSON was/O among/O them/O ,/O the/O great/O raven/O cloak/O fanned/O out/O behind/O him/O ./O 
These/O are/O the/O ones/O who/O keep/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
She/O asked/O herself/O what/O gods/O she/O kept/O these/O days/O ,/O and/O could/O not/O find/O an/O answer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O would/O not/O do/O to/O disturb/O them/O at/O their/O prayers/O ./O 
The/O gods/O must/O have/O their/O due/O .../O even/O cruel/O gods/O who/O would/O take/O Ned/PERSON from/O her/O ,/O and/O her/O lord/O father/O as/O well/O ./O 
So/O Catelyn/PERSON waited/O ./O 
The/O river/O wind/O moved/O through/O the/O high/O branches/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O see/O the/O Wheel/O Tower/O to/O her/O right/O ,/O ivy/O crawling/O up/O its/O side/O ./O 
As/O she/O stood/O there/O ,/O all/O the/O memories/O came/O flooding/O back/O to/O her/O ./O 
Her/O father/O had/O taught/O her/O to/O ride/O amongst/O these/O trees/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O the/O elm/O that/O Edmure/PERSON had/O fallen/O from/O when/O he/O broke/O his/O arm/O ,/O and/O over/O there/O ,/O beneath/O that/O bower/O ,/O she/O and/O Lysa/PERSON had/O played/O at/O kissing/O with/O Petyr/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O not/O thought/O of/O that/O in/O years/O ./O 
How/O young/O they/O all/O had/O been-she/O no/O older/O than/O Sansa/LOCATION ,/O Lysa/PERSON younger/O than/O Arya/PERSON ,/O and/O Petyr/O younger/O still/O ,/O yet/O eager/O ./O 
The/O girls/O had/O traded/O him/O between/O them/O ,/O serious/O and/O giggling/O by/O turns/O ./O 
It/O came/O back/O to/O her/O so/O vividly/O she/O could/O almost/O feel/O his/O sweaty/O fingers/O on/O her/O shoulders/O and/O taste/O the/O mint/O on/O his/O breath/O ./O 
There/O was/O always/O mint/O growing/O in/O the/O godswood/O ,/O and/O Petyr/LOCATION had/O liked/O to/O chew/O it/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O such/O a/O bold/O little/O boy/O ,/O always/O in/O trouble/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O tried/O to/O put/O his/O tongue/O in/O my/O mouth/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O confessed/O to/O her/O sister/O afterward/O ,/O when/O they/O were/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O did/O with/O me/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON had/O whispered/O ,/O shy/O and/O breathless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O liked/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON got/O to/O his/O feet/O slowly/O and/O sheathed/O his/O sword/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON found/O herself/O wondering/O whether/O her/O son/O had/O ever/O kissed/O a/O girl/O in/O the/O godswood/O ./O 
Surely/O he/O must/O have/O ./O 
She/O had/O seen/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON giving/O him/O moist-eyed/O glances/O ,/O and/O some/O of/O the/O serving/O girls/O ,/O even/O ones/O as/O old/O as/O eighteen/O .../O he/O had/O ridden/O in/O battle/O and/O killed/O men/O with/O a/O sword/O ,/O surely/O he/O had/O been/O kissed/O ./O 
There/O were/O tears/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O wiped/O them/O away/O angrily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O when/O he/O saw/O her/O standing/O there/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O call/O a/O council/O ./O 
There/O are/O things/O to/O be/O decided/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O grandfather/O would/O like/O to/O see/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O he/O 's/O very/O sick/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Edmure/O told/O me/O ./O 
I/O am/O sorry/O ,/O Mother/O .../O for/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON and/O for/O you/O ./O 
Yet/O first/O we/O must/O meet/O ./O 
We/O 've/O had/O word/O from/O the/O south/O ./O 
Renly/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON has/O claimed/O his/O brother/O 's/O crown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Renly/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O shocked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O thought/O ,/O surely/O it/O would/O be/O Lord/O Stannis/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O did/O we/O all/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O war/O council/O convened/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O at/O four/O long/O trestle/O tables/O arranged/O in/O a/O broken/O square/O ./O 
Lord/O Hoster/PERSON was/O too/O weak/O to/O attend/O ,/O asleep/O on/O his/O balcony/O ,/O dreaming/O of/O the/O sun/O on/O the/O rivers/O of/O his/O youth/O ./O 
Edmure/PERSON sat/O in/O the/O high/O seat/O of/O the/O Tullys/O ,/O with/O Brynden/PERSON Blackfish/PERSON at/O his/O side/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O 's/O bannermen/O arrayed/O to/O right/O and/O left/O and/O along/O the/O side/O tables/O ./O 
Word/O of/O the/O victory/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION had/O spread/O to/O the/O fugitive/O lords/O of/O the/O Trident/O ,/O drawing/O them/O back/O ./O 
Karyl/PERSON Vance/PERSON came/O in/O ,/O a/O lord/O now/O ,/O his/O father/O dead/O beneath/O the/O Golden/O Tooth/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON was/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O they/O brought/O a/O Darry/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Raymun/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O a/O lad/O no/O older/O than/O Bran/O ./O 
Lord/O Jonos/PERSON Bracken/PERSON arrived/O from/O the/O ruins/O of/O Stone/O Hedge/O ,/O glowering/O and/O blustering/O ,/O and/O took/O a/O seat/O as/O far/O from/O Tytos/PERSON Blackwood/PERSON as/O the/O tables/O would/O permit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O northern/O lords/O sat/O opposite/O ,/O with/O Catelyn/PERSON and/O Robb/PERSON facing/O her/O brother/O across/O the/O tables/O ./O 
They/O were/O fewer/O ./O 
The/O Greatjon/PERSON sat/O at/O Robb/PERSON 's/O left/O hand/O ,/O and/O then/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ;/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON and/O Lady/PERSON Mormont/PERSON were/O to/O the/O right/O of/O Catelyn/LOCATION ./O 
Lord/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ,/O gaunt/O and/O hollow-eyed/O in/O his/O grief/O ,/O took/O his/O seat/O like/O a/O man/O in/O a/O nightmare/O ,/O his/O long/O beard/O uncombed/O and/O unwashed/O ./O 
He/O had/O left/O two/O sons/O dead/O in/O the/O Whispering/O Wood/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O no/O word/O of/O the/O third/O ,/O his/O eldest/O ,/O who/O had/O led/O the/O Karstark/O spears/O against/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON on/O the/O Green/ORGANIZATION Fork/ORGANIZATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O arguing/O raged/O on/O late/O into/O the/O night/O ./O 
Each/O lord/O had/O a/O right/O to/O speak/O ,/O and/O speak/O they/O did/O .../O and/O shout/O ,/O and/O curse/O ,/O and/O reason/O ,/O and/O cajole/O ,/O and/O jest/O ,/O and/O bargain/O ,/O and/O slam/O tankards/O on/O the/O table/O ,/O and/O threaten/O ,/O and/O walk/O out/O ,/O and/O return/O sullen/O or/O smiling/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON sat/O and/O listened/O to/O it/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON had/O re-formed/O the/O battered/O remnants/O of/O their/O other/O host/O at/O the/O mouth/O of/O the/O causeway/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Helman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON and/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON still/O held/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON '/O s/O army/O had/O crossed/O the/O Trident/O ,/O and/O was/O making/O for/O Harrenhal/O ./O 
And/O there/O were/O two/O kings/O in/O the/O realm/O ./O 
Two/O kings/O ,/O and/O no/O agreement/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Many/O of/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O wanted/O to/O march/O on/O Harrenhal/PERSON at/O once/O ,/O to/O meet/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON and/O end/O Lannister/O power/O for/O all/O time/O ./O 
Young/O ,/O hot-tempered/O Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON urged/O a/O strike/O west/O at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION instead/O ./O 
Still/O others/O counseled/O patience/O ./O 
Riverrun/PERSON sat/O athwart/O the/O Lannister/O supply/O lines/O ,/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON pointed/O out/O ;/O let/O them/O bide/O their/O time/O ,/O denying/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON fresh/O levies/O and/O provisions/O while/O they/O strengthened/O their/O defenses/O and/O rested/O their/O weary/O troops/O ./O 
Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON would/O have/O none/O of/O it/O ./O 
They/O should/O finish/O the/O work/O they/O began/O in/O the/O Whispering/LOCATION Wood/LOCATION ./O 
March/O to/O Harrenhal/LOCATION and/O bring/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON 's/O army/O down/O as/O well/O ./O 
What/O Blackwood/PERSON urged/O ,/O Bracken/PERSON opposed/O ,/O as/O ever/O ;/O Lord/O Jonos/PERSON Bracken/PERSON rose/O to/O insist/O they/O ought/O pledge/O their/O fealty/O to/O King/O Renly/O ,/O and/O move/O south/O to/O join/O their/O might/O to/O his/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Renly/O is/O not/O the/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O first/O time/O her/O son/O had/O spoken/O ./O 
Like/O his/O father/O ,/O he/O knew/O how/O to/O listen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O can/O not/O mean/O to/O hold/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O put/O your/O father/O to/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O makes/O him/O evil/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O know/O that/O it/O makes/O Renly/O king/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON is/O still/O Robert/PERSON 's/O eldest/O trueborn/O son/O ,/O so/O the/O throne/O is/O rightfully/O his/O by/O all/O the/O laws/O of/O the/O realm/O ./O 
Were/O he/O to/O die/O ,/O and/O I/O mean/O to/O see/O that/O he/O does/O ,/O he/O has/O a/O younger/O brother/O ./O 
Tommen/O is/O next/O in/O line/O after/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tommen/O is/O no/O less/O a/O Lannister/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON snapped/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Robb/PERSON ,/O troubled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O if/O neither/O one/O is/O king/O ,/O still/O ,/O how/O could/O it/O be/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON ?/O 
He/O 's/O Robert/PERSON 's/O younger/O brother/O ./O 
Bran/O ca/O n't/O be/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/O before/O me/O ,/O and/O Renly/O ca/O n't/O be/O king/O before/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lady/O Mormont/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON has/O the/O better/O claim/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Renly/O is/O crowned/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Highgarden/O and/O Storm/O 's/O End/O support/O his/O claim/O ,/O and/O the/O Dornishmen/O will/O not/O be/O laggardly/O ./O 
If/O Winterfell/PERSON and/O Riverrun/PERSON add/O their/O strength/O to/O his/O ,/O he/O will/O have/O five/O of/O the/O seven/O great/O houses/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Six/O ,/O if/O the/O Arryns/O bestir/O themselves/O !/O 
Six/O against/O the/O Rock/O !/O 
My/O lords/O ,/O within/O the/O year/O ,/O we/O will/O have/O all/O their/O heads/O on/O pikes/O ,/O the/O queen/O and/O the/O boy/O king/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ,/O the/O Imp/O ,/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON ,/O all/O of/O them/O !/O 
That/O is/O what/O we/O shall/O win/O if/O ''/O ,/O ``/O we/O join/O with/O King/O Renly/O ./O 
What/O does/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON have/O against/O that/O ,/O that/O we/O should/O cast/O it/O all/O aside/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O right/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Robb/PERSON stubbornly/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON thought/O he/O sounded/O eerily/O like/O his/O father/O as/O he/O said/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O you/O mean/O us/O to/O declare/O for/O Stannis/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Edmure/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O prayed/O to/O know/O what/O to/O do/O ,/O but/O the/O gods/O did/O not/O answer/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O killed/O my/O father/O for/O a/O traitor/O ,/O and/O we/O know/O that/O was/O a/O lie/O ,/O but/O if/O Joffrey/PERSON is/O the/O lawful/O king/O and/O we/O fight/O against/O him/O ,/O we/O will/O be/O traitors/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O father/O would/O urge/O caution/O ,/O \/O ''/O aged/O Ser/PERSON Stevron/PERSON said/O ,/O with/O the/O weaselly/O smile/O of/O a/O Frey/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wait/O ,/O let/O these/O two/O kings/O play/O their/O game/O of/O thrones/O ./O 
When/O they/O are/O done/O fighting/O ,/O we/O can/O bend/O our/O knees/O to/O the/O victor/O ,/O or/O oppose/O him/O ,/O as/O we/O choose/O ./O 
With/O Renly/O arming/O ,/O likely/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON would/O welcome/O a/O truce/O .../O and/O the/O safe/O return/O of/O his/O son/O ./O 
Noble/O lords/O ,/O allow/O me/O to/O go/O to/O him/O at/O Harrenhal/LOCATION and/O arrange/O good/O terms/O and/O ransoms/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O roar/O of/O outrage/O drowned/O out/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Craven/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON thundered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Begging/O for/O a/O truce/O will/O make/O us/O seem/O weak/O ,/O \/O ''/O declared/O Lady/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Ransoms/O be/O damned/O ,/O we/O must/O not/O give/O up/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ''/O shouted/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O not/O a/O peace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O lords/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O Robb/PERSON 's/O eyes/O she/O felt/O ,/O his/O and/O his/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O they/O murdered/O my/O lord/O father/O ,/O your/O husband/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O grimly/O ./O 
He/O unsheathed/O his/O longsword/O and/O laid/O it/O on/O the/O table/O before/O him/O ,/O the/O bright/O steel/O on/O the/O rough/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O only/O peace/O I/O have/O for/O Lannisters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Greatjon/PERSON bellowed/O his/O approval/O ,/O and/O other/O men/O added/O their/O voices/O ,/O shouting/O and/O drawing/O swords/O and/O pounding/O their/O fists/O on/O the/O table/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON waited/O until/O they/O had/O quieted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O then/O ,/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON was/O your/O liege/O ,/O but/O I/O shared/O his/O bed/O and/O bore/O his/O children/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O I/O love/O him/O any/O less/O than/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O voice/O almost/O broke/O with/O her/O grief/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O a/O long/O breath/O and/O steadied/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O if/O that/O sword/O could/O bring/O him/O back/O ,/O I/O should/O never/O let/O you/O sheathe/O it/O until/O Ned/PERSON stood/O at/O my/O side/O once/O more/O .../O but/O he/O is/O gone/O ,/O and/O hundred/O Whispering/O Woods/O will/O not/O change/O that/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON is/O gone/O ,/O and/O Daryn/PERSON Hornwood/PERSON ,/O and/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON 's/O valiant/O sons/O ,/O and/O many/O other/O good/O men/O besides/O ,/O and/O none/O of/O them/O will/O return/O to/O us/O ./O 
Must/O we/O have/O more/O deaths/O still/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O woman/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON rumbled/O in/O his/O deep/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Women/O do/O not/O understand/O these/O things/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O gentle/O sex/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON ,/O with/O the/O lines/O of/O grief/O fresh/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O man/O has/O a/O need/O for/O vengeance/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Give/O me/O Cersei/O Lannister/O ,/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O would/O see/O how/O gentle/O a/O woman/O can/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O I/O do/O not/O understand/O tactics/O and/O strategy/O .../O but/O I/O understand/O futility/O ./O 
We/O went/O to/O war/O when/O Lannister/PERSON armies/O were/O ravaging/O the/O riverlands/O ,/O and/O Ned/PERSON was/O a/O prisoner/O ,/O falsely/O accused/O of/O treason/O ./O 
We/O fought/O to/O defend/O ourselves/O ,/O and/O to/O win/O my/O lord/O 's/O freedom/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O the/O one/O is/O done/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O forever/O beyond/O our/O reach/O ./O 
I/O will/O mourn/O for/O Ned/PERSON until/O the/O end/O of/O my/O days/O ,/O but/O I/O must/O think/O of/O the/O living/O ./O 
I/O want/O my/O daughters/O back/O ,/O and/O the/O queen/O holds/O ''/O ,/O ``/O them/O still/O ./O 
If/O I/O must/O trade/O our/O four/O Lannisters/O for/O their/O two/O Starks/PERSON ,/O I/O will/O call/O that/O a/O bargain/O and/O thank/O the/O gods/O ./O 
I/O want/O you/O safe/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O ruling/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION from/O your/O father/O 's/O seat/O ./O 
I/O want/O you/O to/O live/O your/O life/O ,/O to/O kiss/O a/O girl/O and/O wed/O a/O woman/O and/O father/O a/O son/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O write/O an/O end/O to/O this/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O go/O home/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O and/O weep/O for/O my/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O hall/O was/O very/O quiet/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON finished/O speaking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Peace/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O her/O uncle/O Brynden/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Peace/O is/O sweet/O ,/O my/O lady/O .../O but/O on/O what/O terms/O ?/O 
It/O is/O no/O good/O hammering/O your/O sword/O into/O a/O plowshare/O if/O you/O must/O forge/O it/O again/O on/O the/O morrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O did/O Torrhen/PERSON and/O my/O Eddard/O die/O for/O ,/O if/O I/O am/O to/O return/O to/O Karhold/O with/O nothing/O but/O their/O bones/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aye/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Lord/O Bracken/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON laid/O waste/O to/O my/O fields/O ,/O slaughtered/O my/O smallfolk/O ,/O and/O left/O Stone/O Hedge/O a/O smoking/O ruin/O ./O 
Am/O I/O now/O to/O bend/O the/O knee/O to/O the/O ones/O who/O sent/O him/O ?/O 
What/O have/O we/O fought/O for/O ,/O if/O we/O are/O to/O put/O all/O back/O as/O it/O was/O before/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON agreed/O ,/O to/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O surprise/O and/O dismay/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O we/O do/O make/O peace/O with/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O are/O we/O not/O then/O traitors/O to/O King/O Renly/O ?/O 
What/O if/O the/O stag/O should/O prevail/O against/O the/O lion/O ,/O where/O would/O that/O leave/O us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Whatever/O you/O may/O decide/O for/O yourselves/O ,/O I/O shall/O never/O call/O a/O Lannister/O my/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O declared/O Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O I/O \/O ''/O yelled/O the/O little/O Darry/PERSON boy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O will/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Again/O the/O shouting/O began/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON sat/O despairing/O ./O 
She/O had/O come/O so/O close/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
They/O had/O almost/O listened/O ,/O almost/O .../O but/O the/O moment/O was/O gone/O ./O 
There/O would/O be/O no/O peace/O ,/O no/O chance/O to/O heal/O ,/O no/O safety/O ./O 
She/O looked/O at/O her/O son/O ,/O watched/O him/O as/O he/O listened/O to/O the/O lords/O debate/O ,/O frowning/O ,/O troubled/O ,/O yet/O wedded/O to/O his/O war/O ./O 
He/O had/O pledged/O himself/O to/O marry/O a/O daughter/O of/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O but/O she/O saw/O his/O true/O bride/O plain/O before/O her/O now/O :/O the/O sword/O he/O had/O laid/O on/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O thinking/O of/O her/O girls/O ,/O wondering/O if/O she/O would/O ever/O see/O them/O again/O ,/O when/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON lurched/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O MY/O LORDS/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ,/O his/O voice/O booming/O off/O the/O rafters/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O is/O what/O I/O say/O to/O these/O two/O kings/O !/O 
\/O ''/O He/O spat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Renly/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON is/O nothing/O to/O me/O ,/O nor/O Stannis/O neither/O ./O 
Why/O should/O they/O rule/O over/O me/O and/O mine/O ,/O from/O some/O flowery/O seat/O in/O Highgarden/LOCATION or/O Dome/LOCATION ?/O 
What/O do/O they/O know/O of/O the/O Wall/O or/O the/O wolfswood/O or/O the/O barrows/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O ?/O 
Even/O their/O gods/O are/O wrong/O ./O 
The/O Others/O take/O the/O Lannisters/O too/O ,/O I/O 've/O had/O a/O bellyful/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O reached/O back/O over/O his/O shoulder/O and/O drew/O his/O immense/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O should/O n't/O we/O rule/O ourselves/O again/O ?/O 
It/O was/O the/O dragons/O we/O married/O ,/O and/O the/O dragons/O are/O all/O dead/O !/O 
\/O ''/O He/O pointed/O at/O Robb/PERSON with/O the/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O sits/O the/O only/O king/O I/O mean/O to/O bow/O my/O knee/O to/O ,/O m/O `/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O thundered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O King/O in/O the/O North/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O he/O knelt/O ,/O and/O laid/O his/O sword/O at/O her/O son/O 's/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O have/O peace/O on/O those/O terms/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O can/O keep/O their/O red/O castle/O and/O their/O iron/O chair/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O eased/O his/O longsword/O from/O its/O scabbard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O King/O in/O the/O North/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O kneeling/O beside/O the/O Greatjon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maege/PERSON Mormont/PERSON stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O King/O of/O Winter/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O declared/O ,/O and/O laid/O her/O spiked/O mace/O beside/O the/O swords/O ./O 
And/O the/O river/O lords/O were/O rising/O too/O ,/O Blackwood/PERSON and/O Bracken/PERSON and/O Mallister/PERSON ,/O houses/O who/O had/O never/O been/O ruled/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O yet/O Catelyn/PERSON watched/O them/O rise/O and/O draw/O their/O blades/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O bending/O their/O knees/O and/O shouting/O the/O old/O words/O that/O had/O not/O been/O heard/O in/O the/O realm/O for/O more/O than/O three/O hundred/O years/O ,/O since/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Dragon/O had/O come/O to/O make/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O one/O ./O 
yet/O now/O were/O heard/O again/O ,/O ringing/O from/O the/O timbers/O of/O her/O father/O 's/O hall/O :/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O King/O in/O the/O North/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O King/O in/O the/O North/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O THE/O KING/O IN/O THE/O NORTH/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
