-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O found/O Littlefinger/PERSON in/O the/O brothel/O 's/O common/O room/O ,/O chatting/O amiably/O with/O a/O tall/O ,/O elegant/O woman/O who/O wore/O a/O feathered/O gown/O over/O skin/O as/O black/O as/O ink/O ./O 
By/O the/O hearth/O ,/O Heward/PERSON and/O a/O buxom/O wench/O were/O playing/O at/O forfeits/O ./O 
From/O the/O look/O of/O it/O ,/O he/O 'd/O lost/O his/O belt/O ,/O his/O cloak/O ,/O his/O mail/O shirt/O ,/O and/O his/O right/O boot/O so/O far/O ,/O while/O the/O girl/O had/O been/O forced/O to/O unbutton/O her/O shift/O to/O the/O waist/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON Cassel/PERSON stood/O beside/O a/O rain-streaked/O window/O with/O a/O wry/O smile/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O watching/O Heward/PERSON turn/O over/O tiles/O and/O enjoying/O the/O view/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON paused/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O stair/O and/O pulled/O on/O his/O gloves/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O time/O we/O took/O our/O leave/O ./O 
My/O business/O here/O is/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Heward/PERSON lurched/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O hurriedly/O gathering/O up/O his/O things/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jory/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O help/O Wyl/O bring/O round/O the/O horses/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O strode/O to/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON took/O his/O time/O saying/O his/O farewells/O ./O 
He/O kissed/O the/O black/O woman/O 's/O hand/O ,/O whispered/O some/O joke/O that/O made/O her/O laugh/O aloud/O ,/O and/O sauntered/O over/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O business/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O lightly/O ,/O \/O ``/O or/O Robert/PERSON 's/O ?/O 
They/O say/O the/O Hand/O dreams/O the/O king/O 's/O dreams/O ,/O speaks/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O voice/O ,/O and/O rules/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O sword/O ./O 
Does/O that/O also/O mean/O you/O fuck/O with/O the/O king/O 's/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON interrupted/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O presume/O too/O much/O ./O 
I/O am/O not/O ungrateful/O for/O your/O help/O ./O 
It/O might/O have/O taken/O us/O years/O to/O find/O this/O brothel/O without/O you/O ./O 
That/O does/O not/O mean/O I/O intend/O to/O endure/O your/O mockery/O ./O 
And/O I/O am/O no/O longer/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O direwolf/O must/O be/O a/O prickly/O beast/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Littlefinger/PERSON with/O a/O sharp/O twist/O of/O his/O mouth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O warm/O rain/O was/O pelting/O down/O from/O a/O starless/O black/O sky/O as/O they/O walked/O to/O the/O stables/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON drew/O up/O the/O hood/O of/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON brought/O out/O his/O horse/O ./O 
Young/PERSON Wyl/PERSON came/O right/O behind/O him/O ,/O leading/O Littlefinger/PERSON 's/O mare/O with/O one/O hand/O while/O the/O other/O fumbled/O with/O his/O belt/O and/O the/O lacings/O of/O his/O trousers/O ./O 
A/O barefoot/O whore/O leaned/O out/O of/O the/O stable/O door/O ,/O giggling/O at/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O we/O be/O going/O back/O to/O the/O castle/O now/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jory/PERSON asked/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON nodded/O and/O swung/O into/O the/O saddle/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON mounted/O up/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON and/O the/O others/O followed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Chataya/O runs/O a/O choice/O establishment/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O as/O they/O rode/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O half/O a/O mind/O to/O buy/O it/O ./O 
Brothels/O are/O a/O much/O sounder/O investment/O than/O ships/O ,/O I/O 've/O found/O ./O 
Whores/O seldom/O sink/O ,/O and/O when/O they/O are/O boarded/O by/O pirates/O ,/O why/O ,/O the/O pirates/O pay/O good/O coin/O like/O everyone/O else/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON chuckled/O at/O his/O own/O wit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O let/O him/O prattle/O on/O ./O 
After/O a/O time/O ,/O he/O quieted/O and/O they/O rode/O in/O silence/O ./O 
The/O streets/O of/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O were/O dark/O and/O deserted/O ./O 
The/O rain/O had/O driven/O everyone/O under/O their/O roofs/O ./O 
It/O beat/O down/O on/O Ned/PERSON 's/O head/O ,/O warm/O as/O blood/O and/O relentless/O as/O old/O guilts/O ./O 
Fat/O drops/O of/O water/O ran/O down/O his/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON will/O never/O keep/O to/O one/O bed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lyanna/PERSON had/O told/O him/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O on/O the/O night/O long/O ago/O when/O their/O father/O had/O promised/O her/O hand/O to/O the/O young/O Lord/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hear/O he/O has/O gotten/O a/O child/O on/O some/O girl/O in/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON had/O held/O the/O babe/O in/O his/O arms/O ;/O he/O could/O scarcely/O deny/O her/O ,/O nor/O would/O he/O lie/O to/O his/O sister/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O assured/O her/O that/O what/O Robert/PERSON did/O before/O their/O betrothal/O was/O of/O no/O matter/O ,/O that/O he/O was/O a/O good/O man/O and/O true/O who/O would/O love/O her/O with/O all/O his/O heart/O ./O 
Lyanna/PERSON had/O only/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Love/O is/O sweet/O ,/O dearest/O Ned/PERSON ,/O but/O it/O can/O not/O change/O a/O man/O 's/O nature/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O girl/O had/O been/O so/O young/O Ned/PERSON had/O not/O dared/O to/O ask/O her/O age/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O she/O 'd/O been/O a/O virgin/O ;/O the/O better/O brothels/O could/O always/O find/O a/O virgin/O ,/O if/O the/O purse/O was/O fat/O enough/O ./O 
She/O had/O light/O red/O hair/O and/O a/O powdering/O of/O freckles/O across/O the/O bridge/O of/O her/O nose/O ,/O and/O when/O she/O slipped/O free/O a/O breast/O to/O give/O her/O nipple/O to/O the/O babe/O ,/O he/O saw/O that/O her/O bosom/O was/O freckled/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O named/O her/O Barra/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O as/O the/O child/O nursed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O looks/O so/O like/O him/O ,/O does/O she/O not/O ,/O milord/O ?/O 
She/O has/O his/O nose/O ,/O and/O his/O hair/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O does/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O touched/O the/O baby/O 's/O fine/O ,/O dark/O hair/O ./O 
It/O flowed/O through/O his/O fingers/O like/O black/O silk/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON 's/O firstborn/O had/O had/O the/O same/O fine/O hair/O ,/O he/O seemed/O to/O recall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O him/O that/O when/O you/O see/O him/O ,/O milord/O ,/O as/O it/O .../O as/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O how/O beautiful/O she/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON had/O promised/O her/O ./O 
That/O was/O his/O curse/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON would/O swear/O undying/O love/O and/O forget/O them/O before/O evenfall/O ,/O but/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON kept/O his/O vows/O ./O 
He/O thought/O of/O the/O promises/O he/O 'd/O made/O Lyanna/PERSON as/O she/O lay/O dying/O ,/O and/O the/O price/O he/O 'd/O paid/O to/O keep/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O tell/O him/O I/O 've/O not/O been/O with/O no/O one/O else/O ./O 
I/O swear/O it/O ,/O milord/O ,/O by/O the/O old/O gods/O and/O new/O ./O 
Chataya/PERSON said/O I/O could/O have/O half/O a/O year/O ,/O for/O the/O baby/O ,/O and/O for/O hoping/O he/O 'd/O come/O back/O ./O 
So/O you/O 'll/O tell/O him/O I/O 'm/O waiting/O ,/O wo/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
I/O do/O n't/O want/O no/O jewels/O or/O nothing/O ,/O just/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O always/O good/O to/O me/O ,/O truly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Good/O to/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O hollowly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O tell/O him/O ,/O child/O ,/O and/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O Barra/PERSON shall/O not/O go/O wanting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O had/O smiled/O then/O ,/O a/O smile/O so/O tremulous/O and/O sweet/O that/O it/O cut/O the/O heart/O out/O of/O him/O ./O 
Riding/O through/O the/O rainy/O night/O ,/O Ned/PERSON saw/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON 's/O face/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ,/O so/O like/O a/O younger/O version/O of/O his/O own/O ./O 
If/O the/O gods/O frowned/O so/O on/O bastards/O ,/O he/O thought/O dully/O ,/O why/O did/O they/O fill/O men/O with/O such/O lusts/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O what/O do/O you/O know/O of/O Robert/PERSON 's/O bastards/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O he/O has/O more/O than/O you/O ,/O for/O a/O start/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O many/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Little/O finger/O shrugged/O ./O 
Rivulets/O of/O moisture/O twisted/O down/O the/O back/O of/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O it/O matter/O ?/O 
If/O you/O bed/O enough/O women/O ,/O some/O will/O give/O you/O presents/O ,/O and/O His/O Grace/O has/O never/O been/O shy/O on/O that/O count/O ./O 
I/O know/O he/O 's/O acknowledged/O that/O boy/O at/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ,/O the/O one/O he/O fathered/O the/O night/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON wed./O ./O 
He/O could/O hardly/O do/O otherwise/O ./O 
The/O mother/O was/O a/O Florent/PERSON ,/O niece/O to/O the/O Lady/PERSON Selyse/PERSON ,/O one/O of/O her/O bedmaids/O ./O 
Renly/PERSON says/O that/O Robert/PERSON carried/O the/O girl/O upstairs/O during/O the/O feast/O ,/O and/O broke/O in/O the/O wedding/O bed/O while/O Stannis/PERSON and/O his/O bride/O were/O still/O dancing/O ./O 
Lord/O Stannis/PERSON seemed/O to/O think/O that/O was/O a/O blot/O on/O the/O honor/O of/O his/O wife/O 's/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O so/O when/O the/O boy/O was/O born/O ,/O he/O shipped/O him/O off/O to/O Renly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O Ned/PERSON a/O sideways/O glance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O also/O heard/O whispers/O that/O Robert/PERSON got/O a/O pair/O of/O twins/O on/O a/O serving/O wench/O at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O three/O years/O ago/O when/O he/O went/O west/O for/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O tourney/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON had/O the/O babes/O killed/O ,/O and/O sold/O the/O mother/O to/O a/O passing/O slaver/O ./O 
Too/O much/O an/O affront/O to/O Lannister/LOCATION pride/O ,/O that/O close/O to/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O Stark/O grimaced/O ./O 
Ugly/O tales/O like/O that/O were/O told/O of/O every/O great/O lord/O in/O the/O realm/O ./O 
He/O could/O believe/O it/O of/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON readily/O enough/O .../O but/O would/O the/O king/O stand/O by/O and/O let/O it/O happen/O ?/O 
The/O Robert/PERSON he/O had/O known/O would/O not/O have/O ,/O but/O the/O Robert/PERSON he/O had/O known/O had/O never/O been/O so/O practiced/O at/O shutting/O his/O eyes/O to/O things/O he/O did/O not/O wish/O to/O see/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O would/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON take/O a/O sudden/O interest/O in/O the/O king/O 's/O baseborn/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O short/O man/O gave/O a/O sodden/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ./O 
Doubtless/O Robert/PERSON asked/O him/O to/O see/O that/O they/O were/O provided/O for/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON was/O soaked/O through/O to/O the/O bone/O ,/O and/O his/O soul/O had/O grown/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O had/O to/O be/O more/O than/O that/O ,/O or/O why/O kill/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON shook/O the/O rain/O from/O his/O hair/O and/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O I/O see/O ./O 
Lord/O Arryn/PERSON learned/O that/O His/O Grace/O had/O filled/O the/O bellies/O of/O some/O whores/O and/O fishwives/O ,/O and/O for/O that/O he/O had/O to/O be/O silenced/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O ./O 
Allow/O a/O man/O like/O that/O to/O live/O ,/O and/O next/O he/O 's/O like/O to/O blurt/O out/O that/O the/O sun/O rises/O in/O the/O east/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O answer/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON could/O give/O to/O that/O but/O a/O frown/O ./O 
For/O the/O first/O time/O in/O years/O ,/O he/O found/O himself/O remembering/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
He/O wondered/O if/O Rhaegar/PERSON had/O frequented/O brothels/O ;/O somehow/O he/O thought/O not/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rain/O was/O falling/O harder/O now/O ,/O stinging/O the/O eyes/O and/O drumming/O against/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Rivers/O of/O black/O water/O were/O running/O down/O the/O hill/O when/O Jory/PERSON called/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O voice/O hoarse/O with/O alarm/O ./O 
And/O in/O an/O instant/O ,/O the/O street/O was/O full/O of/O soldiers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON glimpsed/O ringmail/O over/O leather/O ,/O gauntlets/O and/O greaves/O ,/O steel/O helms/O with/O golden/O lions/O on/O the/O crests/O ./O 
Their/O cloaks/O clung/O to/O their/O backs/O ,/O sodden/O with/O rain/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O time/O to/O count/O ,/O but/O there/O were/O ten/O at/O least/O ,/O a/O line/O of/O them/O ,/O on/O foot/O ,/O blocking/O the/O street/O ,/O with/O longswords/O and/O irontipped/O spears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Behind/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O heard/O Wyl/O cry/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O turned/O his/O horse/O ,/O there/O were/O more/O in/O back/O of/O them/O ,/O cutting/O off/O their/O retreat/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON 's/O sword/O came/O singing/O from/O its/O scabbard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Make/O way/O or/O die/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O wolves/O are/O howling/O ,/O \/O ''/O their/O leader/O said/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON could/O see/O rain/O running/O down/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Such/O a/O small/O pack/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON walked/O his/O horse/O forward/O ,/O step/O by/O careful/O step/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O the/O meaning/O of/O this/O ?/O 
This/O is/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O mud/O muffled/O the/O hooves/O of/O the/O blood/O bay/O stallion/O ./O 
The/O line/O parted/O before/O him/O ./O 
On/O a/O golden/O breastplate/O ,/O the/O lion/O of/O Lannister/O roared/O its/O defiance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O ,/O if/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O sure/O what/O he/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lannister/O ,/O this/O is/O madness/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O us/O pass/O ./O 
We/O are/O expected/O back/O at/O the/O castle/O ./O 
What/O do/O you/O think/O you/O 're/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O knows/O what/O he/O 's/O doing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O calmly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Quite/O true/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O looking/O for/O my/O brother/O ./O 
You/O remember/O my/O brother/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ?/O 
He/O was/O with/O us/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Fair-haired/O ,/O mismatched/O eyes/O ,/O sharp/O of/O tongue/O ./O 
A/O short/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O remember/O him/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O he/O has/O met/O some/O trouble/O on/O the/O road/O ./O 
My/O lord/O father/O is/O quite/O vexed/O ./O 
You/O would/O not/O perchance/O have/O any/O notion/O of/O who/O might/O have/O wished/O my/O brother/O ill/O ,/O would/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O has/O been/O taken/O at/O my/O command/O ,/O to/O answer/O for/O his/O crimes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON groaned/O in/O dismay/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jaime/O ripped/O his/O longsword/O from/O its/O sheath/O and/O urged/O his/O stallion/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Show/O me/O your/O steel/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
I/O 'll/O butcher/O you/O like/O Aerys/O if/O I/O must/O ,/O but/O I/O 'd/O sooner/O you/O died/O with/O a/O blade/O in/O ''/O ,/O ``/O your/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O Littlefinger/PERSON a/O cool/O ,/O contemptuous/O glance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O I/O 'd/O leave/O here/O in/O some/O haste/O if/O I/O did/O not/O care/O to/O get/O bloodstains/O on/O my/O costly/O clothing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON did/O not/O need/O to/O be/O urged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O bring/O the/O City/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O promised/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
The/O Lannister/O line/O parted/O to/O let/O him/O through/O ,/O and/O closed/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON put/O his/O heels/O to/O his/O mare/O and/O vanished/O around/O a/O corner/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O men/O had/O drawn/O their/O swords/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O three/O against/O twenty/O ./O 
Eyes/O watched/O from/O nearby/O windows/O and/O doors/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O was/O about/O to/O intervene/O ./O 
His/O party/O was/O mounted/O ,/O the/O Lannisters/O on/O foot/O save/O for/O Jaime/PERSON himself/O ./O 
A/O charge/O might/O win/O them/O free/O ,/O but/O it/O seemed/O to/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON that/O they/O had/O a/O surer/O ,/O safer/O tactic/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kill/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O warned/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON will/O most/O certainly/O slay/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON poked/O at/O Ned/PERSON 's/O chest/O with/O the/O gilded/O sword/O that/O had/O sipped/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O last/O of/O the/O Dragonkings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O she/O ?/O 
The/O noble/O Catelyn/PERSON Tully/PERSON of/O Riverrun/O murder/O a/O hostage/O ?/O 
I/O think/O .../O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O I/O am/O not/O willing/O to/O chance/O my/O brother/O 's/O life/O on/O a/O woman/O 's/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON slid/O the/O golden/O sword/O into/O its/O sheath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O I/O suppose/O I/O 'll/O let/O you/O run/O back/O to/O Robert/PERSON to/O tell/O him/O how/O I/O frightened/O you/O ./O 
I/O wonder/O if/O he/O 'll/O care/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON pushed/O his/O wet/O hair/O back/O with/O his/O fingers/O and/O wheeled/O his/O horse/O around/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O beyond/O the/O line/O of/O swordsmen/O ,/O he/O glanced/O back/O at/O his/O captain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tregar/O ,/O see/O that/O no/O harm/O comes/O to/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Still/O .../O we/O would/O n't/O want/O him/O to/O leave/O here/O entirely/O unc/O hastened/O ,/O so/O \/O ''/O -/O through/O the/O night/O and/O the/O rain/O ,/O he/O glimpsed/O the/O white/O of/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O smile/O -/O \/O ``/O kill/O his/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON screamed/O ,/O clawing/O for/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON was/O already/O cantering/O off/O down/O the/O street/O as/O he/O heard/O Wyl/O shout/O ./O 
Men/O closed/O from/O both/O sides/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON rode/O one/O down/O ,/O cutting/O at/O phantoms/O in/O red/O cloaks/O who/O gave/O way/O before/O him/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON Cassel/PERSON put/O his/O heels/O into/O his/O mount/O and/O charged/O ./O 
A/O steel-shod/O hoof/O caught/O a/O Lannister/O guardsman/O in/O the/O face/O with/O a/O sickening/O crunch/O ./O 
A/O second/O man/O reeled/O away/O and/O for/O an/O instant/O Jory/PERSON was/O free/O ./O 
Wyl/O cursed/O as/O they/O pulled/O him/O off/O his/O dying/O horse/O ,/O swords/O slashing/O in/O the/O rain/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON galloped/O to/O him/O ,/O bringing/O his/O longsword/O down/O on/O Tregar/PERSON 's/O helm/O ./O 
The/O jolt/O of/O impact/O made/O him/O grit/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
Tregar/PERSON stumbled/O to/O his/O knees/O ,/O his/O lion/O crest/O sheared/O in/O half/O ,/O blood/O running/O down/O his/O face/O ./O 
Heward/PERSON was/O hacking/O at/O the/O hands/O that/O had/O seized/O his/O bridle/O when/O a/O spear/O caught/O him/O in/O the/O belly/O ./O 
Suddenly/O Jory/PERSON was/O back/O among/O them/O ,/O a/O red/O rain/O flying/O from/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jory/PERSON ,/O away/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON 's/O horse/O slipped/O under/O him/O and/O came/O crashing/O down/O in/O the/O mud/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O moment/O of/O blinding/O pain/O and/O the/O taste/O of/O blood/O in/O his/O mouth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O saw/O them/O cut/O the/O legs/O from/O Jory/PERSON 's/O mount/O and/O drag/O him/O to/O the/O earth/O ,/O swords/O rising/O and/O failing/O as/O they/O closed/O in/O around/O him/O ./O 
When/O Ned/PERSON 's/O horse/O lurched/O back/O to/O its/O feet/O ,/O he/O tried/O to/O rise/O ,/O only/O to/O fall/O again/O ,/O choking/O on/O his/O scream/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O the/O splintered/O bone/O poking/O through/O his/O calf/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O last/O thing/O he/O saw/O for/O a/O time/O ./O 
The/O rain/O came/O down/O and/O down/O and/O down/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O opened/O his/O eyes/O again/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O alone/O with/O his/O dead/O ./O 
His/O horse/O moved/O closer/O ,/O caught/O the/O rank/O scent/O of/O blood/O ,/O and/O galloped/O away/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON began/O to/O drag/O himself/O through/O the/O mud/O ,/O gritting/O his/O teeth/O at/O the/O agony/O in/O his/O leg/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O to/O take/O years/O ./O 
Faces/O watched/O from/O candlelit/O windows/O ,/O and/O people/O began/O to/O emerge/O from/O alleys/O and/O doors/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O moved/O to/O help/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Little/O finger/O and/O the/O City/O Watch/O found/O him/O there/O in/O the/O street/O ,/O cradling/O Jory/PERSON Cassel/PERSON 's/O body/O in/O his/O arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Somewhere/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O found/O a/O litter/O ,/O but/O the/O trip/O back/O to/O the/O castle/O was/O a/O blur/O of/O agony/O ,/O and/O Ned/PERSON lost/O consciousness/O more/O than/O once/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O seeing/O the/O Red/O Keep/O looming/O ahead/O of/O him/O in/O the/O first/O grey/O light/O of/O dawn/O ./O 
The/O rain/O had/O darkened/O the/O pale/O pink/O stone/O of/O the/O massive/O walls/O to/O the/O color/O of/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON was/O looming/O over/O him/O ,/O holding/O a/O cup/O ,/O whispering/O ,/O \/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Here/O ./O 
The/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O for/O your/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O remembered/O swallowing/O ,/O and/O Pycelle/PERSON was/O telling/O someone/O to/O heat/O the/O wine/O to/O boiling/O and/O fetch/O him/O clean/O silk/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O the/O last/O he/O knew/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
