-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O stood/O last/O vigil/O for/O him/O myself/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON said/O as/O they/O looked/O down/O at/O the/O body/O in/O the/O back/O of/O the/O cart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O had/O no/O one/O else/O ./O 
A/O mother/O in/O the/O Vale/O ,/O I/O am/O told/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O In/O the/O pale/O dawn/O light/O ,/O the/O young/O knight/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O were/O sleeping/O ./O 
He/O had/O not/O been/O handsome/O ,/O but/O death/O had/O smoothed/O his/O rough-hewn/O features/O and/O the/O silent/O sisters/O had/O dressed/O him/O in/O his/O best/O velvet/O tunic/O ,/O with/O a/O high/O collar/O to/O cover/O the/O ruin/O the/O lance/O had/O made/O of/O his/O throat/O ./O 
Eddard/O Stark/O looked/O at/O his/O face/O ,/O and/O wondered/O if/O it/O had/O been/O for/O his/O sake/O that/O the/O boy/O had/O died/O ./O 
Slain/O by/O a/O Lannister/O bannerman/O before/O Ned/PERSON could/O speak/O to/O him/O ;/O could/O that/O be/O mere/O happenstance/O ?/O 
He/O supposed/O he/O would/O never/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hugh/PERSON was/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O squire/O for/O four/O years/O ,/O \/O ''/O Selmy/PERSON went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O knighted/O him/O before/O he/O rode/O north/O ,/O in/O Jon/PERSON 's/O memory/O ./O 
The/O lad/O wanted/O it/O desperately/O ,/O yet/O I/O fear/O he/O was/O not/O ready/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O slept/O badly/O last/O night/O and/O he/O felt/O tired/O beyond/O his/O years/O ./O 
\/O ``/O None/O of/O us/O is/O ever/O ready/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O knighthood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Gently/O ,/O Ned/PERSON covered/O the/O boy/O with/O his/O cloak/O ,/O a/O bloodstained/O bit/O of/O blue/O bordered/O in/O crescent/O moons/O ./O 
When/O his/O mother/O asked/O why/O her/O son/O was/O dead/O ,/O he/O reflected/O bitterly/O ,/O they/O would/O tell/O her/O he/O had/O fought/O to/O honor/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ,/O Eddard/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O was/O needless/O ./O 
War/O should/O not/O be/O a/O game/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON turned/O to/O the/O woman/O beside/O the/O cart/O ,/O shrouded/O in/O grey/O ,/O face/O hidden/O but/O for/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O silent/O sisters/O prepared/O men/O for/O the/O grave/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O ill/O fortune/O to/O look/O on/O the/O face/O of/O death/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O his/O armor/O home/O to/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
The/O mother/O will/O want/O to/O have/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O worth/O a/O fair/O piece/O of/O silver/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O had/O it/O forged/O special/O for/O the/O tourney/O ./O 
Plain/O work/O ,/O but/O good/O ./O 
I/O do/O not/O know/O if/O he/O had/O finished/O paying/O the/O smith/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O paid/O yesterday/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O and/O he/O paid/O dearly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O ./O 
And/O to/O the/O silent/O sister/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Send/O the/O mother/O the/O armor/O ./O 
I/O will/O deal/O with/O this/O smith/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O bowed/O her/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON walked/O with/O Ned/PERSON to/O the/O king/O 's/O pavilion/O ./O 
The/O camp/O was/O beginning/O to/O stir/O ./O 
Fat/O sausages/O sizzled/O and/O spit/O over/O firepits/O ,/O spicing/O the/O air/O with/O the/O scents/O of/O garlic/O and/O pepper/O ./O 
Young/O squires/O hurried/O about/O on/O errands/O as/O their/O masters/O woke/O ,/O yawning/O and/O stretching/O ,/O to/O meet/O the/O day/O ./O 
A/O serving/O man/O with/O a/O goose/O under/O his/O arm/O bent/O his/O knee/O when/O he/O caught/O sight/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O MTords/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O as/O the/O goose/O honked/O and/O pecked/O at/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O shields/O displayed/O outside/O each/O tent/O heralded/O its/O occupant/O :/O the/O silver/O eagle/O of/O Seagard/LOCATION ,/O Bryce/PERSON Caron/PERSON 's/O field/O of/O nightingales/O ,/O a/O cluster/O of/O grapes/O for/O the/O Redwynes/O ,/O brindled/O boar/O ,/O red/O ox/O ,/O burning/O tree/O ,/O white/O ram/O ,/O triple/O spiral/O ,/O purple/O unicorn/O ,/O dancing/O maiden/O ,/O blackadder/O ,/O twin/O towers/O ,/O horned/O owl/O ,/O and/O last/O the/O pure/O white/O blazons/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O shining/O like/O the/O dawn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O means/O to/O fight/O in/O the/O melee/O today/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON said/O as/O they/O were/O passing/O Ser/O Meryn/O 's/O shield/O ,/O its/O paint/O sullied/O by/O a/O deep/O gash/O where/O Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON 's/O lance/O had/O scarred/O the/O wood/O as/O he/O drove/O him/O from/O his/O saddle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O grimly/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON had/O woken/O him/O last/O night/O to/O bring/O him/O that/O news/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O he/O had/O slept/O so/O badly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O 's/O look/O was/O troubled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O say/O night/O 's/O beauties/O fade/O at/O dawn/O ,/O and/O the/O children/O of/O wine/O are/O oft/O disowned/O in/O the/O morning/O light/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O say/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON agreed/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O not/O of/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Other/O men/O might/O reconsider/O words/O spoken/O in/O drunken/O bravado/O ,/O but/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON would/O remember/O and/O ,/O remembering/O ,/O would/O never/O back/O down/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O king/O 's/O pavilion/O was/O close/O by/O the/O water/O ,/O and/O the/O morning/O mists/O off/O the/O river/O had/O wreathed/O it/O in/O wisps/O of/O grey/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O of/O golden/O silk/O ,/O the/O largest/O and/O grandest/O structure/O in/O the/O camp/O ./O 
Outside/O the/O entrance/O ,/O Robert/PERSON 's/O warhammer/O was/O displayed/O beside/O an/O immense/O iron/O shield/O blazoned/O with/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Baratheon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O hoped/O to/O discover/O the/O king/O still/O abed/O in/O a/O wine-soaked/O sleep/O ,/O but/O luck/O was/O not/O with/O him/O ./O 
They/O found/O Robert/PERSON drinking/O beer/O from/O a/O polished/O horn/O and/O roaring/O his/O displeasure/O at/O two/O young/O squires/O who/O were/O trying/O to/O buckle/O him/O into/O his/O armor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O was/O saying/O ,/O almost/O in/O tears/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O 's/O made/O too/O small/O ,/O it/O wo/O n't/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O fumbled/O ,/O and/O the/O gorget/O he/O was/O trying/O to/O fit/O around/O Robert/PERSON 's/O thick/O neck/O tumbled/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON swore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O I/O have/O to/O do/O it/O myself/O ?/O 
Piss/O on/O the/O both/O of/O you/O ./O 
Pick/O it/O up/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O just/O stand/O there/O gaping/O ,/O Lance/PERSON ,/O pick/O it/O up/O !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O lad/O jumped/O ,/O and/O the/O king/O noticed/O his/O company/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O at/O these/O oafs/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
My/O wife/O insisted/O I/O take/O these/O two/O to/O squire/O for/O me/O ,/O and/O they/O 're/O worse/O than/O useless/O ./O 
Ca/O n't/O even/O put/O a/O man/O 's/O armor/O on/O him/O properly/O ./O 
Squires/PERSON ,/O they/O say/O ./O 
I/O say/O they/O 're/O swineherds/O dressed/O up/O in/O silk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O only/O needed/O a/O glance/O to/O understand/O the/O difficulty/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boys/O are/O not/O at/O fault/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O too/O fat/O for/O your/O armor/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON took/O a/O long/O swallow/O of/O beer/O ,/O tossed/O the/O empty/O horn/O onto/O his/O sleeping/O furs/O ,/O wiped/O his/O mouth/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ,/O and/O said/O darkly/O ,/O \/O ``/O Fat/O ?/O 
Fat/O ,/O is/O it/O ?/O 
Is/O that/O how/O you/O speak/O to/O your/O king/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O let/O go/O his/O laughter/O ,/O sudden/O as/O a/O storm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O damn/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O why/O are/O you/O always/O right/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O squires/O smiled/O nervously/O until/O the/O king/O turned/O on/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O both/O of/O you/O ./O 
You/O heard/O the/O Hand/O ./O 
The/O king/O is/O too/O fat/O for/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Go/O find/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON Santagar/PERSON ./O 
Tell/O him/O I/O need/O the/O breastplate/O stretcher/O ./O 
Now/O !/O 
What/O are/O you/O waiting/O for/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O boys/O tripped/O over/O each/O other/O in/O their/O haste/O to/O be/O quit/O of/O the/O tent/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON managed/O to/O keep/O a/O stern/O face/O until/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O 
Then/O he/O dropped/O back/O into/O a/O chair/O ,/O shaking/O with/O laughter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O chuckled/O with/O him/O ./O 
Even/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON managed/O a/O smile/O ./O 
Always/O ,/O though/O ,/O the/O graver/O thoughts/O crept/O in/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O help/O taking/O note/O of/O the/O two/O squires/O :/O handsome/O boys/O ,/O fair/O and/O well/O made/O ./O 
One/O was/O Sansa/O 's/O age/O ,/O with/O long/O golden/O curls/O ;/O the/O other/O perhaps/O fifteen/O ,/O sandy/O -/O haired/O ,/O with/O a/O wisp/O of/O a/O mustache/O and/O the/O emerald-green/O eyes/O of/O the/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O I/O wish/O I/O could/O be/O there/O to/O see/O Santagar/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O he/O 'll/O have/O the/O wit/O to/O send/O them/O to/O someone/O else/O ./O 
We/O ought/O to/O keep/O them/O running/O all/O day/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Those/O boys/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannisters/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON nodded/O ,/O wiping/O tears/O from/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cousins/O ./O 
Sons/O of/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O brother/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O dead/O ones/O ./O 
Or/O perhaps/O the/O live/O one/O ,/O now/O that/O I/O come/O to/O think/O on/O it/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O recall/O ./O 
My/O wife/O comes/O from/O a/O very/O large/O family/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O very/O ambitious/O family/O ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O ./O 
He/O had/O nothing/O against/O the/O squires/O ,/O but/O it/O troubled/O him/O to/O see/O Robert/PERSON surrounded/O by/O the/O queen/O 's/O kin/O ,/O waking/O and/O sleeping/O ./O 
The/O Lannister/O appetite/O for/O offices/O and/O honors/O seemed/O to/O know/O no/O bounds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O talk/O is/O you/O and/O the/O queen/O had/O angry/O words/O last/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O mirth/O curdled/O on/O Robert/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O woman/O tried/O to/O forbid/O me/O to/O fight/O in/O the/O melee/O ./O 
She/O 's/O sulking/O in/O the/O castle/O now/O ,/O damn/O her/O ./O 
Your/O sister/O would/O never/O have/O shamed/O me/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O never/O knew/O Lyanna/PERSON as/O I/O did/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O saw/O her/O beauty/O ,/O but/O not/O the/O iron/O underneath/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O told/O you/O that/O you/O have/O no/O business/O in/O the/O melee/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O sour/O man/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
Too/O long/O in/O the/O north/O ,/O all/O the/O juices/O have/O frozen/O inside/O you/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O mine/O are/O still/O running/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slapped/O his/O chest/O to/O prove/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O sit/O on/O the/O damn/O iron/O seat/O when/O I/O must/O ./O 
Does/O that/O mean/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O the/O same/O hungers/O as/O other/O men/O ?/O 
A/O bit/O of/O wine/O now/O and/O again/O ,/O a/O girl/O squealing/O in/O bed/O ,/O the/O feel/O of/O a/O horse/O between/O my/O legs/O ?/O 
Seven/O hells/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O I/O want/O to/O hit/O someone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O spoke/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O is/O not/O seemly/O that/O the/O king/O should/O ride/O into/O the/O melee/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O be/O a/O fair/O contest/O ./O 
Who/O would/O dare/O strike/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON seemed/O honestly/O taken/O aback/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O all/O of/O them/O ,/O damn/O it/O ./O 
If/O they/O can/O ./O 
And/O the/O last/O man/O left/O standing/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O will/O be/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON finished/O ./O 
He/O saw/O at/O once/O that/O Selmy/PERSON had/O hit/O the/O mark/O ./O 
The/O dangers/O of/O the/O melee/O were/O only/O a/O savor/O to/O Robert/PERSON ,/O but/O this/O touched/O on/O his/O pride/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O is/O right/O ./O 
There/O 's/O not/O a/O man/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O who/O would/O dare/O risk/O your/O displeasure/O by/O hurting/O YOU/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O rose/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O his/O face/O flushed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O telling/O me/O those/O prancing/O cravens/O will/O let/O me/O win/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O a/O certainty/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON bowed/O his/O head/O in/O silent/O accord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Robert/PERSON was/O so/O angry/O he/O could/O not/O speak/O ./O 
He/O strode/O across/O the/O tent/O ,/O whirled/O ,/O strode/O back/O ,/O his/O face/O dark/O and/O angry/O ./O 
He/O snatched/O up/O his/O breastplate/O from/O the/O ground/O and/O threw/O it/O at/O Barristan/LOCATION Selmy/LOCATION in/O a/O wordless/O fury/O ./O 
Selmy/PERSON dodged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O out/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O then/O ,/O coldly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O out/O before/O I/O kill/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O left/O quickly/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON was/O about/O to/O follow/O when/O the/O king/O called/O out/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON turned/O back/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON took/O up/O his/O horn/O again/O ,/O filled/O it/O with/O beer/O from/O a/O barrel/O in/O the/O corner/O ,/O and/O thrust/O it/O at/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O brusquely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O no/O thirst/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Drink/O ./O 
Your/O king/O commands/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON took/O the/O horn/O and/O drank/O ./O 
The/O beer/O was/O black/O and/O thick/O ,/O so/O strong/O it/O stung/O the/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON sat/O down/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
You/O and/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O I/O loved/O you/O both/O ./O 
What/O have/O you/O done/O to/O me/O ?/O 
You/O were/O the/O one/O should/O have/O been/O king/O ,/O you/O or/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O had/O the/O better/O claim/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O told/O you/O to/O drink/O ,/O not/O to/O argue/O ./O 
You/O made/O me/O king/O ,/O you/O could/O at/O least/O have/O the/O courtesy/O to/O listen/O when/O I/O talk/O ,/O damn/O you/O ./O 
Look/O at/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Look/O at/O what/O kinging/O has/O done/O to/O me/O ./O 
Gods/O ,/O too/O fat/O for/O my/O armor/O ,/O how/O did/O it/O ever/O come/O to/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Drink/O and/O stay/O quiet/O ,/O the/O king/O is/O talking/O ./O 
I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O I/O was/O never/O so/O alive/O as/O when/O I/O was/O winning/O this/O throne/O ,/O or/O so/O dead/O as/O now/O that/O I/O 've/O won/O it/O ./O 
And/O Cersei/O .../O I/O have/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON to/O thank/O for/O her/O ./O 
I/O had/O no/O wish/O to/O marry/O after/O Lyanna/PERSON was/O taken/O from/O me/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON said/O the/O realm/O needed/O an/O heir/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON would/O be/O a/O good/O match/O ,/O he/O told/O me/O ,/O she/O would/O bind/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON to/O me/O should/O Viserys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ever/O try/O to/O win/O back/O his/O father/O 's/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O loved/O that/O old/O man/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ,/O but/O now/O I/O think/O he/O was/O a/O bigger/O fool/O than/O Moon/PERSON Boy/PERSON ./O 
Oh/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON is/O lovely/O to/O look/O at/O ,/O truly/O ,/O but/O cold/O .../O the/O way/O she/O guards/O her/O cunt/O ,/O you/O 'd/O think/O she/O had/O all/O the/O gold/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION between/O her/O legs/O ./O 
Here/O ,/O give/O me/O that/O beer/O if/O you/O wo/O n't/O drink/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O the/O horn/O ,/O upended/O it/O ,/O belched/O ,/O wiped/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O sorry/O for/O your/O girl/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Truly/O ./O 
About/O the/O wolf/O ,/O I/O mean/O ./O 
My/O son/O was/O lying/O ,/O I/O 'd/O stake/O my/O soul/O on/O it/O ./O 
My/O son/O .../O you/O love/O your/O children/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O With/O all/O my/O heart/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O me/O tell/O you/O a/O secret/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
More/O than/O once/O ,/O I/O have/O dreamed/O of/O giving/O up/O the/O crown/O ./O 
Take/O ship/O for/O the/O Free/O Cities/O with/O my/O horse/O and/O my/O hammer/O ,/O spend/O my/O time/O warring/O and/O whoring/O ,/O that/O 's/O what/O I/O was/O made/O for/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O king/O ,/O how/O the/O singers/O would/O love/O me/O ./O 
You/O know/O what/O stops/O me/O ?/O 
The/O thought/O of/O Joffrey/O on/O the/O throne/O ,/O with/O Cersei/PERSON standing/O behind/O him/O whispering/O in/O his/O ear/O ./O 
My/O son/O ./O 
How/O could/O I/O have/O made/O a/O son/O like/O that/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O only/O a/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O awkwardly/O ./O 
He/O had/O small/O liking/O for/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ,/O but/O he/O could/O hear/O the/O pain/O in/O Robert/PERSON 's/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O forgotten/O how/O wild/O you/O were/O at/O his/O age/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O not/O trouble/O me/O if/O the/O boy/O was/O wild/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
You/O do/O n't/O know/O him/O as/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O and/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O perhaps/O you/O are/O right/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON despaired/O of/O me/O often/O enough/O ,/O yet/O I/O grew/O into/O a/O good/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON looked/O at/O Ned/PERSON and/O scowled/O at/O his/O silence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O might/O speak/O up/O and/O agree/O now/O ,/O you/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O .../O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON began/O ,/O carefully/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON slapped/O Ned/PERSON on/O the/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O say/O that/O I/O 'm/O a/O better/O king/O than/O Aerys/O and/O be/O done/O with/O it/O ./O 
You/O never/O could/O lie/O for/O love/O nor/O honor/O ,/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
I/O 'm/O still/O young/O ,/O and/O now/O that/O you/O 're/O here/O with/O me/O ,/O things/O will/O be/O different/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O make/O this/O a/O reign/O to/O sing/O of/O ,/O and/O damn/O the/O Lannisters/O to/O seven/O hells/O ./O 
I/O smell/O bacon/O ./O 
Who/O do/O you/O think/O our/O champion/O will/O be/O today/O ?/O 
Have/O you/O seen/O Mace/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON 's/O boy/O ?/O 
The/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/PERSON ,/O they/O call/O him/O ./O 
Now/O there/O 's/O a/O son/O any/O man/O would/O be/O proud/O to/O own/O to/O ./O 
Last/O tourney/O ,/O he/O dumped/O the/O Kingslayer/O on/O his/O golden/O rump/O ,/O you/O ought/O to/O have/O seen/O the/O look/O on/O Cersei/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
I/O laughed/O till/O my/O sides/O hurt/O ./O 
Renly/PERSON says/O he/O has/O this/O sister/O ,/O a/O maid/O of/O fourteen/O ,/O lovely/O as/O a/O dawn/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O broke/O their/O fast/O on/O black/O bread/O and/O boiled/O goose/O eggs/O and/O fish/O fried/O up/O with/O onions/O and/O bacon/O ,/O at/O a/O trestle/O table/O by/O the/O river/O 's/O edge/O ./O 
The/O king/O 's/O melancholy/O melted/O away/O with/O the/O morning/O mist/O ,/O and/O before/O long/O Robert/PERSON was/O eating/O an/O orange/O and/O waxing/O fond/O about/O a/O morning/O at/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION when/O they/O had/O been/O boys/O ./O 
\/O ''/O .../O had/O given/O Jon/PERSON a/O barrel/O of/O oranges/O ,/O remember/O ?/O 
Only/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O things/O had/O gone/O rotten/O ,/O so/O I/O flung/O mine/O across/O the/O table/O and/O hit/O Dacks/PERSON right/O in/O the/O nose/O ./O 
You/O remember/O ,/O Redfort/PERSON 's/O pock-faced/O squire/O ?/O 
He/O tossed/O one/O back/O at/O me/O ,/O and/O before/O Jon/PERSON could/O so/O much/O as/O fart/O ,/O there/O were/O oranges/O flying/O across/O the/O High/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION in/O every/O direction/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O uproariously/O ,/O and/O even/O Ned/PERSON smiled/O ,/O remembering/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O This/O was/O the/O boy/O he/O had/O grown/O up/O with/O ,/O he/O thought/O ;/O this/O was/O the/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON he/O 'd/O known/O and/O loved/O ./O 
If/O he/O could/O prove/O that/O the/O Lannisters/O were/O behind/O the/O attack/O on/O Bran/O ,/O prove/O that/O they/O had/O murdered/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O this/O man/O would/O listen/O ./O 
Then/O Cersei/PERSON would/O fall/O ,/O and/O the/O Kingslayer/PERSON with/O her/O ,/O and/O if/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON dared/O to/O rouse/O the/O west/O ,/O Robert/PERSON would/O smash/O him/O as/O he/O had/O smashed/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON on/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O it/O all/O so/O clearly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O breakfast/O tasted/O better/O than/O anything/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O eaten/O in/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O and/O afterward/O his/O smiles/O came/O easier/O and/O more/O often/O ,/O until/O it/O was/O time/O for/O the/O tournament/O to/O resume/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON walked/O with/O the/O king/O to/O the/O jousting/O field/O ./O 
He/O had/O promised/O to/O watch/O the/O final/O tilts/O with/O Sansa/ORGANIZATION ;/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON was/O ill/O today/O ,/O and/O his/O daughter/O was/O determined/O not/O to/O miss/O the/O end/O of/O the/O jousting/O ./O 
As/O he/O saw/O Robert/PERSON to/O his/O place/O ,/O he/O noted/O that/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O chosen/O not/O to/O appear/O ;/O the/O place/O beside/O the/O king/O was/O empty/O ./O 
That/O too/O gave/O Ned/PERSON cause/O to/O hope/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O shouldered/O his/O way/O to/O where/O his/O daughter/O was/O seated/O and/O found/O her/O as/O the/O horns/O blew/O for/O the/O day/O 's/O first/O joust/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O so/O engrossed/O she/O scarcely/O seemed/O to/O notice/O his/O arrival/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON was/O the/O first/O rider/O to/O appear/O ./O 
He/O wore/O an/O olive-green/O cloak/O over/O his/O soot-grey/O armor/O ./O 
That/O ,/O and/O his/O hound/O 's/O -/O head/O helm/O ,/O were/O his/O only/O concession/O to/O ornament/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O hundred/O golden/O dragons/O on/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON announced/O loudly/O as/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON entered/O the/O lists/O ,/O riding/O an/O elegant/O blood/O bay/O destrier/O ./O 
The/O horse/O wore/O a/O blanket/O of/O gilded/O ringmail/O ,/O and/O Jaime/PERSON glittered/O from/O head/O to/O heel/O ./O 
Even/O his/O lance/O was/O fashioned/O from/O the/O golden/O wood/O of/O the/O Summer/O Isles/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Done/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON shouted/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Hound/O has/O a/O hungry/O look/O about/O him/O this/O morning/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Even/O hungry/O dogs/O know/O better/O than/O to/O bite/O the/O hand/O that/O feeds/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON called/O dryly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON dropped/O his/O visor/O with/O an/O audible/O clang/O and/O took/O up/O his/O position/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON tossed/O a/O kiss/O to/O some/O woman/O in/O the/O commons/O ,/O gently/O lowered/O his/O visor/O ,/O and/O rode/O to/O the/O end/O of/O the/O lists/O ./O 
Both/O men/O couched/O their/O lances/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON would/O have/O loved/O nothing/O so/O well/O as/O to/O see/O them/O both/O lose/O ,/O but/O Sansa/PERSON was/O watching/O it/O all/O moist-eyed/O and/O eager/O ./O 
The/O hastily/O erected/O gallery/O trembled/O as/O the/O horses/O broke/O into/O a/O gallop/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O leaned/O forward/O as/O he/O rode/O ,/O his/O lance/O rock/O steady/O ,/O but/O Jaime/PERSON shifted/O his/O seat/O deftly/O in/O the/O instant/O before/O impact/O ./O 
Clegane/PERSON 's/O point/O was/O turned/O harmlessly/O against/O the/O golden/O shield/O with/O the/O lion/O blazon/O ,/O while/O his/O own/O hit/O square/O ./O 
Wood/O shattered/O ,/O and/O the/O Hound/O reeled/O ,/O fighting/O to/O keep/O his/O seat/O ./O 
Sansa/O gasped/O ./O 
A/O ragged/O cheer/O went/O up/O from/O the/O commons/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wonder/O how/O I/O ought/O spend/O your/O money/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON called/O down/O to/O Lord/O Renly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O just/O managed/O to/O stay/O in/O his/O saddle/O ./O 
He/O jerked/O his/O mount/O around/O hard/O and/O rode/O back/O to/O the/O lists/O for/O the/O second/O pass/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON tossed/O down/O his/O broken/O lance/O and/O snatched/O up/O a/O fresh/O one/O ,/O jesting/O with/O his/O squire/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O spurred/O forward/O at/O a/O hard/O gallop/O ./O 
Lannister/PERSON rode/O to/O meet/O him/O ./O 
This/O time/O ,/O when/O Jaime/PERSON shifted/O his/O seat/O ,/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON shifted/O with/O him/O ./O 
Both/O lances/O ''/O ,/O ``/O exploded/O ,/O and/O by/O the/O time/O the/O splinters/O had/O settled/O ,/O a/O riderless/O blood/O bay/O was/O trotting/O off/O in/O search/O of/O grass/O while/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON rolled/O in/O the/O dirt/O ,/O golden/O and/O dented/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O knew/O the/O Hound/O would/O win/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON overheard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O know/O who/O 's/O going/O to/O win/O the/O second/O match/O ,/O speak/O up/O now/O before/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON plucks/O me/O clean/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O to/O her/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON smiled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O pity/O the/O Imp/O is/O not/O here/O with/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O have/O won/O twice/O as/O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O back/O on/O his/O feet/O ,/O but/O his/O ornate/O lion/O helmet/O had/O been/O twisted/O around/O and/O dented/O in/O his/O fall/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O could/O not/O get/O it/O off/O ./O 
The/O commons/O were/O hooting/O and/O pointing/O ,/O the/O lords/O and/O ladies/O were/O trying/O to/O stifle/O their/O chuckles/O ,/O and/O failing/O ,/O and/O over/O it/O all/O Ned/PERSON could/O hear/O King/O Robert/PERSON laughing/O ,/O louder/O than/O anyone/O ./O 
Finally/O they/O had/O to/O lead/O the/O Lion/O of/O Lannister/O off/O to/O a/O blacksmith/O ,/O blind/O and/O stumbling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O then/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON was/O in/O position/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O lists/O ./O 
He/O was/O huge/O ,/O the/O biggest/O man/O that/O Eddard/O Stark/O had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON and/O his/O brothers/O were/O all/O big/O men/O ,/O as/O was/O the/O Hound/O ,/O and/O back/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION there/O was/O a/O simpleminded/O stableboy/O named/O Hodor/PERSON who/O dwarfed/O them/O all/O ,/O but/O the/O knight/O they/O called/O the/O Mountain/O That/O Rides/O would/O have/O towered/O over/O Hodor/PERSON ./O 
He/O was/O well/O over/O seven/O feet/O tall/O ,/O closer/O to/O eight/O ,/O with/O massive/O shoulders/O and/O arms/O thick/O as/O the/O trunks/O of/O small/O trees/O ./O 
His/O destrier/O seemed/O a/O pony/O in/O between/O his/O armored/O legs/O ,/O and/O the/O lance/O he/O carried/O looked/O as/O small/O as/O a/O broom/O handle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Unlike/O his/O brother/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON did/O not/O live/O at/O court/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O solitary/O man/O who/O seldom/O left/O his/O own/O lands/O ,/O but/O for/O wars/O and/O tourneys/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O with/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON when/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O fell/O ,/O a/O new-made/O knight/O of/O seventeen/O years/O ,/O even/O then/O distinguished/O by/O his/O size/O and/O his/O implacable/O ferocity/O ./O 
Some/O said/O it/O had/O been/O Gregor/PERSON who/O 'd/O dashed/O the/O skull/O of/O the/O infant/O prince/O Aegon/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON against/O a/O wall/O ,/O and/O whispered/O that/O afterward/O he/O had/O raped/O the/O mother/O ,/O the/O Dornish/O princess/O Elia/PERSON ,/O before/O putting/O her/O to/O the/O sword/O ./O 
These/O things/O were/O not/O said/O in/O Gregor/PERSON 's/O hearing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O Stark/O could/O not/O recall/O ever/O speaking/O to/O the/O man/O ,/O though/O Gregor/PERSON had/O ridden/O with/O them/O during/O Balon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON 's/O rebellion/O ,/O one/O knight/O among/O thousands/O ./O 
He/O watched/O him/O with/O disquiet/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON seldom/O put/O much/O stock/O in/O gossip/O ,/O but/O the/O things/O said/O of/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON were/O more/O than/O ominous/O ./O 
He/O was/O soon/O to/O be/O married/O for/O the/O third/O time/O ,/O and/O one/O heard/O dark/O whisperings/O about/O the/O deaths/O of/O his/O first/O two/O wives/O ./O 
It/O was/O said/O that/O his/O keep/O was/O a/O grim/O place/O where/O servants/O disappeared/O unaccountably/O and/O even/O the/O dogs/O were/O afraid/O to/O enter/O the/O hall/O ./O 
And/O there/O had/O been/O a/O sister/O who/O had/O died/O young/O under/O queer/O circumstances/O ,/O and/O the/O fire/O that/O had/O disfigured/O his/O brother/O ,/O and/O the/O hunting/O accident/O that/O had/O killed/O their/O father/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON had/O inherited/O the/O keep/O ,/O the/O gold/O ,/O and/O the/O family/O estates/O ./O 
His/O younger/O brother/O Sandor/PERSON had/O left/O the/O same/O day/O to/O take/O service/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O as/O a/O sworn/O sword/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O said/O that/O he/O had/O never/O returned/O ,/O not/O even/O to/O visit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/PERSON made/O his/O entrance/O ,/O a/O murmur/O ran/O through/O the/O crowd/O ,/O and/O he/O heard/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O fervent/O whisper/O ,/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O he/O 's/O so/O beautiful/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON was/O slender/O as/O a/O reed/O ,/O dressed/O in/O a/O suit/O of/O fabulous/O silver/O armor/O polished/O to/O a/O blinding/O sheen/O and/O filigreed/O with/O twining/O black/O vines/O and/O tiny/O blue/O forget-me-nots/O ./O 
The/O commons/O realized/O in/O the/O same/O instant/O as/O Ned/PERSON that/O the/O blue/O of/O the/O flowers/O came/O from/O sapphires/O ;/O a/O gasp/O went/O up/O from/O a/O thousand/O throats/O ./O 
Across/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O boy/O 's/O shoulders/O his/O cloak/O hung/O heavy/O ./O 
It/O was/O woven/O of/O forget-me-nots/O ,/O real/O ones/O ,/O hundreds/O of/O fresh/O blooms/O sewn/O to/O a/O heavy/O woolen/O cape/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O courser/O was/O as/O slim/O as/O her/O rider/O ,/O a/O beautiful/O grey/O mare/O ,/O built/O for/O speed/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O huge/O stallion/O trumpeted/O as/O he/O caught/O her/O scent/O ./O 
The/O boy/O from/O Highgarden/LOCATION did/O something/O with/O his/O legs/O ,/O and/O his/O horse/O pranced/O sideways/O ,/O nimble/O as/O a/O dancer/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON clutched/O at/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ,/O do/O n't/O let/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON hurt/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON saw/O she/O was/O wearing/O the/O rose/O that/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON had/O given/O her/O yesterday/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON had/O told/O him/O about/O that/O as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O These/O are/O tourney/O lances/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O his/O daughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O make/O them/O to/O splinter/O on/O impact/O ,/O so/O no/O one/O is/O hurt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Yet/O he/O remembered/O the/O dead/O boy/O in/O the/O cart/O with/O his/O cloak/O of/O crescent/O moons/O ,/O and/O the/O words/O were/O raw/O in/O his/O throat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON was/O having/O trouble/O controlling/O his/O horse/O ./O 
The/O stallion/O was/O screaming/O and/O pawing/O the/O ground/O ,/O shaking/O his/O head/O ./O 
The/O Mountain/O kicked/O at/O the/O animal/O savagely/O with/O an/O armored/O boot/O ./O 
The/O horse/O reared/O and/O almost/O threw/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O saluted/O the/O king/O ,/O rode/O to/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O list/O ,/O and/O couched/O his/O lance/O ,/O ready/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON brought/O his/O animal/O to/O the/O line/O ,/O fighting/O with/O the/O reins/O ./O 
And/O suddenly/O it/O began/O ./O 
The/O Mountain/O 's/O stallion/O broke/O in/O a/O hard/O gallop/O ,/O plunging/O forward/O wildly/O ,/O while/O the/O mare/O charged/O as/O smooth/O as/O a/O flow/O of/O silk/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON wrenched/O his/O shield/O into/O position/O ,/O juggled/O with/O his/O lance/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O while/O fought/O to/O hold/O his/O unruly/O mount/O on/O a/O straight/O line/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON was/O on/O him/O ,/O placing/O the/O point/O of/O his/O lance/O just/O there/O ,/O and/O in/O an/O eye/O blink/O the/O Mountain/O was/O failing/O ./O 
He/O was/O so/O huge/O that/O he/O took/O his/O horse/O down/O with/O him/O in/O a/O tangle/O of/O steel/O and/O flesh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON heard/O applause/O ,/O cheers/O ,/O whistles/O ,/O shocked/O gasps/O ,/O excited/O muttering/O ,/O and/O over/O it/O all/O the/O rasping/O ,/O raucous/O laughter/O of/O the/O Hound/O ./O 
The/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O reined/O up/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O lists/O ./O 
His/O lance/O was/O not/O even/O broken/O ./O 
His/O sapphires/O winked/O in/O the/O sun/O as/O he/O raised/O his/O visor/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
The/O commons/O went/O mad/O for/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O field/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON disentangled/O himself/O and/O came/O boiling/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
He/O wrenched/O off/O his/O helm/O and/O slammed/O it/O down/O onto/O the/O ground/O ./O 
His/O face/O was/O dark/O with/O fury/O and/O his/O hair/O fell/O down/O into/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sword/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O to/O his/O squire/O ,/O and/O the/O boy/O ran/O it/O out/O to/O him/O ./O 
By/O then/O his/O stallion/O was/O back/O on/O its/O feet/O as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON killed/O the/O horse/O with/O a/O single/O blow/O of/O such/O ferocity/O that/O it/O half/O severed/O the/O animal/O 's/O neck/O ./O 
Cheers/O turned/O to/O shrieks/O in/O a/O heartbeat/O ./O 
The/O stallion/O went/O to/O its/O knees/O ,/O screaming/O as/O it/O died/O ./O 
By/O then/O Gregor/PERSON was/O striding/O down/O the/O lists/O toward/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON ,/O his/O bloody/O sword/O clutched/O in/O his/O fist/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stop/O him/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON shouted/O ,/O but/O his/O words/O were/O lost/O in/O the/O roar/O ./O 
Everyone/O else/O was/O yelling/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON was/O crying/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O all/O happened/O so/O fast/O ./O 
The/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O was/O shouting/O for/O his/O own/O sword/O as/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON knocked/O his/O squire/O aside/O and/O made/O a/O grab/O for/O the/O reins/O of/O his/O horse/O ./O 
The/O mare/O scented/O blood/O and/O reared/O ./O 
Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON kept/O his/O seat/O ,/O but/O barely/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON swung/O his/O sword/O ,/O a/O savage/O twohanded/O blow/O that/O took/O the/O boy/O in/O the/O chest/O and/O knocked/O him/O from/O the/O saddle/O ./O 
The/O courser/O dashed/O away/O in/O panic/O as/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON lay/O stunned/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
But/O as/O Gregor/PERSON lifted/O his/O sword/O for/O the/O killing/O blow/O ,/O a/O rasping/O voice/O warned/O ,/O \/O ``/O Leave/O him/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O a/O steel-clad/O hand/O wrenched/O him/O away/O from/O the/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Mountain/O pivoted/O in/O wordless/O fury/O ,/O swinging/O his/O longsword/O in/O a/O killing/O arc/O with/O all/O his/O massive/O strength/O behind/O it/O ,/O but/O the/O Hound/O caught/O the/O blow/O and/O turned/O it/O ,/O and/O for/O what/O seemed/O an/O eternity/O the/O two/O brothers/O stood/O hammering/O at/O each/O other/O as/O a/O dazed/O Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON was/O helped/O to/O safety/O ./O 
Thrice/O Ned/PERSON saw/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON aim/O savage/O blows/O at/O the/O hound/O 's/O -/O head/O helmet/O ,/O yet/O not/O once/O did/O Sandor/PERSON send/O a/O cut/O at/O his/O brother/O 's/O unprotected/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O king/O 's/O voice/O that/O put/O an/O end/O to/O it/O .../O the/O king/O 's/O voice/O and/O twenty/O swords/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O told/O them/O that/O a/O commander/O needs/O a/O good/O battlefield/O voice/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON had/O proved/O the/O truth/O of/O that/O on/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
He/O used/O that/O voice/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O STOP/O THIS/O MADNESS/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O boomed/O ,/O \/O ``/O IN/O THE/O NAME/O OF/O YOUR/O KING/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O went/O to/O one/O knee/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O blow/O cut/O air/O ,/O and/O at/O last/O he/O came/O to/O his/O senses/O ./O 
He/O dropped/O his/O sword/O and/O glared/O at/O Robert/PERSON ,/O surrounded/O by/O his/O Kingsguard/ORGANIZATION and/O a/O dozen/O other/O knights/O and/O guardsmen/O ./O 
Wordlessly/O ,/O he/O turned/O and/O strode/O off/O ,/O shoving/O past/O Barristan/O Selmy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O him/O go/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ,/O and/O as/O quickly/O as/O that/O ,/O it/O was/O over/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O the/O Hound/O the/O champion/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON asked/O Ned/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O will/O be/O one/O final/O joust/O ,/O between/O the/O Hound/O and/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O But/O Sansa/O had/O the/O right/O of/O it/O after/O all/O ./O 
A/O few/O moments/O later/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON walked/O back/O onto/O the/O field/O in/O a/O simple/O linen/O doublet/O and/O said/O to/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O I/O owe/O you/O my/O life/O ./O 
The/O day/O is/O yours/O ,/O ser/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O no/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Hound/O replied/O ,/O but/O he/O took/O the/O victory/O ,/O and/O the/O champion/O 's/O purse/O ,/O and/O ,/O for/O perhaps/O the/O first/O time/O in/O his/O life/O ,/O the/O love/O of/O the/O commons/O ./O 
They/O cheered/O him/O as/O he/O left/O the/O lists/O to/O return/O to/O his/O pavilion/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O Ned/PERSON walked/O with/O Sansa/O to/O the/O archery/O field/O ,/O Little/O finger/O and/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON and/O some/O of/O the/O others/O fell/O in/O with/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrell/PERSON had/O to/O know/O the/O mare/O was/O in/O heat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON was/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O swear/O the/O boy/O planned/O the/O whole/O thing/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON has/O always/O favored/O huge/O ,/O ill-tempered/O stallions/O with/O more/O spirit/O than/O sense/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O notion/O seemed/O to/O amuse/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O did/O not/O amuse/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O small/O honor/O in/O tricks/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O said/O stiffly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Small/O honor/O and/O twenty/O thousand/O golds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON smiled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O afternoon/O a/O boy/O named/O Anguy/PERSON ,/O an/O unheralded/O commoner/O from/O the/O Dornish/O Marches/O ,/O won/O the/O archery/O competition/O ,/O outshooting/O Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON and/O Jalabhar/PERSON Xho/PERSON at/O a/O hundred/O paces/O after/O all/O the/O other/O bowmen/O had/O been/O eliminated/O at/O the/O shorter/O distances/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON sent/O Alyn/PERSON to/O seek/O him/O out/O and/O offer/O him/O a/O position/O with/O the/O Hand/O 's/O guard/O ,/O but/O the/O boy/O was/O flush/O with/O wine/O and/O victory/O and/O riches/O undreamed/O of/O ,/O and/O he/O refused/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O melee/O went/O on/O for/O three/O hours/O ./O 
Near/O forty/O men/O took/O part/O ,/O freeriders/O and/O hedge/O knights/O and/O new-made/O squires/O in/O search/O of/O a/O reputation/O ./O 
They/O fought/O with/O blunted/O weapons/O in/O a/O chaos/O of/O mud/O and/O blood/O ,/O small/O troops/O fighting/O together/O and/O then/O turning/O on/O each/O other/O as/O alliances/O formed/O and/O fractured/O ,/O until/O only/O one/O man/O was/O left/O standing/O ./O 
The/O victor/O was/O the/O red/O priest/O ,/O Thoros/PERSON of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O madman/O who/O shaved/O his/O head/O and/O fought/O with/O a/O flaming/O sword/O ./O 
He/O had/O won/O melees/O before/O ;/O the/O fire/O sword/O frightened/O the/O mounts/O of/O the/O other/O riders/O ,/O and/O nothing/O frightened/O Thoros/O ./O 
The/O final/O tally/O was/O three/O broken/O limbs/O ,/O a/O shattered/O collarbone/O ,/O a/O dozen/O smashed/O fingers/O ,/O two/O horses/O that/O ''/O ,/O ``/O had/O to/O be/O put/O down/O ,/O and/O more/O cuts/O ,/O sprains/O ,/O and/O bruises/O than/O anyone/O cared/O to/O count/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON was/O desperately/O pleased/O that/O Robert/PERSON had/O not/O taken/O part/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O night/O at/O the/O feast/O ,/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O more/O hopeful/O than/O he/O had/O been/O in/O a/O great/O while/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O in/O high/O good/O humor/O ,/O the/O Lannisters/O were/O nowhere/O to/O be/O seen/O ,/O and/O even/O his/O daughters/O were/O behaving/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON brought/O Arya/PERSON down/O to/O join/O them/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON spoke/O to/O her/O sister/O pleasantly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O tournament/O was/O magnificent/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O should/O have/O come/O ./O 
How/O was/O your/O dancing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sore/O all/O over/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON reported/O happily/O ,/O proudly/O displaying/O a/O huge/O purple/O bruise/O on/O her/O leg/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O be/O a/O terrible/O dancer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O doubtfully/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Later/O ,/O while/O Sansa/O was/O off/O listening/O to/O a/O troupe/O of/O singers/O perform/O the/O complex/O round/O of/O interwoven/O ballads/O called/O the/O \/O ``/O Dance/O of/O the/O Dragons/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON inspected/O the/O bruise/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O Forel/O is/O not/O being/O too/O hard/O on/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON stood/O on/O one/O leg/O ./O 
She/O was/O getting/O much/O better/O at/O that/O of/O late/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Syrio/PERSON says/O that/O every/O hurt/O is/O a/O lesson/O ,/O and/O every/O lesson/O makes/O you/O better/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ./O 
The/O man/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON had/O come/O with/O an/O excellent/O reputation/O ,/O and/O his/O flamboyant/O Braavosi/O style/O was/O well/O suited/O to/O Arya/PERSON 's/O slender/O blade/O ,/O yet/O still/O .../O a/O few/O days/O ago/O ,/O she/O had/O been/O wandering/O around/O with/O a/O swatch/O of/O black/O silk/O tied/O over/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Syrio/PERSON was/O teaching/O her/O to/O see/O with/O her/O ears/O and/O her/O nose/O and/O her/O skin/O ,/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
Before/O that/O ,/O he/O had/O her/O doing/O spins/O and/O back/O flips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O are/O you/O certain/O you/O want/O to/O persist/O in/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tomorrow/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O catch/O cats/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cats/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O it/O was/O a/O mistake/O to/O hire/O this/O Braavosi/PERSON ./O 
If/O you/O like/O ,/O I/O will/O ask/O Jory/PERSON to/O take/O over/O your/O lessons/O ./O 
Or/O I/O might/O have/O a/O quiet/O word/O with/O Ser/O Barristan/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O finest/O sword/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O in/O his/O youth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O Syrio/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON ran/O his/O fingers/O through/O his/O hair/O ./O 
Any/O decent/O master-at-arms/O could/O give/O Arya/PERSON the/O rudiments/O of/O slash-and-parry/O without/O this/O nonsense/O of/O blindfolds/O ,/O cartwheels/O ,/O and/O hopping/O about/O on/O one/O leg/O ,/O but/O he/O knew/O his/O youngest/O daughter/O well/O enough/O to/O know/O there/O was/O no/O arguing/O with/O that/O stubborn/O jut/O of/O jaw/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
Surely/O she/O would/O grow/O tired/O of/O this/O soon/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Try/O to/O be/O careful/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O promised/O solemnly/O as/O she/O hopped/O smoothly/O from/O her/O right/O leg/O to/O her/O left/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Much/O later/O ,/O after/O he/O had/O taken/O the/O girls/O back/O through/O the/O city/O and/O seen/O them/O both/O safe/O in/O bed/O ,/O Sansa/O with/O her/O dreams/O and/O Arya/PERSON with/O her/O bruises/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ascended/O to/O his/O own/O chambers/O atop/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ./O 
The/O day/O had/O been/O warm/O and/O the/O room/O was/O close/O and/O stuffy/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON went/O to/O the/O window/O and/O unfastened/O the/O heavy/O shutters/O to/O let/O in/O the/O cool/O night/O air/O ./O 
Across/O the/O Great/LOCATION Yard/LOCATION ,/O he/O noticed/O the/O flickering/O glow/O of/O candlelight/O from/O Little/O finger/O 's/O windows/O ./O 
The/O hour/O was/O well/O past/O midnight/O ./O 
Down/O by/O the/O river/O ,/O the/O revels/O were/O only/O now/O beginning/O to/O dwindle/O and/O die/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O took/O out/O the/O dagger/O and/O studied/O it/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON 's/O blade/O ,/O won/O by/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON in/O a/O tourney/O wager/O ,/O sent/O to/O slay/O Bran/O in/O his/O sleep/O ./O 
Why/O ?/O 
Why/O would/O the/O dwarf/O want/O Bran/O dead/O ?/O 
Why/O would/O anyone/O want/O Bran/O dead/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dagger/O ,/O Bran/O 's/O fall/O ,/O all/O of/O it/O was/O linked/O somehow/O to/O the/O murder/O of/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O he/O could/O feel/O it/O in/O his/O gut/O ,/O but/O the/O truth/O of/O Jon/PERSON 's/O death/O remained/O as/O clouded/O to/O him/O as/O when/O he/O had/O started/O ./O 
Lord/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Stannis/O had/O not/O returned/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O for/O the/O tourney/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON held/O her/O silence/O behind/O the/O high/O walls/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
The/O squire/O was/O dead/O ,/O and/O Jory/PERSON was/O still/O searching/O the/O whorehouses/O ./O 
What/O did/O he/O have/O but/O Robert/PERSON 's/O bastard/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O the/O armorer/O 's/O sullen/O apprentice/O was/O the/O king/O 's/O son/O ,/O Ned/PERSON had/O no/O doubt/O ./O 
The/O Baratheon/PERSON look/O was/O stamped/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O in/O his/O jaw/O ,/O his/O eyes/O ,/O that/O black/O hair/O ./O 
Renly/PERSON was/O too/O young/O to/O have/O fathered/O a/O boy/O of/O that/O age/O ,/O Stannis/PERSON too/O cold/O and/O proud/O in/O his/O honor/O ./O 
Gendry/PERSON had/O to/O be/O Robert/PERSON 's/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O knowing/O all/O that/O ,/O what/O had/O he/O learned/O ?/O 
The/O king/O had/O other/O baseborn/O children/O scattered/O throughout/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
He/O had/O openly/O acknowledged/O one/O of/O his/O bastards/O ,/O a/O boy/O of/O Bran/O 's/O age/O whose/O mother/O was/O highborn/O ./O 
The/O lad/O was/O being/O fostered/O by/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON 's/O castellan/O at/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON remembered/O Robert/PERSON 's/O first/O child/O as/O well/O ,/O a/O daughter/O born/O in/O the/O Vale/LOCATION when/O Robert/PERSON was/O scarcely/O more/O than/O a/O boy/O himself/O ./O 
A/O sweet/O little/O girl/O ;/O the/O young/O lord/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O had/O doted/O on/O her/O ./O 
He/O used/O to/O make/O daily/O visits/O to/O play/O with/O the/O babe/O ,/O long/O after/O he/O had/O lost/O interest/O in/O the/O mother/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON was/O often/O dragged/O along/O for/O company/O ,/O whether/O he/O willed/O it/O or/O not/O ./O 
The/O girl/O would/O be/O seventeen/O or/O eighteen/O now/O ,/O he/O realized/O ;/O older/O than/O Robert/PERSON had/O been/O when/O he/O fathered/O her/O ./O 
A/O strange/O thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON could/O not/O have/O been/O pleased/O by/O her/O lord/O husband/O 's/O by-blows/O ,/O yet/O in/O the/O end/O it/O mattered/O little/O whether/O the/O king/O had/O one/O bastard/O or/O a/O hundred/O ./O 
Law/PERSON and/O custom/O gave/O the/O baseborn/O few/O rights/O ./O 
Gendry/O ,/O the/O girl/O in/O the/O Vale/LOCATION ,/O the/O boy/O at/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ,/O none/O of/O them/O could/O threaten/O Robert/PERSON 's/O trueborn/O children/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O musings/O were/O ended/O by/O a/O soft/O rap/O on/O his/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O man/O to/O see/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Harwin/PERSON called/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O will/O not/O give/O his/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Send/O him/O in/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O wondering/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O visitor/O was/O a/O stout/O man/O in/O cracked/O ,/O mud-caked/O boots/O and/O a/O heavy/O brown/O robe/O of/O the/O coarsest/O roughspun/O ,/O his/O features/O hidden/O by/O a/O cowl/O ,/O his/O hands/O drawn/O up/O into/O voluminous/O sleeves/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O cowled/O man/O said/O in/O a/O strange/O ,/O low/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O speak/O alone/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Curiosity/O was/O stronger/O than/O caution/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Harwin/PERSON ,/O leave/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O commanded/O ./O 
Not/O until/O they/O were/O alone/O behind/O closed/O doors/O did/O his/O visitor/O draw/O back/O his/O cowl/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O in/O astonishment/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O politely/O ,/O seating/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O if/O I/O might/O trouble/O you/O for/O a/O drink/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O filled/O two/O cups/O with/O summerwine/O and/O handed/O one/O to/O Varys/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O might/O have/O passed/O within/O a/O foot/O of/O you/O and/O never/O recognized/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O incredulous/O ./O 
He/O had/O never/O seen/O the/O eunuch/O dress/O in/O anything/O but/O silk/O and/O velvet/O and/O the/O richest/O damasks/O ,/O and/O this/O man/O smelled/O of/O sweat/O instead/O of/O lilacs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O was/O my/O dearest/O hope/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O not/O do/O if/O certain/O people/O learned/O that/O we/O had/O spoken/O in/O private/O ./O 
The/O queen/O watches/O you/O closely/O ./O 
This/O wine/O is/O very/O choice/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O did/O you/O get/O past/O my/O other/O guards/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O ./O 
Porther/O and/O Cayn/PERSON had/O been/O posted/O outside/O the/O tower/O ,/O and/O Alyn/PERSON on/O the/O stairs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Red/O Keep/O has/O ways/O known/O only/O to/O ghosts/O and/O spiders/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Varys/PERSON smiled/O apologetically/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O keep/O you/O long/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
There/O are/O things/O you/O must/O know/O ./O 
You/O are/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ,/O and/O the/O king/O is/O a/O fool/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O 's/O cloying/O tones/O were/O gone/O ;/O now/O his/O voice/O was/O thin/O and/O sharp/O as/O a/O whip/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O friend/O ,/O I/O know/O ,/O yet/O a/O fool/O nonetheless/O .../O and/O doomed/O ,/O unless/O you/O save/O him/O ./O 
Today/O was/O a/O near/O thing/O ./O 
They/O had/O hoped/O to/O kill/O him/O during/O the/O melee/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Ned/PERSON was/O speechless/O with/O shock/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O sipped/O his/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O truly/O need/O to/O tell/O you/O that/O ,/O you/O are/O a/O bigger/O fool/O than/O Robert/PERSON and/O I/O am/O on/O the/O wrong/O side/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O queen/O .../O no/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O believe/O that/O ,/O not/O even/O of/O Cersei/LOCATION ./O 
She/O asked/O him/O not/O to/O fight/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O forbade/O him/O to/O fight/O ,/O in/O front/O of/O his/O brother/O ,/O his/O knights/O ,/O and/O half/O the/O court/O ./O 
Tell/O me/O truly/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O any/O surer/O way/O to/O force/O King/O Robert/PERSON into/O the/O melee/O ?/O 
I/O ask/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O a/O sick/O feeling/O in/O his/O gut/O ./O 
The/O eunuch/O had/O hit/O upon/O a/O truth/O ;/O tell/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON he/O could/O not/O ,/O should/O not/O ,/O or/O must/O not/O do/O a/O thing/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O as/O good/O as/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O if/O he/O 'd/O fought/O ,/O who/O would/O have/O dared/O to/O strike/O the/O king/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O were/O forty/O riders/O in/O the/O melee/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O have/O many/O friends/O ./O 
Amidst/O all/O that/O chaos/O ,/O with/O horses/O screaming/O and/O bones/O breaking/O and/O Thoros/PERSON of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION waving/O that/O absurd/O firesword/O of/O his/O ,/O who/O could/O name/O it/O murder/O if/O some/O chance/O blow/O felled/O His/O Grace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O went/O to/O the/O flagon/O and/O refilled/O his/O cup/O ./O 
\/O ``/O After/O the/O deed/O was/O done/O ,/O the/O slayer/O would/O be/O beside/O himself/O with/O grief/O ./O 
I/O can/O almost/O hear/O him/O weeping/O ./O 
So/O sad/O ./O 
Yet/O no/O doubt/O the/O gracious/O and/O compassionate/O widow/O would/O take/O pity/O ,/O lift/O the/O poor/O unfortunate/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O and/O bless/O him/O with/O a/O gentle/O kiss/O of/O forgiveness/O ./O 
Good/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O have/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O pardon/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O stroked/O his/O cheek/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Or/O perhaps/O Cersei/PERSON would/O let/O Ser/O Ilyn/O strike/O off/O his/O head/O ./O 
Less/O risk/O for/O the/O Lannisters/O that/O way/O ,/O though/O quite/O an/O unpleasant/O surprise/O for/O their/O little/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON felt/O his/O anger/O rise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O knew/O of/O this/O plot/O ,/O and/O yet/O you/O did/O nothing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O command/O whisperers/O ,/O not/O warriors/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O might/O have/O come/O to/O me/O earlier/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ,/O I/O confess/O it/O ./O 
And/O you/O would/O have/O rushed/O straight/O to/O the/O king/O ,/O yes/O ?/O 
And/O when/O Robert/PERSON heard/O of/O his/O peril/O ,/O what/O would/O he/O have/O done/O ?/O 
I/O wonder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON considered/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O would/O have/O damned/O them/O all/O ,/O and/O fought/O anyway/O ,/O to/O show/O he/O did/O not/O fear/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O spread/O his/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O make/O another/O confession/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
I/O was/O curious/O to/O see/O what/O you/O would/O do/O ./O 
Why/O not/O come/O to/O me/O ?/O 
you/O ask/O ,/O and/O I/O must/O answer/O ,/O Why/O ,/O because/O I/O did/O not/O trust/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O did/O not/O trust/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON was/O frankly/O astonished/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Red/O Keep/O shelters/O two/O sorts/O of/O people/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Those/O who/O are/O loyal/O to/O the/O realm/O ,/O and/O those/O who/O are/O loyal/O only/O to/O themselves/O ./O 
Until/O this/O morning/O ,/O I/O could/O not/O say/O which/O you/O might/O be/O .../O so/O I/O waited/O to/O see/O .../O and/O now/O I/O know/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O a/O plump/O tight/O little/O smile/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O moment/O his/O private/O face/O and/O public/O mask/O were/O one/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O begin/O to/O comprehend/O why/O the/O queen/O fears/O you/O so/O much/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O yes/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O one/O she/O ought/O to/O fear/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
I/O am/O what/O I/O am/O ./O 
The/O king/O makes/O use/O of/O me/O ,/O but/O it/O shames/O him/O ./O 
A/O most/O puissant/O warrior/O is/O our/O Robert/PERSON ,/O and/O such/O a/O manly/O man/O has/O little/O love/O for/O sneaks/O and/O spies/O and/O eunuchs/O ./O 
If/O a/O day/O should/O come/O when/O Cersei/PERSON whispers/O ,/O `/O Kill/O that/O man/O ,/O '/O Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON will/O snick/O my/O head/O off/O in/O a/O twinkling/O ,/O and/O who/O will/O mourn/O poor/O Varys/PERSON then/O ?/O 
North/O or/O south/O ,/O they/O sing/O no/O songs/O for/O spiders/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O reached/O out/O and/O touched/O Ned/PERSON with/O a/O soft/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O you/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O .../O I/O think/O .../O no/O ,/O I/O know/O .../O he/O would/O not/O kill/O you/O ,/O not/O even/O for/O his/O queen/O ,/O and/O there/O may/O lie/O our/O salvation/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O all/O too/O much/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON wanted/O nothing/O so/O much/O as/O to/O return/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O to/O the/O clean/O simplicity/O of/O the/O north/O ,/O where/O the/O enemies/O were/O winter/O and/O the/O wildlings/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Surely/O Robert/PERSON has/O other/O loyal/O friends/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O protested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O brothers/O ,/O his/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O wife/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Varys/PERSON finished/O ,/O with/O a/O smile/O that/O cut/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O brothers/O hate/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O true/O enough/O ,/O but/O hating/O the/O queen/O and/O loving/O the/O king/O are/O not/O quite/O the/O same/O thing/O ,/O are/O they/O ?/O 
Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON loves/O his/O honor/O ,/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON loves/O his/O office/O ,/O and/O Littlefinger/PERSON loves/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Kingsguard/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O paper/O shield/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O eunuch/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Try/O not/O to/O look/O so/O shocked/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ./O 
Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON is/O himself/O a/O Sworn/O Brother/O of/O the/O White/LOCATION Swords/LOCATION ,/O and/O we/O all/O know/O what/O his/O oath/O is/O worth/O ./O 
The/O days/O when/O men/O like/O Ryam/PERSON Redwyne/PERSON and/O Prince/O Aemon/PERSON the/O Dragonknight/O wore/O the/O white/O cloak/O are/O gone/O to/O dust/O and/O song/O ./O 
Of/O these/O seven/O ,/O only/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O is/O made/O of/O the/O true/O steel/O ,/O and/O Selmy/PERSON is/O old/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON are/O the/O queen/O 's/O creatures/O to/O the/O bone/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O deep/O suspicions/O of/O the/O others/O ./O 
No/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O when/O the/O swords/O come/O out/O in/O earnest/O ,/O you/O will/O be/O the/O only/O true/O friend/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON will/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON must/O be/O told/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O what/O you/O say/O is/O true/O ,/O if/O even/O a/O part/O of/O it/O is/O true/O ,/O the/O king/O must/O hear/O it/O for/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O proof/O shall/O we/O lay/O before/O him/O ?/O 
My/O words/O against/O theirs/O ?/O 
My/O little/O birds/O against/O the/O queen/O and/O the/O Kingslayer/PERSON ,/O against/O his/O brothers/O and/O his/O council/O ,/O against/O the/O Wardens/O of/O East/LOCATION and/O West/LOCATION ,/O against/O all/O the/O might/O of/O Caster/O ly/O Rock/O ?/O 
Pray/O ,/O send/O for/O Ser/O Ilyn/O directly/O ,/O it/O will/O save/O us/O all/O some/O time/O ./O 
I/O know/O where/O that/O road/O ends/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yet/O if/O what/O you/O say/O is/O true/O ,/O they/O will/O only/O bide/O their/O time/O and/O make/O another/O attempt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Indeed/O they/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O and/O sooner/O rather/O than/O later/O ,/O I/O do/O fear/O ./O 
You/O are/O making/O them/O most/O anxious/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
But/O my/O little/O birds/O will/O be/O listening/O ,/O and/O together/O we/O may/O be/O able/O to/O forestall/O them/O ,/O you/O and/O U/O '/O He/O rose/O and/O pulled/O up/O his/O cowl/O so/O his/O face/O was/O hidden/O once/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O for/O the/O wine/O ./O 
We/O will/O speak/O again/O ./O 
When/O you/O see/O me/O next/O at/O council/O ,/O be/O certain/O to/O treat/O me/O with/O your/O accustomed/O contempt/O ./O 
You/O should/O not/O find/O it/O difficult/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O at/O the/O door/O when/O Ned/PERSON called/O ,/O \/O ``/O Varys/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O turned/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O did/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON die/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wondered/O when/O you/O would/O get/O around/O to/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O tears/O of/O Lys/O ,/O they/O call/O it/O ./O 
A/O rare/O and/O costly/O thing/O ,/O clear/O and/O sweet/O as/O water/O ,/O and/O it/O leaves/O no/O trace/O ./O 
I/O begged/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON to/O use/O a/O taster/O ,/O in/O this/O very/O room/O I/O begged/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O not/O hear/O of/O it/O ./O 
Only/O one/O who/O was/O less/O than/O a/O man/O would/O even/O think/O of/O such/O a/O thing/O ,/O he/O told/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O to/O know/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O gave/O him/O the/O poison/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O dear/O sweet/O friend/O who/O often/O shared/O meat/O and/O mead/O with/O him/O ,/O no/O doubt/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O but/O which/O one/O ?/O 
There/O were/O many/O such/O ./O 
Lord/O Arryn/PERSON was/O a/O kindly/O ,/O trusting/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O was/O one/O boy/O ./O 
All/O he/O was/O ,/O he/O owed/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O but/O when/O the/O widow/O fled/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O with/O her/O household/O ,/O he/O stayed/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O prospered/O ./O 
It/O always/O gladdens/O my/O heart/O to/O see/O the/O young/O rise/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O whip/O was/O in/O his/O voice/O again/O ,/O every/O word/O a/O stroke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O must/O have/O cut/O a/O gallant/O figure/O in/O the/O tourney/O ,/O him/O in/O his/O bright/O new/O armor/O ,/O with/O those/O crescent/O moons/O on/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
A/O pity/O he/O died/O so/O untimely/O ,/O before/O you/O could/O talk/O to/O him/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON felt/O half-poisoned/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O squire/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Hugh/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Wheels/O within/O wheels/O within/O wheels/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON 's/O head/O was/O pounding/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Why/O ?/O 
Why/O now/O ?/O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O been/O Hand/O for/O fourteen/O years/O ./O 
What/O was/O he/O doing/O that/O they/O had/O to/O kill/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Asking/O questions/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ,/O slipping/O out/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
