-LSB-/O ``/O ARYA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O father/O had/O been/O fighting/O with/O the/O council/O again/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON could/O see/O it/O on/O his/O face/O when/O he/O came/O to/O table/O ,/O late/O again/O ,/O as/O he/O had/O been/O so/O often/O ./O 
The/O first/O course/O ,/O a/O thick/O sweet/O soup/O made/O with/O pumpkins/O ,/O had/O already/O been/O taken/O away/O when/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON strode/O into/O the/O Small/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
They/O called/O it/O that/O to/O set/O it/O apart/O from/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O where/O the/O king/O could/O feast/O a/O thousand/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O a/O long/O room/O with/O a/O high/O vaulted/O ceiling/O and/O bench/O space/O for/O two/O hundred/O at/O its/O trestle/O tables/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jory/PERSON said/O when/O Father/O entered/O ./O 
He/O rose/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O and/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O guard/O rose/O with/O him/O ./O 
Each/O man/O wore/O a/O new/O cloak/O ,/O heavy/O grey/O wool/O with/O a/O white/O satin/O border/O ./O 
A/O hand/O of/O beaten/O silver/O clutched/O the/O woolen/O folds/O of/O each/O cloak/O and/O marked/O their/O wearers/O as/O men/O of/O the/O Hand/O 's/O household/O guard/O ./O 
There/O were/O only/O fifty/O of/O them/O ,/O so/O most/O of/O the/O benches/O were/O empty/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Be/O seated/O ,/O \/O ''/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O you/O have/O started/O without/O me/O ./O 
I/O am/O pleased/O to/O know/O there/O are/O still/O some/O men/O of/O sense/O in/O this/O city/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O signaled/O for/O the/O meal/O to/O resume/O ./O 
The/O servants/O began/O bringing/O out/O platters/O of/O ribs/O ,/O roasted/O in/O a/O crust/O of/O garlic/O and/O herbs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O talk/O in/O the/O yard/O is/O we/O shall/O have/O a/O tourney/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jory/PERSON said/O as/O he/O resumed/O his/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O say/O that/O knights/O will/O come/O from/O all/O over/O the/O realm/O to/O joust/O and/O feast/O in/O honor/O of/O your/O appointment/O as/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON could/O see/O that/O her/O father/O was/O not/O very/O happy/O about/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O they/O also/O say/O this/O is/O the/O last/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O I/O would/O have/O wished/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O 's/O eyes/O had/O grown/O wide/O as/O the/O plates/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O tourney/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O breathed/O ./O 
She/O was/O seated/O between/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON and/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON ,/O as/O far/O from/O Arya/PERSON as/O she/O could/O get/O without/O drawing/O a/O reproach/O from/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O we/O be/O permitted/O to/O go/O ,/O Father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O know/O my/O feelings/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ./O 
It/O seems/O I/O must/O arrange/O Robert/PERSON 's/O games/O and/O pretend/O to/O be/O honored/O for/O his/O sake/O ./O 
That/O does/O not/O mean/O I/O must/O subject/O my/O daughters/O to/O this/O folly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O please/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/O spoke/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON will/O be/O there/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O and/O her/O younger/O than/O Lady/PERSON Sansa/PERSON ./O 
All/O the/O ladies/O of/O the/O court/O will/O be/O expected/O at/O a/O grand/O event/O like/O this/O ,/O and/O as/O the/O tourney/O is/O in/O your/O honor/O ,/O it/O would/O look/O queer/O if/O your/O family/O did/O not/O attend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Father/O looked/O pained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O so/O ./O 
Very/O well/O ,/O I/O shall/O arrange/O a/O place/O for/O you/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O saw/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O both/O of/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O about/O their/O stupid/O tourney/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
She/O knew/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON would/O be/O there/O ,/O and/O she/O hated/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O lifted/O her/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O a/O splendid/O event/O ./O 
You/O sha/O n't/O be/O wanted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Anger/O flashed/O across/O Father/O 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Enough/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ./O 
More/O of/O that/O and/O you/O will/O change/O my/O mind/O ./O 
I/O am/O weary/O unto/O death/O of/O this/O endless/O war/O you/O two/O are/O fighting/O ./O 
You/O are/O sisters/O ./O 
I/O expect/O you/O to/O behave/O like/O sisters/O ,/O is/O that/O understood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O bit/O her/O lip/O and/O nodded/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON lowered/O her/O face/O to/O stare/O sullenly/O at/O her/O plate/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O tears/O stinging/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O rubbed/O them/O away/O angrily/O ,/O determined/O not/O to/O cry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O only/O sound/O was/O the/O clatter/O of/O knives/O and/O forks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pray/O excuse/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O announced/O to/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O find/O I/O have/O small/O appetite/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O from/O the/O hall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O he/O was/O gone/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON exchanged/O excited/O whispers/O with/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON ./O 
Down/O the/O table/O Jory/PERSON laughed/O at/O a/O joke/O ,/O and/O Hullen/PERSON started/O in/O about/O horseflesh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O warhorse/O ,/O now/O ,/O he/O may/O not/O be/O the/O best/O one/O for/O the/O joust/O ./O 
Not/O the/O same/O thing/O ,/O oh/O ,/O no/O ,/O not/O the/O same/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O men/O had/O heard/O it/O all/O before/O ;/O Desmond/PERSON ,/O Jacks/O ,/O and/O Hullen/PERSON 's/O son/O Harwin/PERSON shouted/O him/O down/O together/O ,/O and/O Porther/PERSON called/O for/O more/O wine/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O one/O talked/O to/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
She/O did/O n't/O care/O ./O 
She/O liked/O it/O that/O way/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O eaten/O her/O meals/O alone/O in/O her/O bedchamber/O if/O they/O let/O her/O ./O 
Sometimes/O they/O did/O ,/O when/O Father/PERSON had/O to/O dine/O with/O the/O king/O or/O some/O lord/O or/O the/O envoys/O from/O this/O place/O or/O that/O place/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O the/O time/O ,/O they/O ate/O in/O his/O solar/O ,/O just/O him/O and/O her/O and/O Sansa/PERSON ./O 
That/O was/O when/O Arya/PERSON missed/O her/O brothers/O most/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O tease/O Bran/O and/O play/O with/O baby/O Rickon/PERSON and/O have/O Robb/PERSON smile/O at/O her/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O Jon/PERSON to/O muss/O up/O her/O hair/O and/O call/O her/O \/O ``/O little/O sister/O \/O ''/O and/O finish/O her/O sentences/O with/O her/O ./O 
But/O all/O of/O them/O were/O gone/O ./O 
She/O had/O no/O one/O left/O but/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON would/O n't/O even/O talk/O to/O her/O unless/O Father/O made/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Back/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O they/O had/O eaten/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION almost/O half/O the/O time/O ./O 
Her/O father/O used/O to/O say/O that/O a/O lord/O needed/O to/O eat/O with/O his/O men/O ,/O if/O he/O hoped/O to/O keep/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Know/O the/O men/O who/O follow/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O heard/O him/O tell/O Robb/PERSON once/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O let/O them/O know/O you/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O ask/O your/O men/O to/O die/O for/O a/O stranger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O At/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O he/O always/O had/O an/O extra/O seat/O set/O at/O his/O own/O table/O ,/O and/O every/O day/O a/O different/O man/O would/O be/O asked/O to/O join/O him/O ./O 
One/O night/O it/O would/O be/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O talk/O would/O be/O coppers/O and/O bread/O stores/O and/O servants/O ./O 
The/O next/O time/O it/O would/O be/O Mikken/PERSON ,/O and/O her/O father/O would/O listen/O to/O him/O go/O on/O about/O armor/O and/O swords/O and/O how/O hot/O a/O forge/O should/O be/O and/O the/O best/O way/O to/O temper/O steel/O ./O 
Another/O day/O it/O might/O be/O Hullen/PERSON with/O his/O endless/O horse/O talk/O ,/O or/O Septon/O Chayle/O from/O the/O library/O ,/O or/O Jory/PERSON ,/O or/O Ser/O Rodrik/O ,/O or/O even/O Old/O Nan/PERSON with/O her/O stories/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON had/O loved/O nothing/O better/O than/O to/O sit/O at/O her/O father/O 's/O table/O and/O listen/O to/O them/O talk/O ./O 
She/O had/O loved/O listening/O to/O the/O men/O on/O the/O benches/O too/O ;/O to/O freeriders/O tough/O as/O leather/O ,/O courtly/O knights/O and/O bold/O young/O squires/O ,/O grizzled/O old/O men-at-arms/O ./O 
She/O used/O to/O throw/O snowballs/O at/O them/O and/O help/O them/O steal/O pies/O from/O the/O kitchen/O ./O 
Their/O wives/O gave/O her/O scones/O and/O she/O invented/O names/O for/O their/O babies/O and/O played/O monsters-and-maidens/O and/O hide-the-treasure/O and/O come-into-my-castle/O with/O their/O children/O ./O 
Fat/O Tom/PERSON used/O to/O call/O her/O \/O ``/O Arya/O Underfoot/O ,/O \/O ''/O because/O he/O said/O that/O was/O where/O she/O always/O was/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O liked/O that/O a/O lot/O better/O than/O \/O ``/O Arya/PERSON Horseface/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Only/O that/O was/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O a/O world/O away/O ,/O and/O now/O everything/O was/O changed/O ./O 
This/O was/O the/O first/O time/O they/O had/O supped/O with/O the/O men/O since/O arriving/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON hated/O it/O ./O 
She/O hated/O the/O sounds/O of/O their/O voices/O now/O ,/O the/O way/O they/O laughed/O ,/O the/O stories/O they/O told/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O been/O her/O friends/O ,/O she/O 'd/O felt/O safe/O around/O them/O ,/O but/O now/O she/O knew/O that/O was/O a/O lie/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O let/O the/O queen/O kill/O Lady/O ,/O that/O was/O horrible/O enough/O ,/O but/O then/O the/O Hound/O found/O Mycah/PERSON ./O 
Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON had/O told/O Arya/PERSON that/O he/O 'd/O cut/O him/O up/O in/O so/O many/O pieces/O that/O they/O 'd/O given/O him/O back/O to/O the/O butcher/O in/O a/O bag/O ,/O and/O at/O first/O the/O poor/O man/O had/O thought/O it/O was/O a/O pig/O they/O 'd/O slaughtered/O ./O 
And/O no/O one/O had/O raised/O a/O voice/O or/O drawn/O a/O blade/O or/O anything/O ,/O not/O Harwin/PERSON who/O always/O talked/O so/O bold/O ,/O or/O Alyn/PERSON who/O was/O going/O to/O be/O a/O knight/O ,/O or/O Jory/PERSON who/O was/O captain/O of/O the/O guard/O ./O 
Not/O even/O her/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O my/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON whispered/O into/O her/O plate/O ,/O so/O low/O that/O no/O one/O could/O hear/O ./O 
Her/O ribs/O sat/O there/O untouched/O ,/O grown/O cold/O now/O ,/O a/O thin/O film/O of/O grease/O congealing/O beneath/O them/O on/O the/O plate/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON looked/O at/O them/O and/O felt/O ill/O ./O 
She/O pushed/O away/O from/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pray/O ,/O where/O do/O you/O think/O you/O are/O going/O ,/O young/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O hungry/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON found/O it/O an/O effort/O to/O remember/O her/O courtesies/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O I/O be/O excused/O ,/O please/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O recited/O stiffly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O may/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O septa/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O scarcely/O touched/O your/O food/O ./O 
You/O will/O sit/O down/O and/O clean/O your/O plate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O clean/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Before/O anyone/O could/O stop/O her/O ,/O Arya/PERSON bolted/O for/O the/O door/O as/O the/O men/O laughed/O and/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON called/O loudly/O after/O her/O ,/O her/O voice/O rising/O higher/O and/O higher/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON was/O at/O his/O post/O ,/O guarding/O the/O door/O to/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ./O 
He/O blinked/O when/O he/O saw/O Arya/PERSON rushing/O toward/O him/O and/O heard/O the/O septa/O 's/O shouts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O now/O ,/O little/O one/O ,/O hold/O on/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O started/O to/O say/O ,/O reaching/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON slid/O between/O his/O legs/O and/O then/O she/O was/O running/O up/O the/O winding/O tower/O steps/O ,/O her/O feet/O hammering/O on/O the/O stone/O while/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON huffed/O and/O puffed/O behind/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O bedchamber/O was/O the/O only/O place/O that/O Arya/PERSON liked/O in/O all/O of/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O and/O the/O thing/O she/O liked/O best/O about/O it/O was/O the/O door/O ,/O a/O massive/O slab/O of/O dark/O oak/O with/O black/O iron/O bands/O ./O 
When/O she/O slammed/O that/O door/O and/O dropped/O the/O heavy/O crossbar/O ,/O nobody/O could/O get/O into/O her/O room/O ,/O not/O Septa/O Mordane/O or/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON or/O Sansa/O or/O Jory/PERSON or/O the/O Hound/O ,/O nobody/O !/O 
She/O slammed/O it/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O bar/O was/O down/O ,/O Arya/PERSON finally/O felt/O safe/O enough/O to/O cry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O went/O to/O the/O window/O seat/O and/O sat/O there/O ,/O sniffling/O ,/O hating/O them/O all/O ,/O and/O herself/O most/O of/O all/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O her/O fault/O ,/O everything/O bad/O that/O had/O happened/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON said/O so/O ,/O and/O Jeyne/PERSON too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON was/O knocking/O on/O her/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON girl/O ,/O what/O 's/O wrong/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O in/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O shouted/O ./O 
The/O knocking/O stopped/O ./O 
A/O moment/O later/O she/O heard/O him/O going/O away/O ./O 
Fat/O Tom/PERSON was/O always/O easy/O to/O fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON went/O to/O the/O chest/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O her/O bed/O ./O 
She/O knelt/O ,/O opened/O the/O lid/O ,/O and/O began/O pulling/O her/O clothes/O out/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O grabbing/O handfuls/O of/O silk/O and/O satin/O and/O velvet/O and/O wool/O and/O tossing/O them/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
It/O was/O there/O at/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O chest/O ,/O where/O she/O 'd/O hidden/O it/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON lifted/O it/O out/O almost/O tenderly/O and/O drew/O the/O slender/O blade/O from/O its/O sheath/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Needle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O thought/O of/O Mycah/O again/O and/O her/O eyes/O filled/O with/O tears/O ./O 
Her/O fault/O ,/O her/O fault/O ,/O her/O fault/O ./O 
If/O she/O had/O never/O asked/O him/O to/O play/O at/O swords/O with/O her/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O pounding/O at/O her/O door/O ,/O louder/O than/O before/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O you/O open/O this/O door/O at/O once/O ,/O do/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON spun/O around/O ,/O with/O Needle/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O better/O not/O come/O in/O here/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O warned/O ./O 
She/O slashed/O at/O the/O air/O savagely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Hand/O will/O hear/O of/O this/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON raged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O rue/O this/O insolent/O behavior/O ,/O young/O lady/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON listened/O at/O the/O door/O until/O she/O heard/O the/O sound/O of/O the/O septa/O 's/O receding/O footsteps/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O went/O back/O to/O the/O window/O ,/O Needle/O in/O hand/O ,/O and/O looked/O down/O into/O the/O courtyard/O below/O ./O 
If/O only/O she/O could/O climb/O like/O Bran/O ,/O she/O thought/O ;/O she/O would/O go/O out/O the/O window/O and/O down/O the/O tower/O ,/O run/O away/O from/O this/O horrible/O place/O ,/O away/O from/O Sansa/LOCATION and/O Septa/ORGANIZATION Mordane/ORGANIZATION and/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ,/O from/O all/O of/O them/O ./O 
Steal/O some/O food/O from/O the/O kitchens/O ,/O take/O Needle/O and/O her/O good/O boots/O and/O a/O warm/O ''/O ,/O ``/O cloak/O ./O 
She/O could/O find/O Nymeria/LOCATION in/O the/O wild/O woods/O below/O the/O Trident/O ,/O and/O together/O they/O 'd/O return/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O or/O run/O to/O Jon/PERSON on/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
She/O found/O herself/O wishing/O that/O Jon/PERSON was/O here/O with/O her/O now/O ./O 
Then/O maybe/O she/O would/O n't/O feel/O so/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O soft/O knock/O at/O the/O door/O behind/O her/O turned/O Arya/PERSON away/O from/O the/O window/O and/O her/O dreams/O of/O escape/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O 's/O voice/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Open/O the/O door/O ./O 
We/O need/O to/O talk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON crossed/O the/O room/O and/O lifted/O the/O crossbar/O ./O 
Father/O was/O alone/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O more/O sad/O than/O angry/O ./O 
That/O made/O Arya/PERSON feel/O even/O worse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O I/O come/O in/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON nodded/O ,/O then/O dropped/O her/O eyes/O ,/O ashamed/O ./O 
Father/O closed/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Whose/O sword/O is/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON had/O almost/O forgotten/O Needle/O ,/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Give/O it/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Reluctantly/O Arya/PERSON surrendered/O her/O sword/O ,/O wondering/O if/O she/O would/O ever/O hold/O it/O again/O ./O 
Her/O father/O turned/O it/O in/O the/O light/O ,/O examining/O both/O sides/O of/O the/O blade/O ./O 
He/O tested/O the/O point/O with/O his/O thumb/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O bravo/O 's/O blade/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O it/O seems/O to/O me/O that/O I/O know/O this/O maker/O 's/O mark/O ./O 
This/O is/O Mikken/PERSON 's/O work/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON could/O not/O lie/O to/O him/O ./O 
She/O lowered/O her/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O nine-year-old/O daughter/O is/O being/O armed/O from/O my/O own/O forge/O ,/O and/O I/O know/O nothing/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O is/O expected/O to/O rule/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O yet/O it/O seems/O I/O can/O not/O even/O rule/O my/O own/O household/O ./O 
How/O is/O it/O that/O you/O come/O to/O own/O a/O sword/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ?/O 
Where/O did/O you/O get/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON chewed/O her/O lip/O and/O said/O nothing/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O betray/O Jon/PERSON ,/O not/O even/O to/O their/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O a/O while/O ,/O Father/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O suppose/O it/O matters/O ,/O truly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O down/O gravely/O at/O the/O sword/O in/O his/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O toy/O for/O children/O ,/O least/O of/O all/O for/O a/O girl/O ./O 
What/O would/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON say/O if/O she/O knew/O you/O were/O playing/O with/O swords/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O n't/O playing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O Septa/O Mordane/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O father/O 's/O voice/O was/O curt/O and/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O septa/O is/O doing/O no/O more/O than/O is/O her/O duty/O ,/O though/O gods/O know/O you/O have/O made/O it/O a/O struggle/O for/O the/O poor/O woman/O ./O 
Your/O mother/O and/O I/O have/O charged/O her/O with/O the/O impossible/O task/O of/O making/O you/O a/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O be/O a/O lady/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON flared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O ought/O to/O snap/O this/O toy/O across/O my/O knee/O here/O and/O now/O ,/O and/O put/O an/O end/O to/O this/O nonsense/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Needle/O would/O n't/O break/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O defiantly/O ,/O but/O her/O voice/O betrayed/O her/O words/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O has/O a/O name/O ,/O does/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O father/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
You/O have/O a/O wildness/O in/O you/O ,/O child/O ./O 
`/O The/O wolf/O blood/O ,/O '/O my/O father/O used/O to/O call/O it/O ./O 
Lyanna/PERSON had/O a/O touch/O of/O it/O ,/O and/O my/O brother/O Brandon/PERSON more/O than/O a/O touch/O ./O 
It/O brought/O them/O both/O to/O an/O early/O grave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON heard/O sadness/O in/O his/O voice/O ;/O he/O did/O not/O often/O speak/O of/O his/O father/O ,/O or/O of/O the/O brother/O and/O sister/O who/O had/O died/O before/O she/O was/O born/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lyanna/PERSON might/O have/O carried/O a/O sword/O ,/O if/O my/O lord/O father/O had/O allowed/O it/O ./O 
You/O remind/O me/O of/O her/O sometimes/O ./O 
You/O even/O look/O like/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lyanna/PERSON was/O beautiful/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ,/O startled/O ./O 
Everybody/O said/O so/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O a/O thing/O that/O was/O ever/O said/O of/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O ,/O \/O ''/O Eddard/O Stark/O agreed/O ,/O \/O ``/O beautiful/O ,/O and/O willful/O ,/O and/O dead/O before/O her/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O lifted/O the/O sword/O ,/O held/O it/O out/O between/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O what/O did/O you/O think/O to/O do/O with/O this/O .../O Needle/O ?/O 
Who/O ''/O ,/O ``/O did/O you/O hope/O to/O skewer/O ?/O 
Your/O sister/O ?/O 
Septa/O Mordane/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O know/O the/O first/O thing/O about/O sword/O fighting/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O All/O she/O could/O think/O of/O was/O the/O lesson/O Jon/PERSON had/O given/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stick/O them/O with/O the/O pointy/O end/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O blurted/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O father/O snorted/O back/O laughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O the/O essence/O of/O it/O ,/O I/O suppose/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON desperately/O wanted/O to/O explain/O ,/O to/O make/O him/O see/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O trying/O to/O learn/O ,/O but/O .../O \/O ''/O Her/O eyes/O filled/O with/O tears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O asked/O Mycah/PERSON to/O practice/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O grief/O came/O on/O her/O all/O at/O once/O ./O 
She/O turned/O away/O ,/O shaking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O asked/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O cried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O my/O fault/O ,/O it/O was/O me/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Suddenly/O her/O father/O 's/O arms/O were/O around/O her/O ./O 
He/O held/O her/O gently/O as/O she/O turned/O to/O him/O and/O sobbed/O against/O his/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O sweet/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Grieve/PERSON for/O your/O friend/O ,/O but/O never/O blame/O yourself/O ./O 
You/O did/O not/O kill/O the/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ./O 
That/O murder/O lies/O at/O the/O Hound/O 's/O door/O ,/O him/O and/O the/O cruel/O woman/O he/O serves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hate/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON confided/O ,/O red/O -/O faced/O ,/O sniffling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Hound/O and/O the/O queen/O and/O the/O king/O and/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
I/O hate/O all/O of/O them/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON lied/O ,/O it/O was/O n't/O the/O way/O he/O said/O ./O 
I/O hate/O Sansa/O too/O ./O 
She/O did/O remember/O ,/O she/O just/O lied/O so/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O like/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O all/O lie/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Or/O did/O you/O truly/O think/O I/O 'd/O believe/O that/O Nymeria/PERSON ran/O off/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON blushed/O guiltily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jory/PERSON promised/O not/O to/O tell/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jory/PERSON kept/O his/O word/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O said/O with/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O are/O some/O things/O I/O do/O not/O need/O to/O be/O told/O ./O 
Even/O a/O blind/O man/O could/O see/O that/O wolf/O would/O never/O have/O left/O you/O willingly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O had/O to/O throw/O rocks/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O miserably/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O told/O her/O to/O run/O ,/O to/O go/O be/O free/O ,/O that/O I/O did/O n't/O want/O her/O anymore/O ./O 
There/O were/O other/O wolves/O for/O her/O to/O play/O with/O ,/O we/O heard/O them/O howling/O ,/O and/O Jory/PERSON said/O the/O woods/O were/O full/O of/O game/O ,/O so/O she/O 'd/O have/O deer/O to/O hunt/O ./O 
Only/O she/O kept/O following/O ,/O and/O finally/O we/O had/O to/O throw/O rocks/O ./O 
I/O hit/O her/O twice/O ./O 
She/O whined/O and/O looked/O at/O me/O and/O I/O felt/O so/O `/O shamed/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O right/O ,/O was/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
The/O queen/O would/O have/O killed/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O right/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O even/O the/O lie/O was/O .../O not/O without/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O 'd/O put/O Needle/O aside/O when/O he/O went/O to/O Arya/PERSON to/O embrace/O her/O ./O 
Now/O he/O took/O the/O blade/O up/O again/O and/O walked/O to/O the/O window/O ,/O where/O he/O stood/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O looking/O out/O across/O the/O courtyard/O ./O 
When/O he/O turned/O back/O ,/O his/O eyes/O were/O thoughtful/O ./O 
He/O seated/O himself/O on/O the/O window/O seat/O ,/O Needle/O across/O his/O lap/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O sit/O down/O ./O 
I/O need/O to/O try/O and/O explain/O some/O things/O to/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O perched/O anxiously/O on/O the/O edge/O of/O her/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O too/O young/O to/O be/O burdened/O with/O all/O my/O cares/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O you/O are/O also/O a/O Stark/O of/O Winterfell/O ./O 
You/O know/O our/O words/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Winter/O is/O coming/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O hard/O cruel/O times/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O tasted/O them/O on/O the/O Trident/O ,/O child/O ,/O and/O when/O Bran/O fell/O ./O 
You/O were/O born/O in/O the/O long/O summer/O ,/O sweet/O one/O ,/O you/O 've/O never/O known/O anything/O else/O ,/O but/O now/O the/O winter/O is/O truly/O coming/O ./O 
Remember/O the/O sigil/O of/O our/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O direwolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O thinking/O of/O Nymeria/LOCATION ./O 
She/O hugged/O her/O knees/O against/O her/O chest/O ,/O suddenly/O afraid/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O me/O tell/O you/O something/O about/O wolves/O ,/O child/O ./O 
When/O the/O snows/O fall/O and/O the/O white/O winds/O blow/O ,/O the/O lone/O wolf/O dies/O ,/O but/O the/O pack/O survives/O ./O 
Summer/O is/O the/O time/O for/O squabbles/O ./O 
In/O winter/O ,/O we/O must/O protect/O one/O another/O ,/O keep/O each/O other/O warm/O ,/O share/O our/O strengths/O ./O 
So/O if/O you/O must/O hate/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ,/O hate/O ''/O ,/O ``/O those/O who/O would/O truly/O do/O us/O harm/O ./O 
Septa/O Mordane/O is/O a/O good/O woman/O ,/O and/O Sansa/O .../O Sansa/O is/O your/O sister/O ./O 
You/O may/O be/O as/O different/O as/O the/O sun/O and/O the/O moon/O ,/O but/O the/O same/O blood/O flows/O through/O both/O your/O hearts/O ./O 
You/O need/O her/O ,/O as/O she/O needs/O you/O .../O and/O I/O need/O both/O of/O you/O ,/O gods/O help/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O sounded/O so/O tired/O that/O it/O made/O Arya/PERSON sad/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O hate/O Sansa/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O truly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O only/O half/O a/O lie/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O mean/O to/O frighten/O you/O ,/O but/O neither/O will/O I/O lie/O to/O you/O ./O 
We/O have/O come/O to/O a/O dark/O dangerous/O place/O ,/O child/O ./O 
This/O is/O not/O Winterfell/O ./O 
We/O have/O enemies/O who/O mean/O us/O ill/O ./O 
We/O can/O not/O fight/O a/O war/O among/O ourselves/O ./O 
This/O willfulness/O of/O yours/O ,/O the/O running/O off/O ,/O the/O angry/O words/O ,/O the/O disobedience/O .../O at/O home/O ,/O these/O were/O only/O the/O summer/O games/O of/O a/O child/O ./O 
Here/O and/O now/O ,/O with/O winter/O soon/O upon/O us/O ,/O that/O is/O a/O different/O matter/O ./O 
It/O is/O time/O to/O begin/O growing/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON vowed/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O loved/O him/O so/O much/O as/O she/O did/O in/O that/O instant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O be/O strong/O too/O ./O 
I/O can/O be/O as/O strong/O as/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O held/O Needle/O out/O to/O her/O ,/O hilt/O first/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O looked/O at/O the/O sword/O with/O wonder/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O she/O was/O afraid/O to/O touch/O it/O ,/O afraid/O that/O if/O she/O reached/O for/O it/O it/O would/O be/O snatched/O away/O again/O ,/O but/O then/O her/O father/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Go/O on/O ,/O it/O 's/O yours/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O she/O took/O it/O in/O her/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O keep/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O true/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O true/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O took/O it/O away/O ,/O no/O doubt/O I/O 'd/O find/O a/O morningstar/O hidden/O under/O your/O pillow/O within/O the/O fortnight/O ./O 
Try/O not/O to/O stab/O your/O sister/O ,/O whatever/O the/O provocation/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O ./O 
I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON clutched/O Needle/O tightly/O to/O her/O chest/O as/O her/O father/O took/O his/O leave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O next/O morning/O ,/O as/O they/O broke/O their/O fast/O ,/O she/O apologized/O to/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON and/O asked/O for/O her/O pardon/O ./O 
The/O septa/O peered/O at/O her/O suspiciously/O ,/O but/O Father/O nodded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Three/O days/O later/O ,/O at/O midday/O ,/O her/O father/O 's/O steward/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON sent/O Arya/PERSON to/O the/O Small/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
The/O trestle/O tables/O had/O been/O dismantled/O and/O the/O benches/O shoved/O against/O the/O walls/O ./O 
The/O hall/O seemed/O empty/O ,/O until/O an/O unfamiliar/O voice/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O late/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O slight/O man/O with/O a/O bald/O head/O and/O a/O great/O beak/O of/O a/O nose/O stepped/O out/O of/O the/O shadows/O ,/O holding/O a/O pair/O of/O slender/O wooden/O swords/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tomorrow/O you/O will/O be/O here/O at/O midday/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O an/O accent/O ,/O the/O lilt/O of/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O Braavos/PERSON perhaps/O ,/O or/O Myr/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O your/O dancing/O master/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O tossed/O her/O one/O of/O the/O wooden/O blades/O ./O 
She/O grabbed/O for/O it/O ,/O missed/O ,/O and/O heard/O it/O clatter/O to/O the/O floor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tomorrow/O you/O will/O catch/O it/O ./O 
Now/O pick/O it/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O just/O a/O stick/O ,/O but/O a/O true/O wooden/O sword/O complete/O with/O grip/O and/O guard/O and/O pommel/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON picked/O it/O up/O and/O clutched/O it/O nervously/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O holding/O it/O out/O in/O front/O of/O her/O ./O 
It/O was/O heavier/O than/O it/O looked/O ,/O much/O heavier/O than/O Needle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O bald/O man/O clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O not/O the/O way/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
This/O is/O not/O a/O greatsword/O that/O is/O needing/O two/O hands/O to/O swing/O it/O ./O 
You/O will/O take/O the/O blade/O in/O one/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O too/O heavy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O heavy/O as/O it/O needs/O to/O be/O to/O make/O you/O strong/O ,/O and/O for/O the/O balancing/O ./O 
A/O hollow/O inside/O is/O filled/O with/O lead/O ,/O just/O so/O ./O 
One/O hand/O now/O is/O all/O that/O is/O needing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON took/O her/O right/O hand/O off/O the/O grip/O and/O wiped/O her/O sweaty/O palm/O on/O her/O pants/O ./O 
She/O held/O the/O sword/O in/O her/O left/O hand/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O approve/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O left/O is/O good/O ./O 
All/O is/O reversed/O ,/O it/O will/O make/O your/O enemies/O more/O awkward/O ./O 
Now/O you/O are/O standing/O wrong/O ./O 
Turn/O your/O body/O sideface/O ,/O yes/O ,/O so/O ./O 
You/O are/O skinny/O as/O the/O shaft/O of/O a/O spear/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O ./O 
That/O is/O good/O too/O ,/O the/O target/O is/O smaller/O ./O 
Now/O the/O grip/O ./O 
Let/O me/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O moved/O closer/O and/O peered/O at/O her/O hand/O ,/O prying/O her/O fingers/O apart/O ,/O rearranging/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O so/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
Do/O not/O squeeze/O it/O so/O tight/O ,/O no/O ,/O the/O grip/O must/O be/O deft/O ,/O delicate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O if/O I/O drop/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O steel/O must/O be/O part/O of/O your/O arm/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O bald/O man/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O you/O drop/O part/O of/O your/O arm/O ?/O 
No/O ./O 
Nine/O years/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON was/O first/O sword/O to/O the/O Sealord/O of/O Braavos/LOCATION ,/O he/O knows/O these/O things/O ./O 
Listen/O to/O him/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O third/O time/O he/O had/O called/O her/O \/O ``/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O a/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON objected/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Boy/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O sword/O ,/O that/O is/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O so/O ,/O that/O is/O the/O grip/O ./O 
You/O are/O not/O holding/O a/O battle-axe/O ,/O you/O are/O holding/O a/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O --/O needle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON finished/O for/O him/O ,/O fiercely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O so/O ./O 
Now/O we/O will/O begin/O the/O dance/O ./O 
Remember/O ,/O child/O ,/O this/O is/O not/O the/O iron/O dance/O of/O Westeros/LOCATION we/O are/O learning/O ,/O the/O knight/O 's/O dance/O ,/O hacking/O and/O hammering/O ,/O no/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O bravo/O 's/O dance/O ,/O the/O water/O dance/O ,/O swift/O and/O sudden/O ./O 
All/O men/O are/O made/O of/O water/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O this/O ?/O 
When/O you/O pierce/O them/O ,/O the/O water/O leaks/O out/O and/O they/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O a/O step/O backward/O ,/O raised/O his/O own/O wooden/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O you/O will/O try/O to/O strike/O me/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON tried/O to/O strike/O him/O ./O 
She/O tried/O for/O four/O hours/O ,/O until/O every/O muscle/O in/O her/O body/O was/O sore/O and/O aching/O ,/O while/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON clicked/O his/O teeth/O together/O and/O told/O her/O what/O to/O do/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O next/O day/O their/O real/O work/O began/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
