-LSB-/O ``/O BRAN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O oldest/O were/O men/O grown/O ,/O seventeen/O and/O eighteen/O years/O from/O the/O day/O of/O their/O naming/O ./O 
One/O was/O past/O twenty/O ./O 
Most/O were/O younger/O ,/O sixteen/O or/O less/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O watched/O them/O from/O the/O balcony/O of/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON 's/O turret/O ,/O listening/O to/O them/O grunt/O and/O strain/O and/O curse/O as/O they/O swung/O their/O staves/O and/O wooden/O swords/O ./O 
The/O yard/O was/O alive/O to/O the/O clack/O of/O wood/O on/O wood/O ,/O punctuated/O all/O too/O often/O by/O thwacks/O and/O yowls/O of/O pain/O when/O a/O blow/O struck/O leather/O or/O flesh/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON strode/O among/O the/O boys/O ,/O face/O reddening/O beneath/O his/O white/O whiskers/O ,/O muttering/O at/O them/O one/O and/O all/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O never/O seen/O the/O old/O knight/O look/O so/O fierce/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O kept/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ./O 
No/O ./O 
No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O do/O n't/O fight/O very/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O dubiously/O ./O 
He/O scratched/O Summer/O idly/O behind/O the/O ears/O as/O the/O direwolf/O tore/O at/O a/O haunch/O of/O meat/O ./O 
Bones/O crunched/O between/O his/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O a/O certainty/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON agreed/O with/O a/O deep/O sigh/O ./O 
The/O maester/O was/O peering/O through/O his/O big/O Myrish/O lens/O tube/O ,/O measuring/O shadows/O and/O noting/O the/O position/O of/O the/O comet/O that/O hung/O low/O in/O the/O morning/O sky/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O given/O time/O .../O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON has/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ,/O we/O need/O men/O to/O walk/O the/O walls/O ./O 
Your/O lord/O father/O took/O the/O cream/O of/O his/O guard/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O and/O your/O brother/O took/O the/O rest/O ,/O along/O with/O all/O the/O likely/O lads/O for/O leagues/O around/O ./O 
Many/O will/O not/O come/O back/O to/O us/O ,/O and/O we/O must/O needs/O find/O the/O men/O to/O take/O their/O places/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O stared/O resentfully/O at/O the/O sweating/O boys/O below/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O still/O had/O my/O legs/O ,/O I/O could/O beat/O them/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O remembered/O the/O last/O time/O he/O 'd/O held/O a/O sword/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O when/O the/O king/O had/O come/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
It/O was/O only/O a/O wooden/O sword/O ,/O yet/O he/O 'd/O knocked/O Prince/PERSON Tommen/PERSON down/O half/O a/O hundred/O times/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Rodrik/O should/O teach/O me/O to/O use/O a/O poleaxe/O ./O 
If/O I/O had/O a/O poleaxe/O with/O a/O big/O long/O haft/O ,/O Hodor/PERSON could/O be/O my/O legs/O ./O 
We/O could/O be/O a/O knight/O together/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O think/O that/O .../O unlikely/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O when/O a/O man/O fights/O ,/O his/O arms/O and/O legs/O and/O thoughts/O must/O be/O as/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Below/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON was/O yelling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O fight/O like/O a/O goose/O ./O 
He/O pecks/O you/O and/O you/O peck/O him/O harder/O ./O 
Pany/O !/O 
Block/O the/O blow/O ./O 
Goose/O fighting/O will/O not/O suffice/O ./O 
If/O those/O were/O real/O swords/O ,/O the/O first/O peck/O would/O take/O your/O arm/O off/O !/O 
\/O ''/O One/O of/O the/O other/O boys/O laughed/O ,/O and/O the/O old/O knight/O rounded/O on/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O laugh/O ./O 
You/O ./O 
Now/O that/O is/O gall/O ./O 
You/O fight/O like/O a/O hedgehog/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O knight/O once/O who/O could/O n't/O see/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O stubbornly/O ,/O as/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON went/O on/O below/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Old/O Nan/PERSON told/O me/O about/O him/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O long/O staff/O with/O blades/O at/O both/O ends/O and/O he/O could/O spin/O it/O in/O his/O hands/O and/O chop/O two/O men/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Symeon/O Star-Eyes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON said/O as/O he/O marked/O numbers/O in/O a/O book/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O he/O lost/O his/O eyes/O ,/O he/O put/O star/O sapphires/O in/O the/O empty/O sockets/O ,/O or/O so/O the/O singers/O claim/O ./O 
Bran/O ,/O that/O is/O only/O a/O story/O ,/O like/O the/O tales/O of/O Florian/O the/O Fool/O ./O 
A/O fable/O from/O the/O Age/O of/O Heroes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O maester/O tsked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O put/O these/O dreams/O aside/O ,/O they/O will/O only/O break/O your/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O mention/O of/O dreams/O reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O dreamed/O about/O the/O crow/O again/O last/O night/O ./O 
The/O one/O with/O three/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O flew/O into/O my/O bedchamber/O and/O told/O me/O to/O come/O with/O him/O ,/O so/O I/O did/O ./O 
We/O went/O down/O to/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
Father/O was/O there/O ,/O and/O we/O talked/O ./O 
He/O was/O sad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O why/O was/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON peered/O through/O his/O tube/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O something/O to/O do/O about/O Jon/PERSON ,/O I/O think/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O dream/O had/O been/O deeply/O disturbing/O ,/O more/O so/O than/O any/O of/O the/O other/O crow/O dreams/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O wo/O n't/O go/O down/O into/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O maester/O had/O only/O been/O half/O listening/O ,/O Bran/O could/O tell/O ./O 
He/O lifted/O his/O eye/O from/O the/O tube/O ,/O blinking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O wo/O n't/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O down/O into/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
When/O I/O woke/O ,/O I/O told/O him/O to/O take/O me/O down/O ,/O to/O see/O if/O Father/O was/O truly/O there/O ./O 
At/O first/O he/O did/O n't/O know/O what/O I/O was/O saying/O ,/O but/O I/O got/O him/O to/O the/O steps/O by/O telling/O him/O to/O go/O here/O and/O go/O there/O ,/O only/O then/O he/O would/O n't/O go/O down/O ./O 
He/O just/O stood/O on/O the/O top/O step/O and/O said/O `/O Hodor/PERSON ,/O '/O like/O he/O was/O scared/O of/O the/O dark/O ,/O but/O I/O had/O a/O torch/O ./O 
It/O made/O me/O so/O mad/O I/O almost/O gave/O him/O a/O swat/O in/O the/O head/O ,/O like/O Old/O Nan/PERSON is/O always/O doing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O saw/O the/O way/O the/O maester/O was/O frowning/O and/O hurriedly/O added/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ./O 
Hodor/O is/O a/O man/O ,/O not/O a/O mule/O to/O be/O beaten/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O dream/O I/O flew/O down/O with/O the/O crow/O ,/O but/O I/O ca/O n't/O do/O that/O when/O I/O 'm/O awake/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O explained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O you/O want/O to/O go/O down/O to/O the/O crypts/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O told/O you/O ./O 
To/O look/O for/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O maester/O tugged/O at/O the/O chain/O around/O his/O neck/O ,/O as/O he/O often/O did/O when/O he/O was/O uncomfortable/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O sweet/O child/O ,/O one/O day/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON will/O sit/O below/O in/O stone/O ,/O beside/O his/O father/O and/O his/O father/O 's/O father/O and/O all/O the/O Starks/PERSON back/O to/O the/O old/O Kings/O in/O the/O North/O .../O but/O that/O will/O not/O be/O for/O many/O years/O ,/O gods/O be/O good/O ./O 
Your/O father/O is/O a/O prisoner/O of/O the/O queen/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
You/O will/O not/O find/O him/O in/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O there/O last/O night/O ./O 
I/O talked/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stubborn/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O sighed/O ,/O setting/O his/O book/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O you/O like/O to/O go/O see/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O ./O 
Hodor/O wo/O n't/O go/O ,/O and/O the/O steps/O are/O too/O narrow/O and/O twisty/O for/O Dancer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O believe/O I/O can/O solve/O that/O difficulty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O In/O place/O of/O Hodor/LOCATION ,/O the/O wildling/O woman/O Osha/ORGANIZATION was/O summoned/O ./O 
She/O was/O tall/O and/O tough/O and/O uncomplaining/O ,/O willing/O to/O go/O wherever/O she/O was/O commanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O lived/O my/O life/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O a/O hole/O in/O the/O ground/O wo/O n't/O fret/O me/O none/O ,/O m/O `/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Summer/O ,/O come/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O called/O as/O she/O lifted/O him/O in/O wiry-strong/O arms/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O left/O his/O bone/O and/O followed/O as/O Osha/O carried/O Bran/O across/O the/O yard/O and/O down/O the/O spiral/O steps/O to/O the/O cold/O vault/O under/O the/O earth/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON went/O ahead/O with/O a/O torch/O ./O 
Bran/O did/O not/O even/O mind-too/O badly-that/O she/O carried/O him/O in/O her/O arms/O and/O not/O on/O her/O back/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON had/O ordered/O Osha/ORGANIZATION 's/O chain/O struck/O off/O ,/O since/O she/O had/O served/O faithfully/O and/O well/O since/O she/O had/O been/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
She/O still/O wore/O the/O heavy/O iron/O shackles/O around/O her/O ankles-a/O sign/O that/O she/O was/O not/O yet/O wholly/O trusted-but/O they/O did/O not/O hinder/O her/O sure/O strides/O down/O the/O steps/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O could/O not/O recall/O the/O last/O time/O he/O had/O been/O in/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O before/O ,/O for/O certain/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O little/O ,/O he/O used/O to/O play/O down/O here/O with/O Robb/PERSON and/O Jon/PERSON and/O his/O sisters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wished/O they/O were/O here/O now/O ;/O the/O vault/O might/O not/O have/O seemed/O so/O dark/O and/O scary/O ./O 
Summer/O stalked/O out/O in/O the/O echoing/O gloom/O ,/O then/O stopped/O ,/O lifted/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O sniffed/O the/O chill/O dead/O air/O ./O 
He/O bared/O his/O teeth/O and/O crept/O backward/O ,/O eyes/O glowing/O golden/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O maester/O 's/O torch/O ./O 
Even/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O hard/O as/O old/O iron/O ,/O seemed/O uncomfortable/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Grim/O folk/O ,/O by/O the/O look/O of/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O as/O she/O eyed/O the/O long/O row/O of/O granite/O Starks/PERSON on/O their/O stone/O thrones/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O were/O the/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O whispered/O ./O 
Somehow/O it/O felt/O wrong/O to/O talk/O too/O loudly/O in/O this/O place/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Winter/O 's/O got/O no/O king/O ./O 
If/O you/O 'd/O seen/O it/O ,/O you/O 'd/O know/O that/O ,/O summer/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O were/O the/O Kings/O in/O the/O North/O for/O thousands/O of/O years/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ,/O lifting/O the/O torch/O high/O so/O the/O light/O shone/O on/O the/O stone/O faces/O ./O 
Some/O were/O hairy/O and/O bearded/O ,/O shaggy/O men/O fierce/O as/O the/O wolves/O that/O crouched/O by/O their/O feet/O ./O 
Others/O were/O shaved/O clean/O ,/O their/O features/O gaunt/O and/O sharp-edged/O as/O the/O iron/O longswords/O across/O their/O laps/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hard/O men/O for/O a/O hard/O time/O ./O 
Come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O strode/O briskly/O down/O the/O vault/O ,/O past/O the/O procession/O of/O stone/O pillars/O and/O the/O endless/O carved/O figures/O ./O 
A/O tongue/O of/O flame/O trailed/O back/O from/O the/O upraised/O torch/O as/O he/O went/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O vault/O was/O cavernous/O ,/O longer/O than/O Winterfell/O itself/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON had/O told/O him/O once/O that/O there/O were/O other/O levels/O underneath/O ,/O vaults/O even/O deeper/O and/O darker/O where/O the/O older/O kings/O were/O buried/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O do/O to/O lose/O the/O light/O ./O 
Summer/O refused/O to/O move/O from/O the/O steps/O ,/O even/O when/O Osha/ORGANIZATION followed/O the/O torch/O ,/O Bran/O in/O her/O arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O recall/O your/O history/O ,/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O as/O they/O walked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O Osha/O who/O they/O were/O and/O what/O they/O did/O ,/O if/O you/O can/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O looked/O at/O the/O passing/O faces/O and/O the/O tales/O came/O back/O to/O him/O ./O 
The/O maester/O had/O told/O him/O the/O stories/O ,/O and/O Old/O Nan/PERSON had/O made/O them/O come/O alive/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O one/O is/O Jon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
When/O the/O sea/O raiders/O landed/O in/O the/O east/O ,/O he/O drove/O them/O out/O and/O built/O the/O castle/O at/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ./O 
His/O son/O was/O Rickard/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O not/O my/O father/O 's/O father/O but/O another/O Rickard/PERSON ,/O he/O took/O the/O Neck/O away/O from/O the/O Marsh/O King/O and/O married/O his/O daughter/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O the/O real/O thin/O one/O with/O the/O long/O hair/O and/O the/O skinny/O beard/O ./O 
They/O called/O him/O the/O `/O Hungry/O Wolf/PERSON ,/O '/O because/O he/O was/O always/O at/O war/O ./O 
That/O 's/O a/O Brandon/PERSON ,/O the/O tall/O one/O with/O the/O dreamy/O face/O ,/O he/O was/O Brandon/PERSON the/PERSON Shipwright/PERSON ,/O because/O he/O loved/O the/O sea/O ./O 
His/O tomb/O is/O empty/O ./O 
He/O tried/O to/O sail/O west/O across/O the/O Sunset/LOCATION Sea/LOCATION and/O was/O never/O seen/O again/O ./O 
His/O son/O was/O Brandon/PERSON the/PERSON Burner/PERSON ,/O because/O he/O put/O the/O torch/O to/O all/O his/O father/O 's/O ships/O in/O grief/O ./O 
There/O 's/O Rodrik/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O who/O won/O Bear/O Island/O in/O a/O wrestling/O match/O and/O gave/O it/O to/O the/O Mormonts/O ./O 
And/O that/O 's/O Torrhen/O Stark/O ,/O the/O King/O Who/O Knelt/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O last/O King/O in/O the/O North/O and/O the/O first/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O after/O he/O yielded/O to/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O there/O ,/O he/O 's/O Cregan/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
He/O fought/O with/O Prince/PERSON Aemon/PERSON once/O ,/O and/O the/O Dragonknight/PERSON said/O he/O 'd/O never/O faced/O a/O finer/O swordsman/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O were/O almost/O at/O the/O end/O now/O ,/O and/O Bran/ORGANIZATION felt/O a/O sadness/O creeping/O over/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O there/O 's/O my/O grandfather/O ,/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O beheaded/O by/O Mad/O King/O Aerys/O ./O 
His/O daughter/O Lyanna/PERSON and/O his/O son/O Brandon/PERSON are/O in/O the/O tombs/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Not/O me/O ,/O another/O Brandon/PERSON ,/O my/O father/O 's/O brother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O 're/O not/O supposed/O to/O have/O statues/O ,/O that/O 's/O only/O for/O the/O lords/O and/O the/O kings/O ,/O but/O my/O father/O loved/O them/O so/O much/O he/O had/O them/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O maid/O 's/O a/O fair/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON was/O betrothed/O to/O marry/O her/O ,/O but/O Prince/PERSON Rhaegar/PERSON carried/O her/O off/O and/O raped/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O explained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON fought/O a/O war/O to/O win/O her/O back/O ./O 
He/O killed/O Rhaegar/PERSON on/O the/O Trident/O with/O his/O hammer/O ,/O but/O Lyanna/PERSON died/O and/O he/O never/O got/O her/O back/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O sad/O tale/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ``/O but/O those/O empty/O holes/O are/O sadder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O tomb/O ,/O for/O when/O his/O time/O comes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O where/O you/O saw/O your/O father/O in/O your/O dream/O ,/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O memory/O made/O him/O shiver/O ./O 
He/O looked/O around/O the/O vault/O uneasily/O ,/O the/O hairs/O on/O the/O back/O of/O his/O neck/O bristling/O ./O 
Had/O he/O heard/O a/O noise/O ?/O 
Was/O there/O someone/O here/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON stepped/O toward/O the/O open/O sepulchre/O ,/O torch/O in/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O see/O ,/O he/O 's/O not/O here/O ./O 
Nor/O will/O he/O be/O ,/O for/O many/O a/O year/O ./O 
Dreams/O are/O only/O dreams/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O thrust/O his/O arm/O into/O the/O blackness/O inside/O the/O tomb/O ,/O as/O into/O the/O mouth/O of/O some/O great/O beast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O see/O ?/O 
It/O 's/O quite/O empt/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O darkness/O sprang/O at/O him/O ,/O snarling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O saw/O eyes/O like/O green/O fire/O ,/O a/O flash/O of/O teeth/O ,/O fur/O as/O black/O as/O the/O pit/O around/O them/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON yelled/O and/O threw/O up/O his/O hands/O ./O 
The/O torch/O went/O flying/O from/O his/O fingers/O ,/O caromed/O off/O the/O stone/O face/O of/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O and/O tumbled/O to/O the/O statue/O 's/O feet/O ,/O the/O flames/O licking/O up/O his/O legs/O ./O 
In/O the/O drunken/O shifting/O torchlight/O ,/O they/O saw/O Luwin/PERSON struggling/O with/O the/O direwolf/O ,/O beating/O at/O his/O muzzle/O with/O one/O hand/O while/O the/O jaws/O closed/O on/O the/O other/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Summer/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O screamed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O Summer/O came/O ,/O shooting/O from/O the/O dimness/O behind/O them/O ,/O a/O leaping/O shadow/O ./O 
He/O slammed/O into/O Shaggydog/PERSON and/O knocked/O him/O back/O ,/O and/O the/O two/O direwolves/O rolled/O over/O and/O over/O in/O a/O tangle/O of/O grey/O and/O black/O fur/O ,/O snapping/O and/O biting/O at/O each/O other/O ,/O while/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON struggled/O to/O his/O knees/O ,/O his/O arm/O torn/O and/O bloody/O ./O 
Osha/ORGANIZATION propped/O Bran/O up/O against/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON 's/O stone/O wolf/O as/O she/O hurried/O to/O assist/O the/O maester/O ./O 
In/O the/O light/O of/O the/O guttering/O torch/O ,/O shadow/O wolves/O twenty/O feet/O tall/O fought/O on/O the/O wall/O and/O roof/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shaggy/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O small/O voice/O called/O ./O 
When/O Bran/O looked/O up/O ,/O his/O little/O brother/O was/O standing/O in/O the/O mouth/O of/O Father/O 's/O tomb/O ./O 
With/O one/O final/O snap/O at/O Summer/O 's/O face/O ,/O Shaggydog/PERSON broke/O off/O and/O bounded/O to/O Rickon/PERSON 's/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O let/O my/O father/O be/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rickon/PERSON warned/O Luwin/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O let/O him/O be/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O 's/O not/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O he/O is/O ./O 
I/O saw/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tears/O glistened/O on/O Rickon/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O saw/O him/O last/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O your/O dream/O .../O ?/O '/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O leave/O him/O ./O 
You/O leave/O him/O be/O ./O 
He/O 's/O coming/O home/O now/O ,/O like/O he/O promised/O ./O 
He/O 's/O coming/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O had/O never/O seen/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON took/O so/O uncertain/O before/O ./O 
Blood/O dripped/O down/O his/O arm/O where/O Shaggydog/PERSON had/O shredded/O the/O wool/O of/O his/O sleeve/O and/O the/O flesh/O beneath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O torch/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O biting/O through/O his/O pain/O ,/O and/O she/O snatched/O it/O up/O before/O it/O went/O out/O ./O 
Soot/O stains/O blackened/O both/O legs/O of/O his/O uncle/O 's/O likeness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O .../O that/O beast/O ,/O \/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON went/O on/O ,/O \/O ``/O is/O supposed/O to/O be/O chained/O up/O in/O the/O kennels/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON patted/O Shaggydog/PERSON 's/O muzzle/O ,/O damp/O with/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O let/O him/O loose/O ./O 
He/O does/O n't/O like/O chains/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O licked/O at/O his/O fingers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O would/O you/O like/O to/O come/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
I/O like/O it/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O dark/O here/O ./O 
And/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O afraid/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O wait/O for/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O can/O wait/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 'll/O wait/O together/O ,/O you/O and/O me/O and/O our/O wolves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Both/O of/O the/O direwolves/O were/O licking/O wounds/O now/O ,/O and/O would/O bear/O close/O watching/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O firmly/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O you/O mean/O well/O ,/O but/O Shaggydog/PERSON is/O too/O wild/O to/O run/O loose/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O the/O third/O man/O he/O 's/O savaged/O ./O 
Give/O him/O the/O freedom/O of/O the/O castle/O and/O it/O 's/O only/O a/O question/O of/O time/O before/O he/O kills/O someone/O ./O 
The/O truth/O is/O hard/O ,/O but/O the/O wolf/O has/O to/O be/O chained/O ,/O or/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O hesitated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O .../O or/O killed/O ,/O Bran/O thought/O ,/O but/O what/O he/O said/O was/O ,/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O not/O made/O for/O chains/O ./O 
We/O will/O wait/O in/O your/O tower/O ,/O all/O of/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O quite/O impossible/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O 's/O the/O lordling/O here/O ,/O as/O I/O recall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O handed/O Luwin/PERSON back/O his/O torch/O and/O scooped/O Bran/O up/O into/O her/O arms/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O maester/O 's/O tower/O it/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O you/O come/O ,/O Rickon/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O brother/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Shaggy/O comes/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O running/O after/O Osha/ORGANIZATION and/O Bran/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O nothing/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON could/O do/O but/O follow/O ,/O keeping/O a/O wary/O eye/O on/O the/O wolves/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON '/O s/O turret/O was/O so/O cluttered/O that/O it/O seemed/O to/O Bran/O a/O wonder/O that/O he/O ever/O found/O anything/O ./O 
Tottering/O piles/O of/O books/O covered/O tables/O and/O chairs/O ,/O rows/O of/O stoppered/O jars/O lined/O the/O shelves/O ,/O candle/O stubs/O and/O puddles/O of/O dried/O wax/O dotted/O the/O furniture/O ,/O the/O bronze/O Myrish/O lens/O tube/O sat/O on/O a/O tripod/O by/O the/O terrace/O door/O ,/O star/O charts/O hung/O from/O the/O walls/O ,/O shadow/O maps/O lay/O scattered/O among/O the/O rushes/O ,/O papers/O ,/O quills/O ,/O and/O pots/O of/O inks/O were/O everywhere/O ,/O and/O all/O of/O it/O was/O spotted/O with/O droppings/O from/O the/O ravens/O in/O the/O rafters/O ./O 
Their/O strident/O quorks/O drifted/O down/O from/O above/O as/O Osha/ORGANIZATION washed/O and/O cleaned/O and/O bandaged/O the/O maester/O 's/O wounds/O ,/O under/O Luwin/PERSON 's/O terse/O instruction/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O folly/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O small/O grey/O man/O said/O while/O she/O dabbed/O at/O the/O wolf/O bites/O with/O a/O stinging/O ointment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O agree/O that/O it/O is/O odd/O that/O both/O you/O boys/O dreamed/O the/O same/O dream/O ,/O yet/O when/O you/O stop/O to/O consider/O it/O ,/O it/O 's/O only/O natural/O ./O 
You/O miss/O your/O lord/O father/O ,/O and/O you/O know/O that/O he/O is/O a/O captive/O ./O 
Fear/O can/O fever/O a/O man/O 's/O mind/O and/O give/O him/O queer/O thoughts/O ./O 
Rickon/PERSON is/O too/O young/O to/O comprehend/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O four/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rickon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O was/O peeking/O through/O the/O lens/O tube/O at/O the/O gargoyles/O on/O the/O First/O Keep/O ./O 
The/O direwolves/O sat/O on/O opposite/O sides/O of/O the/O large/O round/O room/O ,/O licking/O their/O wounds/O and/O gnawing/O on/O bones/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O too/O young/O ,/O and-ooh/O ,/O seven/O hells/O ,/O that/O burns/O ,/O no/O ,/O do/O n't/O stop/O ,/O more/O ./O 
Too/O young/O ,/O as/O I/O say/O ,/O but/O you/O ,/O Bran/PERSON ,/O you/O 're/O old/O enough/O to/O know/O that/O dreams/O are/O only/O dreams/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O are/O ,/O some/O are/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION poured/O pale/O red/O firemilk/O into/O a/O long/O gash/O ./O 
Luwin/PERSON gasped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O could/O tell/O you/O a/O thing/O or/O two/O about/O dreaming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tears/O were/O streaming/O down/O the/O maester/O 's/O face/O ,/O yet/O he/O shook/O his/O head/O doggedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O children/O .../O live/O only/O in/O dreams/O ./O 
Now/O ./O 
Dead/O and/O gone/O ./O 
Enough/O ,/O that/O 's/O enough/O ./O 
Now/O the/O bandages/O ./O 
Pads/O and/O then/O wrap/O ,/O and/O make/O it/O tight/O ,/O I/O 'll/O be/O bleeding/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Old/O Nan/PERSON says/O the/O children/O knew/O the/O songs/O of/O the/O trees/O ,/O that/O they/O could/O fly/O like/O birds/O and/O swim/O like/O fish/O and/O talk/O to/O the/O animals/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O says/O that/O they/O made/O music/O so/O beautiful/O that/O it/O made/O you/O cry/O like/O a/O little/O baby/O just/O to/O hear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O all/O this/O they/O did/O with/O magic/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ,/O distracted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wish/O they/O were/O here/O now/O ./O 
A/O spell/O would/O heal/O my/O arm/O less/O painfully/O ,/O and/O they/O could/O talk/O to/O Shaggydog/PERSON and/O tell/O him/O not/O to/O ''/O ,/O ``/O bite/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O the/O big/O black/O wolf/O an/O angry/O glance/O out/O of/O the/O corner/O of/O his/O eye/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O a/O lesson/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
The/O man/O who/O trusts/O in/O spells/O is/O dueling/O with/O a/O glass/O sword/O ./O 
As/O the/O children/O did/O ./O 
Here/O ,/O let/O me/O show/O you/O something/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stood/O abruptly/O ,/O crossed/O the/O room/O ,/O and/O returned/O with/O a/O green/O jar/O in/O his/O good/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O a/O look/O at/O these/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O pulled/O the/O stopper/O and/O shook/O out/O a/O handful/O of/O shiny/O black/O arrowheads/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O picked/O one/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O made/O of/O glass/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Curious/O ,/O Rickon/PERSON drifted/O closer/O to/O peer/O over/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dragonglass/O ,/O \/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION named/O it/O as/O she/O sat/O down/O beside/O Luwin/PERSON ,/O bandagings/O in/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Obsidian/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON insisted/O ,/O holding/O out/O his/O wounded/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Forged/O in/O the/O fires/O of/O the/O gods/O ,/O far/O below/O the/O earth/O ./O 
The/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O hunted/O with/O that/O ,/O thousands/O of/O years/O ago/O ./O 
The/O children/O worked/O no/O metal/O ./O 
In/O place/O of/O mail/O ,/O they/O wore/O long/O shirts/O of/O woven/O leaves/O and/O bound/O their/O legs/O in/O bark/O ,/O so/O they/O seemed/O to/O melt/O into/O the/O wood/O ./O 
In/O place/O of/O swords/O ,/O they/O carried/O blades/O of/O obsidian/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O still/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION placed/O soft/O pads/O over/O the/O bites/O on/O the/O maester/O 's/O forearm/O and/O bound/O them/O tight/O with/O long/O strips/O of/O linen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O held/O the/O arrowhead/O up/O close/O ./O 
The/O black/O glass/O was/O slick/O and/O shiny/O ./O 
He/O thought/O it/O beautiful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O I/O keep/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O one/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rickon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O four/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O four/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Luwin/PERSON made/O him/O count/O them/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Careful/O ,/O they/O 're/O still/O sharp/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O cut/O yourself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O about/O the/O children/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
It/O was/O important/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O wish/O to/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Everything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON tugged/O at/O his/O chain/O collar/O where/O it/O chafed/O against/O his/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O people/O of/O the/O Dawn/O Age/O ,/O the/O very/O first/O ,/O before/O kings/O and/O kingdoms/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O those/O days/O ,/O there/O were/O no/O castles/O or/O holdfasts/O ,/O no/O cities/O ,/O not/O so/O much/O as/O a/O market/O town/O to/O be/O found/O between/O here/O and/O the/O sea/LOCATION of/LOCATION Dome/LOCATION ./O 
There/O were/O no/O men/O at/O all/O ./O 
Only/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O dwelt/O in/O the/O lands/O we/O now/O call/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O were/O a/O people/O dark/O and/O beautiful/O ,/O small/O of/O stature/O ,/O no/O taller/O than/O children/O even/O when/O grown/O to/O manhood/O ./O 
They/O lived/O in/O the/O depths/O of/O the/O wood/O ,/O in/O caves/O and/O crannogs/O and/O secret/O tree/O towns/O ./O 
Slight/O as/O they/O were/O ,/O the/O children/O were/O quick/O and/O graceful/O ./O 
Male/O and/O female/O hunted/O together/O ,/O with/O weirwood/O bows/O and/O flying/O snares/O ./O 
Their/O gods/O were/O the/O gods/O of/O the/O forest/O ,/O stream/O ,/O and/O stone/O ,/O the/O old/O gods/O whose/O names/O are/O secret/O ./O 
Their/O wise/O men/O were/O called/O greenseers/O ,/O and/O carved/O strange/O faces/O in/O the/O weirwoods/O to/O keep/O watch/O on/O the/O woods/O ./O 
How/O long/O the/O children/O reigned/O here/O or/O where/O they/O came/O from/O ,/O no/O man/O can/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O some/O twelve/O thousand/O years/O ago/O ,/O the/O First/O Men/O appeared/O from/O the/O east/O ,/O crossing/O the/O Broken/LOCATION Arm/LOCATION of/LOCATION Dome/LOCATION before/O it/O was/O broken/O ./O 
They/O came/O with/O bronze/O swords/O and/O great/O leathern/O shields/O ,/O riding/O horses/O ./O 
No/O horse/O had/O ever/O been/O seen/O on/O this/O side/O of/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O the/O children/O were/O as/O frightened/O by/O the/O horses/O as/O the/O First/O Men/O were/O by/O the/O faces/O in/O the/O trees/O ./O 
As/O the/O First/O Men/O carved/O out/O holdfasts/O and/O farms/O ,/O they/O cut/O down/O the/O faces/O and/O gave/O them/O to/O the/O fire/O ./O 
Horrorstruck/O ,/O the/O children/O went/O to/O war/O ./O 
The/O old/O songs/O say/O that/O the/O greenseers/O used/O dark/O magics/O to/O ''/O ,/O ``/O make/O the/O seas/O rise/O and/O sweep/O away/O the/O land/O ,/O shattering/O the/O Arm/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O too/O late/O to/O close/O the/O door/O ./O 
The/O wars/O went/O on/O until/O the/O earth/O ran/O red/O with/O blood/O of/O men/O and/O children/O both/O ,/O but/O more/O children/O than/O men/O ,/O for/O men/O were/O bigger/O and/O stronger/O ,/O and/O wood/O and/O stone/O and/O obsidian/O make/O a/O poor/O match/O for/O bronze/O ./O 
Finally/O the/O wise/O of/O both/O races/O prevailed/O ,/O and/O the/O chiefs/O and/O heroes/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O met/O the/O greenseers/O and/O wood/O dancers/O amidst/O the/O weirwood/O groves/O of/O a/O small/O island/O in/O the/O great/O lake/O called/O Gods/O Eye/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O they/O forged/O the/O Pact/O ./O 
The/O First/O Men/O were/O given/O the/O coastlands/O ,/O the/O high/O plains/O and/O bright/O meadows/O ,/O the/O mountains/O and/O bogs/O ,/O but/O the/O deep/O woods/O were/O to/O remain/O forever/O the/O children/O 's/O ,/O and/O no/O more/O weirwoods/O were/O to/O be/O put/O to/O the/O axe/O anywhere/O in/O the/O realm/O ./O 
So/O the/O gods/O might/O bear/O witness/O to/O the/O signing/O ,/O every/O tree/O on/O the/O island/O was/O given/O a/O face/O ,/O and/O afterward/O ,/O the/O sacred/O order/O of/O green/O men/O was/O formed/O to/O keep/O watch/O over/O the/O Isle/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Faces/ORGANIZATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Pact/O began/O four/O thousand/O years/O of/O friendship/O between/O men/O and/O children/O ./O 
In/O time/O ,/O the/O First/O Men/O even/O put/O aside/O the/O gods/O they/O had/O brought/O with/O them/O ,/O and/O took/O up/O the/O worship/O of/O the/O secret/O gods/O of/O the/O wood/O ./O 
The/O signing/O of/O the/O Pact/O ended/O the/O Dawn/O Age/O ,/O and/O began/O the/O Age/O of/O Heroes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O 's/O fist/O curled/O around/O the/O shiny/O black/O arrowhead/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O are/O all/O gone/O now/O ,/O you/O said/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O they/O are/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O as/O she/O bit/O off/O the/O end/O of/O the/O last/O bandage/O with/O her/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O North/O of/O the/O Wall/O ,/O things/O are/O different/O ./O 
That/O 's/O where/O the/O children/O went/O ,/O and/O the/O giants/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O old/O races/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Woman/O ,/O by/O rights/O you/O ought/O to/O be/O dead/O or/O in/O chains/O ./O 
The/O Starks/PERSON have/O treated/O you/O more/O gently/O than/O you/O deserve/O ./O 
It/O is/O unkind/O to/O repay/O them/O for/O their/O kindness/O by/O filling/O the/O boys/O '/O heads/O with/O folly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O where/O they/O went/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Me/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rickon/PERSON echoed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O very/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON muttered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O long/O as/O the/O kingdoms/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O held/O sway/O ,/O the/O Pact/O endured/O ,/O all/O through/O the/O Age/O of/O Heroes/O and/O the/O Long/O Night/O and/O the/O birth/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O yet/O finally/O there/O came/O a/O time/O ,/O many/O centuries/O later/O ,/O when/O other/O peoples/O crossed/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Andals/O were/O the/O first/O ,/O a/O race/O of/O tall/O ,/O fair/O -/O haired/O warriors/O who/O came/O with/O steel/O and/O fire/O and/O the/O seven-pointed/O star/O of/O the/O new/O gods/O painted/O on/O their/O chests/O ./O 
The/O wars/O lasted/O hundreds/O of/O years/O ,/O but/O in/O the/O end/O the/O six/O southron/O kingdoms/O all/O fell/O before/O them/O ./O 
Only/O here/O ,/O where/O the/O King/PERSON in/PERSON the/PERSON North/PERSON threw/O back/O every/O army/O that/O tried/O to/O cross/O the/O Neck/O ,/O did/O the/O rule/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O endure/O ./O 
The/O Andals/O burnt/O out/O the/O weirwood/O groves/O ,/O hacked/O down/O the/O faces/O ,/O slaughtered/O the/O children/O where/O they/O found/O them/O ,/O and/O everywhere/O proclaimed/O the/O triumph/O of/O the/O Seven/O over/O the/O old/O gods/O ./O 
So/O the/O children/O fled/O north/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Summer/O began/O to/O howl/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON broke/O off/O ,/O startled/O ./O 
When/O Shaggydog/PERSON bounded/O to/O his/O feet/O and/O added/O his/O voice/O to/O his/O brother/O 's/O ,/O dread/O clutched/O at/O Bran/ORGANIZATION 's/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O coming/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ,/O with/O the/O certainty/O of/O despair/O ./O 
He/O had/O known/O it/O since/O last/O night/O ,/O he/O realized/O ,/O since/O the/O crow/O had/O led/O him/O down/O into/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O crypts/O to/O say/O farewell/O ./O 
He/O had/O known/O it/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O not/O believed/O ./O 
He/O had/O wanted/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON to/O be/O right/O ./O 
The/O crow/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O the/O three-eyed/O crow/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O howling/O stopped/O as/O suddenly/O as/O it/O had/O begun/O ./O 
Summer/O padded/O across/O the/O tower/O floor/O to/O Shaggydog/LOCATION ,/O and/O began/O to/O lick/O at/O a/O mat/O of/O bloody/O fur/O on/O the/O back/O of/O his/O brother/O 's/O neck/O ./O 
From/O the/O window/O came/O a/O flutter/O of/O wings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O raven/O landed/O on/O the/O grey/O stone/O sill/O ,/O opened/O its/O beak/O ,/O and/O gave/O a/O harsh/O ,/O raucous/O rattle/O of/O distress/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON began/O to/O cry/O ./O 
His/O arrowheads/O fell/O from/O his/O hand/O one/O by/O one/O and/O clattered/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
Bran/O pulled/O him/O close/O and/O hugged/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON stared/O at/O the/O black/O bird/O as/O if/O it/O were/O a/O scorpion/O with/O feathers/O ./O 
He/O rose/O ,/O slow/O as/O a/O sleepwalker/O ,/O and/O moved/O to/O the/O window/O ./O 
When/O he/O whistled/O ,/O the/O raven/O hopped/O onto/O his/O bandaged/O forearm/O ./O 
There/O was/O dried/O blood/O on/O its/O wings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O hawk/O ,/O \/O ''/O Luwin/PERSON murmured/O ,/O \/O ``/O perhaps/O an/O owl/O ./O 
Poor/O thing/O ,/O a/O wonder/O it/O got/O through/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O the/O letter/O from/O its/O leg/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O found/O himself/O shivering/O as/O the/O maester/O unrolled/O the/O paper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O holding/O his/O brother/O all/O the/O harder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O know/O what/O it/O is/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Osha/ORGANIZATION said/O ,/O not/O unkindly/O ./O 
She/O put/O her/O hand/O on/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON looked/O up/O at/O them/O numbly/O ,/O a/O small/O grey/O man/O with/O blood/O on/O the/O sleeve/O of/O his/O grey/O wool/O robe/O and/O tears/O in/O his/O bright/O grey/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O the/O sons/O ,/O in/O a/O voice/O gone/O hoarse/O and/O shrunken/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O .../O we/O shall/O need/O to/O find/O a/O stonecarver/O who/O knew/O his/O likeness/O well/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
