-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O north/O went/O on/O forever/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O knew/O the/O maps/O as/O well/O as/O anyone/O ,/O but/O a/O fortnight/O on/O the/O wild/O track/O that/O passed/O for/O the/O kingsroad/O up/O here/O had/O brought/O home/O the/O lesson/O that/O the/O map/O was/O one/O thing/O and/O the/O land/O quite/O another/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O left/O Winterfell/PERSON on/O the/O same/O day/O as/O the/O king/O ,/O amidst/O all/O the/O commotion/O of/O the/O royal/O departure/O ,/O riding/O out/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O men/O shouting/O and/O horses/O snorting/O ,/O to/O the/O rattle/O of/O wagons/O and/O the/O groaning/O of/O the/O queen/O 's/O huge/O wheelhouse/O ,/O as/O a/O light/O snow/O flurried/O about/O them/O ./O 
The/O kingsroad/O was/O just/O beyond/O the/O sprawl/O of/O castle/O and/O town/O ./O 
There/O the/O banners/O and/O the/O wagons/O and/O the/O columns/O of/O knights/O and/O freeriders/O turned/O south/O ,/O taking/O the/O tumult/O with/O them/O ,/O while/O Tyrion/PERSON turned/O north/O with/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON and/O his/O nephew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O had/O grown/O colder/O after/O that/O ,/O and/O far/O more/O quiet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O West/O of/O the/O road/O were/O flint/O hills/O ,/O grey/O and/O rugged/O ,/O with/O tall/O watchtowers/O on/O their/O stony/O summits/O ./O 
To/O the/O east/O the/O land/O was/O lower/O ,/O the/O ground/O flattening/O to/O a/O rolling/O plain/O that/O stretched/O away/O as/O far/O as/O the/O eye/O could/O see/O ./O 
Stone/O bridges/O spanned/O swift/O ,/O narrow/O rivers/O ,/O while/O small/O farms/O spread/O in/O rings/O around/O holdfasts/O walled/O in/O wood/O and/O stone/O ./O 
The/O road/O was/O well/O trafficked/O ,/O and/O at/O night/O for/O their/O comfort/O there/O were/O rude/O inns/O to/O be/O found/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Three/O days/O ride/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O however/O ,/O the/O farmland/O gave/O way/O to/O dense/O wood/O ,/O and/O the/O kingsroad/O grew/O lonely/O ./O 
The/O flint/O hills/O rose/O higher/O and/O wilder/O with/O each/O passing/O mile/O ,/O until/O by/O the/O fifth/O day/O they/O had/O turned/O into/O mountains/O ,/O cold/O blue-grey/O giants/O with/O jagged/O promontories/O and/O snow/O on/O their/O shoulders/O ./O 
When/O the/O wind/O blew/O from/O the/O north/O ,/O long/O plumes/O of/O ice/O crystals/O flew/O from/O the/O high/O peaks/O like/O banners/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O With/O the/O mountains/O a/O wall/O to/O the/O west/O ,/O the/O road/O veered/O north/O by/O northeast/O through/O the/O wood/O ,/O a/O forest/O of/O oak/O and/O evergreen/O and/O black/O brier/O that/O seemed/O older/O and/O darker/O than/O any/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O ever/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wolfswood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON called/O it/O ,/O and/O indeed/O their/O nights/O came/O alive/O with/O the/O howls/O of/O distant/O packs/O ,/O and/O some/O not/O so/O distant/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON 's/O albino/O direwo/O If/O pricked/O up/O his/O ears/O at/O the/O nightly/O howling/O ,/O but/O never/O raised/O his/O own/O voice/O in/O reply/O ./O 
There/O was/O something/O very/O unsettling/O about/O that/O animal/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O were/O eight/O in/O the/O party/O by/O then/O ,/O not/O counting/O the/O wolf/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON traveled/O with/O two/O of/O his/O own/O men/O ,/O as/O befit/O a/O Lannister/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O only/O his/O bastard/O nephew/O and/O some/O fresh/O mounts/O for/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O but/O at/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O wolfswood/O they/O stayed/O a/O night/O behind/O the/O wooden/O walls/O of/O a/O forest/O holdfast/O ,/O and/O there/O joined/O up/O with/O another/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O ,/O one/O Yoren/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON was/O stooped/O and/O sinister/O ,/O his/O features/O hidden/O behind/O a/O beard/O as/O black/O as/O his/O clothing/O ,/O but/O he/O seemed/O as/O tough/O as/O an/O old/O root/O and/O as/O hard/O as/O stone/O ./O 
With/O him/O were/O a/O pair/O of/O ragged/O peasant/O boys/O from/O the/O Fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rapers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Yoren/PERSON said/O with/O a/O cold/O look/O at/O his/O charges/O ./O 
Tyrion/O understood/O ./O 
Life/O on/O the/O Wall/O was/O said/O to/O be/O hard/O ,/O but/O no/O doubt/O it/O was/O preferable/O to/O castration/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Five/O men/O ,/O three/O boys/O ,/O a/O direwolf/O ,/O twenty/O horses/O ,/O and/O a/O cage/O of/O ravens/O given/O over/O to/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON by/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O 
No/O doubt/O they/O made/O a/O curious/O fellowship/O for/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O or/O any/O road/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O noticed/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON watching/O Yoren/PERSON and/O his/O sullen/O companions/O ,/O with/O an/O odd/O cast/O to/O his/O face/O that/O looked/O uncomfortably/O like/O dismay/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON had/O a/O twisted/O shoulder/O and/O a/O sour/O smell/O ,/O his/O hair/O and/O beard/O were/O matted/O and/O greasy/O and/O full/O of/O lice/O ,/O his/O clothing/O old/O ,/O patched/O ,/O and/O seldom/O washed/O ./O 
His/O two/O young/O recruits/O smelled/O even/O worse/O ,/O and/O seemed/O as/O stupid/O as/O they/O were/O cruel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O doubt/O the/O boy/O had/O made/O the/O mistake/O of/O thinking/O that/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O was/O made/O up/O of/O men/O like/O his/O uncle/O ./O 
If/O so/O ,/O Yoren/PERSON and/O his/O companions/O were/O a/O rude/O awakening/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON felt/O sorry/O for/O the/O boy/O ./O 
He/O had/O chosen/O a/O hard/O life/O .../O or/O perhaps/O he/O should/O say/O that/O a/O hard/O life/O had/O been/O chosen/O for/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O rather/O less/O sympathy/O for/O the/O uncle/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON seemed/O to/O share/O his/O brother/O 's/O distaste/O for/O Lannisters/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O not/O been/O pleased/O when/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O told/O him/O of/O his/O intentions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O warn/O you/O ,/O Lannister/O ,/O you/O 'll/O find/O no/O inns/O at/O the/O Wall/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O had/O said/O ,/O looking/O down/O on/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O doubt/O you/O 'll/O find/O some/O place/O to/O put/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O might/O have/O noticed/O ,/O I/O 'm/O small/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O One/O did/O not/O say/O no/O to/O the/O queen/O 's/O brother/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O so/O that/O had/O settled/O the/O matter/O ,/O but/O Stark/PERSON had/O not/O been/O happy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O not/O like/O the/O ride/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O 'd/O said/O curtly/O ,/O and/O since/O the/O moment/O they/O set/O out/O ,/O he/O had/O done/O all/O he/O could/O to/O live/O up/O to/O that/O promise/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O the/O end/O of/O the/O first/O week/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O thighs/O were/O raw/O from/O hard/O riding/O ,/O his/O legs/O were/O cramping/O badly/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O chilled/O to/O the/O bone/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O complain/O ./O 
He/O was/O damned/O if/O he/O would/O give/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON that/O satisfaction/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O took/O a/O small/O revenge/O in/O the/O matter/O of/O his/O riding/O fur/O ,/O a/O tattered/O bearskin/O ,/O old/O and/O musty/O -/O smelling/O ./O 
Stark/PERSON had/O offered/O it/O to/O him/O in/O an/O excess/O of/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O gallantry/O ,/O no/O doubt/O expecting/O him/O to/O graciously/O decline/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O accepted/O with/O a/O smile/O ./O 
He/O had/O brought/O his/O warmest/O clothing/O with/O him/O when/O they/O rode/O out/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O soon/O discovered/O that/O it/O was/O nowhere/O near/O warm/O enough/O ./O 
It/O was/O cold/O up/O here/O ,/O and/O growing/O colder/O ./O 
The/O nights/O were/O well/O below/O freezing/O now/O ,/O and/O when/O the/O wind/O blew/O it/O was/O like/O a/O knife/O cutting/O right/O through/O his/O warmest/O woolens/O ./O 
By/O now/O Stark/PERSON was/O no/O doubt/O regretting/O his/O chivalrous/O impulse/O ./O 
Perhaps/O he/O had/O learned/O a/O lesson/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O never/O declined/O ,/O graciously/O or/O otherwise/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O took/O what/O was/O offered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Farms/O and/O holdfasts/O grew/O scarcer/O and/O smaller/O as/O they/O pressed/O northward/O ,/O ever/O deeper/O into/O the/O darkness/O of/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O until/O finally/O there/O were/O no/O more/O roofs/O to/O shelter/O under/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O thrown/O back/O on/O their/O own/O resources/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O was/O never/O much/O use/O in/O making/O a/O camp/O or/O breaking/O one/O ./O 
Too/O small/O ,/O too/O hobbled/O ,/O too/O in/O -/O the-way/O ./O 
So/O while/O Stark/O and/O Yoren/PERSON and/O the/O other/O men/O erected/O rude/O shelters/O ,/O tended/O the/O horses/O ,/O and/O built/O a/O fire/O ,/O it/O became/O his/O custom/O to/O take/O his/O fur/O and/O a/O wineskin/O and/O go/O off/O by/O himself/O to/O read/O ./O 
On/O the/O eighteenth/O night/O of/O their/O journey/O ,/O the/O wine/O was/O a/O rare/O sweet/O amber/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION that/O he/O had/O brought/O all/O the/O way/O north/O from/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O the/O book/O a/O rumination/O on/O the/O history/O and/O properties/O of/O dragons/O ./O 
With/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O permission/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION had/O borrowed/O a/O few/O rare/O volumes/O from/O the/O Winterfell/LOCATION library/O and/O packed/O them/O for/O the/O ride/O north/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O found/O a/O comfortable/O spot/O just/O beyond/O the/O noise/O of/O the/O camp/O ,/O beside/O a/O swift-running/O stream/O with/O waters/O clear/O and/O cold/O as/O ice/O ./O 
A/O grotesquely/O ancient/O oak/O provided/O shelter/O from/O the/O biting/O wind/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON curled/O up/O in/O his/O fur/O with/O his/O back/O against/O the/O trunk/O ,/O took/O a/O sip/O of/O the/O wine/O ,/O and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O began/O to/O read/O about/O the/O properties/O of/O dragonbone/O ./O 
Dragonbone/O is/O black/O because/O of/O its/O high/O iron/O content/O ,/O the/O book/O told/O him/O ./O 
It/O is/O strong/O as/O steel/O ,/O yet/O lighter/O and/O far/O more/O flexible/O ,/O and/O of/O course/O utterly/O impervious/O to/O fire/O ./O 
Dragonbone/O bows/O are/O greatly/O prized/O by/O the/O Dothraki/O ,/O and/O small/O wonder/O ./O 
An/O archer/O so/O armed/O can/O outrange/O any/O wooden/O bow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O had/O a/O morbid/O fascination/O with/O dragons/O ./O 
When/O he/O had/O first/O come/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O for/O his/O sister/O 's/O wedding/O to/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O he/O had/O made/O it/O a/O point/O to/O seek/O out/O the/O dragon/O skulls/O that/O had/O hung/O on/O the/O walls/O of/O Targaryen/PERSON 's/O throne/O room/O ./O 
King/O Robert/PERSON had/O replaced/O them/O with/O banners/O and/O tapestries/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O persisted/O until/O he/O found/O the/O skulls/O in/O the/O dank/O cellar/O where/O they/O had/O been/O stored/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O expected/O to/O find/O them/O impressive/O ,/O perhaps/O even/O frightening/O ./O 
He/O had/O not/O thought/O to/O find/O them/O beautiful/O ./O 
Yet/O they/O were/O ./O 
As/O black/O as/O onyx/O ,/O polished/O smooth/O ,/O so/O the/O bone/O seemed/O to/O shimmer/O in/O the/O light/O of/O his/O torch/O ./O 
They/O liked/O the/O fire/O ,/O he/O sensed/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O thrust/O the/O torch/O into/O the/O mouth/O of/O one/O of/O the/O larger/O skulls/O and/O made/O the/O shadows/O leap/O and/O dance/O on/O the/O wall/O behind/O him/O ./O 
The/O teeth/O were/O long/O ,/O curving/O knives/O of/O black/O diamond/O ./O 
The/O flame/O of/O the/O torch/O was/O nothing/O to/O them/O ;/O they/O had/O bathed/O in/O the/O heat/O of/O far/O greater/O fires/O ./O 
When/O he/O had/O moved/O away/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O have/O sworn/O that/O the/O beast/O 's/O empty/O eye/O sockets/O had/O watched/O him/O go/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O were/O nineteen/O skulls/O ./O 
The/O oldest/O was/O more/O than/O three/O thousand/O years/O old/O ;/O the/O youngest/O a/O mere/O century/O and/O a/O half/O ./O 
The/O most/O recent/O were/O also/O the/O smallest/O ;/O a/O matched/O pair/O no/O bigger/O than/O mastiffs/O skulls/O ,/O and/O oddly/O misshapen/O ,/O all/O that/O remained/O of/O the/O last/O two/O hatchlings/O born/O on/O Dragonstone/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O last/O of/O the/O Targaryen/O dragons/O ,/O perhaps/O the/O last/O dragons/O anywhere/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O not/O lived/O very/O long/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O there/O the/O skulls/O ranged/O upward/O in/O size/O to/O the/O three/O great/O monsters/O of/O song/O and/O story/O ,/O the/O dragons/O that/O Aegon/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON and/O his/O sisters/O had/O unleashed/O on/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O of/O old/O ./O 
The/O singers/O had/O given/O them/O the/O names/O of/O gods/O :/O Balerion/LOCATION ,/O Meraxes/LOCATION ,/O Vhaghar/PERSON ./O 
Tyrion/O had/O stood/O between/O their/O gaping/O jaws/O ,/O wordless/O and/O awed/O ./O 
You/O could/O have/O ridden/O a/O horse/O down/O Vhaghar/PERSON 's/O gullet/O ,/O although/O you/O would/O not/O have/O ridden/O it/O out/O again/O ./O 
Meraxes/PERSON was/O even/O bigger/O ./O 
And/O the/O greatest/O of/O them/O ,/O Balerion/LOCATION ,/O the/O Black/O Dread/O ,/O could/O have/O swallowed/O an/O aurochs/O whole/O ,/O or/O even/O one/O of/O the/O hairy/O mammoths/O said/O to/O roam/O the/O cold/O wastes/O beyond/O the/O Port/O of/O Ibben/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O stood/O in/O that/O dank/O cellar/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O staring/O at/O Balerion/LOCATION 's/O huge/O ,/O empty-eyed/O skull/O until/O his/O torch/O burned/O low/O ,/O trying/O to/O grasp/O the/O size/O of/O the/O living/O animal/O ,/O to/O imagine/O how/O it/O must/O have/O looked/O when/O it/O spread/O its/O great/O black/O wings/O and/O swept/O across/O the/O skies/O ,/O breathing/O fire/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O own/O remote/O ancestor/O ,/O King/PERSON Loren/PERSON of/O the/O Rock/O ,/O had/O tried/O to/O stand/O against/O the/O fire/O when/O he/O joined/O with/O King/O Mern/PERSON of/O the/O Reach/O to/O oppose/O the/O Targaryen/O conquest/O ./O 
That/O was/O close/O on/O three/O hundred/O years/O ago/O ,/O when/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O were/O kingdoms/O ,/O and/O not/O mere/O provinces/O of/O a/O greater/O realm/O ./O 
Between/O them/O ,/O the/O Two/ORGANIZATION Kings/ORGANIZATION had/O six/O hundred/O banners/O flying/O ,/O five/O thousand/O mounted/O knights/O ,/O and/O ten/O times/O as/O many/O freeriders/O and/O men-at-arms/O ./O 
Aegon/ORGANIZATION Dragonlord/ORGANIZATION had/O perhaps/O a/O fifth/O that/O number/O ,/O the/O chroniclers/O said/O ,/O and/O most/O of/O those/O were/O conscripts/O from/O the/O ranks/O of/O the/O last/O king/O he/O had/O slain/O ,/O their/O loyalties/O uncertain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O hosts/O met/O on/O the/O broad/O plains/O of/O the/O Reach/O ,/O amidst/O golden/O fields/O of/O wheat/O ripe/O for/O harvest/O ./O 
When/O the/O Two/O Kings/O charged/O ,/O the/O Targaryen/O army/O shivered/O and/O shattered/O and/O began/O to/O run/O ./O 
For/O ''/O ,/O ``/O a/O few/O moments/O ,/O the/O chroniclers/O wrote/O ,/O the/O conquest/O was/O at/O an/O end/O .../O but/O only/O for/O those/O few/O moments/O ,/O before/O Aegon/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON and/O his/O sisters/O joined/O the/O battle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O only/O time/O that/O Vhaghar/PERSON ,/O Meraxes/PERSON ,/O and/O Balerion/LOCATION were/O all/O unleashed/O at/O once/O ./O 
The/O singers/O called/O it/O the/O Field/O of/O Fire/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Near/O four/O thousand/O men/O had/O burned/O that/O day/O ,/O among/O them/O King/O Mern/PERSON of/O the/O Reach/O ./O 
King/O Loren/PERSON had/O escaped/O ,/O and/O lived/O long/O enough/O to/O surrender/O ,/O pledge/O his/O fealty/O to/O the/O Targaryens/O ,/O and/O beget/O a/O son/O ,/O for/O which/O Tyrion/O was/O duly/O grateful/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O do/O you/O read/O so/O much/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O looked/O up/O at/O the/O sound/O of/O the/O voice/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON was/O standing/O a/O few/O feet/O away/O ,/O regarding/O him/O curiously/O ./O 
He/O closed/O the/O book/O on/O a/O finger/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Look/O at/O me/O and/O tell/O me/O what/O you/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O boy/O looked/O at/O him/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O some/O kind/O of/O trick/O ?/O 
I/O see/O you/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O remarkably/O polite/O for/O a/O bastard/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
What/O you/O see/O is/O a/O dwarf/O ./O 
You/O are/O what/O ,/O twelve/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fourteen/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fourteen/O ,/O and/O you/O 're/O taller/O than/O I/O will/O ever/O be/O ./O 
My/O legs/O are/O short/O and/O twisted/O ,/O and/O I/O walk/O with/O difficulty/O ./O 
I/O require/O a/O special/O saddle/O to/O keep/O from/O falling/O off/O my/O horse/O ./O 
A/O saddle/O of/O my/O own/O design/O ,/O you/O may/O be/O interested/O to/O know/O ./O 
It/O was/O either/O that/O or/O ride/O a/O pony/O ./O 
My/O arms/O are/O strong/O enough/O ,/O but/O again/O ,/O too/O short/O ./O 
I/O will/O never/O make/O a/O swordsman/O ./O 
Had/O I/O been/O born/O a/O peasant/O ,/O they/O might/O have/O left/O me/O out/O to/O die/O ,/O or/O sold/O me/O to/O some/O slaver/O 's/O grotesquerie/O ./O 
Alas/O ,/O I/O was/O born/O a/O Lannister/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O and/O the/O grotesqueries/O are/O all/O the/O poorer/O ./O 
Things/O are/O expected/O of/O me/O ./O 
My/O father/O was/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O for/O twenty/O years/O ./O 
My/O brother/O later/O killed/O that/O very/O same/O king/O ,/O as/O it/O turns/O out/O ,/O but/O life/O is/O full/O of/O these/O little/O ironies/O ./O 
My/O sister/O married/O the/O new/O king/O and/O my/O repulsive/O nephew/O will/O be/O king/O after/O him/O ./O 
I/O must/O do/O my/O part/O for/O the/O honor/O of/O my/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O would/O n't/O you/O agree/O ?/O 
Yet/O how/O ?/O 
Well/O ,/O my/O legs/O may/O be/O too/O small/O for/O my/O body/O ,/O but/O my/O head/O is/O too/O large/O ,/O although/O I/O prefer/O to/O think/O it/O is/O just/O large/O enough/O for/O my/O mind/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O realistic/O grasp/O of/O my/O own/O strengths/O and/O weaknesses/O ./O 
My/O mind/O is/O my/O weapon/O ./O 
My/O brother/O has/O his/O sword/O ,/O King/O Robert/PERSON has/O his/O warhammer/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O my/O mind/O .../O and/O a/O mind/O needs/O books/O as/O a/O sword/O needs/O a/O whetstone/O ,/O if/O it/O is/O to/O keep/O its/O edge/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O tapped/O the/O leather/O cover/O of/O the/O book/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O why/O I/O read/O so/O much/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O boy/O absorbed/O that/O all/O in/O silence/O ./O 
He/O had/O the/O Stark/O face/O if/O not/O the/O name/O :/O long/O ,/O solemn/O ,/O guarded/O ,/O a/O face/O that/O gave/O nothing/O away/O ./O 
Whoever/O his/O mother/O had/O been/O ,/O she/O had/O left/O little/O of/O herself/O in/O her/O son/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O reading/O about/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dragons/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O good/O is/O that/O ?/O 
There/O are/O no/O more/O dragons/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O with/O the/O easy/O certainty/O of/O youth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O they/O say/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sad/O ,/O is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
When/O I/O was/O your/O age/O ,/O used/O to/O dream/O of/O having/O a/O dragon/O of/O my/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O did/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O suspiciously/O ./O 
Perhaps/O he/O thought/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O making/O fun/O of/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
Even/O a/O stunted/O ,/O twisted/O ,/O ugly/O little/O boy/O can/O look/O down/O over/O the/O world/O when/O he/O 's/O seated/O on/O a/O dragon/O 's/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON pushed/O the/O bearskin/O aside/O and/O climbed/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O used/O to/O start/O fires/O in/O the/O bowels/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION and/O stare/O at/O the/O flames/O for/O hours/O ,/O pretending/O they/O were/O ''/O ,/O ``/O dragonfire/O ./O 
Sometimes/O I/O 'd/O imagine/O my/O father/O burning/O ./O 
At/O other/O times/O ,/O my/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON was/O staring/O at/O him/O ,/O a/O look/O equal/O parts/O horror/O and/O fascination/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON guffawed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O look/O at/O me/O that/O way/O ,/O bastard/O ./O 
I/O know/O your/O secret/O ./O 
You/O 've/O dreamt/O the/O same/O kind/O of/O dreams/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON said/O ,/O horrified/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O n't/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ?/O 
Never/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON raised/O an/O eyebrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O no/O doubt/O the/O Starks/PERSON have/O been/O terribly/O good/O to/O you/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O certain/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON treats/O you/O as/O if/O you/O were/O one/O of/O her/O own/O ./O 
And/O your/O brother/O Robb/PERSON ,/O he/O 's/O always/O been/O kind/O ,/O and/O why/O not/O ?/O 
He/O gets/O Winterfell/PERSON and/O you/O get/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
And/O your/O father/O .../O he/O must/O have/O good/O reasons/O for/O packing/O you/O off/O to/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON said/O ,/O his/O face/O dark/O with/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O a/O noble/O calling/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O too/O smart/O to/O believe/O that/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O a/O midden/O heap/O for/O all/O the/O misfits/O of/O the/O realm/O ./O 
I/O 've/O seen/O you/O looking/O at/O Yoren/LOCATION and/O his/O boys/O ./O 
Those/O are/O your/O new/O brothers/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O how/O do/O you/O like/O them/O ?/O 
Sullen/O peasants/O ,/O debtors/O ,/O poachers/O ,/O rapers/O ,/O thieves/O ,/O and/O bastards/O like/O you/O all/O wind/O up/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O watching/O for/O grumkins/O and/O snarks/O and/O all/O the/O other/O monsters/O your/O wet/O nurse/O warned/O you/O about/O ./O 
The/O good/O part/O is/O there/O are/O no/O grumkins/O or/O snarks/O ,/O so/O it/O 's/O scarcely/O dangerous/O work/O ./O 
The/O bad/O part/O is/O you/O freeze/O your/O balls/O off/O ,/O but/O since/O you/O 're/O not/O allowed/O to/O breed/O anyway/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O suppose/O that/O matters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O boy/O screamed/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O step/O forward/O ,/O his/O hands/O coiling/O into/O fists/O ,/O close/O to/O tears/O ./O 
Suddenly/O ,/O absurdly/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON felt/O guilty/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O step/O forward/O ,/O intending/O to/O give/O the/O boy/O a/O reassuring/O pat/O on/O the/O shoulder/O or/O mutter/O some/O word/O of/O apology/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O never/O saw/O the/O wolf/O ,/O where/O it/O was/O or/O how/O it/O came/O at/O him/O ./O 
One/O moment/O he/O was/O walking/O toward/O Snow/O and/O the/O next/O he/O was/O flat/O on/O his/O back/O on/O the/O hard/O rocky/O ground/O ,/O the/O book/O spinning/O away/O from/O him/O as/O he/O fell/O ,/O the/O breath/O going/O out/O of/O him/O at/O the/O sudden/O impact/O ,/O his/O mouth/O full/O of/O dirt/O and/O blood/O and/O rotting/O leaves/O ./O 
As/O he/O tried/O to/O get/O up/O ,/O his/O back/O spasmed/O painfully/O ./O 
He/O must/O have/O wrenched/O it/O in/O the/O fall/O ./O 
He/O ground/O his/O teeth/O in/O frustration/O ,/O grabbed/O a/O root/O ,/O and/O pulled/O himself/O back/O to/O a/O sitting/O position/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Help/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O the/O boy/O ,/O reaching/O up/O a/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O suddenly/O the/O wolf/O was/O between/O them/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O growl/O ./O 
The/O damned/O thing/O never/O made/O a/O sound/O ./O 
He/O only/O looked/O at/O him/O with/O those/O bright/O red/O eyes/O ,/O and/O showed/O him/O his/O teeth/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O more/O than/O enough/O ./O 
Tyrion/O sagged/O back/O to/O the/O ground/O with/O a/O grunt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O help/O me/O ,/O then/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O sit/O right/O here/O until/O you/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/O Snow/O stroked/O Ghost/O 's/O thick/O white/O fur/O ,/O smiling/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ask/O me/O nicely/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O felt/O the/O anger/O coiling/O inside/O him/O ,/O and/O crushed/O it/O out/O with/O a/O will/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O the/O first/O time/O in/O his/O life/O he/O had/O been/O humiliated/O ,/O and/O it/O would/O not/O be/O the/O last/O ./O 
Perhaps/O he/O even/O deserved/O this/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O be/O very/O grateful/O for/O your/O kind/O assistance/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O mildly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Down/O ,/O Ghost/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O sat/O on/O his/O haunches/O ./O 
Those/O red/O eyes/O never/O left/O Tyrion/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON came/O around/O behind/O him/O ,/O slid/O his/O hands/O under/O his/O arms/O ,/O and/O lifted/O him/O easily/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
Then/O he/O picked/O up/O the/O book/O and/O handed/O it/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O did/O he/O attack/O me/O '/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O with/O a/O sidelong/O glance/O at/O the/O direwolf/O ./O 
He/O wiped/O blood/O and/O dirt/O from/O his/O mouth/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O he/O thought/O you/O were/O a/O grumkin/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O glanced/O at/O him/O sharply/O ./O 
Then/O he/O laughed/O ,/O a/O raw/O snort/O of/O amusement/O that/O came/O bursting/O out/O through/O his/O nose/O entirely/O without/O his/O permission/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O choking/O on/O his/O laughter/O and/O shaking/O his/O head/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O suppose/O I/O do/O rather/O look/O like/O a/O grumkin/O ./O 
What/O does/O he/O do/O to/O snarks/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON picked/O up/O the/O wineskin/O and/O handed/O it/O to/O Tyrion/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O pulled/O out/O the/O stopper/O ,/O tilted/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O squeezed/O a/O long/O stream/O into/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
The/O wine/O was/O cool/O fire/O as/O it/O trickled/O down/O his/O throat/O and/O warmed/O his/O belly/O ./O 
He/O held/O out/O the/O skin/O to/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Want/O some/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O boy/O took/O the/O skin/O and/O tried/O a/O cautious/O swallow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O true/O ,/O is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O when/O he/O was/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O you/O said/O about/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O nodded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON set/O his/O mouth/O in/O a/O grim/O line/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O that/O 's/O what/O it/O is/O ,/O that/O 's/O what/O it/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O grinned/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O good/O ,/O bastard/O ./O 
Most/O men/O would/O rather/O deny/O a/O hard/O truth/O than/O face/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Most/O men/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O boy/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O not/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON admitted/O ,/O \/O ``/O not/O me/O ./O 
I/O seldom/O even/O dream/O of/O dragons/O anymore/O ./O 
There/O are/O no/O dragons/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O scooped/O up/O the/O fallen/O bearskin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O we/O had/O better/O return/O to/O camp/O before/O your/O uncle/O calls/O the/O banners/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O walk/O was/O short/O ,/O but/O the/O ground/O was/O rough/O underfoot/O and/O his/O legs/O were/O cramping/O badly/O by/O the/O time/O they/O got/O back/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON offered/O a/O hand/O to/O help/O him/O over/O a/O thick/O tangle/O of/O roots/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON shook/O him/O off/O ./O 
He/O would/O make/O his/O own/O way/O ,/O as/O he/O had/O all/O his/O life/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O the/O camp/O was/O a/O welcome/O sight/O ./O 
The/O shelters/O had/O been/O thrown/O up/O against/O the/O tumbledown/O wall/O of/O a/O long/O -/O abandoned/O holdfast/O ,/O a/O shield/O against/O the/O wind/O ./O 
The/O horses/O had/O been/O fed/O and/O a/O fire/O had/O been/O laid/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON sat/O on/O a/O stone/O ,/O skinning/O a/O squirrel/O ./O 
The/O savory/O smell/O of/O stew/O filled/O Tyrion/O 's/O nostrils/O ./O 
He/O dragged/O himself/O over/O to/O where/O his/O man/O Morrec/PERSON was/O tending/O the/O stewpot/O ./O 
Wordlessly/O ,/O Morrec/PERSON handed/O him/O the/O ladle/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON tasted/O and/O handed/O it/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O More/O pepper/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON emerged/O from/O the/O shelter/O he/O shared/O with/O his/O nephew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O you/O are/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON ,/O damn/O it/O ,/O do/O n't/O go/O off/O like/O that/O by/O yourself/O ./O 
I/O thought/O the/O Others/O had/O gotten/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O grumkins/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O laughing/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
Stark/O shot/O a/O baffled/O look/O at/O Yoren/PERSON ./O 
The/O old/O man/O grunted/O ,/O shrugged/O ,/O and/O went/O back/O to/O his/O bloody/O work/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O squirrel/O gave/O some/O body/O to/O the/O stew/O ,/O and/O they/O ate/O it/O with/O black/O bread/O and/O hard/O cheese/O that/O night/O around/O their/O fire/O ./O 
Tyrion/O shared/O around/O his/O skin/O of/O wine/O until/O even/O Yoren/PERSON grew/O mellow/O ./O 
One/O by/O one/O the/O company/O drifted/O off/O to/O their/O shelters/O and/O to/O sleep/O ,/O all/O but/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O drawn/O the/O night/O 's/O first/O watch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O was/O the/O last/O to/O retire/O ,/O as/O always/O ./O 
As/O he/O stepped/O into/O the/O shelter/O his/O men/O had/O built/O for/O him/O ,/O he/O paused/O and/O looked/O back/O at/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ./O 
The/O boy/O stood/O near/O the/O fire/O ,/O his/O face/O still/O and/O hard/O ,/O looking/O deep/O into/O the/O flames/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O smiled/O sadly/O and/O went/O to/O bed/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
