-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O he/O stood/O in/O the/O predawn/O chill/O watching/O Chiggen/O butcher/O his/O horse/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON chalked/O up/O one/O more/O debt/O owed/O the/O Starks/PERSON ./O 
Steam/O rose/O from/O inside/O the/O carcass/O when/O the/O squat/O sellsword/O opened/O the/O belly/O with/O his/O skinning/O knife/O ./O 
His/O hands/O moved/O deftly/O ,/O with/O never/O a/O wasted/O cut/O ;/O the/O work/O had/O to/O be/O done/O quickly/O ,/O before/O the/O stink/O of/O blood/O brought/O shadowcats/O down/O from/O the/O heights/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O None/O of/O us/O will/O go/O hungry/O tonight/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O was/O near/O a/O shadow/O himself/O ;/O bone/O thin/O and/O bone/O hard/O ,/O with/O black/O eyes/O and/O black/O hair/O and/O a/O stubble/O of/O beard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O of/O us/O may/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O fond/O of/O eating/O horse/O ./O 
Particularly/O my/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Meat/O is/O meat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O with/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O like/O horse/O more/O than/O beef/O or/O pork/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O take/O me/O for/O a/O Dothraki/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON asked/O sourly/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON ate/O horse/O ,/O in/O truth/O ;/O they/O also/O left/O deformed/O children/O out/O for/O the/O feral/O dogs/O who/O ran/O behind/O their/O khalasars/O ./O 
Dothraki/O customs/O had/O scant/O appeal/O for/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Chiggen/O sliced/O a/O thin/O strip/O of/O bloody/O meat/O off/O the/O carcass/O and/O held/O it/O up/O for/O inspection/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Want/O a/O taste/O ,/O dwarf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON gave/O me/O that/O mare/O for/O my/O twenty-third/O name/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O in/O a/O flat/O voice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O him/O for/O us/O ,/O then/O ./O 
If/O you/O ever/O see/O him/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Chiggen/PERSON grinned/O ,/O showing/O yellow/O teeth/O ,/O and/O swallowed/O the/O raw/O meat/O in/O two/O bites/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tastes/O well/O bred/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Better/O if/O you/O fry/O it/O up/O with/O onions/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON put/O in/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Wordlessly/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON limped/O away/O ./O 
The/O cold/O had/O settled/O deep/O in/O his/O bones/O ,/O and/O his/O legs/O were/O so/O sore/O he/O could/O scarcely/O walk/O ./O 
Perhaps/O his/O dead/O mare/O was/O the/O lucky/O one/O ./O 
He/O had/O hours/O more/O riding/O ahead/O of/O him/O ,/O followed/O by/O a/O few/O mouthfuls/O of/O food/O and/O a/O short/O ,/O cold/O sleep/O on/O hard/O ground/O ,/O and/O then/O another/O night/O of/O the/O same/O ,/O and/O another/O ,/O and/O another/O ,/O and/O the/O gods/O only/O knew/O how/O it/O would/O end/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O as/O he/O struggled/O up/O the/O road/O to/O rejoin/O his/O captors/O ,/O remembering/O ,/O \/O ``/O damn/O her/O and/O all/O the/O Starks/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O memory/O was/O still/O bitter/O ./O 
One/O moment/O he/O 'd/O been/O ordering/O supper/O ,/O and/O an/O eye/O blink/O later/O he/O was/O facing/O a/O room/O of/O armed/O men/O ,/O with/O Jyck/PERSON reaching/O for/O a/O sword/O and/O the/O fat/O innkeep/O shrieking/O ,/O \/O ``/O No/O swords/O ,/O not/O here/O ,/O please/O ,/O m/O `/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O wrenched/O down/O Jyck/PERSON 's/O arm/O hurriedly/O ,/O before/O he/O got/O them/O both/O hacked/O to/O pieces/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O your/O courtesies/O ,/O Jyck/PERSON ?/O 
Our/O good/O hostess/O said/O no/O swords/O ./O 
Do/O as/O she/O asks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O forced/O a/O smile/O that/O must/O have/O looked/O as/O queasy/O as/O it/O felt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O making/O a/O sad/O mistake/O ,/O Lady/O Stark/O ./O 
I/O had/O no/O part/O in/O any/O attack/O on/O your/O son/O ./O 
On/O my/O honor/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lannister/O honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O was/O all/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O held/O up/O her/O hands/O for/O all/O the/O room/O to/O see/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O dagger/O left/O these/O scars/O ./O 
The/O blade/O he/O sent/O to/O open/O my/O son/O 's/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O felt/O the/O anger/O all/O around/O him/O ,/O thick/O and/O smoky/O ,/O fed/O by/O the/O deep/O cuts/O in/O the/O Stark/O woman/O 's/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kill/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O hissed/O some/O drunken/O slattern/O from/O the/O back/O ,/O and/O other/O voices/O took/O up/O the/O call/O ,/O faster/O than/O he/O would/O have/O believed/O ./O 
Strangers/O all/O ,/O friendly/O enough/O only/O a/O moment/O ago/O ,/O and/O yet/O now/O they/O cried/O for/O his/O blood/O like/O hounds/O on/O a/O trail/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O spoke/O up/O loudly/O ,/O trying/O to/O keep/O the/O quaver/O from/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON believes/O I/O have/O some/O crime/O to/O answer/O for/O ,/O I/O will/O go/O with/O her/O and/O answer/O for/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O only/O possible/O course/O ./O 
Trying/O to/O cut/O their/O way/O out/O of/O this/O was/O a/O sure/O invitation/O to/O an/O early/O grave/O ./O 
A/O good/O dozen/O swords/O had/O responded/O to/O the/O Stark/O woman/O 's/O plea/O for/O help/O :/O the/O Harrenhal/O man/O ,/O the/O three/O Brackens/PERSON ,/O a/O pair/O of/O unsavory/O sellswords/O who/O looked/O as/O though/O they/O 'd/O kill/O him/O as/O soon/O as/O spit/O ,/O and/O some/O fool/O field/O hands/O who/O doubtless/O had/O no/O idea/O what/O they/O were/O doing/O ./O 
Against/O that/O ,/O what/O did/O Tyrion/PERSON have/O ?/O 
A/O dagger/O at/O his/O belt/O ,/O and/O two/O men/O ./O 
Jyck/PERSON swung/O a/O fair/O enough/O sword/O ,/O but/O Morrec/PERSON scarcely/O counted/O ;/O he/O was/O part/O groom/O ,/O part/O cook/O ,/O part/O body/O servant/O ,/O and/O no/O soldier/O ./O 
As/O for/O Yoren/PERSON ,/O whatever/O his/O feelings/O might/O have/O been/O ,/O the/O black/O brothers/O were/O sworn/O to/O take/O no/O part/O in/O the/O quarrels/O of/O the/O realm/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON would/O do/O nothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O indeed/O ,/O the/O black/O brother/O stepped/O aside/O silently/O when/O the/O old/O knight/O by/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O side/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Take/O their/O weapons/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O the/O sellsword/O Bronn/PERSON stepped/O forward/O to/O pull/O the/O sword/O from/O Jyck/PERSON 's/O fingers/O and/O relieve/O them/O all/O of/O their/O daggers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Good/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O said/O as/O the/O tension/O in/O the/O common/O room/O ebbed/O palpably/O ,/O \/O ``/O excellent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON recognized/O the/O gruff/O voice/O ;/O Winterfell/PERSON 's/O master-at-arms/O ,/O shorn/O of/O his/O whiskers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Scarlet-tinged/O spittle/O flew/O from/O the/O fat/O innkeep/O 's/O mouth/O as/O she/O begged/O of/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O kill/O him/O here/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O kill/O him/O anywhere/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O urged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O him/O somewheres/O else/O ,/O no/O blood/O here/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ,/O I/O wants/O no/O high/O lordlin/O 's/O quarrels/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O are/O taking/O him/O back/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O Well/O ,/O perhaps/O .../O By/O then/O he/O 'd/O had/O a/O moment/O to/O glance/O over/O the/O room/O and/O get/O a/O better/O idea/O of/O the/O situation/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O altogether/O displeased/O by/O what/O he/O saw/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O the/O Stark/O woman/O had/O been/O clever/O ,/O no/O doubt/O of/O it/O ./O 
Force/O them/O to/O make/O a/O public/O affirmation/O of/O the/O oaths/O sworn/O her/O father/O by/O the/O lords/O they/O served/O ,/O and/O then/O call/O on/O them/O for/O succor/O ,/O and/O her/O a/O woman/O ,/O yes/O ,/O that/O was/O sweet/O ./O 
Yet/O her/O success/O was/O not/O as/O complete/O as/O she/O might/O have/O liked/O ./O 
There/O were/O close/O to/O fifty/O in/O the/O common/O room/O by/O his/O rough/O count/O ./O 
Catelyn/O Stark/O 's/O plea/O had/O roused/O a/O bare/O dozen/O ;/O the/O others/O looked/O confused/O ,/O or/O frightened/O ,/O or/O sullen/O ./O 
Only/O two/O of/O the/O Freys/ORGANIZATION had/O stirred/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON noted/O ,/O and/O they/O 'd/O sat/O back/O down/O quick/O enough/O when/O their/O captain/O failed/O to/O move/O ./O 
He/O might/O have/O smiled/O if/O he/O 'd/O dared/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Winterfell/O it/O is/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O instead/O ./O 
That/O was/O a/O long/O ride/O ,/O as/O he/O could/O well/O attest/O ,/O having/O just/O ridden/O it/O the/O other/O way/O ./O 
So/O many/O things/O could/O happen/O along/O the/O way/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O will/O wonder/O what/O has/O become/O of/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O added/O ,/O catching/O the/O eye/O of/O the/O swordsman/O who/O 'd/O offered/O to/O yield/O up/O his/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 'll/O pay/O a/O handsome/O reward/O to/O any/O man/O who/O brings/O him/O word/O of/O what/O happened/O here/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON would/O do/O no/O such/O thing/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON would/O make/O up/O for/O it/O if/O he/O won/O free/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON glanced/O at/O his/O lady/O ,/O his/O look/O worried/O ,/O as/O well/O it/O might/O be/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O men/O come/O with/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O old/O knight/O announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O we/O 'll/O thank/O the/O rest/O of/O you/O to/O stay/O quiet/O about/O what/O you/O 've/O seen/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O all/O Tyrion/O could/O do/O not/O to/O laugh/O ./O 
Quiet/O ?/O 
The/O old/O fool/O ./O 
Unless/O he/O took/O the/O whole/O inn/O ,/O the/O word/O would/O begin/O to/O spread/O the/O instant/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O 
The/O freerider/O with/O the/O gold/O coin/O in/O his/O pocket/O would/O fly/O to/O easterly/O Rock/O like/O an/O arrow/O ./O 
If/O not/O him/O ,/O then/O someone/O else/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON would/O ''/O ,/O ``/O carry/O the/O story/O south/O ./O 
That/O fool/O singer/O might/O make/O a/O lay/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O Freys/O would/O report/O back/O to/O their/O lord/O ,/O and/O the/O gods/O only/O knew/O what/O he/O might/O do/O ./O 
Lord/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON might/O be/O sworn/O to/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O but/O he/O was/O a/O cautious/O man/O who/O had/O lived/O a/O long/O time/O by/O making/O certain/O he/O was/O always/O on/O the/O winning/O side/O ./O 
At/O the/O very/O least/O he/O would/O send/O his/O birds/O winging/O south/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O and/O he/O might/O well/O dare/O more/O than/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O wasted/O no/O time/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O must/O ride/O at/O once/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O want/O fresh/O mounts/O ,/O and/O provisions/O for/O the/O road/O ./O 
You/O men/O ,/O know/O that/O you/O have/O the/O eternal/O gratitude/O of/O House/O Stark/O ./O 
If/O any/O of/O you/O choose/O to/O help/O us/O guard/O our/O captives/O and/O get/O them/O safe/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O I/O promise/O you/O shall/O be/O well/O rewarded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O That/O was/O all/O it/O took/O ;/O the/O fools/O came/O rushing/O forward/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON studied/O their/O faces/O ;/O they/O would/O indeed/O be/O well/O rewarded/O ,/O he/O vowed/O to/O himself/O ,/O but/O perhaps/O not/O quite/O as/O they/O imagined/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O even/O as/O they/O were/O bundling/O him/O outside/O ,/O saddling/O the/O horses/O in/O the/O rain/O ,/O and/O tying/O his/O hands/O with/O a/O length/O of/O coarse/O rope/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O not/O truly/O afraid/O ./O 
They/O would/O never/O get/O him/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O he/O would/O have/O given/O odds/O on/O that/O ./O 
Riders/O would/O be/O after/O them/O within/O the/O day/O ,/O birds/O would/O take/O wing/O ,/O and/O surely/O one/O of/O the/O river/O lords/O would/O want/O to/O curry/O favor/O with/O his/O father/O enough/O to/O take/O a/O hand/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON was/O congratulating/O himself/O on/O his/O subtlety/O when/O someone/O pulled/O a/O hood/O down/O over/O his/O eyes/O and/O lifted/O him/O up/O onto/O a/O saddle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O set/O out/O through/O the/O rain/O at/O a/O hard/O gallop/O ,/O and/O before/O long/O Tyrion/O 's/O thighs/O were/O cramped/O and/O aching/O and/O his/O butt/O throbbed/O with/O pain/O ./O 
Even/O when/O they/O were/O safely/O away/O from/O the/O inn/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON slowed/O them/O to/O a/O trot/O ,/O it/O was/O a/O miserable/O pounding/O journey/O over/O rough/O ground/O ,/O made/O worse/O by/O his/O blindness/O ./O 
Every/O twist/O and/O turn/O put/O him/O in/O danger/O of/O falling/O off/O his/O horse/O ./O 
The/O hood/O muffled/O sound/O ,/O so/O he/O could/O not/O make/O out/O what/O was/O being/O said/O around/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O rain/O soaked/O through/O the/O cloth/O and/O made/O it/O cling/O to/O his/O face/O ,/O until/O even/O breathing/O was/O a/O struggle/O ./O 
The/O rope/O chafed/O his/O wrists/O raw/O and/O seemed/O to/O grow/O tighter/O as/O the/O night/O wore/O on/O ./O 
I/O was/O about/O to/O settle/O down/O to/O a/O warm/O fire/O and/O a/O roast/O fowl/O ,/O and/O that/O wretched/O singer/O had/O to/O open/O his/O mouth/O ,/O he/O thought/O mournfully/O ./O 
The/O wretched/O singer/O had/O come/O along/O with/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O a/O great/O song/O to/O be/O made/O from/O this/O ,/O and/O I/O 'm/O the/O one/O to/O make/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON when/O he/O announced/O his/O intention/O of/O riding/O with/O them/O to/O see/O how/O the/O \/O ``/O splendid/O adventure/O \/O ''/O turned/O out/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON wondered/O whether/O the/O boy/O would/O think/O the/O adventure/O quite/O so/O splendid/O once/O the/O Lannister/O riders/O caught/O up/O with/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rain/O had/O finally/O stopped/O and/O dawn/O light/O was/O seeping/O through/O the/O wet/O cloth/O over/O his/O eyes/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON gave/O the/O command/O to/O dismount/O ./O 
Rough/O hands/O pulled/O him/O down/O from/O his/O horse/O ,/O untied/O his/O wrists/O ,/O and/O yanked/O the/O hood/O off/O his/O head/O ./O 
When/O he/O saw/O the/O narrow/O stony/O road/O ,/O the/O foothills/O rising/O high/O and/O wild/O all/O around/O them/O ,/O and/O the/O jagged/O snowcapped/O peaks/O on/O the/O distant/O horizon/O ,/O all/O the/O hope/O went/O out/O of/O him/O in/O a/O rush/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O high/O road/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O gasped/O ,/O looking/O at/O Lady/O Stark/O with/O accusation/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O eastern/O road/O ./O 
You/O said/O we/O were/O riding/O for/O Winterfell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O favored/O him/O with/O the/O faintest/O of/O smiles/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Often/O and/O loudly/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O doubt/O your/O friends/O will/O ride/O that/O way/O when/O they/O come/O after/O us/O ./O 
I/O wish/O them/O good/O speed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Even/O now/O ,/O long/O days/O later/O ,/O the/O memory/O filled/O him/O with/O a/O bitter/O rage/O ./O 
All/O his/O life/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O prided/O himself/O on/O his/O cunning/O ,/O the/O only/O gift/O the/O gods/O had/O seen/O fit/O to/O give/O him/O ,/O and/O yet/O this/O seven/O -/O ''/O ,/O ``/O times-damned/O shewolf/O Catelyn/O Stark/O had/O outwitted/O him/O at/O every/O turn/O ./O 
The/O knowledge/O was/O more/O galling/O than/O the/O bare/O fact/O of/O his/O abduction/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O stopped/O only/O as/O long/O as/O it/O took/O to/O feed/O and/O water/O the/O horses/O ,/O and/O then/O they/O were/O off/O again/O ./O 
This/O time/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O spared/O the/O hood/O ./O 
After/O the/O second/O night/O they/O no/O longer/O bound/O his/O hands/O ,/O and/O once/O they/O had/O gained/O the/O heights/O they/O scarcely/O bothered/O to/O guard/O him/O at/O all/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O they/O did/O not/O fear/O his/O escape/O ./O 
And/O why/O should/O they/O ?/O 
Up/O here/O the/O land/O was/O harsh/O and/O wild/O ,/O and/O the/O high/O road/O little/O more/O than/O a/O stony/O track/O ./O 
If/O he/O did/O run/O ,/O how/O far/O could/O he/O hope/O to/O go/O ,/O alone/O and/O without/O provisions/O ?/O 
The/O shadowcats/O would/O make/O a/O morsel/O of/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O clans/O that/O dwelt/O in/O the/O mountain/O fastnesses/O were/O brigands/O and/O murderers/O who/O bowed/O to/O no/O law/O but/O the/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O still/O the/O Stark/O woman/O drove/O them/O forward/O relentlessly/O ./O 
He/O knew/O where/O they/O were/O bound/O ./O 
He/O had/O known/O it/O since/O the/O moment/O they/O pulled/O off/O his/O hood/O ./O 
These/O mountains/O were/O the/O domain/O of/O House/O Arryn/O ,/O and/O the/O late/O Hand/O 's/O widow/O was/O a/O Tully/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O sister/O .../O and/O no/O friend/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O known/O the/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON slightly/O during/O her/O years/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O and/O did/O not/O look/O forward/O to/O renewing/O the/O acquaintance/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O captors/O were/O clustered/O around/O a/O stream/O a/O short/O ways/O down/O the/O high/O road/O ./O 
The/O horses/O had/O drunk/O their/O fill/O of/O the/O icy/O cold/O water/O ,/O and/O were/O grazing/O on/O clumps/O of/O brown/O grass/O that/O grew/O from/O clefts/O in/O the/O rock/O ./O 
Jyck/PERSON and/O Morrec/PERSON huddled/O close/O ,/O sullen/O and/O miserable/O ./O 
Mohor/PERSON stood/O over/O them/O ,/O leaning/O on/O his/O spear/O and/O wearing/O a/O rounded/O iron/O cap/O that/O made/O him/O look/O as/O if/O he/O had/O a/O bowl/O on/O his/O head/O ./O 
Nearby/O ,/O Marillion/PERSON the/O singer/O sat/O oiling/O his/O woodharp/O ,/O complaining/O of/O what/O the/O damp/O was/O doing/O to/O his/O strings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O must/O have/O some/O rest/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O hedge/O knight/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON was/O saying/O to/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON as/O Tyrion/PERSON approached/O ./O 
He/O was/O Lady/PERSON Whent/PERSON 's/O man/O ,/O stiff-necked/O and/O stolid/O ,/O and/O the/O first/O to/O rise/O to/O aid/O Catelyn/O Stark/O back/O at/O the/O inn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON speaks/O truly/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O third/O horse/O we/O have/O lost/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O will/O lose/O more/O than/O horses/O if/O we/O 're/O overtaken/O by/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O reminded/O them/O ./O 
Her/O face/O was/O windburnt/O and/O gaunt/O ,/O but/O it/O had/O lost/O none/O of/O its/O determination/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Small/O chance/O of/O that/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O put/O in/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O lady/O did/O not/O ask/O your/O views/O ,/O dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O snapped/O Kurleket/PERSON ,/O a/O great/O fat/O oaf/O with/O short-cropped/O hair/O and/O a/O pig/O 's/O face/O ./O 
He/O was/O one/O of/O the/O Brackens/PERSON ,/O a/O man-at-arms/O in/O the/O service/O of/O Lord/O Jonos/PERSON ./O 
Tyrion/O had/O made/O a/O special/O effort/O to/O learn/O all/O their/O names/O ,/O so/O he/O might/O thank/O them/O later/O for/O their/O tender/O treatment/O of/O him/O ./O 
A/O Lannister/O always/O paid/O his/O debts/O ./O 
Kurleket/PERSON would/O learn/O that/O someday/O ,/O as/O would/O his/O friends/O Lharys/PERSON and/O Mohor/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O good/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O sellswords/O Bronn/LOCATION and/O Chiggen/LOCATION ./O 
He/O planned/O an/O especially/O sharp/O lesson/O for/O Marillion/O ,/O him/O of/O the/O woodharp/O and/O the/O sweet/O tenor/O voice/O ,/O who/O was/O struggling/O so/O manfully/O to/O rhyme/O imp/O with/O gimp/O and/O limp/O so/O he/O could/O make/O a/O song/O of/O this/O outrage/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O him/O speak/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON commanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O seated/O himself/O on/O a/O rock/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O now/O our/O pursuit/O is/O likely/O racing/O across/O the/O Neck/O ,/O chasing/O your/O lie/O up/O the/O kingsroad/O .../O assuming/O there/O is/O a/O pursuit/O ,/O which/O is/O by/O no/O means/O certain/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O no/O doubt/O the/O word/O has/O reached/O my/O father/O .../O but/O my/O father/O does/O not/O love/O me/O overmuch/O ,/O and/O I/O am/O not/O at/O all/O sure/O that/O he/O will/O bother/O to/O bestir/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O only/O half/O a/O lie/O ;/O Lord/O Tywin/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lannister/O cared/O not/O a/O fig/O for/O his/O deformed/O son/O ,/O but/O he/O tolerated/O no/O slights/O on/O the/O honor/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O a/O cruel/O land/O ,/O Lady/O Stark/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O find/O no/O succor/O until/O you/O reach/O the/O Vale/O ,/O and/O each/O mount/O you/O lose/O burdens/O the/O others/O all/O the/O more/O ./O 
Worse/O ,/O you/O risk/O losing/O me/O ./O 
I/O am/O small/O ,/O and/O not/O strong/O ,/O and/O if/O I/O die/O ,/O then/O what/O 's/O the/O point/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O That/O was/O no/O lie/O at/O all/O ;/O Tyrion/PERSON did/O not/O know/O how/O much/O longer/O he/O could/O endure/O this/O pace/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O might/O be/O said/O that/O your/O death/O is/O the/O point/O ,/O Lannister/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O think/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O wanted/O me/O dead/O ,/O you/O had/O only/O to/O say/O the/O word/O ,/O and/O one/O of/O these/O staunch/O friends/O of/O yours/O would/O gladly/O have/O given/O me/O a/O red/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O at/O Kurleket/LOCATION ,/O but/O the/O man/O was/O too/O dim/O to/O taste/O the/O mockery/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Starks/O do/O not/O murder/O men/O in/O their/O beds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O do/O I/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
-/O I/O tell/O you/O again/O ,/O I/O had/O no/O part/O in/O the/O attempt/O to/O kill/O your/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O assassin/O was/O armed/O with/O your/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O felt/O the/O heat/O rise/O in/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O my/O dagger/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O many/O times/O must/O I/O swear/O to/O that/O ?/O 
Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O whatever/O you/O may/O believe/O of/O me/O ,/O I/O am/O not/O a/O stupid/O man/O ./O 
Only/O a/O fool/O would/O arm/O a/O common/O footpad/O with/O his/O own/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Just/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O he/O thought/O he/O saw/O a/O flicker/O of/O doubt/O in/O her/O eyes/O ,/O but/O what/O she/O said/O was/O ,/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O Petyr/O lie/O to/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O does/O a/O bear/O shit/O in/O the/O woods/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O demanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Because/O it/O is/O his/O nature/O ./O 
Lying/O comes/O as/O easily/O as/O breathing/O to/O a/O man/O like/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
You/O ought/O to/O know/O that/O ,/O you/O of/O all/O people/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O took/O a/O step/O toward/O him/O ,/O her/O face/O tight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O does/O that/O mean/O ,/O Lannister/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O cocked/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O every/O man/O at/O court/O has/O heard/O him/O tell/O how/O he/O took/O your/O maidenhead/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O a/O lie/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O wicked/O little/O imp/O ,/O \/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON said/O ,/O shocked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Kurleket/PERSON drew/O his/O dirk/O ,/O a/O vicious/O piece/O of/O black/O iron/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O your/O word/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ,/O I/O 'll/O toss/O his/O lying/O tongue/O at/O your/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O pig/O eyes/O were/O wet/O with/O excitement/O at/O the/O prospect/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O stared/O at/O Tyrion/LOCATION with/O a/O coldness/O on/O her/O face/O such/O as/O he/O had/O never/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON loved/O me/O once/O ./O 
He/O was/O only/O a/O boy/O ./O 
His/O passion/O was/O a/O tragedy/O for/O all/O of/O us/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O real/O ,/O and/O pure/O ,/O and/O nothing/O to/O be/O made/O mock/O of/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O my/O hand/O ./O 
That/O is/O the/O truth/O of/O the/O matter/O ./O 
You/O are/O truly/O an/O evil/O man/O ,/O Lannister/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O are/O truly/O a/O fool/O ,/O Lady/O Stark/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON has/O never/O loved/O anyone/O but/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O and/O I/O promise/O you/O that/O it/O is/O not/O your/O hand/O that/O he/O boasts/O of/O ,/O it/O 's/O those/O ripe/O breasts/O of/O yours/O ,/O and/O that/O sweet/O mouth/O ,/O and/O the/O heat/O between/O your/O legs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Kurleket/PERSON grabbed/O a/O handful/O of/O hair/O and/O yanked/O his/O head/O back/O in/O a/O hard/O jerk/O ,/O baring/O his/O throat/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON felt/O the/O cold/O kiss/O of/O steel/O beneath/O his/O chin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shall/O I/O bleed/O him/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Kill/O me/O and/O the/O truth/O dies/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON gasped/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O him/O talk/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON commanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Kurleket/O let/O go/O of/O Tyrion/O '/O s/O hair/O ,/O reluctantly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O took/O a/O deep/O breath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O did/O Littlefinger/PERSON tell/O you/O I/O came/O by/O this/O dagger/O of/O his/O ?/O 
Answer/O me/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O won/O it/O from/O him/O in/O a/O wager/O ,/O during/O the/O tourney/O on/O Prince/LOCATION Joffrey/LOCATION 's/O name/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O my/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON was/O unhorsed/O by/O the/O Knight/PERSON of/PERSON Flowers/PERSON ,/O that/O was/O his/O story/O ,/O no/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O admitted/O ./O 
A/O line/O creased/O her/O brow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Riders/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O shriek/O came/O from/O the/O wind-carved/O ridge/O above/O them/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON had/O sent/O Lharys/PERSON scrambling/O up/O the/O rock/O face/O to/O watch/O the/O road/O while/O they/O took/O their/O rest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O a/O long/O second/O ,/O no/O one/O moved/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O the/O first/O to/O react/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON ,/O to/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O the/O other/O mounts/O behind/O us/O ./O 
Mohor/PERSON ,/O guard/O the/O prisoners/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Arm/O us/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O sprang/O to/O his/O feet/O and/O seized/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O need/O every/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O knew/O he/O was/O right/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O see/O it/O ./O 
The/O mountain/O clans/O cared/O nothing/O for/O the/O enmities/O of/O the/O great/O houses/O ;/O they/O would/O slaughter/O Stark/O and/O Lannister/O with/O equal/O fervor/O ,/O as/O they/O slaughtered/O each/O other/O ./O 
They/O might/O spare/O Catelyn/PERSON herself/O ;/O she/O was/O still/O young/O enough/O to/O bear/O sons/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O she/O hesitated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hear/O them/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON called/O out/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON turned/O his/O head/O to/O listen/O ,/O and/O there/O it/O was/O :/O hoofbeats/O ,/O a/O dozen/O horses/O or/O more/O ,/O coming/O nearer/O ./O 
Suddenly/O everyone/O was/O moving/O ,/O reaching/O for/O weapons/O ,/O running/O to/O their/O mounts/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pebbles/O rained/O down/O around/O them/O as/O Lharys/O came/O springing/O and/O sliding/O down/O the/O ridge/O ./O 
He/O landed/O breathless/O in/O front/O of/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ,/O an/O ungainly/O -/O looking/O man/O with/O wild/O tufts/O of/O rust/O -/O colored/O hair/O sticking/O out/O from/O under/O a/O conical/O steel/O cap/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Twenty/O men/O ,/O maybe/O twenty/O -/O five/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O breathless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Milk/O Snakes/O or/O Moon/O Brothers/O ,/O by/O my/O guess/O ./O 
They/O must/O have/O eyes/O out/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O .../O hidden/O watchers/O .../O they/O know/O we/O 're/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON was/O already/O ahorse/O ,/O a/O longsword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
Mohor/PERSON crouched/O behind/O a/O boulder/O ,/O both/O hands/O on/O his/O iron-tipped/O spear/O ,/O a/O dagger/O between/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ,/O singer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Help/O me/O with/O this/O breastplate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON sat/O frozen/O ,/O clutching/O his/O woodharp/O ,/O his/O face/O as/O pale/O as/O milk/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O man/O Morrec/PERSON bounded/O quickly/O to/O his/O feet/O and/O moved/O to/O help/O the/O knight/O with/O his/O armor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON kept/O his/O grip/O on/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O no/O choice/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O of/O us/O ,/O and/O a/O fourth/O man/O wasted/O guarding/O us/O .../O four/O men/O can/O be/O the/O difference/O between/O life/O and/O death/O up/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Give/O me/O your/O word/O that/O you/O will/O put/O down/O your/O swords/O again/O after/O the/O fight/O is/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O word/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O hoofbeats/O were/O louder/O now/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON grinned/O crookedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O that/O you/O have/O ,/O my/O lady/O .../O on/O my/O honor/O as/O a/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O he/O thought/O she/O would/O spit/O at/O him/O ,/O but/O instead/O she/O snapped/O ,/O \/O ``/O Arm/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O as/O quick/O as/O that/O she/O was/O pulling/O away/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tossed/O Jyck/PERSON his/O sword/O and/O scabbard/O ,/O and/O wheeled/O to/O meet/O the/O foe/O ./O 
Morrec/PERSON helped/O himself/O to/O a/O bow/O and/O quiver/O ,/O and/O went/O to/O one/O knee/O beside/O the/O road/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O better/O archer/O than/O swordsman/O ./O 
And/O Bronn/PERSON rode/O up/O to/O offer/O Tyrion/O a/O double/O -/O bladed/O axe/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O never/O fought/O with/O an/O axe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O weapon/O felt/O awkward/O and/O unfamiliar/O in/O his/O hands/O ./O 
It/O had/O a/O short/O haft/O ,/O a/O heavy/O head/O ,/O a/O nasty/O spike/O on/O top/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pretend/O you/O 're/O splitting/O logs/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O ,/O drawing/O his/O longsword/O from/O the/O scabbard/O across/O his/O back/O ./O 
He/O spat/O ,/O and/O trotted/O off/O to/O form/O up/O beside/O Chiggen/LOCATION and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON mounted/O up/O ''/O ,/O ``/O to/O join/O them/O ,/O fumbling/O with/O his/O helmet/O ,/O a/O metal/O pot/O with/O a/O thin/O slit/O for/O his/O eyes/O and/O a/O long/O black/O silk/O plume/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Logs/O do/O n't/O bleed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O to/O no/O one/O in/O particular/O ./O 
He/O felt/O naked/O without/O armor/O ./O 
He/O looked/O around/O for/O a/O rock/O and/O ran/O over/O to/O where/O Marillion/PERSON was/O hiding/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Move/O over/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O away/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O boy/O screamed/O back/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O a/O singer/O ,/O I/O want/O no/O part/O of/O this/O fight/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O ,/O lost/O your/O taste/O for/O adventure/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O kicked/O at/O the/O youth/O until/O he/O slid/O over/O ,/O and/O not/O a/O moment/O too/O soon/O ./O 
A/O heartbeat/O later/O ,/O the/O riders/O were/O on/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O were/O no/O heralds/O ,/O no/O banners/O ,/O no/O horns/O nor/O drums/O ,/O only/O the/O twang/O of/O bowstrings/O as/O Morrec/PERSON and/O Lharys/O let/O fly/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O the/O clansmen/O came/O thundering/O out/O of/O the/O dawn/O ,/O lean/O dark/O men/O in/O boiled/O leather/O and/O mismatched/O armor/O ,/O faces/O hidden/O behind/O barred/O halffielms/O ./O 
In/O gloved/O hands/O were/O clutched/O all/O manner/O of/O weapons/O :/O longswords/O and/O lances/O and/O sharpened/O scythes/O ,/O spiked/O clubs/O and/O daggers/O and/O heavy/O iron/O mauls/O ./O 
At/O their/O head/O rode/O a/O big/O man/O in/O a/O striped/O shadowskin/O cloak/O ,/O armed/O with/O a/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON shouted/O \/O ``/O Winterfell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O and/O rode/O to/O meet/O him/O ,/O with/O Bronn/PERSON and/O Chiggen/PERSON beside/O him/O ,/O screaming/O some/O wordless/O battle/O cry/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON followed/O ,/O swinging/O a/O spiked/O morningstar/O around/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Harrenhal/O !/O 
Harrenhal/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O sang/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON felt/O a/O sudden/O urge/O to/O leap/O up/O ,/O brandish/O his/O axe/O ,/O and/O boom/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O Caster/O ly/O Rock/O !/O 
\/O ''/O but/O the/O insanity/O passed/O quickly/O and/O he/O crouched/O down/O lower/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O heard/O the/O screams/O of/O frightened/O horses/O and/O the/O crash/O of/O metal/O on/O metal/O ./O 
Chiggen/PERSON 's/O sword/O raked/O across/O the/O naked/O face/O of/O a/O mailed/O rider/O ,/O and/O Bronn/PERSON plunged/O through/O the/O clansmen/O like/O a/O whirlwind/O ,/O cutting/O down/O foes/O right/O and/O left/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON hammered/O at/O the/O big/O man/O in/O the/O shadowskin/O cloak/O ,/O their/O horses/O dancing/O round/O each/O other/O as/O they/O traded/O blow/O for/O blow/O ./O 
Jyck/PERSON vaulted/O onto/O a/O horse/O and/O galloped/O bareback/O into/O the/O fray/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON saw/O an/O arrow/O sprout/O from/O the/O throat/O of/O the/O man/O in/O the/O shadowskin/O cloak/O ./O 
When/O he/O opened/O his/O mouth/O to/O scream/O ,/O only/O blood/O came/O out/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O he/O fell/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON was/O fighting/O someone/O else/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O Marillion/PERSON shrieked/O ,/O covering/O his/O head/O with/O his/O woodharp/O as/O a/O horse/O leapt/O over/O their/O rock/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON scrambled/O to/O his/O feet/O as/O the/O rider/O turned/O to/O come/O back/O at/O them/O ,/O hefting/O a/O spiked/O maul/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON swung/O his/O axe/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
The/O blade/O caught/O the/O charging/O horse/O in/O the/O throat/O with/O a/O meaty/O thunk/O ,/O angling/O upward/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON almost/O lost/O his/O grip/O as/O the/O animal/O screamed/O and/O collapsed/O ./O 
He/O managed/O to/O wrench/O the/O axe/O free/O and/O lurch/O clumsily/O out/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
Marillion/PERSON was/O less/O fortunate/O ./O 
Horse/O and/O rider/O crashed/O to/O the/O ground/O in/O a/O tangle/O on/O top/O of/O the/O singer/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON danced/O back/O in/O while/O the/O brigand/O 's/O leg/O was/O still/O pinned/O beneath/O his/O fallen/O mount/O ,/O and/O buried/O the/O axe/O in/O the/O man/O 's/O neck/O ,/O just/O above/O the/O shoulder/O blades/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O he/O struggled/O to/O yank/O the/O blade/O loose/O ,/O he/O heard/O Marillion/O moaning/O under/O the/O bodies/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Someone/O help/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O singer/O gasped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O I/O 'm/O bleeding/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O believe/O that/O 's/O horse/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O singer/O 's/O hand/O came/O crawling/O out/O from/O beneath/O the/O dead/O animal/O ,/O scrabbling/O in/O the/O dirt/O like/O a/O spider/O with/O five/O legs/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON put/O his/O heel/O on/O the/O grasping/O fingers/O and/O felt/O a/O satisfying/O crunch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Close/O your/O eyes/O and/O pretend/O you/O 're/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O advised/O the/O singer/O before/O he/O hefted/O the/O axe/O and/O turned/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O that/O ,/O things/O ran/O together/O ./O 
The/O dawn/O was/O full/O of/O shouts/O and/O screams/O and/O heavy/O with/O the/O scent/O of/O blood/O ,/O and/O the/O world/O had/O turned/O to/O chaos/O ./O 
Arrows/O hissed/O past/O his/O ear/O and/O clattered/O off/O the/O rocks/O ./O 
He/O saw/O Bronn/PERSON unhorsed/O ,/O fighting/O with/O a/O sword/O in/O each/O hand/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON kept/O on/O the/O fringes/O of/O the/O fight/O ,/O sliding/O from/O rock/O to/O rock/O and/O darting/O out/O of/O the/O shadows/O to/O hew/O at/O the/O legs/O of/O passing/O horses/O ./O 
He/O found/O a/O wounded/O clansman/O and/O left/O him/O dead/O ,/O helping/O himself/O to/O the/O man/O 's/O halfhelm/O ./O 
It/O fit/O too/O snugly/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O glad/O of/O any/O protection/O at/O all/O ./O 
Jyck/PERSON was/O cut/O down/O from/O behind/O while/O he/O sliced/O at/O a/O man/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ,/O and/O later/O Tyrion/PERSON stumbled/O over/O Kurleket/PERSON 's/O body/O ./O 
The/O pig/O face/O had/O been/O smashed/O in/O with/O a/O mace/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON recognized/O the/O dirk/O as/O he/O plucked/O it/O from/O the/O man/O 's/O dead/O fingers/O ./O 
He/O was/O sliding/O it/O through/O his/O belt/O when/O he/O heard/O a/O woman/O 's/O scream/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O was/O trapped/O against/O the/O stone/O face/O of/O the/O mountain/O with/O three/O men/O around/O her/O ,/O one/O still/O mounted/O and/O the/O other/O two/O on/O foot/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O dagger/O clutched/O awkwardly/O in/O her/O maimed/O hands/O ,/O but/O her/O back/O was/O to/O the/O rock/O now/O and/O they/O had/O penned/O her/O on/O three/O sides/O ./O 
Let/O them/O have/O the/O bitch/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O and/O welcome/O to/O her/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O he/O was/O moving/O ./O 
He/O caught/O the/O first/O man/O in/O the/O back/O of/O the/O knee/O before/O they/O even/O knew/O he/O was/O there/O ,/O and/O the/O heavy/O axehead/O split/O flesh/O and/O bone/O like/O rotten/O wood/O ./O 
Logs/O that/O bleed/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O inanely/O as/O the/O second/O man/O came/O for/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON ducked/O under/O his/O sword/O ,/O lashed/O out/O with/O the/O axe/O ,/O the/O man/O reeled/O backward/O .../O and/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON stepped/O up/O behind/O him/O and/O opened/O his/O throat/O ./O 
The/O horseman/O remembered/O an/O urgent/O engagement/O elsewhere/O and/O galloped/O off/O suddenly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O looked/O around/O ./O 
The/O enemy/O were/O all/O vanquished/O or/O vanished/O ./O 
Somehow/O the/O fighting/O had/O ended/O when/O he/O was/O n't/O looking/O ./O 
Dying/O horses/O and/O wounded/O men/O lay/O all/O around/O ,/O screaming/O or/O moaning/O ./O 
To/O his/O vast/O astonishment/O ,/O he/O was/O not/O one/O of/O them/O ./O 
He/O opened/O his/O fingers/O and/O let/O the/O axe/O thunk/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
His/O hands/O were/O sticky/O with/O blood/O ./O 
He/O could/O have/O sworn/O they/O had/O been/O fighting/O for/O half/O a/O day/O ,/O but/O the/O sun/O seemed/O scarcely/O to/O have/O moved/O at/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O first/O battle/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON asked/O later/O as/O he/O bent/O over/O Jyck/PERSON 's/O body/O ,/O pulling/O off/O his/O boots/O ./O 
They/O were/O good/O boots/O ,/O as/O befit/O one/O of/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O men/O ;/O heavy/O leather/O ,/O oiled/O and/O supple/O ,/O much/O finer/O than/O what/O Bronn/PERSON was/O wearing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O will/O be/O so/O proud/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
His/O legs/O were/O cramping/O so/O badly/O he/O could/O scarcely/O stand/O ./O 
Odd/O ,/O he/O had/O never/O once/O noticed/O the/O pain/O during/O the/O battle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O need/O a/O woman/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON said/O with/O a/O glint/O in/O his/O black/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O shoved/O the/O boots/O into/O his/O saddlebag/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nothing/O like/O a/O woman/O after/O a/O man/O 's/O been/O blooded/O ,/O take/O my/O word/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chiggen/PERSON stopped/O looting/O the/O corpses/O of/O the/O brigands/O long/O enough/O to/O snort/O and/O lick/O his/O lips/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O glanced/O over/O to/O where/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O dressing/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON 's/O wounds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O willing/O if/O she/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
The/O freeriders/O broke/O into/O laughter/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON grinned/O and/O thought/O ,/O There/O 's/O a/O start/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O he/O knelt/O by/O the/O stream/O and/O washed/O the/O blood/O off/O his/O face/O in/O water/O cold/O as/O ice/O ./O 
As/O he/O limped/O back/O to/O the/O others/O ,/O he/O glanced/O again/O at/O the/O slain/O ./O 
The/O dead/O clansmen/O were/O thin/O ,/O ragged/O men/O ,/O their/O horses/O scrawny/O and/O undersized/O ,/O with/O every/O rib/O showing/O ./O 
What/O weapons/O Bronn/LOCATION and/O Chiggen/PERSON had/O left/O them/O were/O none/O too/O impressive/O ./O 
Mauls/O ,/O clubs/O ,/O a/O scythe/O .../O He/O remembered/O the/O big/O man/O in/O the/O shadowskin/O cloak/O who/O had/O dueled/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON with/O a/O two-handed/O greatsword/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O found/O his/O corpse/O sprawled/O on/O the/O stony/O ground/O ,/O the/O man/O was/O not/O so/O big/O after/O all/O ,/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O cloak/O was/O gone/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON saw/O that/O the/O blade/O was/O badly/O notched/O ,/O its/O cheap/O steel/O spotted/O with/O rust/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O the/O clansmen/O had/O left/O nine/O bodies/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O only/O three/O dead/O ;/O two/O of/O Lord/O Bracken/PERSON 's/O men-at-arms/O ,/O Kurleket/PERSON and/O Mohor/PERSON ,/O and/O his/O own/O man/O Jyck/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O made/O such/O a/O bold/O show/O with/O his/O bareback/O charge/O ./O 
A/O fool/O to/O the/O end/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O I/O urge/O you/O to/O press/O on/O ,/O with/O all/O haste/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON said/O ,/O his/O eyes/O scanning/O the/O ridgetops/O warily/O through/O the/O slit/O in/O his/O helm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O drove/O them/O off/O for/O the/O moment/O ,/O but/O they/O will/O not/O have/O gone/O far/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O must/O bury/O our/O dead/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O were/O brave/O men/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O leave/O them/O to/O the/O crows/O and/O shadowcats/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O soil/O is/O too/O stony/O for/O digging/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O we/O shall/O gather/O stones/O for/O cairns/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gather/O all/O the/O stones/O you/O want/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON told/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O do/O it/O without/O me/O or/O Chiggen/LOCATION ./O 
I/O 've/O better/O things/O to/O do/O than/O pile/O rocks/O on/O dead/O men/O .../O breathing/O ,/O for/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O over/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O survivors/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Any/O of/O you/O who/O hope/O to/O be/O alive/O come/O nightfall/O ,/O ride/O with/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O I/O fear/O he/O speaks/O the/O truth/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O wearily/O ./O 
The/O old/O knight/O had/O been/O wounded/O in/O the/O fight/O ,/O a/O deep/O gash/O in/O his/O left/O arm/O and/O a/O spear/O thrust/O that/O grazed/O his/O neck/O ,/O and/O he/O sounded/O his/O age/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O linger/O here/O ,/O they/O will/O be/O on/O us/O again/O for/O a/O certainty/O ,/O and/O we/O may/O not/O live/O through/O a/O second/O attack/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O could/O see/O the/O anger/O in/O Catelyn/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O no/O choice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O the/O gods/O forgive/O us/O ,/O then/O ./O 
We/O will/O ride/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O shortage/O of/O horses/O now/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON moved/O his/O saddle/O to/O Jyck/PERSON 's/O spotted/O gelding/O ,/O who/O looked/O strong/O enough/O to/O last/O another/O three/O or/O four/O days/O at/O least/O ./O 
He/O was/O about/O to/O mount/O when/O Lharys/PERSON stepped/O up/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O take/O that/O dirk/O now/O ,/O dwarf/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O him/O keep/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON looked/O down/O from/O her/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O see/O that/O he/O has/O his/O axe/O back/O as/O well/O ./O 
We/O may/O have/O need/O of/O it/O if/O we/O are/O attacked/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O my/O thanks/O ,/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O mounting/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Save/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O curtly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O trust/O you/O no/O more/O than/O I/O did/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O was/O gone/O before/O he/O could/O frame/O a/O reply/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O adjusted/O his/O stolen/O helm/O and/O took/O the/O axe/O from/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
He/O remembered/O how/O he/O had/O begun/O the/O journey/O ,/O with/O his/O wrists/O bound/O and/O a/O hood/O pulled/O down/O over/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O decided/O that/O this/O was/O a/O definite/O improvement/O ./O 
Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON could/O keep/O her/O trust/O ;/O so/O long/O as/O he/O could/O keep/O the/O axe/O ,/O he/O would/O count/O himself/O ahead/O in/O the/O game/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON led/O them/O out/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON took/O the/O rear/O ,/O with/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON safely/O in/O the/O middle/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON a/O shadow/O beside/O her/O ./O 
Marillion/PERSON kept/O throwing/O sullen/O looks/O back/O at/O Tyrion/LOCATION as/O they/O rode/O ./O 
The/O singer/O had/O broken/O several/O ribs/O ,/O his/O woodharp/O ,/O and/O all/O four/O fingers/O on/O his/O playing/O hand/O ,/O yet/O the/O day/O had/O not/O been/O an/O utter/O loss/O to/O him/O ;/O somewhere/O he/O had/O acquired/O a/O magnificent/O shadowskin/O cloak/O ,/O thick/O black/O fur/O slashed/O by/O stripes/O of/O white/O ./O 
He/O huddled/O beneath/O its/O folds/O silently/O ,/O and/O for/O once/O had/O nothing/O to/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O heard/O the/O deep/O growls/O of/O shadowcats/O behind/O them/O before/O they/O had/O gone/O half/O a/O mile/O ,/O and/O later/O the/O wild/O snarling/O of/O the/O beasts/O fighting/O over/O the/O corpses/O they/O had/O left/O behind/O ./O 
Marillion/O grew/O visibly/O pale/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON trotted/O up/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Craven/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O rhymes/O nicely/O with/O raven/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O kicked/O his/O horse/O and/O moved/O past/O the/O singer/O ,/O up/O to/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON and/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O looked/O at/O him/O ,/O lips/O pressed/O tightly/O together/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O I/O was/O saying/O before/O we/O were/O so/O rudely/O interrupted/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O began/O ,/O \/O ``/O there/O is/O a/O serious/O flaw/O in/O Littlefinger/PERSON 's/O fable/O ./O 
Whatever/O you/O may/O believe/O of/O me/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O I/O promise/O you/O this/O -/O 1/O never/O bet/O against/O my/O family/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
