-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O were/O times-not/O many/O ,/O but/O a/O few-when/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON was/O glad/O he/O was/O a/O bastard/O ./O 
As/O he/O filled/O his/O wine/O cup/O once/O more/O from/O a/O passing/O flagon/O ,/O it/O struck/O him/O that/O this/O might/O be/O one/O of/O them/O ./O 
He/O settled/O back/O in/O his/O place/O on/O the/O bench/O among/O the/O younger/O squires/O and/O drank/O ./O 
The/O sweet/O ,/O fruity/O taste/O of/O summerwine/O filled/O his/O mouth/O and/O brought/O a/O smile/O to/O his/O lips/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Great/O Hall/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION was/O hazy/O with/O smoke/O and/O heavy/O with/O the/O smell/O of/O roasted/O meat/O and/O fresh-baked/O bread/O ./O 
Its/O grey/O stone/O walls/O were/O draped/O with/O banners/O ./O 
White/O ,/O gold/O ,/O crimson/O :/O the/O direwolf/O of/O Stark/O ,/O Baratheon/PERSON 's/O crowned/O stag/O ,/O the/O lion/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION ./O 
A/O singer/O was/O playing/O the/O high/O harp/O and/O reciting/O a/O ballad/O ,/O but/O down/O at/O this/O end/O of/O the/O hall/O his/O voice/O could/O scarcely/O be/O heard/O above/O the/O roar/O of/O the/O fire/O ,/O the/O clangor/O of/O pewter/O plates/O and/O cups/O ,/O and/O the/O low/O mutter/O of/O a/O hundred/O drunken/O conversations/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O fourth/O hour/O of/O the/O welcoming/O feast/O laid/O for/O the/O king/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON 's/O brothers/O and/O sisters/O had/O been/O seated/O with/O the/O royal/O children/O ,/O beneath/O the/O raised/O platform/O where/O Lord/O and/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON hosted/O the/O king/O and/O queen/O ./O 
In/O honor/O of/O the/O occasion/O ,/O his/O lord/O father/O would/O doubtless/O permit/O each/O child/O a/O glass/O of/O wine/O ,/O but/O no/O more/O than/O that/O ./O 
Down/O here/O on/O the/O benches/O ,/O there/O was/O no/O one/O to/O stop/O Jon/PERSON drinking/O as/O much/O as/O he/O had/O a/O thirst/O for/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O he/O was/O finding/O that/O he/O had/O a/O man/O 's/O thirst/O ,/O to/O the/O raucous/O delight/O of/O the/O youths/O around/O him/O ,/O who/O urged/O him/O on/O every/O time/O he/O drained/O a/O glass/O ./O 
They/O were/O fine/O company/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON relished/O the/O stories/O they/O were/O telling/O ,/O tales/O of/O battle/O and/O bedding/O and/O the/O hunt/O ./O 
He/O was/O certain/O that/O his/O companions/O were/O more/O entertaining/O than/O the/O king/O 's/O offspring/O ./O 
He/O had/O sated/O his/O curiosity/O about/O the/O visitors/O when/O they/O made/O their/O entrance/O ./O 
The/O procession/O had/O passed/O not/O a/O foot/O from/O the/O place/O he/O had/O been/O given/O on/O the/O bench/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON had/O gotten/O a/O good/O long/O look/O at/O them/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O lord/O father/O had/O come/O first/O ,/O escorting/O the/O queen/O ./O 
She/O was/O as/O beautiful/O as/O men/O said/O ./O 
A/O jeweled/O tiara/O gleamed/O amidst/O her/O long/O golden/O hair/O ,/O its/O emeralds/O a/O perfect/O match/O for/O the/O green/O of/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
His/O father/O helped/O her/O up/O the/O steps/O to/O the/O dais/O and/O led/O her/O to/O her/O seat/O ,/O but/O the/O queen/O never/O so/O much/O as/O looked/O at/O him/O ./O 
Even/O at/O fourteen/O ,/O Jon/PERSON could/O see/O through/O her/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Next/O had/O come/O King/O Robert/PERSON himself/O ,/O with/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON on/O his/O arm/O ./O 
The/O king/O was/O a/O great/O disappointment/O to/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
His/O father/O had/O talked/O of/O him/O often/O :/O the/O peerless/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O demon/O of/O the/O Trident/O ,/O the/O fiercest/O warrior/O of/O the/O realm/O ,/O a/O giant/O among/O princes/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON saw/O only/O a/O fat/O man/O ,/O red/O -/O faced/O under/O his/O beard/O ,/O sweating/O through/O his/O silks/O ./O 
He/O walked/O like/O a/O man/O half/O in/O his/O cups/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O them/O came/O the/O children/O ./O 
Little/O Rickon/PERSON first/O ,/O managing/O the/O long/O walk/O with/O all/O the/O dignity/O a/O three-year-old/O could/O muster/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O to/O urge/O him/O on/O when/O he/O stopped/O to/O visit/O ./O 
Close/O behind/O came/O Robb/PERSON ,/O in/O grey/O wool/O trimmed/O with/O white/O ,/O the/O Stark/O colors/O ./O 
He/O had/O the/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON on/O his/O arm/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O wisp/O of/O a/O girl/O ,/O not/O quite/O eight/O ,/O her/O hair/O a/O cascade/O of/O golden/O curls/O under/O a/O jeweled/O net/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON noticed/O the/O shy/O looks/O she/O gave/O Robb/PERSON as/O they/O passed/O between/O the/O tables/O and/O the/O timid/O way/O she/O smiled/O at/O him/O ./O 
He/O decided/O she/O was/O insipid/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON did/O n't/O even/O have/O the/O sense/O to/O realize/O how/O stupid/O she/O was/O ;/O he/O was/O grinning/O like/O a/O fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O half/O sisters/O escorted/O the/O royal/O princes/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O paired/O with/O plump/O young/O Tommen/PERSON ,/O whose/O white-blond/O hair/O was/O longer/O than/O hers/O ./O 
Sansa/O ,/O two/O years/O older/O ,/O drew/O the/O crown/O prince/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON ''/O ,/O ``/O Baratheon/O ./O 
He/O was/O twelve/O ,/O younger/O than/O Jon/PERSON or/O Robb/PERSON ,/O but/O taller/O than/O either/O ,/O to/O Jon/PERSON 's/O vast/O dismay/O ./O 
Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON had/O his/O sister/O 's/O hair/O and/O his/O mother/O 's/O deep/O green/O eyes/O ./O 
A/O thick/O tangle/O of/O blond/O curls/O dripped/O down/O past/O his/O golden/O choker/O and/O high/O velvet/O collar/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON looked/O radiant/O as/O she/O walked/O beside/O him/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O like/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O pouty/O lips/O or/O the/O bored/O ,/O disdainful/O way/O he/O looked/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O more/O interested/O in/O the/O pair/O that/O came/O behind/O him/O :/O the/O queen/O 's/O brothers/O ,/O the/O Lannisters/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O 
The/O Lion/O and/O the/O Imp/O ;/O there/O was/O no/O mistaking/O which/O was/O which/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O twin/O to/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON ;/O tall/O and/O golden/O ,/O with/O flashing/O green/O eyes/O and/O a/O smile/O that/O cut/O like/O a/O knife/O ./O 
He/O wore/O crimson/O silk/O ,/O high/O black/O boots/O ,/O a/O black/O satin/O cloak/O ./O 
On/O the/O breast/O of/O his/O tunic/O ,/O the/O lion/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION was/O embroidered/O in/O gold/O thread/O ,/O roaring/O its/O defiance/O ./O 
They/O called/O him/O the/O Lion/O of/O Lannister/O to/O his/O face/O and/O whispered/O \/O ``/O Kings/O layer/O \/O ''/O behind/O his/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON found/O it/O hard/O to/O look/O away/O from/O him/O ./O 
This/O is/O what/O a/O king/O should/O look/O like/O ,/O he/O thought/O to/O himself/O as/O the/O man/O passed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O he/O saw/O the/O other/O one/O ,/O waddling/O along/O half-hidden/O by/O his/O brother/O 's/O side/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O the/O youngest/O of/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O brood/O and/O by/O far/O the/O ugliest/O ./O 
All/O that/O the/O gods/O had/O given/O to/O Cersei/LOCATION and/O Jaime/PERSON ,/O they/O had/O denied/O Tyrion/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O dwarf/O ,/O half/O his/O brother/O 's/O height/O ,/O struggling/O to/O keep/O pace/O on/O stunted/O legs/O ./O 
His/O head/O was/O too/O large/O for/O his/O body/O ,/O with/O a/O brute/O 's/O squashed-in/O face/O beneath/O a/O swollen/O shelf/O of/O brow/O ./O 
One/O green/O eye/O and/O one/O black/O one/O peered/O out/O from/O under/O a/O lank/O fall/O of/O hair/O so/O blond/O it/O seemed/O white/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON watched/O him/O with/O fascination/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O last/O of/O the/O high/O lords/O to/O enter/O were/O his/O uncle/O ,/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O 's/O ward/O ,/O young/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ./O 
Benjen/PERSON gave/O Jon/PERSON a/O warm/O smile/O as/O he/O went/O by/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON ignored/O him/O utterly/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O nothing/O new/O in/O that/O ./O 
After/O all/O had/O been/O seated/O ,/O toasts/O were/O made/O ,/O thanks/O were/O given/O and/O returned/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O feasting/O began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O started/O drinking/O then/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O not/O stopped/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Something/O rubbed/O against/O his/O leg/O beneath/O the/O table/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON saw/O red/O eyes/O staring/O up/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hungry/O again/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
There/O was/O still/O half/O a/O honeyed/O chicken/O in/O the/O center/O of/O the/O table/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON reached/O out/O to/O tear/O off/O a/O leg/O ,/O then/O had/O a/O better/O idea/O ./O 
He/O knifed/O the/O bird/O whole/O and/O let/O the/O carcass/O slide/O to/O the/O floor/O between/O his/O legs/O ./O 
Ghost/O ripped/O into/O it/O in/O savage/O silence/O ./O 
His/O brothers/O and/O sisters/O had/O not/O been/O permitted/O to/O bring/O their/O wolves/O to/O the/O banquet/O ,/O but/O there/O were/O more/O curs/O than/O Jon/PERSON could/O count/O at/O this/O end/O of/O the/O hall/O ,/O and/O no/O one/O had/O said/O a/O word/O about/O his/O pup/O ./O 
He/O told/O himself/O he/O was/O fortunate/O in/O that/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O stung/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON rubbed/O at/O them/O savagely/O ,/O cursing/O the/O smoke/O ./O 
He/O swallowed/O another/O gulp/O of/O wine/O and/O watched/O his/O direwo/O If/O devour/O the/O chicken/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dogs/O moved/O between/O the/O tables/O ,/O trailing/O after/O the/O serving/O girls/O ./O 
One/O of/O them/O ,/O a/O black/O mongrel/O bitch/O with/O long/O yellow/O eyes/O ,/O caught/O a/O scent/O of/O the/O chicken/O ./O 
She/O stopped/O and/O edged/O under/O the/O bench/O to/O get/O a/O share/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON watched/O the/O confrontation/O ./O 
The/O bitch/O growled/O low/O in/O her/O throat/O and/O moved/O closer/O ./O 
Ghost/O looked/O up/O ,/O silent/O ,/O and/O fixed/O the/O dog/O with/O those/O hot/O red/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O bitch/O snapped/O an/O angry/O challenge/O ./O 
She/O was/O three/O times/O the/O size/O of/O the/O direwolf/O pup/O ./O 
Ghost/O did/O not/O move/O ./O 
He/O stood/O over/O his/O prize/O and/O opened/O his/O mouth/O ,/O baring/O his/O fangs/O ./O 
The/O bitch/O tensed/O ,/O barked/O ''/O ,/O ``/O again/O ,/O then/O thought/O better/O of/O this/O fight/O ./O 
She/O turned/O and/O slunk/O away/O ,/O with/O one/O last/O defiant/O snap/O to/O save/O her/O pride/O ./O 
Ghost/O went/O back/O to/O his/O meal/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON grinned/O and/O reached/O under/O the/O table/O to/O ruffle/O the/O shaggy/O white/O fur/O ./O 
The/O direwo/O If/O looked/O up/O at/O him/O ,/O nipped/O gently/O at/O his/O hand/O ,/O then/O went/O back/O to/O eating/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O this/O one/O of/O the/O direwolves/O I/O 've/O heard/O so/O much/O of/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O a/O familiar/O voice/O asked/O close/O at/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON looked/O up/O happily/O as/O his/O uncle/O Ben/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O head/O and/O ruffled/O his/O hair/O much/O as/O Jon/PERSON had/O ruffled/O the/O wolfs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O name/O is/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O squires/O interrupted/O the/O bawdy/O story/O he/O 'd/O been/O telling/O to/O make/O room/O at/O the/O table/O for/O their/O lord/O 's/O brother/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON straddled/O the/O bench/O with/O ,/O long/O legs/O and/O took/O the/O wine/O cup/O out/O of/O Jon/PERSON 's/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Summerwine/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O after/O a/O taste/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nothing/O so/O sweet/O ./O 
How/O many/O cups/O have/O you/O had/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON smiled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O I/O feared/O ./O 
Ah/O ,/O well/O ./O 
I/O believe/O I/O was/O younger/O than/O you/O the/O first/O time/O I/O got/O truly/O and/O sincerely/O drunk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O snagged/O a/O roasted/O onion/O ,/O dripping/O brown/O with/O gravy/O ,/O from/O a/O nearby/O trencher/O and/O bit/O into/O it/O ./O 
It/O crunched/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O uncle/O was/O sharp/O -/O featured/O and/O gaunt/O as/O a/O mountain/O crag/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O always/O a/O hint/O of/O laughter/O in/O his/O blue-grey/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O dressed/O in/O black/O ,/O as/O befitted/O a/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
Tonight/O it/O was/O rich/O black/O velvet/O ,/O with/O high/O leather/O boots/O and/O a/O wide/O belt/O with/O a/O silver/O buckle/O ./O 
A/O heavy/O silver/O chain/O was/O looped/O round/O his/O neck/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON watched/O Ghost/O with/O amusement/O as/O he/O ate/O his/O onion/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O very/O quiet/O wolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O observed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O not/O like/O the/O others/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O never/O makes/O a/O sound/O ./O 
That/O 's/O why/O I/O named/O him/O Ghost/O ./O 
That/O ,/O and/O because/O he/O 's/O white/O ./O 
The/O others/O are/O all/O dark/O ,/O grey/O or/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O still/O direwolves/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
We/O hear/O them/O on/O our/O rangings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON gave/O Jon/PERSON a/O long/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O you/O usually/O eat/O at/O table/O with/O your/O brothers/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Most/O times/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON answered/O in/O a/O flat/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O tonight/O Lady/O Stark/O thought/O it/O might/O give/O insult/O to/O the/O royal/O family/O to/O seat/O a/O bastard/O among/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O uncle/O glanced/O over/O his/O shoulder/O at/O the/O raised/O table/O at/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O hall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O does/O not/O seem/O very/O festive/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O noticed/O that/O too/O ./O 
A/O bastard/O had/O to/O learn/O to/O notice/O things/O ,/O to/O read/O the/O truth/O that/O people/O hid/O behind/O their/O eyes/O ./O 
His/O father/O was/O observing/O all/O the/O courtesies/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O tightness/O in/O him/O that/O Jon/PERSON had/O seldom/O seen/O before/O ./O 
He/O said/O little/O ,/O looking/O out/O over/O the/O hall/O with/O hooded/O eyes/O ,/O seeing/O nothing/O ./O 
Two/O seats/O away/O ,/O the/O king/O had/O been/O drinking/O heavily/O all/O night/O ./O 
His/O broad/O face/O was/O flushed/O behind/O his/O great/O black/O beard/O ./O 
He/O made/O many/O a/O toast/O ,/O laughed/O loudly/O at/O every/O jest/O ,/O and/O attacked/O each/O dish/O like/O a/O starving/O man/O ,/O but/O beside/O him/O the/O queen/O seemed/O as/O cold/O as/O an/O ice/O sculpture/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O queen/O is/O angry/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O his/O uncle/O in/O a/O low/O ,/O quiet/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O took/O the/O king/O down/O to/O the/O crypts/O this/O afternoon/O ./O 
The/O queen/O did/O n't/O want/O him/O to/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Benjen/PERSON gave/O Jon/PERSON a/O careful/O ,/O measuring/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O miss/O much/O ,/O do/O you/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
We/O could/O use/O a/O man/O like/O you/O on/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON swelled/O with/O pride/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON is/O a/O stronger/O lance/O than/O I/O am/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O the/O better/O sword/O ,/O and/O Hullen/PERSON says/O I/O sit/O a/O horse/O as/O well/O as/O anyone/O in/O the/O castle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Notable/O achievements/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O me/O with/O you/O when/O you/O go/O back/O to/O the/O Wall/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O in/O a/O sudden/O rush/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O will/O give/O me/O leave/O to/O go/O if/O you/O ask/O him/O ,/O I/O know/O he/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Uncle/O Benjen/PERSON studied/O his/O face/O carefully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Wall/O is/O a/O hard/O place/O for/O a/O boy/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON protested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O turn/O fifteen/O on/O my/O next/O name/O day/O ,/O and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON says/O bastards/O grow/O up/O faster/O than/O other/O children/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O true/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Benjen/PERSON said/O with/O a/O downward/O twist/O of/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
He/O took/O Jon/PERSON 's/O cup/O from/O the/O table/O ,/O filled/O it/O fresh/O from/O a/O nearby/O pitcher/O ,/O and/O drank/O down/O a/O long/O swallow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Daeren/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON was/O only/O fourteen/O when/O he/O conquered/O Dome/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O Young/PERSON Dragon/PERSON was/O one/O of/O his/O heroes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O conquest/O that/O lasted/O a/O summer/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O uncle/O pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Boy/O King/PERSON lost/O ten/O thousand/O men/O taking/O the/O place/O ,/O and/O another/O fifty/O trying/O to/O hold/O it/O ./O 
Someone/O should/O have/O told/O him/O that/O war/O is/O n't/O a/O game/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O another/O sip/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Also/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O wiping/O his/O mouth/O ,/O \/O ``/O Daeren/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON was/O only/O eighteen/O when/O he/O died/O ./O 
Or/O have/O you/O forgotten/O that/O part/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O forget/O nothing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON boasted/O ./O 
The/O wine/O was/O making/O him/O bold/O ./O 
He/O tried/O to/O sit/O very/O straight/O ,/O to/O make/O himself/O seem/O taller/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O serve/O in/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O Uncle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O had/O thought/O on/O it/O long/O and/O hard/O ,/O lying/O abed/O at/O night/O while/O his/O brothers/O slept/O around/O him/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON would/O someday/O inherit/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O would/O command/O great/O armies/O as/O the/O Warden/O of/O the/O North/O ./O 
Bran/O and/O Rickon/PERSON would/O be/O Robb/PERSON 's/O bannermen/O and/O rule/O holdfasts/O in/O his/O name/O ./O 
His/O sisters/O Arya/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON would/O marry/O the/O heirs/O of/O other/O great/O houses/O and/O go/O south/O as/O mistress/O of/O castles/O of/O their/O own/O ./O 
But/O what/O place/O could/O a/O bastard/O hope/O to/O earn/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O you/O 're/O asking/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O a/O sworn/O brotherhood/O ./O 
We/O have/O no/O families/O ./O 
None/O of/O us/O will/O ever/O father/O sons/O ./O 
Our/O wife/O is/O duty/O ./O 
Our/O mistress/O is/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O bastard/O can/O have/O honor/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O ready/O to/O swear/O your/O oath/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O boy/O of/O fourteen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Benjen/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O a/O man/O ,/O not/O yet/O ./O 
Until/O you/O have/O known/O a/O woman/O ,/O you/O can/O not/O understand/O what/O you/O would/O be/O giving/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O about/O that/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O hotly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O might/O ,/O if/O you/O knew/O what/O it/O meant/O ,/O \/O ''/O Benjen/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O knew/O what/O the/O oath/O would/O cost/O you/O ,/O you/O might/O be/O less/O eager/O to/O pay/O the/O price/O ,/O son/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON felt/O anger/O rise/O inside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O your/O son/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Benjen/O Stark/O stood/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O More/O 's/O the/O pity/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O put/O a/O hand/O on/O Jon/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O back/O to/O me/O after/O you/O 've/O fathered/O a/O few/O bastards/O of/O your/O own/O ,/O and/O we/O 'll/O see/O how/O you/O feel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON trembled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O never/O father/O a/O bastard/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O carefully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Never/O !/O 
\/O ''/O He/O spat/O it/O out/O like/O venom/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O he/O realized/O that/O the/O table/O had/O fallen/O silent/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O all/O looking/O at/O him/O ./O 
He/O felt/O the/O tears/O begin/O to/O well/O behind/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O pushed/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O must/O be/O excused/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O with/O the/O last/O of/O his/O dignity/O ./O 
He/O whirled/O and/O bolted/O before/O they/O could/O see/O him/O cry/O ./O 
He/O must/O have/O drunk/O more/O wine/O than/O he/O had/O realized/O ./O 
His/O feet/O got/O tangled/O under/O him/O as/O he/O tried/O to/O leave/O ,/O and/O he/O lurched/O sideways/O into/O a/O serving/O girl/O and/O sent/O a/O flagon/O of/O spiced/O wine/O crashing/O to/O the/O floor/O ./O 
Laughter/O boomed/O all/O around/O him/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON felt/O hot/O tears/O on/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O cheeks/O ./O 
Someone/O tried/O to/O steady/O him/O ./O 
He/O wrenched/O free/O of/O their/O grip/O and/O ran/O ,/O half-blind/O ,/O for/O the/O door/O ./O 
Ghost/O followed/O close/O at/O his/O heels/O ,/O out/O into/O the/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O yard/O was/O quiet/O and/O empty/O ./O 
A/O lone/O sentry/O stood/O high/O on/O the/O battlements/O of/O the/O inner/O wall/O ,/O his/O cloak/O pulled/O tight/O around/O him/O against/O the/O cold/O ./O 
He/O looked/O bored/O and/O miserable/O as/O he/O huddled/O there/O alone/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON would/O have/O traded/O places/O with/O him/O in/O an/O instant/O ./O 
Otherwise/O the/O castle/O was/O dark/O and/O deserted/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O seen/O an/O abandoned/O holdfast/O once/O ,/O a/O drear/O place/O where/O nothing/O moved/O but/O the/O wind/O and/O the/O stones/O kept/O silent/O about/O whatever/O people/O had/O lived/O there/O ./O 
Winterfell/PERSON reminded/O him/O of/O that/O tonight/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sounds/O of/O music/O and/O song/O spilled/O through/O the/O open/O windows/O behind/O him/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O last/O things/O Jon/PERSON wanted/O to/O hear/O ./O 
He/O wiped/O away/O his/O tears/O on/O the/O sleeve/O of/O his/O shirt/O ,/O furious/O that/O he/O had/O let/O them/O fall/O ,/O and/O turned/O to/O go/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O called/O out/O to/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON turned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O was/O sitting/O on/O the/O ledge/O above/O the/O door/O to/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O looking/O for/O all/O the/O world/O like/O a/O gargoyle/O ./O 
The/O dwarf/O grinned/O down/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O animal/O a/O wolf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O direwolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O name/O is/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stared/O up/O at/O the/O little/O man/O ,/O his/O disappointment/O suddenly/O forgotten/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O doing/O up/O there/O ?/O 
Why/O are/O n't/O you/O at/O the/O feast/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Too/O hot/O ,/O too/O noisy/O ,/O and/O I/O 'd/O drunk/O too/O much/O wine/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O learned/O long/O ago/O that/O it/O is/O considered/O rude/O to/O vomit/O on/O your/O brother/O ./O 
Might/O I/O have/O a/O closer/O look/O at/O your/O wolf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON hesitated/O ,/O then/O nodded/O slowly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O you/O climb/O down/O ,/O or/O shall/O I/O bring/O a/O ladder/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O bleed/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O little/O man/O said/O ./O 
He/O pushed/O himself/O off/O the/O ledge/O into/O empty/O air/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON gasped/O ,/O then/O watched/O with/O awe/O as/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O spun/O around/O in/O a/O tight/O ball/O ,/O landed/O lightly/O on/O his/O hands/O ,/O then/O vaulted/O backward/O onto/O his/O legs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O backed/O away/O from/O him/O uncertainly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O dusted/O himself/O off/O and/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O believe/O I/O 've/O frightened/O your/O wolf/O ./O 
My/O apologies/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O not/O scared/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O knelt/O and/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O ,/O come/O here/O ./O 
Come/O on/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wolf/O pup/O padded/O closer/O and/O nuzzled/O at/O Jon/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O but/O he/O kept/O a/O wary/O eye/O on/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O and/O when/O the/O dwarf/O reached/O out/O to/O pet/O him/O ,/O he/O drew/O back/O and/O bared/O his/O fangs/O in/O a/O silent/O snarl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shy/O ,/O is/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON observed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sit/O ,/O Ghost/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON commanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
Keep/O still/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O up/O at/O the/O dwarf/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O can/O touch/O him/O now/O ./O 
He/O wo/O n't/O move/O until/O I/O tell/O him/O to/O ./O 
I/O 've/O been/O training/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O ruffled/O the/O snow-white/O fur/O between/O Ghost/O 's/O ears/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Nice/O wolf/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O I/O was/O n't/O here/O ,/O he/O 'd/O tear/O out/O your/O throat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
It/O was/O n't/O actually/O true/O yet/O ,/O but/O it/O would/O be/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O that/O case/O ,/O you/O had/O best/O stay/O close/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O said/O ./O 
He/O cocked/O his/O oversized/O head/O to/O one/O side/O and/O looked/O Jon/PERSON over/O with/O his/O mismatched/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O rose/O ./O 
Standing/O ,/O he/O was/O taller/O than/O the/O dwarf/O ./O 
It/O made/O him/O feel/O strange/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O bastard/O ,/O are/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON felt/O a/O coldness/O pass/O right/O through/O him/O ./O 
He/O pressed/O his/O lips/O together/O and/O said/O nothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O I/O offend/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sorry/O ./O 
Dwarfs/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O be/O tactful/O ./O 
Generations/O of/O capering/O fools/O in/O motley/O have/O won/O me/O the/O right/O to/O dress/O badly/O and/O say/O any/O damn/O thing/O that/O comes/O into/O my/O head/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O bastard/O ,/O though/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/O Stark/O is/O my/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON admitted/O stiffly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lannister/PERSON studied/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O see/O it/O ./O 
You/O have/O more/O of/O the/O north/O in/O you/O than/O your/O brothers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Half/O brothers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON corrected/O ./O 
He/O was/O pleased/O by/O the/O dwarfs/O comment/O ,/O but/O he/O tried/O not/O to/O let/O it/O show/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O me/O give/O you/O some/O counsel/O ,/O bastard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Never/O forget/O what/O you/O are/O ,/O for/O surely/O the/O world/O will/O not/O ./O 
Make/O it/O your/O strength/O ./O 
Then/O it/O can/O never/O be/O your/O weakness/O ./O 
Armor/O yourself/O in/O it/O ,/O and/O it/O will/O never/O be/O used/O to/O hurt/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O in/O no/O mood/O for/O anyone/O 's/O counsel/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O know/O about/O being/O a/O bastard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O dwarfs/O are/O bastards/O in/O their/O father/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O your/O mother/O 's/O trueborn/O son/O of/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Am/O I/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O replied/O ,/O sardonic/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O tell/O my/O lord/O father/O ./O 
MY/O mother/O died/O birthing/O me/O ,/O and/O he/O 's/O never/O been/O sure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O even/O know/O who/O my/O mother/O was/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Some/O woman/O ,/O no/O doubt/O ./O 
Most/O of/O them/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O favored/O Jon/PERSON with/O a/O rueful/O grin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O this/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
All/O dwarfs/O may/O be/O bastards/O ,/O yet/O not/O all/O bastards/O need/O be/O dwarfs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O with/O that/O he/O turned/O and/O sauntered/O back/O into/O the/O feast/O ,/O whistling/O a/O tune/O ./O 
When/O he/O opened/O the/O door/O ,/O the/O light/O from/O within/O threw/O his/O shadow/O clear/O across/O the/O yard/O ,/O and/O for/O just/O a/O moment/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON stood/O tall/O as/O a/O king/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
