-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O In/O the/O tower/O room/O at/O the/O heart/O of/O Maegor/LOCATION 's/O Holdfast/LOCATION ,/O Sansa/PERSON gave/O herself/O to/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
She/O drew/O the/O curtains/O around/O her/O bed/O ,/O slept/O ,/O woke/O weeping/O ,/O and/O slept/O again/O ./O 
When/O she/O could/O not/O sleep/O she/O lay/O under/O her/O blankets/O shivering/O with/O grief/O ./O 
Servants/O came/O and/O went/O ,/O bringing/O meals/O ,/O but/O the/O sight/O of/O food/O was/O more/O than/O she/O could/O bear/O ./O 
The/O dishes/O piled/O up/O on/O the/O table/O beneath/O her/O window/O ,/O untouched/O and/O spoiling/O ,/O until/O the/O servants/O took/O them/O away/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sometimes/O her/O sleep/O was/O leaden/O and/O dreamless/O ,/O and/O she/O woke/O from/O it/O more/O tired/O than/O when/O she/O had/O closed/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Yet/O those/O were/O the/O best/O times/O ,/O for/O when/O she/O dreamed/O ,/O she/O dreamed/O of/O Father/O ./O 
Waking/O or/O sleeping/O ,/O she/O saw/O him/O ,/O saw/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O fling/O him/O down/O ,/O saw/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON striding/O forward/O ,/O unsheathing/O Ice/O from/O the/O scabbard/O on/O his/O back/O ,/O saw/O the/O moment/O .../O the/O moment/O when/O .../O she/O had/O wanted/O to/O look/O away/O ,/O she/O had/O wanted/O to/O ,/O her/O legs/O had/O gone/O out/O from/O under/O her/O and/O she/O had/O fallen/O to/O her/O knees/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O she/O could/O not/O turn/O her/O head/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O people/O were/O screaming/O and/O shouting/O ,/O and/O her/O prince/O had/O smiled/O at/O her/O ,/O he/O 'd/O smiled/O and/O she/O 'd/O felt/O safe/O ,/O but/O only/O for/O a/O heartbeat/O ,/O until/O he/O said/O those/O words/O ,/O and/O her/O father/O 's/O legs/O .../O that/O was/O what/O she/O remembered/O ,/O his/O legs/O ,/O the/O way/O they/O 'd/O jerked/O when/O Ser/O Ilyn/O .../O when/O the/O sword/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Perhaps/O I/O will/O die/O too/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O and/O the/O thought/O did/O not/O seem/O so/O terrible/O to/O her/O ./O 
If/O she/O flung/O herself/O from/O the/O window/O ,/O she/O could/O put/O an/O end/O to/O her/O suffering/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O years/O to/O come/O the/O singers/O would/O write/O songs/O of/O her/O grief/O ./O 
Her/O body/O would/O lie/O on/O the/O stones/O below/O ,/O broken/O and/O innocent/O ,/O shaming/O all/O those/O who/O had/O betrayed/O her/O ./O 
Sansa/O went/O so/O far/O as/O to/O cross/O the/O bedchamber/O and/O throw/O open/O the/O shutters/O .../O but/O then/O her/O courage/O left/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O ran/O back/O to/O her/O bed/O ,/O sobbing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O serving/O girls/O tried/O to/O talk/O to/O her/O when/O they/O brought/O her/O meals/O ,/O but/O she/O never/O answered/O them/O ./O 
Once/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O came/O with/O a/O box/O of/O flasks/O and/O bottles/O ,/O to/O ask/O if/O she/O was/O ill/O ./O 
He/O felt/O her/O brow/O ,/O made/O her/O undress/O ,/O and/O touched/O her/O all/O over/O while/O her/O bedmaid/O held/O her/O down/O ./O 
When/O he/O left/O he/O gave/O her/O a/O potion/O of/O honeywater/O and/O herbs/O and/O told/O her/O to/O drink/O a/O swallow/O every/O night/O ./O 
She/O drank/O it/O all/O right/O then/O and/O went/O back/O to/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O dreamt/O of/O footsteps/O on/O the/O tower/O stair/O ,/O an/O ominous/O scraping/O of/O leather/O on/O stone/O as/O a/O man/O climbed/O slowly/O toward/O her/O bedchamber/O ,/O step/O by/O step/O ./O 
All/O she/O could/O do/O was/O huddle/O behind/O her/O door/O and/O listen/O ,/O trembling/O ,/O as/O he/O came/O closer/O and/O closer/O ./O 
It/O was/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O coming/O for/O her/O with/O Ice/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O coming/O to/O take/O her/O head/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O place/O to/O run/O ,/O no/O place/O to/O hide/O ,/O no/O way/O to/O bar/O the/O door/O ./O 
Finally/O the/O footsteps/O stopped/O and/O she/O knew/O he/O was/O just/O outside/O ,/O standing/O there/O silent/O with/O his/O dead/O eyes/O and/O his/O long/O pocked/O face/O ./O 
That/O was/O when/O she/O realized/O she/O was/O naked/O ./O 
She/O crouched/O down/O ,/O trying/O to/O cover/O herself/O with/O her/O hands/O ,/O as/O her/O door/O began/O to/O swing/O open/O ,/O creaking/O ,/O the/O point/O of/O the/O greatsword/O poking/O through/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O woke/O murmuring/O ,/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O please/O ,/O I/O 'll/O be/O good/O ,/O I/O 'll/O be/O good/O ,/O please/O do/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O but/O there/O was/O no/O one/O to/O hear/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O they/O finally/O came/O for/O her/O in/O truth/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON never/O heard/O their/O footsteps/O ./O 
It/O was/O Joffrey/PERSON who/O opened/O her/O door/O ,/O not/O Ser/O Ilyn/O but/O the/O boy/O who/O had/O been/O her/O prince/O ./O 
She/O was/O in/O bed/O ,/O curled/O up/O tight/O ,/O her/O curtains/O drawn/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O not/O have/O said/O if/O it/O was/O noon/O or/O midnight/O ./O 
The/O first/O thing/O ''/O ,/O ``/O she/O heard/O was/O the/O slam/O of/O the/O door/O ./O 
Then/O her/O bed/O hangings/O were/O yanked/O back/O ,/O and/O she/O threw/O up/O a/O hand/O against/O the/O sudden/O light/O and/O saw/O them/O standing/O over/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O attend/O me/O in/O court/O this/O afternoon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O that/O you/O bathe/O and/O dress/O as/O befits/O my/O betrothed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON stood/O at/O his/O shoulder/O in/O a/O plain/O brown/O doublet/O and/O green/O mantle/O ,/O his/O burned/O face/O hideous/O in/O the/O morning/O light/O ./O 
Behind/O them/O were/O two/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O in/O long/O white/O satin/O cloaks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O drew/O her/O blanket/O up/O to/O her/O chin/O to/O cover/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whimpered/O ,/O \/O ``/O please/O .../O leave/O me/O be/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O wo/O n't/O rise/O and/O dress/O yourself/O ,/O my/O Hound/O will/O do/O it/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O beg/O of/O you/O ,/O my/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O king/O now/O ./O 
Dog/O ,/O get/O her/O out/O of/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON scooped/O her/O up/O around/O the/O waist/O and/O lifted/O her/O off/O the/O featherbed/O as/O she/O struggled/O feebly/O ./O 
Her/O blanket/O fell/O to/O the/O floor/O ./O 
Underneath/O she/O had/O only/O a/O thin/O bedgown/O to/O cover/O her/O nakedness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O as/O you/O 're/O bid/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Clegane/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dress/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pushed/O her/O toward/O her/O wardrobe/O ,/O almost/O gently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/PERSON backed/O away/O from/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O as/O the/O queen/O asked/O ,/O I/O wrote/O the/O letters/O ,/O I/O wrote/O what/O she/O told/O me/O ./O 
You/O promised/O you/O 'd/O be/O merciful/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O let/O me/O go/O home/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O do/O any/O treason/O ,/O I/O 'll/O be/O good/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O traitor/O 's/O blood/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O ./O 
I/O only/O want/O to/O go/O home/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Remembering/O her/O courtesies/O ,/O she/O lowered/O her/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O finished/O weakly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O does/O not/O please/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/PERSON says/O I/O 'm/O still/O to/O marry/O you/O ,/O so/O you/O 'll/O stay/O here/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O obey/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O marry/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O wailed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O chopped/O off/O my/O father/O 's/O head/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O a/O traitor/O ./O 
I/O never/O promised/O to/O spare/O him/O ,/O only/O that/O I/O 'd/O be/O merciful/O ,/O and/O I/O was/O ./O 
If/O he/O had/O n't/O been/O your/O father/O ,/O I/O would/O have/O had/O him/O torn/O or/O flayed/O ,/O but/O I/O gave/O him/O a/O clean/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O stared/O at/O him/O ,/O seeing/O him/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
He/O was/O wearing/O a/O padded/O crimson/O doublet/O patterned/O with/O lions/O and/O a/O cloth-of-gold/O cape/O with/O a/O high/O collar/O that/O framed/O his/O face/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O how/O she/O could/O ever/O have/O thought/O him/O handsome/O ./O 
His/O lips/O were/O as/O soft/O and/O red/O as/O the/O worms/O you/O found/O after/O a/O rain/O ,/O and/O his/O eyes/O were/O vain/O and/O cruel/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O face/O hardened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O mother/O tells/O me/O that/O it/O is/O n't/O fitting/O that/O a/O king/O should/O strike/O his/O wife/O ./O 
Ser/O Meryn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O knight/O was/O on/O her/O before/O she/O could/O think/O ,/O yanking/O back/O her/O hand/O as/O she/O tried/O to/O shield/O her/O face/O and/O backhanding/O her/O across/O the/O ear/O with/O a/O gloved/O fist/O ./O 
Sansa/O did/O not/O remember/O failing/O ,/O yet/O the/O next/O she/O knew/O she/O was/O sprawled/O on/O one/O knee/O amongst/O the/O rushes/O ./O 
Her/O head/O was/O ringing/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON stood/O over/O her/O ,/O with/O blood/O on/O the/O knuckles/O of/O his/O white/O silk/O glove/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O you/O obey/O now/O ,/O or/O shall/O I/O have/O him/O chastise/O you/O again/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O 's/O ear/O felt/O numb/O ./O 
She/O touched/O it/O ,/O and/O her/O fingertips/O came/O away/O wet/O and/O red/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
as/O .../O as/O you/O command/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON corrected/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O look/O for/O you/O in/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O and/O left/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Meryn/O and/O Ser/PERSON Arys/PERSON followed/O him/O out/O ,/O but/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON lingered/O long/O enough/O to/O yank/O her/O roughly/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Save/O yourself/O some/O pain/O ,/O girl/O ,/O and/O give/O him/O what/O he/O wants/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O .../O what/O does/O he/O want/O ?/O 
Please/O ,/O tell/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O wants/O you/O to/O smile/O and/O smell/O sweet/O and/O be/O his/O lady/O love/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Hound/O rasped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O wants/O to/O hear/O you/O recite/O all/O your/O pretty/O little/O words/O the/O way/O the/O septa/O taught/O you/O ./O 
He/O wants/O you/O to/O love/O him/O .../O and/O fear/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O After/O he/O was/O gone/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON sank/O back/O onto/O the/O rushes/O ,/O staring/O at/O the/O wall/O until/O two/O of/O her/O bedmaids/O crept/O timidly/O into/O the/O chamber/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O need/O hot/O water/O for/O my/O bath/O ,/O please/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O perfume/O ,/O and/O some/O powder/O to/O hide/O this/O bruise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O right/O side/O of/O her/O face/O was/O swollen/O and/O beginning/O to/O ache/O ,/O but/O she/O knew/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O want/O her/O to/O be/O beautiful/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O hot/O water/O made/O her/O think/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O she/O took/O strength/O from/O that/O ./O 
She/O had/O not/O washed/O since/O the/O day/O her/O father/O died/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O startled/O at/O how/O filthy/O the/O water/O became/O ./O 
Her/O maids/O sluiced/O the/O blood/O off/O her/O face/O ,/O scrubbed/O the/O dirt/O from/O her/O back/O ,/O washed/O her/O hair/O and/O brushed/O it/O out/O until/O it/O sprang/O back/O in/O thick/O auburn/O curls/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON did/O not/O speak/O to/O them/O ,/O except/O to/O give/O them/O commands/O ;/O they/O were/O Lannister/O servants/O ,/O not/O her/O own/O ,/O and/O she/O did/O not/O trust/O them/O ./O 
When/O the/O time/O came/O to/O dress/O ,/O she/O chose/O the/O green/O silk/O gown/O that/O she/O had/O worn/O to/O the/O tourney/O ./O 
She/O recalled/O how/O gallant/O Joff/PERSON had/O been/O to/O her/O that/O night/O at/O the/O feast/O ./O 
Perhaps/O it/O would/O make/O him/O remember/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O treat/O her/O more/O gently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O drank/O a/O glass/O of/O buttermilk/O and/O nibbled/O at/O some/O sweet/O biscuits/O as/O she/O waited/O ,/O to/O settle/O her/O stomach/O ./O 
It/O was/O midday/O when/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON returned/O ./O 
He/O had/O donned/O his/O white/O armor/O ;/O a/O shirt/O of/O enameled/O scales/O chased/O with/O gold/O ,/O a/O tall/O helm/O with/O a/O golden/O sunburst/O crest/O ,/O greaves/O and/O gorget/O and/O gauntlet/O and/O boots/O of/O gleaming/O plate/O ,/O a/O heavy/O wool/O cloak/O clasped/O with/O a/O golden/O lion/O ./O 
His/O visor/O had/O been/O removed/O from/O his/O helm/O ,/O to/O better/O show/O his/O dour/O face/O ;/O pouchy/O bags/O under/O his/O eyes/O ,/O a/O wide/O sour/O mouth/O ,/O rusty/O hair/O spotted/O with/O grey/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O bowing/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O not/O beaten/O her/O bloody/O only/O three/O hours/O past/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O Grace/O has/O instructed/O me/O to/O escort/O you/O to/O the/O throne/O room/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O he/O instruct/O you/O to/O hit/O me/O if/O I/O refused/O to/O come/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O you/O refusing/O to/O come/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O look/O he/O gave/O her/O was/O without/O expression/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O so/O much/O as/O glance/O at/O the/O bruise/O he/O had/O left/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O did/O not/O hate/O her/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON realized/O ;/O neither/O did/O he/O love/O her/O ./O 
He/O felt/O nothing/O for/O her/O at/O all/O ./O 
She/O was/O only/O a./O ./O 
./O 
a/O thing/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O rising/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O rage/O ,/O to/O hurt/O him/O as/O he/O 'd/O hurt/O her/O ,/O to/O warn/O him/O that/O when/O she/O was/O queen/O she/O would/O have/O him/O exiled/O if/O he/O ever/O dared/O strike/O her/O again/O .../O but/O she/O remembered/O what/O the/O Hound/O had/O told/O her/O ,/O so/O all/O she/O said/O was/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O do/O whatever/O His/O Grace/O commands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O I/O do/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O .../O but/O you/O are/O no/O true/O knight/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON would/O have/O laughed/O at/O that/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON knew/O ./O 
Other/O men/O might/O have/O cursed/O her/O ,/O warned/O her/O to/O keep/O silent/O ,/O even/O begged/O for/O her/O forgiveness/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON did/O none/O of/O these/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON Trant/PERSON simply/O did/O not/O care/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O balcony/O was/O deserted/O save/O for/O Sansa/O ./O 
She/O stood/O with/O her/O head/O bowed/O ,/O fighting/O to/O hold/O back/O her/O tears/O ,/O while/O below/O Joffrey/PERSON sat/O on/O his/O Iron/O Throne/O and/O dispensed/O what/O it/O pleased/O him/O to/O call/O justice/O ./O 
Nine/O cases/O out/O often/O seemed/O to/O bore/O him/O ;/O those/O he/O allowed/O his/O council/O to/O handle/O ,/O squirming/O restlessly/O while/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O ,/O or/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON resolved/O the/O matter/O ./O 
When/O he/O did/O choose/O to/O make/O a/O ruling/O ,/O though/O ,/O not/O even/O his/O queen/O mother/O could/O sway/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O thief/O was/O brought/O before/O him/O and/O he/O had/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON chop/O his/O hand/O off/O ,/O right/O there/O in/O court/O ./O 
Two/O knights/O came/O to/O him/O with/O a/O dispute/O about/O some/O land/O ,/O and/O he/O decreed/O that/O they/O should/O duel/O for/O it/O on/O the/O morrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O the/O death/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O added/O ./O 
A/O woman/O fell/O to/O her/O knees/O to/O plead/O for/O the/O head/O of/O a/O man/O executed/O as/O a/O traitor/O ./O 
She/O had/O loved/O him/O ,/O she/O said/O ,/O and/O she/O wanted/O to/O see/O him/O decently/O buried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O loved/O a/O traitor/O ,/O you/O must/O be/O a/O traitor/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
Two/O gold/O cloaks/O dragged/O her/O off/O to/O the/O dungeons/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Frog-faced/O Lord/O Slynt/PERSON sat/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O council/O table/O wearing/O a/O black/O velvet/O doublet/O and/O a/O shiny/O cloth-of-gold/O cape/O ,/O nodding/O with/O approval/O every/O time/O the/O king/O pronounced/O a/O sentence/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON stared/O hard/O at/O his/O ugly/O face/O ,/O remembering/O how/O he/O had/O thrown/O down/O her/O father/O for/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON to/O behead/O ,/O wishing/O she/O could/O hurt/O him/O ,/O wishing/O that/O some/O hero/O would/O throw/O him/O down/O and/O cut/O off/O his/O head/O ./O 
But/O a/O voice/O inside/O her/O whispered/O ,/O There/O are/O no/O heroes/O ,/O and/O she/O remembered/O what/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON had/O said/O to/O her/O ,/O here/O in/O this/O very/O hall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Life/O is/O not/O a/O song/O ,/O sweetling/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O 'd/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O may/O learn/O that/O one/O day/O to/O your/O sorrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O In/O life/O ,/O the/O monsters/O win/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O and/O now/O it/O was/O the/O Hound/O 's/O voice/O she/O heard/O ,/O a/O cold/O rasp/O ,/O metal/O on/O stone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Save/O yourself/O some/O pain/O ,/O girl/O ,/O and/O give/O him/O what/O he/O wants/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O last/O case/O was/O a/O plump/O tavern/O singer/O ,/O accused/O of/O making/O a/O song/O that/O ridiculed/O the/O late/O King/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
Jo/PERSON ff/O commanded/O them/O to/O fetch/O his/O woodharp/O and/O ordered/O him/O to/O perform/O the/O song/O for/O the/O court/O ./O 
The/O singer/O wept/O and/O swore/O he/O would/O never/O sing/O that/O song/O again/O ,/O but/O the/O king/O insisted/O ./O 
It/O was/O sort/O of/O a/O funny/O song/O ,/O all/O about/O Robert/PERSON fighting/O with/O a/O pig/O ./O 
The/O pig/O was/O the/O boar/O who/O 'd/O killed/O him/O ,/O Sansa/O knew/O ,/O but/O in/O some/O verses/O it/O almost/O sounded/O as/O if/O he/O were/O singing/O about/O the/O queen/O ./O 
When/O the/O song/O was/O done/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON announced/O that/O he/O 'd/O decided/O to/O be/O merciful/O ./O 
The/O singer/O could/O keep/O either/O his/O fingers/O or/O his/O tongue/O ./O 
He/O would/O have/O a/O day/O to/O make/O his/O choice/O ./O 
Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON nodded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O final/O business/O of/O the/O afternoon/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON saw/O with/O relief/O ,/O but/O her/O ordeal/O was/O not/O yet/O done/O ./O 
When/O the/O herald/O 's/O voice/O dismissed/O the/O court/O ,/O she/O fled/O the/O balcony/O ,/O only/O to/O find/O Joffrey/PERSON waiting/O for/O her/O at/O the/O base/O of/O the/O curving/O stairs/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O was/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
The/O young/O king/O examined/O her/O critically/O ,/O top/O to/O bottom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O look/O much/O better/O than/O you/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
Hollow/O words/O ,/O but/O they/O made/O him/O nod/O and/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Walk/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON commanded/O ,/O offering/O her/O his/O arm/O ./O 
She/O had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O take/O it/O ./O 
The/O touch/O of/O his/O hand/O would/O have/O thrilled/O her/O once/O ;/O now/O it/O made/O her/O flesh/O crawl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O name/O day/O will/O be/O here/O soon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O as/O they/O slipped/O out/O the/O rear/O of/O the/O throne/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O will/O be/O a/O great/O feast/O ,/O and/O gifts/O ./O 
What/O are/O you/O going/O to/O give/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O had/O not/O thought/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O truly/O are/O a/O stupid/O girl/O ,/O are/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
My/O mother/O says/O so/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O does/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O After/O all/O that/O had/O happened/O ,/O his/O words/O should/O have/O lost/O their/O power/O to/O hurt/O her/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O they/O had/O not/O ./O 
The/O queen/O had/O always/O been/O so/O kind/O to/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
She/O worries/O about/O our/O children/O ,/O whether/O they/O 'll/O be/O stupid/O like/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O told/O her/O not/O to/O trouble/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O gestured/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON opened/O a/O door/O for/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O murmured/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O was/O right/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O I/O am/O only/O a/O little/O bird/O ,/O repeating/O the/O words/O they/O taught/O me/O ./O 
The/O sun/O had/O fallen/O below/O the/O western/O wall/O ,/O and/O the/O stones/O of/O the/O Red/O Keep/O glowed/O dark/O as/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O get/O you/O with/O child/O as/O soon/O as/O you/O 're/O able/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O as/O he/O escorted/O her/O across/O the/O practice/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O first/O one/O is/O stupid/O ,/O I/O 'll/O chop/O off/O your/O head/O and/O find/O a/O smarter/O wife/O ./O 
When/O do/O you/O think/O you/O 'll/O be/O able/O to/O have/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O could/O not/O look/O at/O him/O ,/O he/O shamed/O her/O so/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON says/O most/O .../O most/O highborn/O girls/O have/O their/O flowering/O at/O twelve/O or/O thirteen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O led/O her/O into/O the/O gatehouse/O ,/O to/O the/O base/O of/O the/O steps/O that/O led/O up/O to/O the/O battlements/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O jerked/O back/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O trembling/O ./O 
Suddenly/O she/O knew/O where/O they/O were/O going/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O her/O voice/O a/O frightened/O gasp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O no/O ,/O do/O n't/O make/O me/O ,/O I/O beg/O you/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON pressed/O his/O lips/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O show/O you/O what/O happens/O to/O traitors/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O shook/O her/O head/O wildly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O have/O Ser/O Meryn/O drag/O you/O up/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O wo/O n't/O like/O that/O ./O 
You/O had/O better/O do/O what/O I/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON reached/O for/O her/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON cringed/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O backing/O into/O the/O Hound/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O it/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON told/O her/O ,/O pushing/O her/O back/O toward/O the/O king/O ./O 
His/O mouth/O twitched/O on/O the/O burned/O side/O of/O his/O face/O and/O Sansa/PERSON could/O almost/O hear/O the/O rest/O of/O it/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O have/O you/O up/O there/O no/O matter/O what/O ,/O so/O give/O him/O what/O he/O wants/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O forced/O herself/O to/O take/O King/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON 's/O hand/O ./O 
The/O climb/O was/O something/O out/O of/O a/O nightmare/O ;/O every/O step/O was/O a/O struggle/O ,/O as/O if/O she/O were/O pulling/O her/O feet/O out/O of/O ankle-deep/O mud/O ,/O and/O there/O were/O more/O steps/O than/O she/O would/O have/O believed/O ,/O a/O thousand/O thousand/O steps/O ,/O and/O horror/O waiting/O on/O the/O ramparts/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O the/O high/O battlements/O of/O the/O gatehouse/O ,/O the/O whole/O world/O spread/O out/O below/O them/O ./O 
Sansa/O could/O see/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION on/O Visenya/PERSON 's/O hill/O ,/O where/O her/O father/O had/O died/O ./O 
At/O the/O other/O end/O of/O the/O Street/O of/O the/O Sisters/O stood/O the/O fire-blackened/O ruins/O of/O the/O Dragonpit/O ./O 
To/O the/O west/O ,/O the/O swollen/O red/O sun/O was/O half-hidden/O behind/O the/O Gate/O of/O the/O Gods/O ./O 
The/O salt/O sea/O was/O at/O her/O back/O ,/O and/O to/O the/O south/O was/O the/O fish/O market/O and/O the/O docks/O and/O the/O swirling/O torrent/O of/O the/O Blackwater/O Rush/O ./O 
And/O to/O the/O north/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O turned/O that/O way/O ,/O and/O saw/O only/O the/O city/O ,/O streets/O and/O alleys/O and/O hills/O and/O bottoms/O and/O more/O streets/O and/O more/O alleys/O and/O the/O stone/O of/O distant/O walls/O ./O 
Yet/O she/O knew/O that/O beyond/O them/O was/O open/O country/O ,/O farms/O and/O fields/O and/O forests/O ,/O and/O beyond/O that/O ,/O north/O and/O north/O and/O north/O again/O ,/O stood/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O looking/O at/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O what/O I/O wanted/O you/O to/O see/O ,/O right/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O thick/O stone/O parapet/O protected/O the/O outer/O edge/O of/O the/O rampart/O ,/O reaching/O as/O high/O as/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O chin/O ,/O with/O crenellations/O cut/O into/O it/O every/O five/O feet/O for/O archers/O ./O 
The/O heads/O were/O mounted/O between/O the/O crenels/O ,/O along/O the/O top/O of/O the/O wall/O ,/O impaled/O on/O iron/O spikes/O so/O they/O faced/O out/O over/O the/O city/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O noted/O them/O the/O moment/O she/O 'd/O stepped/O out/O onto/O the/O wallwalk/O ,/O but/O the/O river/O and/O the/O bustling/O streets/O and/O the/O setting/O sun/O were/O ever/O so/O much/O prettier/O ./O 
He/O can/O make/O me/O look/O at/O the/O heads/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O but/O he/O ca/O n't/O make/O me/O see/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O one/O is/O your/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O one/O here/O ./O 
Dog/O ,/O turn/O it/O around/O so/O she/O can/O see/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON took/O the/O head/O by/O the/O hair/O and/O turned/O it/O ./O 
The/O severed/O head/O had/O been/O dipped/O in/O tar/O to/O preserve/O it/O longer/O ./O 
Sansa/O looked/O at/O it/O calmly/O ,/O not/O seeing/O it/O at/O all/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O really/O look/O like/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O she/O thought/O ;/O it/O did/O not/O even/O look/O real/O \/O ``/O How/O long/O do/O I/O have/O to/O look/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/O seemed/O disappointed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O want/O to/O see/O the/O rest/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O There/O was/O a/O long/O row/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O it/O please/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON marched/O her/O down/O the/O wallwalk/O ,/O past/O a/O dozen/O more/O heads/O and/O two/O empty/O spikes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O saving/O those/O for/O my/O uncle/O Stannis/PERSON and/O my/O uncle/O Renly/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O explained/O ./O 
The/O other/O heads/O had/O been/O dead/O and/O mounted/O much/O longer/O than/O her/O father/O ./O 
Despite/O the/O tar/O ,/O most/O were/O long/O past/O being/O recognizable/O ./O 
The/O king/O pointed/O to/O one/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O your/O septa/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O but/O Sansa/PERSON could/O not/O even/O have/O told/O that/O it/O was/O a/O woman/O ./O 
The/O jaw/O had/O rotted/O off/O her/O face/O ,/O and/O birds/O had/O eaten/O one/O ear/O and/O most/O of/O a/O cheek/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O wondered/O what/O had/O happened/O to/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON ,/O although/O she/O supposed/O she/O had/O known/O all/O along/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O did/O you/O kill/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O was/O godsworn/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O was/O a/O traitor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON looked/O pouty/O ;/O somehow/O she/O was/O upsetting/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O n't/O said/O what/O you/O mean/O to/O give/O me/O for/O my/O name/O day/O ./O 
Maybe/O I/O should/O give/O you/O something/O instead/O ,/O would/O you/O like/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O smiled/O ,/O she/O knew/O he/O was/O mocking/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O is/O a/O traitor/O too/O ,/O you/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON 's/O head/O back/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O remember/O your/O brother/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
My/O dog/O called/O him/O the/O lord/O of/O the/O wooden/O sword/O ./O 
Did/O n't/O you/O ,/O dog/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O I/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Hound/O replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O recall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON gave/O a/O petulant/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O defeated/O my/O uncle/O Jaime/PERSON ./O 
My/O mother/O says/O it/O was/O treachery/O and/O deceit/O ./O 
She/O wept/O when/O she/O heard/O ./O 
Women/O are/O all/O weak/O ,/O even/O her/O ,/O though/O she/O pretends/O she/O is/O n't/O ./O 
She/O says/O we/O need/O to/O stay/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O in/O case/O my/O other/O uncles/O attack/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O ./O 
After/O my/O name/O day/O feast/O ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O raise/O a/O host/O and/O kill/O your/O brother/O myself/O ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O I/O 'll/O give/O you/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Sansa/PERSON ./O 
Your/O brother/O 's/O head/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O kind/O of/O madness/O took/O over/O her/O then/O ,/O and/O she/O heard/O herself/O say/O ,/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O my/O brother/O will/O give/O me/O your/O head/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON scowled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O never/O mock/O me/O like/O that/O ./O 
A/O true/O wife/O does/O not/O mock/O her/O lord/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON ,/O teach/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O This/O time/O the/O knight/O grasped/O her/O beneath/O the/O jaw/O and/O held/O her/O head/O still/O as/O he/O struck/O her/O ./O 
He/O hit/O her/O twice/O ,/O left/O to/O right/O ,/O and/O harder/O ,/O right/O to/O left/O ./O 
Her/O lip/O split/O and/O blood/O ran/O down/O her/O chin/O ,/O to/O mingle/O with/O the/O salt/O of/O her/O tears/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O should/O n't/O be/O crying/O all/O the/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O more/O pretty/O when/O you/O smile/O and/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O made/O herself/O smile/O ,/O afraid/O that/O he/O would/O have/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON hit/O her/O again/O if/O she/O did/O not/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O no/O good/O ,/O the/O king/O still/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wipe/O off/O the/O blood/O ,/O you/O 're/O all/O messy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O outer/O parapet/O came/O up/O to/O her/O chin/O ,/O but/O along/O the/O inner/O edge/O of/O the/O walk/O was/O nothing/O ,/O nothing/O but/O a/O long/O plunge/O to/O the/O bailey/O seventy/O or/O eighty/O feet/O below/O ./O 
All/O it/O would/O take/O was/O a/O shove/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
He/O was/O standing/O right/O there/O ,/O right/O there/O ,/O smirking/O at/O her/O with/O those/O fat/O wormlips/O ./O 
You/O could/O do/O it/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
You/O could/O ./O 
Do/O it/O right/O now/O ./O 
It/O would/O n't/O even/O matter/O if/O she/O went/O over/O with/O him/O ./O 
It/O would/O n't/O matter/O at/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON knelt/O before/O her/O ,/O between/O her/O and/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
With/O a/O delicacy/O surprising/O in/O such/O a/O big/O man/O ,/O he/O dabbed/O at/O the/O blood/O welling/O from/O her/O broken/O lip/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O moment/O was/O gone/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON lowered/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O when/O he/O was/O done/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O good/O girl/O ,/O and/O always/O remembered/O her/O courtesies/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
