-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Are/O you/O certain/O that/O you/O must/O leave/O us/O so/O soon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Past/O certain/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON will/O be/O wondering/O what/O has/O become/O of/O me/O ./O 
He/O may/O decide/O that/O you/O have/O convinced/O me/O to/O take/O the/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O could/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON picked/O up/O a/O crab/O claw/O and/O cracked/O it/O in/O his/O fist/O ./O 
Old/O as/O he/O was/O ,/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O still/O had/O the/O strength/O of/O a/O bear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O a/O cunning/O man/O ,/O Tyrion/O ./O 
We/O have/O need/O of/O men/O of/O your/O sort/O on/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O I/O shall/O scour/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O for/O dwarfs/O and/O ship/O them/O all/O to/O you/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O As/O they/O laughed/O ,/O he/O sucked/O the/O meat/O from/O a/O crab/O leg/O and/O reached/O for/O another/O ./O 
The/O crabs/O had/O arrived/O from/O Eastwatch/LOCATION only/O this/O morning/O ,/O packed/O in/O a/O barrel/O of/O snow/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O succulent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON was/O the/O only/O man/O at/O table/O who/O did/O not/O so/O much/O as/O crack/O a/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannister/O mocks/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O you/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
This/O time/O the/O laughter/O round/O the/O table/O had/O a/O nervous/O ,/O uncertain/O quality/O to/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Thome/O 's/O black/O eyes/O fixed/O on/O Tyrion/O with/O loathing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O a/O bold/O tongue/O for/O someone/O who/O is/O less/O than/O half/O a/O man/O ./O 
Perhaps/O you/O and/O I/O should/O visit/O the/O yard/O together/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Tyrion/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O crabs/O are/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O remark/O brought/O more/O guffaws/O from/O the/O others/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON stood/O up/O ,/O his/O mouth/O a/O tight/O line/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O and/O make/O your/O japes/O with/O steel/O in/O your/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O looked/O pointedly/O at/O his/O right/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O I/O have/O steel/O in/O my/O hand/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON ,/O although/O it/O appears/O to/O be/O a/O crab/O fork/O ./O 
Shall/O we/O duel/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O hopped/O up/O on/O his/O chair/O and/O began/O poking/O at/O Thome/PERSON 's/O chest/O with/O the/O tiny/O fork/O ./O 
Roars/O of/O laughter/O filled/O the/O tower/O room/O ./O 
Bits/O of/O crab/O flew/O from/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O mouth/O as/O he/O began/O to/O gasp/O and/O choke/O ./O 
Even/O his/O raven/O joined/O in/O ,/O cawing/O loudly/O from/O above/O the/O window/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Duel/O !/O 
Duel/O !/O 
Duel/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON walked/O from/O the/O room/O so/O stiffly/O it/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O had/O a/O dagger/O up/O his/O butt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON was/O still/O gasping/O for/O breath/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON pounded/O him/O on/O the/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O the/O victor/O goes/O the/O spoils/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O claim/O Thome/PERSON 's/O share/O of/O the/O crabs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Finally/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O recovered/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O wicked/O man/O ,/O to/O provoke/O our/O Ser/O Alliser/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O scolded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O seated/O himself/O and/O took/O a/O sip/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O a/O man/O paints/O a/O target/O on/O his/O chest/O ,/O he/O should/O expect/O that/O sooner/O or/O later/O someone/O will/O loose/O an/O arrow/O at/O him/O ./O 
I/O have/O seen/O dead/O men/O with/O more/O humor/O than/O your/O Ser/O Alliser/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O objected/O the/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON ,/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON ,/O a/O man/O as/O round/O and/O red/O as/O a/O pomegranate/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ought/O to/O hear/O the/O droll/O names/O he/O gives/O the/O lads/O he/O trains/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O had/O heard/O a/O few/O of/O those/O droll/O names/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O wager/O the/O lads/O have/O a/O few/O names/O for/O him/O as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Chip/O the/O ice/O off/O your/O eyes/O ,/O my/O good/O lords/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON should/O be/O mucking/O out/O your/O stables/O ,/O not/O drilling/O your/O young/O warriors/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Watch/O has/O no/O shortage/O of/O stableboys/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O seems/O to/O be/O all/O they/O send/O us/O these/O days/O ./O 
Stableboys/O and/O sneak/O thieves/O and/O rapers/O ./O 
Ser/O Alliser/O is/O an/O anointed/O knight/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O few/O to/O take/O the/O black/O since/O I/O have/O been/O Lord/O Commander/O ./O 
He/O fought/O bravely/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O On/O the/O wrong/O side/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON commented/O dryly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ought/O to/O know/O ,/O I/O was/O there/O on/O the/O battlements/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON gave/O us/O a/O splendid/O choice/O ./O 
Take/O the/O black/O ,/O or/O see/O our/O heads/O on/O spikes/O before/O evenfall/O ./O 
No/O offense/O intended/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O None/O taken/O ,/O Ser/O Jaremy/O ./O 
My/O father/O is/O very/O fond/O of/O spiked/O heads/O ,/O especially/O those/O of/O people/O who/O have/O annoyed/O him/O in/O some/O fashion/O ./O 
And/O a/O face/O as/O noble/O as/O yours/O ,/O well/O ,/O no/O doubt/O he/O saw/O you/O decorating/O the/O city/O wall/O above/O the/O King/O 's/O Gate/O ./O 
I/O think/O you/O would/O have/O looked/O very/O striking/O up/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O sardonic/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON cleared/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sometimes/O I/O fear/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON saw/O you/O true/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
You/O do/O mock/O us/O and/O our/O noble/O purpose/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O all/O need/O to/O be/O mocked/O from/O time/O to/O time/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON ,/O lest/O we/O start/O to/O take/O ourselves/O too/O seriously/O ./O 
More/O wine/O ,/O please/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O held/O out/O his/O cup/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O Rykker/O filled/O it/O for/O him/O ,/O Bo/PERSON wen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O a/O great/O thirst/O for/O a/O small/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O think/O that/O Lord/O Tyrion/O is/O quite/O a/O large/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON said/O from/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O table/O ./O 
He/O spoke/O softly/O ,/O yet/O the/O high/O officers/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O all/O fell/O quiet/O ,/O the/O better/O to/O hear/O what/O the/O ancient/O had/O to/O say/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O he/O is/O a/O giant/O come/O among/O us/O ,/O here/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O answered/O gently/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O been/O called/O many/O things/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O giant/O is/O seldom/O one/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nonetheless/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON said/O as/O his/O clouded/O ,/O milk-white/O eyes/O moved/O to/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O think/O it/O is/O true/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O once/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON found/O himself/O at/O a/O loss/O for/O words/O ./O 
He/O could/O only/O bow/O his/O head/O politely/O and/O say/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O too/O kind/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O blind/O man/O smiled/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O tiny/O thing/O ,/O wrinkled/O and/O hairless/O ,/O shrunken/O beneath/O the/O weight/O of/O a/O hundred/O years/O so/O his/O maester/O 's/O collar/O with/O its/O links/O of/O many/O metals/O hung/O loose/O about/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O been/O called/O many/O things/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O kind/O is/O seldom/O one/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O This/O time/O Tyrion/PERSON himself/O led/O the/O laughter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Much/O later/O ,/O when/O the/O serious/O business/O of/O eating/O was/O done/O and/O the/O others/O had/O left/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON offered/O Tyrion/O a/O chair/O beside/O the/O fire/O and/O a/O cup/O of/O mulled/O spirits/O so/O strong/O they/O brought/O tears/O to/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O kingsroad/O can/O be/O perilous/O this/O far/O north/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O told/O him/O as/O they/O drank/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O Jyck/PERSON and/O Morrec/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O Yoren/PERSON is/O riding/O south/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yoren/O is/O only/O one/O man/O ./O 
The/O Watch/O shall/O escort/O you/O as/O far/O as/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON announced/O in/O a/O tone/O that/O brooked/O no/O argument/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O men/O should/O be/O sufficient/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O insist/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O might/O send/O young/O Snow/O ./O 
He/O would/O be/O glad/O for/O a/O chance/O to/O see/O his/O brothers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/O frowned/O through/O his/O thick/O grey/O beard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Snow/O ?/O 
Oh/O ,/O the/O Stark/O bastard/O ./O 
I/O think/O not/O ./O 
The/O young/O ones/O need/O to/O forget/O the/O lives/O they/O left/O behind/O them/O ,/O the/O brothers/O and/O mothers/O and/O all/O that/O ./O 
A/O visit/O home/O would/O only/O stir/O up/O feelings/O best/O left/O alone/O ./O 
I/O know/O these/O things/O ./O 
My/O own/O blood/O kin/O .../O my/O sister/O Maege/PERSON rules/O Bear/O Island/O now/O ,/O since/O my/O son/O 's/O dishonor/O ./O 
I/O have/O nieces/O I/O have/O never/O seen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O a/O swallow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Besides/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON is/O only/O a/O boy/O ./O 
You/O shall/O have/O three/O strong/O swords/O ,/O to/O keep/O you/O safe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O touched/O by/O your/O concern/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O strong/O drink/O was/O making/O Tyrion/O light/O -/O headed/O ,/O but/O not/O so/O drunk/O that/O he/O did/O not/O realize/O that/O the/O Old/O Bear/O wanted/O something/O from/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O I/O can/O repay/O your/O kindness/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O can/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O bluntly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O sister/O sits/O beside/O the/O king/O ./O 
Your/O brother/O is/O a/O great/O knight/O ,/O and/O your/O father/O the/O most/O powerful/O lord/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
Speak/O to/O them/O for/O us/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O of/O our/O need/O here/O ./O 
You/O have/O seen/O for/O yourself/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O dying/O ./O 
Our/O strength/O is/O less/O than/O a/O thousand/O now/O ./O 
Six/O hundred/O here/O ,/O two/O hundred/O in/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O even/O fewer/O at/O Eastwatch/LOCATION ,/O and/O a/O scant/O third/O of/O those/O fighting/O men/O ./O 
The/O Wall/O is/O a/O hundred/O leagues/O long/O ./O 
Think/O on/O that/O ./O 
Should/O an/O attack/O come/O ,/O I/O have/O three/O men/O to/O defend/O each/O mile/O of/O wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Three/O and/O a/O third/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O with/O a/O yawn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/O scarcely/O seemed/O to/O hear/O him/O ./O 
The/O old/O man/O warmed/O his/O hands/O before/O the/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O sent/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON to/O search/O after/O Yohn/PERSON Royce/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O lost/O on/O his/O first/O ranging/O ./O 
The/O Royce/O boy/O was/O green/O as/O summer/O grass/O ,/O yet/O he/O insisted/O on/O the/O honor/O of/O his/O own/O command/O ,/O saying/O it/O was/O his/O due/O as/O a/O knight/O ./O 
I/O did/O not/O wish/O to/O offend/O his/O lord/O father/O ,/O so/O I/O yielded/O ./O 
I/O sent/O him/O out/O with/O two/O men/O I/O deemed/O as/O good/O as/O any/O in/O the/O Watch/O ./O 
More/O fool/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O agreed/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON glanced/O up/O ./O 
The/O bird/O peered/O down/O at/O him/O with/O those/O beady/O black/O eyes/O ,/O ruffling/O its/O wings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O it/O called/O again/O ./O 
Doubtless/O old/O Mormont/PERSON would/O take/O it/O amiss/O if/O he/O throttled/O the/O creature/O ./O 
A/O pity/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O took/O no/O notice/O of/O the/O irritating/O bird/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gared/PERSON was/O near/O as/O old/O as/O I/O am/O and/O longer/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O went/O on/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O it/O would/O seem/O he/O forswore/O himself/O and/O fled/O ./O 
I/O should/O never/O have/O believed/O it/O ,/O not/O of/O him/O ,/O but/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON sent/O me/O his/O head/O from/O Winterfell/PERSON ./O 
Of/O Royce/O ,/O there/O is/O no/O word/O ./O 
One/O deserter/O and/O two/O men/O lost/O ,/O and/O now/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON too/O has/O gone/O missing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O deeply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O am/O I/O to/O send/O searching/O after/O him/O ?/O 
In/O two/O years/O I/O will/O be/O seventy/O ./O 
Too/O old/O and/O too/O weary/O for/O the/O burden/O I/O bear/O ,/O yet/O if/O I/O set/O it/O down/O ,/O who/O will/O pick/O it/O up/O ?/O 
Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON ?/O 
Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON ?/O 
I/O would/O have/O to/O be/O as/O blind/O as/O Maester/O Aemon/O not/O to/O see/O what/O they/O are/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O has/O become/O an/O army/O of/O sullen/O boys/O and/O tired/O old/O men/O ./O 
Apart/O from/O the/O men/O at/O my/O table/O tonight/O ,/O I/O have/O perhaps/O twenty/O who/O can/O read/O ,/O and/O even/O fewer/O who/O can/O think/O ,/O or/O plan/O ,/O or/O lead/O ./O 
Once/O the/O Watch/O spent/O its/O summers/O building/O ,/O and/O each/O Lord/O Commander/O raised/O the/O Wall/O higher/O than/O he/O found/O it/O ./O 
Now/O it/O is/O all/O we/O can/O do/O to/O stay/O alive/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O in/O deadly/O earnest/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON realized/O ./O 
He/O felt/O faintly/O embarrassed/O for/O the/O old/O man/O ./O 
Lord/O Mormont/PERSON had/O spent/O a/O good/O part/O of/O his/O life/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O he/O needed/O to/O believe/O if/O those/O years/O were/O to/O have/O any/O meaning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O promise/O ,/O the/O king/O will/O hear/O of/O your/O need/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O gravely/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O will/O speak/O to/O my/O father/O and/O my/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O he/O would/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O ''/O ,/O ``/O was/O as/O good/O as/O his/O word/O ./O 
He/O left/O the/O rest/O unsaid/O ;/O that/O King/O Robert/PERSON would/O ignore/O him/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON would/O ask/O if/O he/O had/O taken/O leave/O of/O his/O senses/O ,/O and/O Jaime/PERSON would/O only/O laugh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O young/O man/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O many/O winters/O have/O you/O seen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Eight/O ,/O nine/O ./O 
I/O misremember/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O all/O of/O them/O short/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O been/O born/O in/O the/O dead/O of/O winter/O ,/O a/O terrible/O cruel/O one/O that/O the/O maesters/O said/O had/O lasted/O near/O three/O years/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O earliest/O memories/O were/O of/O spring/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O was/O a/O boy/O ,/O it/O was/O said/O that/O a/O long/O summer/O always/O meant/O a/O long/O winter/O to/O come/O ./O 
This/O summer/O has/O lasted/O nine/O years/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ,/O and/O a/O tenth/O will/O soon/O be/O upon/O us/O ./O 
Think/O on/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O was/O a/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O my/O wet/O nurse/O told/O me/O that/O one/O day/O ,/O if/O men/O were/O good/O ,/O the/O gods/O would/O give/O the/O world/O a/O summer/O without/O ending/O ./O 
Perhaps/O we/O 've/O been/O better/O than/O we/O thought/O ,/O and/O the/O Great/O Summer/O is/O finally/O at/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O grinned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O did/O not/O seem/O amused/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O not/O fool/O enough/O to/O believe/O that/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Already/O the/O days/O grow/O shorter/O ./O 
There/O can/O be/O no/O mistake/O ,/O Aemon/PERSON has/O had/O letters/O from/O the/O Citadel/ORGANIZATION ,/O findings/O in/O accord/O with/O his/O own/O ./O 
The/O end/O of/O summer/O stares/O us/O in/O the/O face/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON reached/O out/O and/O clutched/O Tyrion/O tightly/O by/O the/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O make/O them/O understand/O ./O 
I/O tell/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O the/O darkness/O is/O coming/O ./O 
There/O are/O wild/O things/O in/O the/O woods/O ,/O direwolves/O and/O mammoths/O and/O snow/O bears/O the/O size/O of/O aurochs/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O seen/O darker/O shapes/O in/O my/O dreams/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O your/O dreams/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O echoed/O ,/O thinking/O how/O badly/O he/O needed/O another/O strong/O drink/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON was/O deaf/O to/O the/O edge/O in/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O fisherfolk/O near/O Eastwatch/LOCATION have/O glimpsed/O white/O walkers/O on/O the/O shore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O This/O time/O Tyrion/PERSON could/O not/O hold/O his/O tongue/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O fisherfolk/O of/O Lannisport/LOCATION often/O glimpse/O merlings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Denys/PERSON Mallister/PERSON writes/O that/O the/O mountain/O people/O are/O moving/O south/O ,/O slipping/O past/O the/O Shadow/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION in/O numbers/O greater/O than/O ever/O before/O ./O 
They/O are/O running/O ,/O my/O lord/O .../O but/O running/O from/O what/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON moved/O to/O the/O window/O and/O stared/O out/O into/O the/O night/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O are/O old/O bones/O ,/O Lannister/PERSON ,/O but/O they/O have/O never/O felt/O a/O chill/O like/O this/O ./O 
Tell/O the/O king/O what/O I/O say/O ,/O I/O pray/O you/O ./O 
Winter/O is/O coming/O ,/O and/O when/O the/O Long/O Night/O falls/O ,/O only/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O will/O stand/O between/O the/O realm/O and/O the/O darkness/O that/O sweeps/O from/O the/O north/O ./O 
The/O gods/O help/O us/O all/O if/O we/O are/O not/O ready/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gods/O help/O me/O if/O I/O do/O not/O get/O some/O sleep/O tonight/O ./O 
Yoren/O is/O determined/O to/O ride/O at/O first/O light/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON got/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O sleepy/O from/O wine/O and/O tired/O of/O doom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O for/O all/O the/O courtesies/O you/O have/O done/O me/O ,/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O them/O ,/O Tyrion/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O and/O make/O them/O believe/O ./O 
That/O is/O all/O the/O thanks/O I/O need/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O whistled/O ,/O and/O his/O raven/O flew/O to/O him/O and/O perched/O on/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON smiled/O and/O gave/O the/O bird/O some/O corn/O from/O his/O pocket/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O how/O Tyrion/PERSON left/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O bitter/O cold/O outside/O ./O 
Bundled/O thickly/O in/O his/O furs/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON pulled/O on/O his/O gloves/O and/O nodded/O to/O the/O poor/O frozen/O wretches/O standing/O sentry/O outside/O the/O Commander/O 's/O Keep/O ./O 
He/O set/O off/O across/O the/O yard/O for/O his/O own/O chambers/O in/O the/O King/O 's/O Tower/O ,/O walking/O as/O briskly/O as/O his/O legs/O could/O manage/O ./O 
Patches/O of/O snow/O crunched/O beneath/O his/O feet/O as/O his/O boots/O broke/O the/O night/O 's/O crust/O ,/O and/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O breath/O steamed/O before/O him/O like/O a/O banner/O ./O 
He/O shoved/O his/O hands/O into/O his/O armpits/O and/O walked/O faster/O ,/O praying/O that/O Morrec/PERSON had/O remembered/O to/O warm/O his/O bed/O with/O hot/O bricks/O from/O the/O fire/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Behind/O the/O King/O 's/O Tower/O ,/O the/O Wall/O glimmered/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O moon/LOCATION ,/O immense/O and/O mysterious/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON stopped/O for/O a/O moment/O to/O look/O up/O at/O it/O ./O 
His/O legs/O ached/O of/O cold/O and/O haste/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O a/O strange/O madness/O took/O hold/O of/O him/O ,/O a/O yearning/O to/O look/O once/O more/O off/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O his/O last/O chance/O ,/O he/O thought/O ;/O tomorrow/O he/O would/O ride/O south/O ,/O and/O he/O could/O not/O imagine/O why/O he/O would/O ever/O want/O to/O return/O to/O this/O frozen/O desolation/O ./O 
The/O King/O 's/O Tower/O was/O before/O him/O ,/O with/O its/O promise/O of/O warmth/O and/O a/O soft/O bed/O ,/O yet/O Tyrion/O found/O himself/O walking/O past/O it/O ,/O toward/O the/O vast/O pale/O palisade/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O wooden/O stair/O ascended/O the/O south/O face/O ,/O anchored/O on/O huge/O roughhewn/O beams/O sunk/O deep/O into/O the/O ice/O and/O frozen/O in/O place/O ./O 
Back/O and/O forth/O it/O switched/O ,/O clawing/O its/O way/O upward/O as/O crooked/O as/O a/O bolt/O of/O lightning/O ./O 
The/O black/PERSON brothers/O assured/O him/O that/O it/O was/O much/O stronger/O than/O it/O looked/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON 's/O legs/O were/O cramping/O too/O badly/O for/O him/O to/O even/O contemplate/O the/O ascent/O ./O 
He/O went/O instead/O to/O the/O iron/O cage/O beside/O the/O well/O ,/O clambered/O inside/O ,/O and/O yanked/O hard/O on/O the/O bell/O rope/O ,/O three/O quick/O pulls/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O had/O to/O wait/O what/O seemed/O an/O eternity/O ,/O standing/O there/O inside/O the/O bars/O with/O the/O Wall/O to/O his/O back/O ./O 
Long/O enough/O for/O Tyrion/O to/O begin/O to/O wonder/O why/O he/O was/O doing/O this/O ./O 
He/O had/O just/O about/O decided/O to/O forget/O his/O sudden/O whim/O and/O go/O to/O bed/O when/O the/O cage/O gave/O a/O jerk/O and/O began/O to/O ascend/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O moved/O upward/O slowly/O ,/O by/O fits/O and/O starts/O at/O first/O ,/O then/O more/O smoothly/O ./O 
The/O ground/O fell/O away/O beneath/O him/O ,/O the/O cage/O swung/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON wrapped/O his/O hands/O around/O the/O iron/O bars/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O the/O cold/O of/O the/O metal/O even/O through/O his/O gloves/O ./O 
Morrec/PERSON had/O a/O fire/O burning/O in/O his/O room/O ,/O he/O noted/O with/O approval/O ,/O but/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O tower/O was/O dark/O ./O 
The/O Old/O Bear/O had/O more/O sense/O than/O he/O did/O ,/O it/O seemed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O he/O was/O above/O the/O towers/O ,/O still/O inching/O his/O way/O upward/O ./O 
Castle/PERSON Black/PERSON lay/O below/O him/O ,/O etched/O in/O moonlight/O ./O 
You/O could/O see/O how/O stark/O and/O empty/O it/O was/O from/O up/O here/O ;/O windowless/O keeps/O ,/O crumbling/O walls/O ,/O courtyards/O choked/O with/O broken/O stone/O ./O 
Farther/O off/O ,/O he/O could/O see/O the/O lights/O of/O Mole/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Town/LOCATION ,/O the/O little/O village/O half/O a/O league/O south/O along/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O and/O here/O and/O there/O the/O bright/O glitter/O of/O moonlight/O on/O water/O where/O icy/O streams/O descended/O from/O the/O mountain/O heights/O to/O cut/O across/O the/O plains/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O the/O world/O was/O a/O bleak/O emptiness/O of/O windswept/O hills/O and/O rocky/O fields/O spotted/O with/O snow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Finally/O a/O thick/O voice/O behind/O him/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O ,/O it/O 's/O the/O dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O the/O cage/O jerked/O to/O a/O sudden/O stop/O and/O hung/O there/O ,/O swinging/O slowly/O back/O and/O forth/O ,/O the/O ropes/O creaking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bring/O him/O in/O ,/O damn/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O was/O a/O grunt/O and/O a/O loud/O groaning/O of/O wood/O as/O the/O cage/O slid/O sideways/O and/O then/O the/O Wall/O was/O beneath/O him/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON waited/O until/O the/O swinging/O had/O stopped/O before/O he/O pushed/O open/O the/O cage/O door/O and/O hopped/O down/O onto/O the/O ice/O ./O 
A/O heavy/O figure/O in/O black/O was/O leaning/O on/O the/O winch/O ,/O while/O a/O second/O held/O the/O cage/O with/O a/O gloved/O hand/O ./O 
Their/O faces/O were/O muffled/O in/O woolen/O scarves/O so/O only/O their/O eyes/O showed/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O plump/O with/O layers/O of/O wool/O and/O leather/O ,/O black/O on/O black/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O will/O you/O be/O wanting/O ,/O this/O time/O of/O night/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O one/O by/O the/O winch/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O last/O look/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O men/O exchanged/O sour/O glances/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O all/O you/O want/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O other/O one/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O have/O a/O care/O you/O do/O n't/O fall/O off/O ,/O little/O man/O ./O 
The/O Old/O Bear/O would/O have/O our/O hides/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O small/O wooden/O shack/O stood/O under/O the/O great/O crane/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/LOCATION saw/O the/O dull/O glow/O of/O a/O brazier/O and/O felt/O a/O brief/O gust/O of/O warmth/O when/O the/O winch/O men/O opened/O the/O door/O and/O went/O back/O inside/O ./O 
And/O then/O he/O was/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O bitingly/O cold/O up/O here/O ,/O and/O the/O wind/O pulled/O at/O his/O clothes/O like/O an/O insistent/O lover/O ./O 
The/O top/O of/O the/O Wall/O was/O wider/O than/O the/O kingsroad/O often/O was/O ,/O so/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O no/O fear/O of/O falling/O ,/O although/O the/O footing/O was/O slicker/O than/O he/O would/O have/O liked/O ./O 
The/O brothers/O spread/O crushed/O stone/O across/O the/O walkways/O ,/O but/O the/O weight/O of/O countless/O footsteps/O would/O melt/O the/O Wall/O beneath/O ,/O so/O the/O ice/O would/O seem/O to/O grow/O around/O the/O gravel/O ,/O swallowing/O it/O ,/O until/O the/O path/O was/O bare/O again/O and/O it/O was/O time/O to/O crush/O more/O stone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Still/O ,/O it/O was/O nothing/O that/O Tyrion/O could/O not/O manage/O ./O 
He/O looked/O off/O to/O the/O east/O and/O west/O ,/O at/O the/O Wall/O stretching/O before/O him/O ,/O a/O vast/O white/O road/O with/O no/O beginning/O and/O no/O end/O and/O a/O dark/O abyss/O on/O either/O side/O ./O 
West/O ,/O he/O decided/O ,/O for/O no/O special/O reason/O ,/O and/O he/O began/O to/O walk/O that/O way/O ,/O following/O the/O pathway/O nearest/O the/O north/O edge/O ,/O where/O the/O gravel/O looked/O freshest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O bare/O cheeks/O were/O ruddy/O with/O the/O cold/O ,/O and/O his/O legs/O complained/O more/O loudly/O with/O every/O step/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON ignored/O them/O ./O 
The/O wind/O swirled/O around/O him/O ,/O gravel/O crunched/O beneath/O his/O boots/O ,/O while/O ahead/O the/O white/O ribbon/O followed/O the/O lines/O of/O the/O hills/O ,/O rising/O higher/O and/O higher/O ,/O until/O it/O was/O lost/O beyond/O the/O western/O horizon/O ./O 
He/O passed/O a/O massive/O catapult/O ,/O as/O tall/O as/O a/O city/O wall/O ,/O its/O base/O sunk/O deep/O into/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
The/O throwing/O arm/O had/O been/O taken/O off/O for/O repairs/O and/O then/O forgotten/O ;/O it/O lay/O there/O like/O a/O broken/O toy/O ,/O half-embedded/O in/O the/O ice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O On/O the/O far/O side/O of/O the/O catapult/O ,/O a/O muffled/O voice/O called/O out/O a/O challenge/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O goes/O there/O ?/O 
Halt/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O stopped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O halt/O too/O long/O I/O 'll/O freeze/O in/O place/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O a/O shaggy/O pale/O shape/O slid/O toward/O him/O silently/O and/O sniffed/O at/O his/O furs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hello/O ,/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/O Snow/O moved/O closer/O ./O 
He/O looked/O bigger/O and/O heavier/O in/O his/O layers/O of/O fur/O and/O leather/O ,/O the/O hood/O of/O his/O cloak/O pulled/O down/O over/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannister/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O yanking/O loose/O the/O scarf/O to/O uncover/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O last/O place/O I/O would/O have/O expected/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O carried/O a/O heavy/O spear/O tipped/O in/O iron/O ,/O taller/O than/O he/O was/O ,/O and/O a/O sword/O hung/O at/O his/O side/O in/O a/O leather/O sheath/O ./O 
Across/O his/O chest/O was/O a/O gleaming/O black/O warhorn/O ,/O banded/O with/O silver/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O last/O place/O I/O would/O have/O expected/O to/O be/O seen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O captured/O by/O a/O whim/O ./O 
If/O I/O touch/O Ghost/O ,/O will/O he/O chew/O my/O hand/O off/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O with/O me/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON promised/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O scratched/O the/O white/O wolf/O behind/O the/O ears/O ./O 
The/O red/O eyes/O watched/O him/O impassively/O ./O 
The/O beast/O came/O up/O as/O high/O as/O his/O chest/O now/O ./O 
Another/O year/O ,/O and/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O the/O gloomy/O feeling/O he/O 'd/O be/O looking/O up/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O doing/O up/O here/O tonight/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Besides/O freezing/O your/O manhood/O off/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O drawn/O night/O guard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Again/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON has/O kindly/O arranged/O for/O the/O watch/O commander/O to/O take/O a/O special/O interest/O in/O me/O ./O 
He/O seems/O to/O think/O that/O if/O they/O keep/O me/O awake/O half/O the/O night/O ,/O I/O 'll/O fall/O asleep/O during/O morning/O drill/O ./O 
So/O far/O I/O have/O disappointed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O has/O Ghost/O learned/O to/O juggle/O yet/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Jon/PERSON ,/O smiling/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O Grenn/PERSON held/O his/O own/O against/O Haider/PERSON this/O morning/O ,/O and/O Pyp/O is/O no/O longer/O dropping/O his/O sword/O quite/O so/O often/O as/O he/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pyp/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pypar/O is/O his/O real/O name/O ./O 
The/O small/O boy/O with/O the/O large/O ears/O ./O 
He/O saw/O me/O working/O with/O Grenn/PERSON and/O asked/O for/O help/O ./O 
Thorne/PERSON had/O never/O even/O shown/O him/O the/O proper/O way/O to/O grip/O a/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O to/O look/O north/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O a/O mile/O of/O Wall/O to/O guard/O ./O 
Will/O you/O walk/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O walk/O slowly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O watch/O commander/O tells/O me/O I/O must/O walk/O ,/O to/O keep/O my/O blood/O from/O freezing/O ,/O but/O he/O never/O said/O how/O fast/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O walked/O ,/O with/O Ghost/O pacing/O along/O beside/O Jon/PERSON like/O a/O white/O shadow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O leave/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON sounded/O strangely/O sad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O plan/O to/O stop/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION on/O the/O way/O south/O ./O 
If/O there/O is/O any/O message/O that/O you/O would/O like/O me/O to/O deliver/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O Robb/PERSON that/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O command/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O and/O keep/O him/O safe/O ,/O so/O he/O might/O as/O well/O take/O up/O needlework/O with/O the/O girls/O and/O have/O Mikken/PERSON melt/O down/O his/O sword/O for/O horseshoes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O is/O bigger/O than/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O with/O a/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O decline/O to/O deliver/O any/O message/O that/O might/O get/O me/O killed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON will/O ask/O when/O I/O 'm/O coming/O home/O ./O 
Try/O to/O explain/O where/O I/O 've/O gone/O ,/O if/O you/O can/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O he/O can/O have/O all/O my/O things/O while/O I/O 'm/O away/O ,/O he/O 'll/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O People/O seemed/O to/O be/O asking/O a/O great/O deal/O of/O him/O today/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O could/O put/O all/O this/O in/O a/O letter/O ,/O you/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/O ca/O n't/O read/O yet/O ./O 
Bran/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O stopped/O suddenly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O message/O to/O send/O to/O Bran/O ./O 
Help/O him/O ,/O Tyrion/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O help/O could/O I/O give/O him/O ?/O 
I/O am/O no/O maester/O ,/O to/O ease/O his/O pain/O ./O 
I/O have/O no/O spells/O to/O give/O him/O back/O his/O legs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O gave/O me/O help/O when/O I/O needed/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O gave/O you/O nothing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Words/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O give/O your/O words/O to/O Bran/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O asking/O a/O lame/O man/O to/O teach/O a/O cripple/O how/O to/O dance/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O However/O sincere/O the/O lesson/O ,/O the/O result/O is/O likely/O to/O be/O grotesque/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O I/O know/O what/O it/O is/O to/O love/O a/O brother/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
I/O will/O give/O Bran/O whatever/O small/O help/O is/O in/O my/O power/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pulled/O off/O his/O glove/O and/O offered/O his/O bare/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Friend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/O found/O himself/O oddly/O touched/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Most/O of/O my/O kin/O are/O bastards/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O with/O a/O wry/O smile/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O you/O 're/O the/O first/O I/O 've/O had/O to/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pulled/O a/O glove/O off/O with/O his/O teeth/O and/O clasped/O Snow/O by/O the/O hand/O ,/O flesh/O against/O flesh/O ./O 
The/O boy/O 's/O grip/O was/O firm/O and/O strong/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O had/O donned/O his/O glove/O again/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON turned/O abruptly/O and/O walked/O to/O the/O low/O ,/O icy/O northern/O parapet/O ./O 
Beyond/O him/O the/O Wall/O fell/O away/O sharply/O ;/O beyond/O him/O there/O was/O only/O the/O darkness/O and/O the/O wild/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON followed/O him/O ,/O and/O side/O by/O side/O they/O stood/O upon/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O world/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O permitted/O the/O forest/O to/O come/O no/O closer/O than/O half/O a/O mile/O of/O the/O north/O face/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
The/O thickets/O of/O ironwood/O and/O sentinel/O and/O oak/O that/O had/O once/O grown/O there/O had/O been/O harvested/O centuries/O ago/O ,/O to/O create/O a/O broad/O swath/O of/O open/O ground/O through/O which/O no/O enemy/O could/O hope/O to/O pass/O unseen/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON had/O heard/O that/O elsewhere/O along/O the/O Wall/O ,/O between/O the/O three/O fortresses/O ,/O the/O wildwood/O had/O come/O creeping/O back/O over/O the/O decades/O ,/O that/O there/O were/O places/O where/O greygreen/O sentinels/O and/O pale/O white/O weirwoods/O had/O taken/O root/O in/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O Wall/O itself/O ,/O but/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION had/O a/O prodigious/O appetite/O for/O firewood/O ,/O and/O here/O the/O forest/O was/O still/O kept/O at/O bay/O by/O the/O axes/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O never/O far/O ,/O though/O ./O 
From/O up/O here/O Tyrion/O could/O see/O it/O ,/O the/O dark/O trees/O looming/O beyond/O the/O stretch/O of/O open/O ground/O ,/O like/O a/O second/O wall/O built/O parallel/O to/O the/O first/O ,/O a/O wall/O of/O night/O ./O 
Few/O axes/O had/O ever/O swung/O in/O that/O black/O wood/O ,/O where/O even/O the/O moonlight/O could/O not/O penetrate/O the/O ancient/O tangle/O of/O root/O and/O thorn/O and/O grasping/O limb/O ./O 
Out/O there/O the/O trees/O grew/O huge/O ,/O and/O the/O rangers/O said/O they/O seemed/O to/O brood/O and/O knew/O not/O men/O ./O 
It/O was/O small/O wonder/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O named/O it/O the/O haunted/O forest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O he/O stood/O there/O and/O looked/O at/O all/O that/O darkness/O with/O no/O fires/O burning/O anywhere/O ,/O with/O the/O wind/O blowing/O and/O the/O cold/O like/O a/O spear/O in/O his/O guts/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON felt/O as/O though/O he/O could/O almost/O believe/O the/O talk/O of/O the/O Others/O ,/O the/O enemy/O in/O the/O night/O ./O 
His/O jokes/O of/O grumkins/O and/O snarks/O no/O longer/O seemed/O quite/O so/O droll/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O uncle/O is/O out/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON said/O softly/O ,/O leaning/O on/O his/O spear/O as/O he/O stared/O off/O into/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O first/O night/O they/O sent/O me/O up/O here/O ,/O I/O thought/O ,/O Uncle/O Benjen/PERSON will/O ride/O back/O tonight/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O see/O him/O first/O and/O blow/O the/O horn/O ./O 
He/O never/O came/O ,/O though/O ./O 
Not/O that/O night/O and/O not/O any/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Give/O him/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Far/O off/O to/O the/O north/O ,/O a/O wolf/O began/O to/O howl/O ./O 
Another/O voice/O picked/O up/O the/O call/O ,/O then/O another/O ./O 
Ghost/O cocked/O his/O head/O and/O listened/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O he/O does/O n't/O come/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON promised/O ,/O \/O ``/O Ghost/O and/O I/O will/O go/O find/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O put/O his/O hand/O on/O the/O direwolf/O s/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O believe/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O but/O what/O he/O thought/O was/O ,/O And/O who/O will/O go/O find/O you/O ?/O 
He/O shivered/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
