-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O too/O far/O to/O make/O out/O the/O banners/O clearly/O ,/O but/O even/O through/O the/O drifting/O fog/O she/O could/O see/O that/O they/O were/O white/O ,/O with/O a/O dark/O smudge/O in/O their/O center/O that/O could/O only/O be/O the/O direwolf/O of/O Stark/O ,/O grey/O upon/O its/O icy/O field/O ./O 
When/O she/O saw/O it/O with/O her/O own/O eyes/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON reined/O up/O her/O horse/O and/O bowed/O her/O head/O in/O thanks/O ./O 
The/O gods/O were/O good/O ./O 
She/O was/O not/O too/O late/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O await/O our/O coming/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/O Wylis/O Manderly/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O as/O my/O lord/O father/O swore/O they/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O us/O not/O keep/O them/O waiting/O any/O longer/O ,/O ser/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON put/O the/O spurs/O to/O his/O horse/O and/O trotted/O briskly/O toward/O the/O banners/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON rode/O beside/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Wylis/O and/O his/O brother/O Ser/PERSON Wendel/PERSON followed/O ,/O leading/O their/O levies/O ,/O near/O fifteen/O hundred/O men/O :/O some/O twenty-odd/O knights/O and/O as/O many/O squires/O ,/O two/O hundred/O mounted/O lances/O ,/O swordsmen/O ,/O and/O freeriders/O ,/O and/O the/O rest/O foot/O ,/O armed/O with/O spears/O ,/O pikes/O and/O tridents/O ./O 
Lord/O Wyman/PERSON had/O remained/O behind/O to/O see/O to/O the/O defenses/O of/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ./O 
A/O man/O of/O near/O sixty/O years/O ,/O he/O had/O grown/O too/O stout/O to/O sit/O a/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O I/O had/O thought/O to/O see/O war/O again/O in/O my/O lifetime/O ,/O I/O should/O have/O eaten/O a/O few/O less/O eels/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O 'd/O told/O Catelyn/PERSON when/O he/O met/O her/O ship/O ,/O slapping/O his/O massive/O belly/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
His/O fingers/O were/O fat/O as/O sausages/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O boys/O will/O see/O you/O safe/O to/O your/O son/O ,/O though/O ,/O have/O no/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O \/O ``/O boys/O \/O ''/O were/O both/O older/O than/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O and/O she/O might/O have/O wished/O that/O they/O did/O not/O take/O after/O their/O father/O quite/O so/O closely/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Wylis/PERSON was/O only/O a/O few/O eels/O short/O of/O not/O being/O able/O to/O mount/O his/O own/O horse/O ;/O she/O pitied/O the/O poor/O animal/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Wendel/PERSON ,/O the/O younger/O boy/O ,/O would/O have/O been/O the/O fattest/O man/O she/O 'd/O ever/O known/O ,/O had/O she/O only/O neglected/O to/O meet/O his/O father/O and/O brother/O ./O 
Wylis/PERSON was/O quiet/O and/O formal/O ,/O Wendel/PERSON loud/O and/O boisterous/O ;/O both/O had/O ostentatious/O walrus/O mustaches/O and/O heads/O as/O bare/O as/O a/O baby/O 's/O bottom/O ;/O neither/O seemed/O to/O own/O a/O single/O garment/O that/O was/O not/O spotted/O with/O food/O stains/O ./O 
Yet/O she/O liked/O them/O well/O enough/O ;/O they/O had/O gotten/O her/O to/O Robb/PERSON ,/O as/O their/O father/O had/O vowed/O ,/O and/O nothing/O else/O mattered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O was/O pleased/O to/O see/O that/O her/O son/O had/O sent/O eyes/O out/O ,/O even/O to/O the/O east/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O would/O come/O from/O the/O south/O when/O they/O came/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O good/O that/O Robb/PERSON was/O being/O careful/O ./O 
My/O son/O is/O leading/O a/O host/O to/O war/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O still/O only/O half/O believing/O it/O ./O 
She/O was/O desperately/O afraid/O for/O him/O ,/O and/O for/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O yet/O she/O could/O not/O deny/O feeling/O a/O certain/O pride/O as/O well/O ./O 
A/O year/O ago/O he/O had/O been/O a/O boy/O ./O 
What/O was/O he/O now/O ?/O 
she/O wondered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outriders/O spied/O the/O Manderly/O banners-the/O white/O merman/O with/O trident/O in/O hand/O ,/O rising/O from/O a/O blue-green/O sea-and/O hailed/O them/O warmly/O ./O 
They/O were/O led/O to/O a/O spot/O of/O high/O ground/O dry/O enough/O for/O a/O camp/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Wylis/PERSON called/O a/O halt/O there/O ,/O and/O remained/O behind/O with/O his/O men/O to/O see/O the/O fires/O laid/O and/O the/O horses/O tended/O ,/O while/O his/O brother/O Wendel/PERSON rode/O on/O with/O Catelyn/PERSON and/O her/O uncle/O to/O present/O their/O father/O 's/O respects/O to/O their/O liege/O lord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O ground/O under/O their/O horses/O '/O hooves/O was/O soft/O and/O wet/O ./O 
It/O fell/O away/O slowly/O beneath/O them/O as/O they/O rode/O past/O smoky/O peat/O fires/O ,/O lines/O of/O horses/O ,/O and/O wagons/O heavy-laden/O with/O hardbread/O and/O salt/O beef/O ./O 
On/O a/O stony/O outcrop/O of/O land/O higher/O than/O the/O surrounding/O country/O ,/O they/O passed/O a/O lord/O 's/O pavilion/O with/O walls/O of/O heavy/O sailcloth/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON recognized/O the/O banner/O ,/O the/O bull/O moose/O of/O the/O Hornwoods/O ,/O brown/O on/O its/O dark/O orange/O field/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Just/O beyond/O ,/O through/O the/O mists/O ,/O she/O glimpsed/O the/O walls/O and/O towers/O of/O Moat/O Cailin/O .../O or/O what/O remained/O of/O them/O ./O 
Immense/O blocks/O of/O black/O basalt/O ,/O each/O as/O large/O as/O a/O crofter/O 's/O cottage/O ,/O lay/O scattered/O and/O tumbled/O like/O a/O child/O 's/O wooden/O blocks/O ,/O half-sunk/O in/O the/O soft/O boggy/O soil/O ./O 
Nothing/O else/O remained/O of/O a/O curtain/O wall/O that/O had/O once/O stood/O as/O high/O as/O Winterfell/PERSON 's/O ./O 
The/O wooden/O keep/O was/O gone/O entirely/O ,/O rotted/O away/O a/O thousand/O years/O past/O ,/O with/O not/O so/O much/O as/O a/O timber/O to/O mark/O where/O it/O had/O stood/O ./O 
All/O that/O was/O left/O of/O the/O great/O stronghold/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O were/O three/O towers/O .../O three/O where/O there/O had/O once/O been/O twenty/O ,/O if/O the/O taletellers/O could/O be/O believed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Gatehouse/O Tower/O looked/O sound/O enough/O ,/O and/O even/O boasted/O a/O few/O feet/O of/O standing/O wall/O to/O either/O side/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O Drunkard/O 's/O Tower/O ,/O off/O in/O the/O bog/O where/O the/O south/O and/O west/O walls/O had/O once/O met/O ,/O leaned/O like/O a/O man/O about/O to/O spew/O a/O bellyful/O of/O wine/O into/O the/O gutter/O ./O 
And/O the/O tall/O ,/O slender/O Children/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O where/O legend/O said/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O had/O once/O called/O upon/O their/O nameless/O gods/O to/O send/O the/O hammer/O of/O the/O waters/O ,/O had/O lost/O half/O its/O crown/O ./O 
It/O looked/O as/O if/O some/O great/O beast/O had/O taken/O a/O bite/O out/O of/O the/O crenellations/O along/O the/O tower/O top/O ,/O and/O spit/O the/O rubble/O across/O the/O bog/O ./O 
All/O three/O towers/O were/O green/O with/O moss/O ./O 
A/O tree/O was/O growing/O out/O between/O the/O stones/O on/O the/O north/O side/O of/O the/O Gatehouse/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O its/O gnarled/O limbs/O festooned/O with/O ropy/O white/O blankets/O of/O ghostskin/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON exclaimed/O when/O he/O saw/O what/O lay/O before/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ?/O 
It/O 's/O no/O more/O than/O a/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O death/O trap/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON finished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O how/O it/O looks/O ,/O Uncle/O ./O 
I/O thought/O the/O same/O the/O first/O time/O I/O saw/O it/O ,/O but/O Ned/PERSON assured/O me/O that/O this/O ruin/O is/O more/O formidable/O than/O it/O seems/O ./O 
The/O three/O surviving/O towers/O command/O the/O causeway/O from/O all/O sides/O ,/O and/O any/O enemy/O must/O pass/O between/O them/O ./O 
The/O bogs/O here/O are/O impenetrable/O ,/O full/O of/O quicksands/O and/O suckholes/O and/O teeming/O with/O snakes/O ./O 
To/O assault/O any/O of/O the/O towers/O ,/O an/O army/O would/O need/O to/O wade/O through/O waist-deep/O black/O muck/O ,/O cross/O a/O moat/O full/O of/O lizard-lions/O ,/O and/O scale/O walls/O slimy/O with/O moss/O ,/O all/O the/O while/O exposing/O themselves/O to/O fire/O from/O archers/O in/O the/O other/O towers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O gave/O her/O uncle/O a/O grim/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O when/O night/O falls/O ,/O there/O are/O said/O to/O be/O ghosts/O ,/O cold/O vengeful/O spirits/O of/O the/O north/O who/O hunger/O for/O southron/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Brynden/PERSON chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remind/O me/O not/O to/O linger/O here/O ./O 
Last/O I/O looked/O ,/O I/O was/O southron/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Standards/O had/O been/O raised/O atop/O all/O three/O towers/O ./O 
The/O Karstark/O sunburst/O hung/O from/O the/O Drunkard/O 's/O Tower/O ,/O beneath/O the/O direwolf/O ;/O on/O the/O Children/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Tower/ORGANIZATION it/O was/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON 's/O giant/O in/O shattered/O chains/O ./O 
But/O on/O the/O Gatehouse/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O the/O Stark/O banner/O flew/O alone/O ./O 
That/O was/O where/O Robb/PERSON had/O made/O his/O seat/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON made/O for/O it/O ,/O with/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Wendel/PERSON behind/O her/O ,/O their/O horses/O stepping/O slowly/O down/O the/O log-andplank/O road/O that/O had/O been/O laid/O across/O the/O green-and-black/O fields/O of/O mud/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O found/O her/O son/O surrounded/O by/O his/O father/O 's/O lords/O bannermen/O ,/O in/O a/O drafty/O hall/O with/O a/O peat/O fire/O smoking/O in/O a/O black/O hearth/O ./O 
He/O was/O seated/O at/O a/O massive/O stone/O table/O ,/O a/O pile/O of/O maps/O and/O papers/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ,/O talking/O intently/O with/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON and/O the/O Greatjon/O ./O 
At/O first/O he/O did/O not/O notice/O her/O .../O but/O his/O wolf/O did/O ./O 
The/O great/O grey/O beast/O was/O lying/O near/O the/O fire/O ,/O but/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON entered/O he/O lifted/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O his/O golden/O eyes/O met/O hers/O ./O 
The/O lords/O fell/O silent/O one/O by/O one/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON looked/O up/O at/O the/O sudden/O quiet/O and/O saw/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O voice/O thick/O with/O emotion/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON wanted/O to/O run/O to/O him/O ,/O to/O kiss/O his/O sweet/O brow/O ,/O to/O wrap/O him/O in/O her/O arms/O and/O hold/O him/O so/O tightly/O that/O he/O would/O never/O come/O to/O harm/O .../O but/O here/O in/O front/O of/O his/O lords/O ,/O she/O dared/O not/O ./O 
He/O was/O playing/O a/O man/O 's/O part/O now/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O not/O take/O that/O away/O from/O him/O ./O 
So/O she/O held/O herself/O at/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O basalt/O slab/O they/O were/O using/O for/O a/O table/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O got/O to/O his/O feet/O and/O padded/O across/O the/O room/O to/O where/O she/O stood/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O bigger/O than/O a/O wolf/O ought/O to/O be/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O grown/O a/O beard/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O to/O Robb/PERSON ,/O while/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON sniffed/O her/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O rubbed/O his/O stubbled/O jaw/O ,/O suddenly/O awkward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O chin/O hairs/O were/O redder/O than/O the/O ones/O on/O his/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O like/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON stroked/O the/O wolfs/O head/O ,/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O makes/O you/O look/O like/O my/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON nipped/O at/O her/O fingers/O ,/O playful/O ,/O and/O trotted/O back/O to/O his/O place/O by/O the/O fire/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Helman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON was/O the/O first/O to/O follow/O the/O direwolf/O across/O the/O room/O to/O pay/O his/O respects/O ,/O kneeling/O before/O her/O and/O pressing/O his/O brow/O to/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O you/O are/O fair/O as/O ever/O ,/O a/O welcome/O sight/O in/O troubled/O times/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O Glovers/O followed/O ,/O Galbart/PERSON and/O Robert/PERSON ,/O and/O Greatjon/O Umber/O ,/O and/O the/O rest/O ,/O one/O by/O one/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON was/O the/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O not/O looked/O to/O see/O you/O here/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O knelt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O not/O thought/O to/O be/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O until/O I/O came/O ashore/O at/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ,/O and/O Lord/O Wyman/PERSON told/O me/O that/O Robb/PERSON had/O called/O the/O banners/O ./O 
You/O know/O his/O son/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Wendel/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Wendel/PERSON Manderly/PERSON stepped/O forward/O and/O bowed/O as/O low/O as/O his/O girth/O would/O allow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O my/O uncle/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O left/O my/O sister/O 's/O service/O for/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Blackfish/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O for/O joining/O us/O ,/O ser/O ./O 
We/O need/O men/O of/O your/O courage/O ./O 
And/O you/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Wendel/PERSON ,/O I/O am/O glad/O to/O have/O you/O here/O ./O 
Is/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON with/O you/O as/O well/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ?/O 
I/O 've/O missed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON is/O on/O his/O way/O north/O from/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ./O 
I/O have/O named/O him/O castellan/O and/O commanded/O him/O to/O hold/O Winterfell/PERSON till/O our/O return/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON is/O a/O wise/O counsellor/O ,/O but/O unskilled/O in/O the/O arts/O of/O war/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Have/O no/O fear/O on/O that/O count/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON told/O her/O in/O his/O bass/O rumble/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Winterfell/O is/O safe/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O shove/O our/O swords/O up/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O bunghole/O soon/O enough/O ,/O begging/O your/O pardons/O ,/O and/O then/O it/O 's/O on/O to/O the/O Red/O Keep/O to/O free/O Ned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O a/O question/O ,/O as/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Dreadfort/O ,/O had/O a/O small/O voice/O ,/O yet/O when/O he/O spoke/O larger/O men/O quieted/O to/O listen/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O curiously/O pale/O ,/O almost/O without/O color/O ,/O and/O his/O look/O disturbing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O said/O that/O you/O hold/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O dwarf/O son/O as/O captive/O ./O 
Have/O you/O brought/O him/O to/O us/O ?/O 
I/O vow/O ,/O we/O should/O make/O good/O use/O of/O such/O a/O hostage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O hold/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O but/O no/O longer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O forced/O to/O admit/O ./O 
A/O chorus/O of/O consternation/O greeted/O the/O news/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O no/O more/O pleased/O than/O you/O ,/O my/O lords/O ./O 
The/O gods/O saw/O fit/O to/O free/O him/O ,/O with/O some/O help/O from/O my/O fool/O of/O a/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O ought/O not/O to/O be/O so/O open/O in/O her/O contempt/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O but/O her/O parting/O from/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION had/O not/O been/O pleasant/O ./O 
She/O had/O offered/O to/O take/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON with/O her/O ,/O to/O foster/O him/O at/O Winterfell/ORGANIZATION for/O a/O few/O years/O ./O 
The/O company/O of/O other/O boys/O would/O do/O him/O good/O ,/O she/O had/O dared/O to/O suggest/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON 's/O rage/O had/O been/O frightening/O to/O behold/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sister/O or/O no/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O had/O replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O if/O you/O try/O to/O steal/O my/O son/O ,/O you/O will/O leave/O by/O the/O Moon/LOCATION Door/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O After/O that/O there/O was/O no/O more/O to/O be/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O lords/O were/O anxious/O to/O question/O her/O further/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON raised/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O doubt/O we/O will/O have/O time/O for/O all/O this/O later/O ,/O but/O my/O journey/O has/O fatigued/O me/O ./O 
I/O would/O speak/O with/O my/O son/O alone/O ./O 
I/O know/O you/O will/O forgive/O me/O ,/O my/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O gave/O them/O no/O choice/O ;/O led/O by/O the/O ever-obliging/O Lord/O Hornwood/PERSON ,/O the/O bannermen/O bowed/O and/O took/O their/O leave/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O you/O ,/O Theon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O added/O when/O Greyjoy/PERSON lingered/O ./O 
He/O smiled/O and/O left/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O was/O ale/O and/O cheese/O on/O the/O table/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON tilled/O a/O horn/O ,/O sat/O ,/O sipped/O ,/O and/O studied/O her/O son/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O taller/O than/O when/O she/O 'd/O left/O ,/O and/O the/O wisps/O of/O beard/O did/O make/O him/O look/O older/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Edmure/PERSON was/O sixteen/O when/O he/O grew/O his/O first/O whiskers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O be/O sixteen/O soon/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O are/O fifteen/O now/O ./O 
Fifteen/O ,/O and/O leading/O a/O host/O to/O battle/O ./O 
Can/O you/O understand/O why/O I/O might/O fear/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O look/O grew/O stubborn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O one/O else/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pray/O ,/O who/O were/O those/O men/O I/O saw/O here/O a/O moment/O ago/O ?/O 
Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON ,/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ,/O Galbart/PERSON and/O Robert/PERSON Glover/PERSON ,/O the/O Greatjon/LOCATION ,/O Heiman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON .../O you/O might/O have/O given/O the/O command/O to/O any/O of/O them/O ./O 
Gods/O be/O good/O ,/O you/O might/O even/O have/O sent/O Theon/PERSON ,/O though/O he/O would/O not/O be/O my/O choice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O are/O not/O Starks/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O are/O men/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O seasoned/O in/O battle/O ./O 
You/O were/O fighting/O with/O wooden/O swords/O less/O than/O a/O year/O past/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O saw/O anger/O in/O his/O eyes/O at/O that/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O gone/O as/O quick/O as/O it/O came/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O he/O was/O a/O boy/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O abashed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O .../O are/O you/O sending/O me/O back/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O ./O 
You/O ought/O never/O have/O left/O ./O 
Yet/O I/O dare/O not/O ,/O not/O now/O ./O 
You/O have/O come/O too/O far/O ./O 
Someday/O these/O lords/O will/O look/O to/O you/O as/O their/O liege/O ./O 
If/O I/O pack/O you/O off/O now/O ,/O like/O a/O child/O being/O sent/O to/O bed/O without/O his/O supper/O ,/O they/O will/O remember/O ,/O and/O laugh/O about/O it/O in/O their/O cups/O ./O 
The/O day/O will/O come/O when/O you/O need/O them/O to/O respect/O you/O ,/O even/O fear/O you/O a/O little/O ./O 
Laughter/O is/O poison/O to/O fear/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O do/O that/O to/O you/O ,/O much/O as/O I/O might/O wish/O to/O keep/O you/O safe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O my/O thanks/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O relief/O obvious/O beneath/O the/O formality/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O reached/O across/O his/O table/O and/O touched/O his/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O my/O firstborn/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
I/O have/O only/O to/O look/O at/O you/O to/O remember/O the/O day/O you/O came/O into/O the/O world/O ,/O red/O -/O faced/O and/O squalling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O rose/O ,/O clearly/O uncomfortable/O with/O her/O touch/O ,/O and/O walked/O to/O the/O hearth/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON rubbed/O his/O head/O against/O his/O leg/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O .../O about/O Father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O reports/O of/O Robert/PERSON 's/O sudden/O death/O and/O Ned/PERSON 's/O fall/O had/O frightened/O Catelyn/LOCATION more/O than/O she/O could/O say/O ,/O but/O she/O would/O not/O let/O her/O son/O see/O her/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Manderly/PERSON told/O me/O when/O I/O landed/O at/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ./O 
Have/O you/O had/O any/O word/O of/O your/O sisters/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O letter/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ,/O scratching/O his/O direwolf/O under/O the/O jaw/O ./O 
\/O ``/O One/O for/O you/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O it/O came/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O went/O to/O the/O table/O ,/O rummaged/O among/O some/O maps/O and/O papers/O ,/O and/O returned/O with/O a/O crumpled/O parchment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O one/O she/O wrote/O me/O ,/O I/O never/O thought/O to/O bring/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Something/O in/O Robb/PERSON 's/O tone/O troubled/O her/O ./O 
She/O smoothed/O out/O the/O paper/O and/O read/O ./O 
Concern/O gave/O way/O to/O disbelief/O ,/O then/O to/O anger/O ,/O and/O lastly/O to/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O Cersei/PERSON 's/O letter/O ,/O not/O your/O sister/O 's/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O ''/O ,/O ``/O said/O when/O she/O was/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O real/O message/O is/O in/O what/O Sansa/O does/O not/O say/O ./O 
All/O this/O about/O how/O kindly/O and/O gently/O the/O Lannisters/O are/O treating/O her/O .../O I/O know/O the/O sound/O of/O a/O threat/O ,/O even/O whispered/O ./O 
They/O have/O Sansa/O hostage/O ,/O and/O they/O mean/O to/O keep/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O 's/O no/O mention/O of/O Arya/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON pointed/O out/O ,/O miserable/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON did/O not/O want/O to/O think/O what/O that/O might/O mean/O ,/O not/O now/O ,/O not/O here/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O hoped/O .../O if/O you/O still/O held/O the/O Imp/O ,/O a/O trade/O of/O hostages/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O took/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O letter/O and/O crumpled/O it/O in/O his/O fist/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O tell/O from/O the/O way/O he/O did/O it/O that/O it/O was/O not/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O there/O word/O from/O the/O Eyrie/O ?/O 
I/O wrote/O to/O Aunt/PERSON Lysa/PERSON ,/O asking/O help/O ./O 
Has/O she/O called/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O banners/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O ?/O 
Will/O the/O knights/O of/O the/O Vale/O come/O join/O us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O best/O of/O them/O ,/O my/O uncle/O .../O but/O Brynden/PERSON Blackfish/PERSON was/O a/O Tully/O first/O ./O 
My/O sister/O is/O not/O about/O to/O stir/O beyond/O her/O Bloody/O Gate/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON took/O it/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O what/O are/O we/O going/O to/O do/O ?/O 
I/O brought/O this/O whole/O army/O together/O ,/O eighteen/O thousand/O men/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O n't/O .../O I/O 'm/O not/O certain/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O looked/O to/O her/O ,/O his/O eyes/O shining/O ,/O the/O proud/O young/O lord/O melted/O away/O in/O an/O instant/O ,/O and/O quick/O as/O that/O he/O was/O a/O child/O again/O ,/O a/O fifteen/O -/O year-old/O boy/O looking/O to/O his/O mother/O for/O answers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O would/O not/O do/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O so/O afraid/O of/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O gently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O his/O head/O away/O ,/O to/O hide/O the/O first/O tear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O march/O .../O even/O if/O we/O win/O .../O the/O Lannisters/O hold/O Sansa/LOCATION ,/O and/O Father/O ./O 
They/O 'll/O kill/O them/O ,/O wo/O n't/O they/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O want/O us/O to/O think/O so/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O mean/O they/O 're/O lying/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O know/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
What/O I/O do/O know/O is/O that/O you/O have/O no/O choice/O ./O 
If/O you/O go/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O swear/O fealty/O ,/O you/O will/O never/O be/O allowed/O to/O leave/O ./O 
If/O you/O turn/O your/O tail/O and/O retreat/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O your/O lords/O will/O lose/O all/O respect/O for/O you/O ./O 
Some/O may/O even/O go/O over/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Then/O the/O queen/O ,/O with/O that/O much/O less/O to/O fear/O ,/O can/O do/O as/O she/O likes/O with/O her/O prisoners/O ./O 
Our/O best/O hope/O ,/O our/O only/O true/O hope/O ,/O is/O that/O you/O can/O defeat/O the/O foe/O in/O the/O field/O ./O 
If/O you/O should/O chance/O to/O take/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON or/O the/O Kingslayer/O captive/O ,/O why/O then/O a/O trade/O might/O very/O well/O be/O possible/O ,/O but/O that/O is/O not/O the/O heart/O of/O it/O ./O 
So/O long/O as/O you/O have/O power/O enough/O that/O they/O must/O fear/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON and/O your/O sister/O should/O be/O safe/O ./O 
Cersei/O is/O wise/O enough/O to/O know/O that/O she/O may/O need/O them/O to/O make/O her/O peace/O ,/O should/O the/O fighting/O go/O against/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O if/O the/O fighting/O does/O n't/O go/O against/O her/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O if/O it/O goes/O against/O us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O I/O will/O not/O soften/O the/O truth/O for/O you/O ./O 
If/O you/O lose/O ,/O there/O is/O no/O hope/O for/O any/O of/O us/O ./O 
They/O say/O there/O is/O naught/O but/O stone/O at/O the/O heart/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O 
Remember/O the/O fate/O of/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O children/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O saw/O the/O fear/O in/O his/O young/O eyes/O then/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O a/O strength/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O I/O will/O not/O lose/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O vowed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O what/O you/O know/O of/O the/O fighting/O in/O the/O riverlands/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O learn/O if/O he/O was/O truly/O ready/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Less/O than/O a/O fortnight/O past/O ,/O they/O fought/O a/O battle/O in/O the/O hills/O below/O the/O Golden/O Tooth/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Uncle/O Edmure/PERSON had/O sent/O Lord/O Vance/PERSON and/O Lord/O Piper/PERSON to/O hold/O the/O pass/O ,/O but/O the/O Kingslayer/O ''/O ,/O ``/O descended/O on/O them/O and/O put/O them/O to/O flight/O ./O 
Lord/O Vance/PERSON was/O slain/O ./O 
The/O last/O word/O we/O had/O was/O that/O Lord/O Piper/PERSON was/O falling/O back/O to/O join/O your/O brother/O and/O his/O other/O bannermen/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O with/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON on/O his/O heels/O ./O 
That/O 's/O not/O the/O worst/O of/O it/O ,/O though/O ./O 
All/O the/O time/O they/O were/O battling/O in/O the/O pass/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON was/O bringing/O a/O second/O Lannister/O army/O around/O from/O the/O south/O ./O 
It/O 's/O said/O to/O be/O even/O larger/O than/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O host/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Father/O must/O have/O known/O that/O ,/O because/O he/O sent/O out/O some/O men/O to/O oppose/O them/O ,/O under/O the/O king/O 's/O own/O banner/O ./O 
He/O gave/O the/O command/O to/O some/O southron/O lordling/O ,/O Lord/O Erik/PERSON or/O Derik/PERSON or/O something/O like/O that/O ,/O but/O Ser/PERSON Raymun/PERSON Darry/PERSON rode/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O letter/O said/O there/O were/O other/O knights/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O a/O force/O of/O Father/O 's/O own/O guardsmen/O ./O 
Only/O it/O was/O a/O trap/O ./O 
Lord/O Derik/PERSON had/O no/O sooner/O crossed/O the/O Red/O Fork/O than/O the/O Lannisters/O fell/O upon/O him/O ,/O the/O king/O 's/O banner/O be/O damned/O ,/O and/O Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON took/O them/O in/O the/O rear/O as/O they/O tried/O to/O pull/O back/O across/O the/O Mummer/O 's/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ./O 
This/O Lord/O Derik/PERSON and/O a/O few/O others/O may/O have/O escaped/O ,/O no/O one/O is/O certain/O ,/O but/O Ser/PERSON Raymun/PERSON was/O killed/O ,/O and/O most/O of/O our/O men/O from/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON has/O closed/O off/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O it/O 's/O said/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O 's/O marching/O north/O toward/O Harrenhal/PERSON ,/O burning/O as/O he/O goes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Grim/O and/O grimmer/O ,/O thought/O Catelyn/O ./O 
It/O was/O worse/O than/O she/O 'd/O imagined/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O mean/O to/O meet/O him/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O comes/O so/O far/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O thinks/O he/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O sent/O word/O to/O Howland/PERSON Reed/PERSON ,/O Father/O 's/O old/O friend/O at/O Greywater/O Watch/O ./O 
If/O the/O Lannisters/O come/O up/O the/O Neck/O ,/O the/O crannogmen/O will/O bleed/O them/O every/O step/O of/O the/O way/O ,/O but/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON says/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON is/O too/O smart/O for/O that/O ,/O and/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON agrees/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O stay/O close/O to/O the/O Trident/O ,/O they/O believe/O ,/O taking/O the/O castles/O of/O the/O river/O lords/O one/O by/O one/O ,/O until/O Riverrun/PERSON stands/O alone/O ./O 
We/O need/O to/O march/O south/O to/O meet/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O very/O idea/O of/O it/O chilled/O Catelyn/O to/O the/O bone/O ./O 
What/O chance/O would/O a/O fifteen/O -/O year-old/O boy/O have/O against/O seasoned/O battle/O commanders/O like/O Jaime/PERSON and/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O wise/O ?/O 
You/O are/O strongly/O placed/O here/O ./O 
It/O 's/O said/O that/O the/O old/O Kings/O in/O the/O North/O could/O stand/O at/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON and/O throw/O back/O hosts/O ten/O times/O the/O size/O of/O their/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O but/O our/O food/O and/O supplies/O are/O running/O low/O ,/O and/O this/O is/O not/O land/O we/O can/O live/O off/O easily/O ./O 
We/O 've/O been/O waiting/O for/O Lord/O Manderly/O ,/O but/O now/O that/O his/O sons/O have/O joined/O us/O ,/O we/O need/O to/O march/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O was/O hearing/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O speaking/O with/O her/O son/O 's/O voice/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
Over/O the/O years/O ,/O she/O had/O hosted/O many/O of/O them/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O been/O welcomed/O with/O Ned/PERSON to/O their/O own/O hearths/O and/O tables/O ./O 
She/O knew/O what/O sorts/O of/O men/O they/O were/O ,/O each/O one/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O if/O Robb/PERSON did/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O yet/O there/O was/O sense/O in/O what/O they/O said/O ./O 
This/O host/O her/O son/O had/O assembled/O was/O not/O a/O standing/O army/O such/O as/O the/O Free/O Cities/O were/O accustomed/O to/O maintain/O ,/O nor/O a/O force/O of/O guardsmen/O paid/O in/O coin/O ./O 
Most/O of/O them/O were/O smallfolk/O :/O crofters/O ,/O fieldhands/O ,/O fishermen/O ,/O sheepherders/O ,/O the/O sons/O of/O innkeeps/O and/O traders/O and/O tanners/O ,/O leavened/O with/O a/O smattering/O of/O sellswords/O and/O freeriders/O hungry/O for/O plunder/O ./O 
When/O their/O lords/O called/O ,/O they/O came/O .../O but/O not/O forever/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Marching/O is/O all/O very/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O to/O her/O son/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O where/O ,/O and/O to/O what/O purpose/O ?/O 
What/O do/O you/O mean/O to/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON hesitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Greatjon/PERSON thinks/O we/O should/O take/O the/O battle/O to/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON and/O surprise/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O the/O Glovers/O and/O the/O Karstarks/PERSON feel/O we/O 'd/O be/O wiser/O to/O go/O around/O his/O army/O and/O join/O up/O with/O Uncle/O Ser/O Edmure/O against/O the/O Kingslayer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O ran/O his/O fingers/O through/O his/O shaggy/O ''/O ,/O ``/O mane/O of/O auburn/O hair/O ,/O looking/O unhappy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Though/O by/O the/O time/O we/O reach/O Riverrun/O .../O I/O 'm/O not/O certain/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Be/O certain/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O her/O son/O ,/O \/O ``/O or/O go/O home/O and/O take/O up/O that/O wooden/O sword/O again/O ./O 
You/O can/O not/O afford/O to/O seem/O indecisive/O in/O front/O of/O men/O like/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON and/O Rickard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON ./O 
Make/O no/O mistake/O ,/O Robb-these/O are/O your/O bannermen/O ,/O not/O your/O friends/O ./O 
You/O named/O yourself/O battle/O commander/O ./O 
Command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O son/O looked/O at/O her/O ,/O startled/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O could/O not/O credit/O what/O he/O was/O hearing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O ask/O you/O again/O ./O 
What/O do/O you/O mean/O to/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON drew/O a/O map/O across/O the/O table/O ,/O a/O ragged/O piece/O of/O old/O leather/O covered/O with/O lines/O of/O faded/O paint/O ./O 
One/O end/O curled/O up/O from/O being/O rolled/O ;/O he/O weighed/O it/O down/O with/O his/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Both/O plans/O have/O virtues/O ,/O but/O .../O look/O ,/O if/O we/O try/O to/O swing/O around/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O host/O ,/O we/O take/O the/O risk/O of/O being/O caught/O between/O him/O and/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O and/O if/O we/O attack/O him/O .../O by/O all/O reports/O ,/O he/O has/O more/O men/O than/O I/O do/O ,/O and/O a/O lot/O more/O armored/O horse/O ./O 
The/O Greatjon/PERSON says/O that/O wo/O n't/O matter/O if/O we/O catch/O him/O with/O his/O breeches/O down/O ,/O but/O it/O seems/O to/O me/O that/O a/O man/O who/O has/O fought/O as/O many/O battles/O as/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON wo/O n't/O be/O so/O easily/O surprised/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O echoes/O of/O Ned/PERSON in/O his/O voice/O ,/O as/O he/O sat/O there/O ,/O puzzling/O over/O the/O map/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O more/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O leave/O a/O small/O force/O here/O to/O hold/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ,/O archers/O mostly/O ,/O and/O march/O the/O rest/O down/O the/O causeway/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O once/O we/O 're/O below/O the/O Neck/O ,/O I/O 'd/O split/O our/O host/O in/O two/O ./O 
The/O foot/O can/O continue/O down/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O while/O our/O horsemen/O cross/O the/O Green/ORGANIZATION Fork/ORGANIZATION at/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pointed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON gets/O word/O that/O we/O 've/O come/O south/O ,/O he/O 'll/O march/O north/O to/O engage/O our/O main/O host/O ,/O leaving/O our/O riders/O free/O to/O hurry/O down/O the/O west/O bank/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON sat/O back/O ,/O not/O quite/O daring/O to/O smile/O ,/O but/O pleased/O with/O himself/O and/O hungry/O for/O her/O praise/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O frowned/O down/O at/O the/O map/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'd/O put/O a/O river/O between/O the/O two/O parts/O of/O your/O army/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O between/O Jaime/O and/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O eagerly/O ./O 
The/O smile/O came/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O no/O crossing/O on/O the/O Green/LOCATION Fork/LOCATION above/O the/O ruby/O ford/O ,/O where/O Robert/PERSON won/O his/O crown/O ./O 
Not/O until/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ,/O all/O the/O way/O up/O here/O ,/O and/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON controls/O that/O bridge/O ./O 
He/O 's/O your/O father/O 's/O bannerman/O ,/O is/O n't/O that/O so/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Late/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O admitted/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O my/O father/O has/O never/O trusted/O him/O ./O 
Nor/O should/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O think/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O was/O impressed/O despite/O herself/O ./O 
He/O looks/O like/O a/O Tully/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O yet/O he/O 's/O still/O his/O father/O 's/O son/O ,/O and/O Ned/PERSON taught/O him/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Which/O force/O would/O you/O command/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O answered/O at/O once/O ./O 
Again/O like/O his/O father/O ;/O Ned/PERSON would/O always/O take/O the/O more/O dangerous/O task/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O the/O other/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Greatjon/O is/O always/O saying/O that/O we/O should/O smash/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ./O 
I/O thought/O I/O 'd/O give/O him/O the/O honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O his/O first/O misstep/O ,/O but/O how/O to/O make/O him/O see/O it/O without/O wounding/O his/O fledgling/O confidence/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O Your/O father/O once/O told/O me/O that/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON was/O as/O fearless/O as/O any/O man/O he/O had/O ever/O known/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON ate/O two/O of/O his/O fingers/O ,/O and/O he/O laughed/O about/O it/O ./O 
So/O you/O agree/O ,/O then/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O is/O not/O fearless/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O brave/O ,/O but/O that/O is/O very/O different/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O son/O considered/O that/O for/O a/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O eastern/O host/O will/O be/O all/O that/O stands/O between/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON and/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O them/O and/O whatever/O few/O bowmen/O I/O leave/O here/O at/O the/O Moat/O ./O 
So/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O someone/O fearless/O ,/O do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
You/O want/O cold/O cunning/O ,/O I/O should/O think/O ,/O not/O courage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Roose/PERSON Bolton/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O man/O scares/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O let/O us/O pray/O he/O will/O scare/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON nodded/O and/O rolled/O up/O the/O map/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O give/O the/O commands/O ,/O and/O assemble/O an/O escort/O to/O take/O you/O home/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O fought/O to/O keep/O herself/O strong/O ,/O for/O Ned/PERSON 's/O sake/O and/O for/O this/O stubborn/O brave/O son/O of/O theirs/O ./O 
She/O had/O put/O despair/O and/O fear/O aside/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O were/O garments/O she/O did/O not/O choose/O to/O wear/O .../O but/O now/O she/O saw/O that/O she/O had/O donned/O them/O after/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O going/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O heard/O herself/O say/O ,/O surprised/O at/O the/O sudden/O rush/O of/O tears/O that/O blurred/O her/O vision/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O may/O be/O dying/O behind/O the/O walls/O of/O Riverrun/O ./O 
My/O brother/O is/O surrounded/O by/O foes/O ./O 
I/O must/O go/O to/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
