-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O summons/O came/O in/O the/O hour/O before/O the/O dawn/O ,/O when/O the/O world/O was/O still/O and/O grey/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Alyn/PERSON shook/O him/O roughly/O from/O his/O dreams/O and/O Ned/PERSON stumbled/O into/O the/O predawn/O chill/O ,/O groggy/O from/O sleep/O ,/O to/O find/O his/O horse/O saddled/O and/O the/O king/O already/O mounted/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON wore/O thick/O brown/O gloves/O and/O a/O heavy/O fur/O cloak/O with/O a/O hood/O that/O covered/O his/O ears/O ,/O and/O looked/O for/O all/O the/O world/O like/O a/O bear/O sitting/O a/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Up/O ,/O Stark/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O roared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Up/O ,/O up/O !/O 
We/O have/O matters/O of/O state/O to/O discuss/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O By/O all/O means/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O inside/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Alyn/PERSON lifted/O the/O flap/O of/O the/O tent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O no/O ,/O no/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
His/O breath/O steamed/O with/O every/O word/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O camp/O is/O full/O of/O ears/O ./O 
Besides/O ,/O I/O want/O to/O ride/O out/O and/O taste/O this/O country/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON waited/O behind/O him/O with/O a/O dozen/O guardsmen/O ,/O Ned/PERSON saw/O ./O 
There/O was/O nothing/O to/O do/O but/O rub/O the/O sleep/O from/O his/O eyes/O ,/O dress/O ,/O and/O mount/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON set/O the/O pace/O ,/O driving/O his/O huge/O black/O destrier/O hard/O as/O Ned/PERSON galloped/O along/O beside/O him/O ,/O trying/O to/O keep/O up/O ./O 
He/O called/O out/O a/O question/O as/O they/O rode/O ,/O but/O the/O wind/O blew/O his/O words/O away/O ,/O and/O the/O king/O did/O not/O hear/O him/O ./O 
After/O that/O Ned/PERSON rode/O in/O silence/O ./O 
They/O soon/O left/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O took/O off/O across/O rolling/O plains/O dark/O with/O mist/O ./O 
By/O then/O the/O guard/O had/O fallen/O back/O a/O small/O distance/O ,/O safely/O out/O of/O earshot/O ,/O but/O still/O Robert/PERSON would/O not/O slow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dawn/O broke/O as/O they/O crested/O a/O low/O ridge/O ,/O and/O finally/O the/O king/O pulled/O up/O ./O 
By/O then/O they/O were/O miles/O south/O of/O the/O main/O party/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O flushed/O and/O exhilarated/O as/O Ned/PERSON reined/O up/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O ,/O laughing/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O feels/O good/O to/O get/O out/O and/O tide/O the/O way/O a/O man/O was/O meant/O to/O ride/O !/O 
I/O swear/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O this/O creeping/O along/O is/O enough/O to/O drive/O a/O man/O mad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O never/O been/O a/O patient/O man/O ,/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O damnable/O wheelhouse/O ,/O the/O way/O it/O creaks/O and/O groans/O ,/O climbing/O every/O Burnp/PERSON in/O the/O road/O as/O if/O it/O were/O a/O mountain/O .../O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O if/O that/O wretched/O thing/O breaks/O another/O axle/O ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O burn/O it/O ,/O and/O Cersei/LOCATION can/O walk/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O gladly/O light/O the/O torch/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O man/O !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O clapped/O him/O on/O the/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O half/O a/O mind/O to/O leave/O them/O all/O behind/O and/O just/O keep/O going/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O smile/O touched/O Ned/PERSON 's/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O believe/O you/O mean/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ,/O I/O do/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O say/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ?/O 
Just/O you/O and/O me/O ,/O two/O vagabond/O knights/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O our/O swords/O at/O our/O sides/O and/O the/O gods/O know/O what/O in/O front/O of/O us/O ,/O and/O maybe/O a/O farmer/O 's/O daughter/O or/O a/O tavern/O wench/O to/O warm/O our/O beds/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O that/O we/O could/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O we/O have/O duties/O now/O ,/O my/O liege/O .../O to/O the/O realm/O ,/O to/O our/O children/O ,/O I/O to/O my/O lady/O wife/O and/O you/O to/O your/O queen/O ./O 
We/O are/O not/O the/O boys/O we/O were/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O were/O never/O the/O boy/O you/O were/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O More/O 's/O the/O pity/O ./O 
And/O yet/O there/O was/O that/O one/O time/O .../O what/O was/O her/O name/O ,/O that/O common/O girl/O of/O yours/O ?/O 
Becca/PERSON ?/O 
No/O ,/O she/O was/O one/O of/O mine/O ,/O gods/O love/O her/O ,/O black/O hair/O and/O these/O sweet/O big/O eyes/O ,/O you/O could/O drown/O in/O them/O ./O 
Yours/O was/O .../O Aleena/PERSON ?/O 
No/O ./O 
You/O told/O me/O once/O ./O 
Was/O it/O Merryl/PERSON ?/O 
You/O know/O the/O one/O I/O mean/O ,/O your/O bastard/O 's/O mother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Her/O name/O was/O Wylla/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O with/O cool/O courtesy/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O would/O sooner/O not/O speak/O of/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wylla/O ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O grinned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O must/O have/O been/O a/O rare/O wench/O if/O she/O could/O make/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON forget/O his/O honor/O ,/O even/O for/O an/O hour/O ./O 
You/O never/O told/O me/O what/O she/O looked/O like/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O mouth/O tightened/O in/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nor/O will/O I./O Leave/O it/O be/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O for/O the/O love/O you/O say/O you/O bear/O me/O ./O 
I/O dishonored/O myself/O and/O I/O dishonored/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O in/O the/O sight/O of/O gods/O and/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O you/O scarcely/O knew/O Catelyn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O taken/O her/O to/O wife/O ./O 
She/O was/O carrying/O my/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O too/O hard/O on/O yourself/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
You/O always/O were/O ./O 
Damn/O it/O ,/O no/O woman/O wants/O Baelor/PERSON the/O Blessed/O in/O her/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slapped/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O knee/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O I/O 'll/O not/O press/O you/O if/O you/O feel/O so/O strong/O about/O it/O ,/O though/O I/O swear/O ,/O at/O times/O you/O 're/O so/O prickly/O you/O ought/O to/O take/O the/O hedgehog/O as/O your/O sigil/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O rising/O sun/O sent/O fingers/O of/O light/O through/O the/O pale/O white/O mists/O of/O dawn/O ./O 
A/O wide/O plain/O spread/O out/O beneath/O them/O ,/O bare/O and/O brown/O ,/O its/O flatness/O here/O and/O there/O relieved/O by/O long/O ,/O low/O hummocks/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON pointed/O them/O out/O to/O his/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O barrows/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O we/O ridden/O onto/O a/O graveyard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O barrows/O everywhere/O in/O the/O north/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O land/O is/O old/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O cold/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON grumbled/O ,/O pulling/O his/O cloak/O more/O tightly/O around/O himself/O ./O 
The/O guard/O had/O reined/O up/O well/O behind/O them/O ,/O at/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O ridge/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O I/O did/O not/O bring/O you/O out/O here/O to/O talk/O of/O graves/O or/O bicker/O about/O your/O bastard/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O rider/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O from/O Lord/LOCATION Varys/LOCATION in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
Here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O pulled/O a/O paper/O from/O his/O belt/O and/O handed/O it/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Varys/O the/O eunuch/O was/O the/O king/O 's/O master/O of/O whisperers/O ./O 
He/O served/O Robert/PERSON now/O as/O he/O had/O once/O served/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
Ned/PERSON unrolled/O the/O paper/O with/O trepidation/O ,/O thinking/O of/O Lysa/PERSON and/O her/O terrible/O accusation/O ,/O but/O the/O message/O did/O not/O concern/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O the/O source/O for/O this/O information/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O remember/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O might/O forget/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O bluntly/O ./O 
The/O Mormonts/O of/O Bear/LOCATION Island/LOCATION were/O an/O old/O house/O ,/O proud/O and/O honorable/O ,/O but/O their/O lands/O were/O cold/O and/O distant/O and/O poor/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O tried/O to/O swell/O the/O family/O coffers/O by/O selling/O some/O poachers/O to/O a/O Tyroshi/O slaver/O ./O 
As/O the/O Mormonts/O were/O bannermen/O to/O the/O Starks/PERSON ,/O his/O crime/O had/O dishonored/O the/O north/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O made/O the/O long/O journey/O west/O to/O Bear/LOCATION Island/LOCATION ,/O only/O to/O find/O when/O he/O arrived/O that/O Jorah/PERSON had/O taken/O ship/O beyond/O the/O reach/O of/O Ice/O and/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ./O 
Five/O years/O had/O passed/O since/O then/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O is/O now/O in/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O anxious/O to/O earn/O a/O royal/O pardon/O that/O would/O allow/O him/O to/O return/O from/O exile/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON explained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON makes/O good/O use/O of/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O the/O slaver/O has/O become/O a/O spy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O with/O distaste/O ./O 
He/O handed/O the/O letter/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O rather/O he/O become/O a/O corpse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Varys/O tells/O me/O that/O spies/O are/O more/O useful/O than/O corpses/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jorah/PERSON aside/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O make/O of/O his/O report/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Daenerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON has/O wed/O some/O Dothraki/O horselord/O ./O 
What/O of/O it/O ?/O 
Shall/O we/O send/O her/O a/O wedding/O gift/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O knife/O ,/O perhaps/O ./O 
A/O good/O sharp/O one/O ,/O and/O a/O bold/O man/O to/O wield/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O did/O not/O feign/O surprise/O ;/O Robert/PERSON 's/O hatred/O of/O the/O Targaryens/O was/O a/O madness/O in/O him/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O the/O angry/O words/O they/O had/O exchanged/O when/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O presented/O Robert/PERSON ''/O ,/O ``/O with/O the/O corpses/O of/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O wife/O and/O children/O as/O a/O token/O of/O fealty/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O named/O that/O murder/O ;/O Robert/PERSON called/O it/O war/O ./O 
When/O he/O had/O protested/O that/O the/O young/O prince/O and/O princess/O were/O no/O more/O than/O babes/O ,/O his/O new-made/O king/O had/O replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O no/O babes/O ./O 
Only/O dragonspawn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Not/O even/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O been/O able/O to/O calm/O that/O storm/O ./O 
Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O ridden/O out/O that/O very/O day/O in/O a/O cold/O rage/O ,/O to/O fight/O the/O last/O battles/O of/O the/O war/O alone/O in/O the/O south/O ./O 
It/O had/O taken/O another/O death/O to/O reconcile/O them/O ;/O Lyanna/PERSON 's/O death/O ,/O and/O the/O grief/O they/O had/O shared/O over/O her/O passing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O This/O time/O ,/O Ned/PERSON resolved/O to/O keep/O his/O temper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O the/O girl/O is/O scarcely/O more/O than/O a/O child/O ./O 
You/O are/O no/O Tywin/O Lannister/O ,/O to/O slaughter/O innocents/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O said/O that/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O little/O girl/O had/O cried/O as/O they/O dragged/O her/O from/O beneath/O her/O bed/O to/O face/O the/O swords/O ./O 
The/O boy/O had/O been/O no/O more/O than/O a/O babe/O in/O arms/O ,/O yet/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O soldiers/O had/O torn/O him/O from/O his/O mother/O 's/O breast/O and/O dashed/O his/O head/O against/O a/O wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O how/O long/O will/O this/O one/O remain/O an/O innocent/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON 's/O mouth/O grew/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O child/O will/O soon/O enough/O spread/O her/O legs/O and/O start/O breeding/O more/O dragonspawn/O to/O plague/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nonetheless/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O murder/O of/O children/O .../O it/O would/O be/O vile/O .../O unspeakable/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unspeakable/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O king/O roared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O Aerys/PERSON did/O to/O your/O brother/O Brandon/PERSON was/O unspeakable/O ./O 
The/O way/O your/O lord/O father/O died/O ,/O that/O was/O unspeakable/O ./O 
And/O Rhaegar/O .../O how/O many/O times/O do/O you/O think/O he/O raped/O your/O sister/O ?/O 
How/O many/O hundreds/O of/O times/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O had/O grown/O so/O loud/O that/O his/O horse/O whinnied/O nervously/O beneath/O him/O ./O 
The/O king/O jerked/O the/O reins/O hard/O ,/O quieting/O the/O animal/O ,/O and/O pointed/O an/O angry/O finger/O at/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O kill/O every/O Targaryen/O I/O can/O get/O my/O hands/O on/O ,/O until/O they/O are/O as/O dead/O as/O their/O dragons/O ,/O and/O then/O I/O will/O piss/O on/O their/O graves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON knew/O better/O than/O to/O defy/O him/O when/O the/O wrath/O was/O on/O him/O ./O 
If/O the/O years/O had/O not/O quenched/O Robert/PERSON 's/O thirst/O for/O revenge/O ,/O no/O words/O of/O his/O would/O help/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O get/O your/O hands/O on/O this/O one/O ,/O can/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O quietly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O king/O 's/O mouth/O twisted/O in/O a/O bitter/O grimace/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O gods/O be/O cursed/O ./O 
Some/O pox-ridden/O Pentoshi/LOCATION cheesemonger/O had/O her/O brother/O and/O her/O walled/O up/O on/O his/O estate/O with/O pointy-hatted/O eunuchs/O all/O around/O them/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O 's/O handed/O them/O over/O to/O the/O Dothraki/O ./O 
I/O should/O have/O had/O them/O both/O killed/O years/O ago/O ,/O when/O it/O was/O easy/O to/O get/O at/O them/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON was/O as/O bad/O as/O you/O ./O 
More/O fool/O I/O ,/O I/O listened/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON was/O a/O wise/O man/O and/O a/O good/O Hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
The/O anger/O was/O leaving/O him/O as/O suddenly/O as/O it/O had/O come/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON is/O said/O to/O have/O a/O hundred/O thousand/O men/O in/O his/O horde/O ./O 
What/O would/O Jon/PERSON say/O to/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O would/O say/O that/O even/O a/O million/O Dothraki/O are/O no/O threat/O to/O the/O realm/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O remain/O on/O the/O other/O side/O of/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ,/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON replied/O calmly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O barbarians/O have/O no/O ships/O ./O 
They/O hate/O and/O fear/O the/O open/O sea/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O shifted/O uncomfortably/O in/O his/O saddle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O ./O 
There/O are/O ships/O to/O be/O had/O in/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O though/O ./O 
I/O tell/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O I/O do/O not/O like/O this/O marriage/O ./O 
There/O are/O still/O those/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O who/O call/O me/O Usurper/O ./O 
Do/O you/O forget/O how/O many/O houses/O fought/O for/O Targaryen/O in/O the/O war/O ?/O 
They/O bide/O their/O time/O for/O now/O ,/O but/O give/O them/O half/O a/O chance/O ,/O they/O will/O murder/O me/O in/O my/O bed/O ,/O and/O my/O sons/O with/O me/O ./O 
If/O the/O beggar/O king/O crosses/O with/O a/O Dothraki/O horde/O at/O his/O back/O ,/O the/O traitors/O will/O join/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O not/O cross/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O if/O by/O some/O mischance/O he/O does/O ,/O we/O will/O throw/O him/O back/O into/O the/O sea/O ./O 
Once/O you/O choose/O a/O new/O Warden/O of/O the/O East/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O groaned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O the/O last/O time/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O name/O the/O Arryn/LOCATION boy/O Warden/LOCATION ./O 
I/O know/O the/O boy/O is/O your/O nephew/O ,/O but/O with/O Targaryens/O climbing/O in/O bed/O with/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O I/O would/O be/O mad/O to/O rest/O one/O quarter/O of/O the/O realm/O on/O the/O shoulders/O of/O a/O sickly/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON was/O ready/O for/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O we/O still/O must/O have/O a/O Warden/O of/O the/O East/O ./O 
If/O Robert/PERSON Arryn/PERSON will/O not/O do/O ,/O name/O one/O of/O your/O brothers/O ./O 
Stannis/PERSON proved/O himself/O at/O the/O siege/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ,/O surely/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O let/O the/O name/O hang/O there/O for/O a/O moment/O ./O 
The/O king/O frowned/O and/O said/O nothing/O ./O 
He/O looked/O uncomfortable/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON finished/O quietly/O ,/O watching/O ,/O \/O ``/O unless/O you/O have/O already/O promised/O the/O honor/O to/O another/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Robert/PERSON had/O the/O grace/O to/O look/O startled/O ./O 
Just/O as/O quickly/O ,/O the/O look/O became/O annoyance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O if/O I/O have/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O is/O it/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON kicked/O his/O horse/O back/O into/O motion/O and/O started/O down/O the/O ridge/O toward/O the/O barrows/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON kept/O pace/O with/O him/O ./O 
The/O king/O rode/O on/O ,/O eyes/O straight/O ahead/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O last/O ./O 
A/O single/O hard/O word/O to/O end/O the/O matter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O rumors/O were/O true/O ,/O then/O ./O 
He/O rode/O on/O dangerous/O ground/O now/O ,/O he/O knew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O An/O able/O and/O courageous/O man/O ,/O no/O doubt/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O carefully/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O his/O father/O is/O Warden/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
In/O time/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON will/O succeed/O to/O that/O honor/O ./O 
No/O one/O man/O should/O hold/O both/O East/O and/O West/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O left/O unsaid/O his/O real/O concern/O ;/O that/O the/O appointment/O would/O put/O half/O the/O armies/O of/O the/O realm/O into/O the/O hands/O of/O Lannisters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O fight/O that/O battle/O when/O the/O enemy/O appears/O on/O the/O field/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O said/O stubbornly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O the/O moment/O ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON looms/O eternal/O as/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O so/O I/O doubt/O that/O Jaime/PERSON will/O be/O succeeding/O anytime/O soon/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O vex/O me/O about/O this/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O the/O stone/O has/O been/O set/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O may/O I/O speak/O frankly/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O seem/O unable/O to/O stop/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
They/O rode/O through/O tall/O brown/O grasses/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O you/O trust/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O my/O wife/O 's/O twin/O ,/O a/O Sworn/O Brother/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON Kingsguard/PERSON ,/O his/O life/O and/O fortune/O and/O honor/O all/O bound/O to/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O they/O were/O bound/O to/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON 's/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O should/O I/O mistrust/O him/O ?/O 
He/O has/O done/O everything/O I/O have/O ever/O asked/O of/O him/O ./O 
His/O sword/O helped/O win/O the/O throne/O I/O sit/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O sword/O helped/O taint/O the/O throne/O you/O sit/O on/O ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O permit/O the/O words/O to/O pass/O his/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O swore/O a/O vow/O to/O protect/O his/O king/O 's/O life/O with/O his/O own/O ./O 
Then/O he/O opened/O that/O king/O 's/O throat/O with/O a/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Seven/O hells/O ,/O someone/O had/O to/O kill/O Aerys/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ,/O reining/O his/O mount/O to/O a/O sudden/O halt/O beside/O an/O ancient/O barrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Jaime/PERSON had/O n't/O done/O it/O ,/O it/O would/O have/O been/O left/O for/O you/O or/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O were/O not/O Sworn/O Brothers/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O time/O had/O come/O for/O Robert/PERSON to/O hear/O the/O whole/O truth/O ,/O he/O decided/O then/O and/O there/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O remember/O the/O Trident/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O won/O my/O crown/O there/O ./O 
How/O should/O I/O forget/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O took/O a/O wound/O from/O Rhaegar/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O when/O the/O Targaryen/O host/O broke/O and/O ran/O ,/O you/O gave/O the/O pursuit/O into/O my/O hands/O ./O 
The/O remnants/O of/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O army/O fled/O back/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
We/O followed/O ./O 
Aerys/PERSON was/O in/O the/O Red/O Keep/O with/O several/O thousand/O loyalists/O ./O 
I/O expected/O to/O find/O the/O gates/O closed/O to/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON gave/O an/O impatient/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Instead/O you/O found/O that/O our/O men/O had/O already/O taken/O the/O city/O ./O 
What/O of/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O our/O men/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O patiently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannister/O men/O ./O 
The/O lion/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION flew/O over/O the/O ramparts/O ,/O not/O the/O crowned/O stag/O ./O 
And/O they/O had/O taken/O the/O city/O by/O treachery/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O war/O had/O raged/O for/O close/O to/O a/O year/O ./O 
Lords/O great/O and/O small/O had/O flocked/O to/O Robert/PERSON 's/O banners/O ;/O others/O had/O remained/O loyal/O to/O Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
The/O mighty/O Lannisters/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O the/O Wardens/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O had/O remained/O aloof/O from/O the/O struggle/O ,/O ignoring/O calls/O to/O arms/O from/O both/O rebels/O and/O royalists/O ./O 
Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON must/O have/O thought/O that/O his/O gods/O had/O answered/O his/O prayers/O when/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON appeared/O before/O the/O gates/O of/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O with/O an/O army/O twelve/O thousand/O strong/O ,/O professing/O loyalty/O ./O 
So/O the/O mad/O king/O had/O ordered/O his/O last/O mad/O act/O ./O 
He/O had/O opened/O his/O city/O to/O the/O lions/O at/O the/O gate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Treachery/O was/O a/O coin/O the/O Targaryens/O knew/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O anger/O was/O building/O in/O him/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lannister/O paid/O them/O back/O in/O kind/O ./O 
It/O was/O no/O less/O than/O they/O deserved/O ./O 
I/O shall/O not/O trouble/O my/O sleep/O over/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O were/O not/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O bitterness/O in/O his/O voice/O ./O 
Troubled/O sleep/O was/O no/O stranger/O to/O him/O ./O 
He/O had/O lived/O his/O lies/O for/O fourteen/O years/O ,/O yet/O they/O still/O haunted/O him/O at/O night/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O honor/O in/O that/O conquest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O take/O your/O honor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON swore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O did/O any/O Targaryen/PERSON ever/O know/O of/O honor/O ?/O 
Go/O down/O into/O your/O crypt/O and/O ask/O Lyanna/PERSON about/O the/O dragon/O 's/O honor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O avenged/O Lyanna/PERSON at/O the/O Trident/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O halting/O beside/O the/O king/O ./O 
Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O she/O had/O whispered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O did/O not/O bring/O her/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robert/PERSON looked/O away/O ,/O off/O into/O the/O grey/O distance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O be/O damned/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O hollow/O victory/O they/O gave/O me/O ./O 
A/O crown/O .../O it/O was/O the/O girl/O I/O prayed/O them/O for/O ./O 
Your/O sister/O ,/O safe/O .../O and/O mine/O again/O ,/O as/O she/O was/O meant/O to/O be/O ./O 
I/O ask/O you/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O what/O good/O is/O it/O to/O wear/O a/O crown/O ?/O 
The/O gods/O mock/O the/O prayers/O of/O kings/O and/O cowherds/O alike/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O not/O answer/O for/O the/O gods/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O .../O only/O for/O what/O I/O found/O when/O I/O rode/O into/O the/O throne/O room/O that/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Aerys/O was/O dead/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O drowned/O in/O his/O own/O blood/O ./O 
His/O dragon/O skulls/O stared/O down/O from/O the/O walls/O ./O 
Lannister/PERSON 's/O men/O were/O everywhere/O ./O 
Jaime/PERSON wore/O the/O white/O cloak/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/PERSON over/O his/O golden/O armor/O ./O 
I/O can/O see/O him/O still/O ./O 
Even/O his/O sword/O was/O gilded/O ./O 
He/O was/O seated/O on/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O high/O above/O his/O knights/O ,/O wearing/O a/O helm/O fashioned/O in/O the/O shape/O of/O a/O lion/O 's/O head/O ./O 
How/O he/O glittered/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O well/O known/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O king/O complained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O still/O mounted/O ./O 
I/O rode/O the/O length/O of/O the/O hall/O in/O silence/O ,/O between/O the/O long/O rows/O of/O dragon/O skulls/O ./O 
It/O felt/O as/O though/O they/O were/O watching/O me/O ,/O somehow/O ./O 
I/O stopped/O in/O front/O of/O the/O throne/O ,/O looking/O up/O at/O him/O ./O 
His/O golden/O sword/O was/O across/O his/O legs/O ,/O its/O edge/O red/O with/O a/O king/O 's/O blood/O ./O 
My/O ''/O ,/O ``/O men/O were/O filling/O the/O room/O behind/O me/O ./O 
Lannister/PERSON 's/O men/O drew/O back/O ./O 
I/O never/O said/O a/O word/O ./O 
I/O looked/O at/O him/O seated/O there/O on/O the/O throne/O ,/O and/O I/O waited/O ./O 
At/O last/O Jaime/PERSON laughed/O and/O got/O up/O ./O 
He/O took/O off/O his/O helm/O ,/O and/O he/O said/O to/O me/O ,/O `/O Have/O no/O fear/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
I/O was/O only/O keeping/O it/O warm/O for/O our/O friend/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O a/O very/O comfortable/O seat/O ,/O I/O 'm/O afraid/O ./O '/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O king/O threw/O back/O his/O head/O and/O roared/O ./O 
His/O laughter/O startled/O a/O flight/O of/O crows/O from/O the/O tall/O brown/O grass/O ./O 
They/O took/O to/O the/O air/O in/O a/O wild/O beating/O of/O wings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O think/O I/O should/O mistrust/O Lannister/O because/O he/O sat/O on/O my/O throne/O for/O a/O few/O moments/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O shook/O with/O laughter/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON was/O all/O of/O seventeen/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
Scarce/O more/O than/O a/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Boy/O or/O man/O ,/O he/O had/O no/O right/O to/O that/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O he/O was/O tired/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON suggested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Killing/O kings/O is/O weary/O work/O ./O 
Gods/O know/O ,/O there/O 's/O no/O place/O else/O to/O rest/O your/O ass/O in/O that/O damnable/O room/O ./O 
And/O he/O spoke/O truly/O ,/O it/O is/O a/O monstrous/O uncomfortable/O chair/O ./O 
In/O more/O ways/O than/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O now/O I/O know/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O dark/O sin/O ,/O and/O the/O matter/O can/O be/O forgotten/O ./O 
I/O am/O heartily/O sick/O of/O secrets/O and/O squabbles/O and/O matters/O of/O state/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
It/O 's/O all/O as/O tedious/O as/O counting/O coppers/O ./O 
Come/O ,/O let/O 's/O ride/O ,/O you/O used/O to/O know/O how/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O feel/O the/O wind/O in/O my/O hair/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O kicked/O his/O horse/O back/O into/O motion/O and/O galloped/O up/O over/O the/O barrow/O ,/O raining/O earth/O down/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Ned/PERSON did/O not/O follow/O ./O 
He/O had/O run/O out/O of/O words/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O filled/O with/O a/O vast/O sense/O of/O helplessness/O ./O 
Not/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ,/O he/O wondered/O what/O he/O was/O doing/O here/O and/O why/O he/O had/O come/O ./O 
He/O was/O no/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O to/O curb/O the/O wildness/O of/O his/O king/O and/O teach/O him/O wisdom/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON would/O do/O what/O he/O pleased/O ,/O as/O he/O always/O had/O ,/O and/O nothing/O Ned/PERSON could/O say/O or/O do/O would/O change/O that/O ./O 
He/O belonged/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
He/O belonged/O with/O Catelyn/PERSON in/O her/O grief/O ,/O and/O with/O Bran/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O man/O could/O not/O always/O be/O where/O he/O belonged/O ,/O though/O ./O 
Resigned/O ,/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON put/O his/O boots/O into/O his/O horse/O and/O set/O off/O after/O the/O king/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
