-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O mare/O whickered/O softly/O as/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON tightened/O the/O cinch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Easy/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O soft/O voice/O ,/O quieting/O her/O with/O a/O touch/O ./O 
Wind/O whispered/O through/O the/O stable/O ,/O a/O cold/O dead/O breath/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON paid/O it/O no/O mind/O ./O 
He/O strapped/O his/O roll/O to/O the/O saddle/O ,/O his/O scarred/O fingers/O stiff/O and/O clumsy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O softly/O ,/O \/O ``/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O the/O wolf/O was/O there/O ,/O eyes/O like/O embers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O please/O ./O 
You/O must/O not/O do/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O mounted/O ,/O the/O reins/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O and/O wheeled/O the/O horse/O around/O to/O face/O the/O night/O ./O 
Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON stood/O in/O the/O stable/O door/O ,/O a/O full/O moon/O peering/O over/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
He/O threw/O a/O giant/O 's/O shadow/O ,/O immense/O and/O black/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O out/O of/O my/O way/O ,/O Sam/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O let/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O sooner/O not/O hurt/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Move/O aside/O ,/O Sam/PERSON ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O ride/O you/O down/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O wo/O n't/O ./O 
You/O have/O to/O listen/O to/O me/O ./O 
Please/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON put/O his/O spurs/O to/O horseflesh/O ,/O and/O the/O mare/O bolted/O for/O the/O door/O ./O 
For/O an/O instant/O Sam/PERSON stood/O his/O ground/O ,/O his/O face/O as/O round/O and/O pale/O as/O the/O moon/O behind/O him/O ,/O his/O mouth/O a/O widening/O O/O of/O surprise/O ./O 
At/O the/O last/O moment/O ,/O when/O they/O were/O almost/O on/O him/O ,/O he/O jumped/O aside/O as/O Jon/PERSON had/O known/O he/O would/O ,/O stumbled/O ,/O and/O fell/O ./O 
The/O mare/O leapt/O over/O him/O ,/O out/O into/O the/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON raised/O the/O hood/O of/O his/O heavy/O cloak/O and/O gave/O the/O horse/O her/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Castle/O Black/O was/O silent/O and/O still/O as/O he/O rode/O out/O ,/O with/O Ghost/O racing/O at/O his/O side/O ./O 
Men/O watched/O from/O the/O Wall/O behind/O him/O ,/O he/O knew/O ,/O but/O their/O eyes/O were/O turned/O north/O ,/O not/O south/O ./O 
No/O one/O would/O see/O him/O go/O ,/O no/O one/O but/O Sam/PERSON Tarly/PERSON ,/O struggling/O back/O to/O his/O feet/O in/O the/O dust/O of/O the/O old/O stables/O ./O 
He/O hoped/O Sam/PERSON had/O n't/O hurt/O himself/O ,/O falling/O like/O that/O ./O 
He/O was/O so/O heavy/O and/O so/O ungainly/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O just/O like/O him/O to/O break/O a/O wrist/O or/O twist/O his/O ankle/O getting/O out/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O warned/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O aloud/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O nothing/O to/O do/O with/O him/O ,/O anyway/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O flexed/O his/O burned/O hand/O as/O he/O rode/O ,/O opening/O and/O closing/O the/O scarred/O fingers/O ./O 
They/O still/O pained/O him/O ,/O but/O it/O felt/O good/O to/O have/O the/O wrappings/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Moonlight/O silvered/O the/O hills/O as/O he/O followed/O the/O twisting/O ribbon/O of/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
He/O needed/O to/O get/O as/O far/O from/O the/O Wall/O as/O he/O could/O before/O they/O realized/O he/O was/O gone/O ./O 
On/O the/O morrow/O he/O would/O leave/O the/O road/O and/O strike/O out/O overland/O through/O field/O and/O bush/O and/O stream/O to/O throw/O off/O pursuit/O ,/O but/O for/O the/O moment/O speed/O was/O more/O important/O than/O deception/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O as/O though/O they/O would/O not/O guess/O where/O he/O was/O going/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O was/O accustomed/O to/O rise/O at/O first/O light/O ,/O so/O Jon/PERSON had/O until/O dawn/O to/O put/O as/O many/O leagues/O as/O he/O could/O between/O him/O and/O the/O Wall/O .../O if/O Sam/PERSON Tarly/PERSON did/O not/O betray/O him/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O was/O dutiful/O and/O easily/O frightened/O ,/O but/O he/O loved/O Jon/PERSON like/O a/O brother/O ./O 
If/O questioned/O ,/O Sam/PERSON would/O doubtless/O tell/O them/O the/O truth/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON could/O not/O imagine/O him/O braving/O the/O guards/O in/O front/O of/O the/O Mng/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION to/O wake/O Mormont/O from/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O appear/O to/O fetch/O the/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O breakfast/O from/O the/O kitchen/O ,/O they/O 'd/O look/O in/O his/O cell/O and/O find/O Longclaw/LOCATION on/O the/O bed/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O hard/O to/O abandon/O it/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON was/O not/O so/O lost/O to/O honor/O as/O to/O take/O it/O with/O him/O ./O 
Even/O Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON had/O not/O done/O that/O ,/O when/O he/O fled/O in/O disgrace/O ./O 
Doubtless/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON would/O find/O someone/O more/O worthy/O of/O the/O blade/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON felt/O bad/O when/O he/O thought/O of/O the/O old/O man/O ./O 
He/O knew/O his/O desertion/O would/O be/O salt/O in/O the/O still-raw/O wound/O of/O his/O son/O 's/O ''/O ,/O ``/O disgrace/O ./O 
That/O seemed/O a/O poor/O way/O to/O repay/O him/O for/O his/O trust/O ,/O but/O it/O could/O n't/O be/O helped/O ./O 
No/O matter/O what/O he/O did/O ,/O Jon/PERSON felt/O as/O though/O he/O were/O betraying/O someone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O now/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O know/O if/O he/O was/O doing/O the/O honorable/O thing/O ./O 
The/O southron/O had/O it/O easier/O ./O 
They/O had/O their/O septons/O to/O talk/O to/O ,/O someone/O to/O tell/O them/O the/O gods/O '/O will/O and/O help/O sort/O out/O right/O from/O wrong/O ./O 
But/O the/O Starks/PERSON worshiped/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O the/O nameless/O gods/O ,/O and/O if/O the/O heart/O trees/O heard/O ,/O they/O did/O not/O speak/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O last/O lights/O of/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION vanished/O behind/O him/O ,/O Jon/PERSON slowed/O his/O mare/O to/O a/O walk/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O long/O journey/O ahead/O and/O only/O the/O one/O horse/O to/O see/O him/O through/O ./O 
There/O were/O holdfasts/O and/O farming/O villages/O along/O the/O road/O south/O where/O he/O might/O be/O able/O to/O trade/O the/O mare/O for/O a/O fresh/O mount/O when/O he/O needed/O one/O ,/O but/O not/O if/O she/O were/O injured/O or/O blown/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O would/O need/O to/O find/O new/O clothes/O soon/O ;/O most/O like/O ,/O he/O 'd/O need/O to/O steal/O them/O ./O 
He/O was/O clad/O in/O black/O from/O head/O to/O heel/O ;/O high/O leather/O riding/O boots/O ,/O roughspun/O breeches/O and/O tunic/O ,/O sleeveless/O leather/O jerkin/O ,/O and/O heavy/O wool/O cloak/O ./O 
His/O longsword/O and/O dagger/O were/O sheathed/O in/O black/O moleskin/O ,/O and/O the/O hauberk/O and/O coif/O in/O his/O saddlebag/O were/O black/O ringmail/O ./O 
Any/O bit/O of/O it/O could/O mean/O his/O death/O if/O he/O were/O taken/O ./O 
A/O stranger/O wearing/O black/O was/O viewed/O with/O cold/O suspicion/O in/O every/O village/O and/O holdfast/O north/O of/O the/O Neck/O ,/O and/O men/O would/O soon/O be/O watching/O for/O him/O ./O 
Once/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON 's/O ravens/O took/O flight/O ,/O Jon/PERSON knew/O he/O would/O find/O no/O safe/O haven/O ./O 
Not/O even/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Bran/O might/O want/O to/O let/O him/O in/O ,/O but/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON had/O better/O sense/O ./O 
He/O would/O bar/O the/O gates/O and/O send/O Jon/PERSON away/O ,/O as/O he/O should/O ./O 
Better/O not/O to/O call/O there/O at/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O he/O saw/O the/O castle/O clear/O in/O his/O mind/O 's/O eye/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O left/O it/O only/O yesterday/O ;/O the/O towering/O granite/O walls/O ,/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION with/O its/O smells/O of/O smoke/O and/O dog/O and/O roasting/O meat/O ,/O his/O father/O 's/O solar/O ,/O the/O turret/O room/O where/O he/O had/O slept/O ./O 
Part/O of/O him/O wanted/O nothing/O so/O much/O as/O to/O hear/O Bran/O laugh/O again/O ,/O to/O sup/O on/O one/O of/O Gage/PERSON 's/O beef-and-bacon/O pies/O ,/O to/O listen/O to/O Old/O Nan/PERSON tell/O her/O tales/O of/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O and/O Florian/O the/O Fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O he/O had/O not/O left/O the/O Wall/O for/O that/O ;/O he/O had/O left/O because/O he/O was/O after/O all/O his/O father/O 's/O son/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON 's/O brother/O ./O 
The/O gift/O of/O a/O sword/O ,/O even/O a/O sword/O as/O fine/O as/O Longclaw/PERSON ,/O did/O not/O make/O him/O a/O Mormont/O ./O 
Nor/O was/O he/O Aemon/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
Three/O times/O the/O old/O man/O had/O chosen/O ,/O and/O three/O times/O he/O had/O chosen/O honor/O ,/O but/O that/O was/O him/O ./O 
Even/O now/O ,/O Jon/PERSON could/O not/O decide/O whether/O the/O maester/O had/O stayed/O because/O he/O was/O weak/O and/O craven/O ,/O or/O because/O he/O was/O strong/O and/O true/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O understood/O what/O the/O old/O man/O had/O meant/O ,/O about/O the/O pain/O of/O choosing/O ;/O he/O understood/O that/O all/O too/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O had/O claimed/O that/O most/O men/O would/O rather/O deny/O a/O hard/O truth/O than/O face/O it/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON was/O done/O with/O denials/O ./O 
He/O was/O who/O he/O was/O ;/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O bastard/O and/O oathbreaker/O ,/O motherless/O ,/O friendless/O ,/O and/O damned/O ./O 
For/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O life-however/O long/O that/O might/O be-he/O would/O be/O condemned/O to/O be/O an/O outsider/O ,/O the/O silent/O man/O standing/O in/O the/O shadows/O who/O dares/O not/O speak/O his/O true/O name/O ./O 
Wherever/O he/O might/O go/O throughout/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O he/O would/O need/O to/O live/O a/O lie/O ,/O lest/O every/O man/O 's/O hand/O be/O raised/O against/O him/O ./O 
But/O it/O made/O no/O matter/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O he/O lived/O long/O enough/O to/O take/O his/O place/O by/O his/O brother/O 's/O side/O and/O help/O avenge/O his/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O remembered/O Robb/PERSON as/O he/O had/O last/O seen/O him/O ,/O standing/O in/O the/O yard/O with/O snow/O melting/O in/O his/O auburn/O hair/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON would/O have/O to/O come/O to/O him/O in/O secret/O ,/O disguised/O ./O 
He/O tried/O to/O imagine/O the/O look/O on/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON 's/O face/O when/O he/O revealed/O himself/O ./O 
His/O brother/O would/O shake/O his/O head/O and/O smile/O ,/O and/O he/O 'd/O say/O .../O he/O 'd/O say/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O could/O not/O see/O the/O smile/O ./O 
Hard/O as/O he/O tried/O ,/O he/O could/O not/O see/O it/O ./O 
He/O found/O himself/O thinking/O of/O the/O deserter/O his/O father/O had/O beheaded/O the/O day/O they/O 'd/O found/O the/O direwolves/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O said/O the/O words/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON had/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O took/O a/O vow/O ,/O before/O your/O brothers/O ,/O before/O the/O old/O gods/O and/O the/O new/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Desmond/PERSON and/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON had/O dragged/O the/O man/O to/O the/O stump/O ./O 
Bran/O 's/O eyes/O had/O been/O wide/O as/O saucers/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON had/O to/O remind/O him/O to/O keep/O his/O pony/O in/O hand/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O the/O look/O on/O Father/O 's/O face/O when/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON brought/O forth/O Ice/O ,/O the/O spray/O of/O blood/O on/O the/O snow/O ,/O the/O way/O Theon/PERSON had/O kicked/O the/O head/O when/O it/O came/O rolling/O at/O his/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O wondered/O what/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON might/O have/O done/O if/O the/O deserter/O had/O been/O his/O brother/O Benjen/PERSON instead/O of/O that/O ragged/O stranger/O ./O 
Would/O it/O have/O been/O any/O different/O ?/O 
It/O must/O ,/O surely/O ,/O surely/O .../O and/O Robb/PERSON would/O welcome/O him/O ,/O for/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
He/O had/O to/O ,/O or/O else/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O did/O not/O bear/O thinking/O about/O ./O 
Pain/O throbbed/O ,/O deep/O in/O his/O fingers/O ,/O as/O he/O clutched/O the/O reins/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON put/O his/O heels/O into/O his/O horse/O and/O broke/O into/O a/O gallop/O ,/O racing/O down/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O as/O if/O to/O outrun/O his/O doubts/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON was/O not/O afraid/O of/O death/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O want/O to/O die/O like/O that/O ,/O trussed/O and/O bound/O and/O beheaded/O like/O a/O common/O brigand/O ./O 
If/O he/O must/O perish/O ,/O let/O it/O be/O with/O a/O sword/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O fighting/O his/O father/O 's/O killers/O ./O 
He/O was/O no/O true/O Stark/O ,/O had/O never/O been/O one/O .../O but/O he/O could/O die/O like/O one/O ./O 
Let/O them/O say/O that/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O fathered/O four/O sons/O ,/O not/O three/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O kept/O pace/O with/O them/O for/O almost/O half/O a/O mile/O ,/O red/O tongue/O lolling/O from/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
Man/O and/O horse/O alike/O lowered/O their/O heads/O as/O he/O asked/O the/O mare/O for/O more/O speed/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O slowed/O ,/O stopped/O ,/O watching/O ,/O his/O eyes/O glowing/O red/O in/O the/O moonlight/O ./O 
He/O vanished/O behind/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON knew/O he/O would/O follow/O ,/O at/O his/O own/O pace/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Scattered/O lights/O flickered/O through/O the/O trees/O ahead/O of/O him/O ,/O on/O both/O sides/O of/O the/O road/O :/O Mole/O 's/O Town/O ./O 
A/O dog/O barked/O as/O he/O rode/O through/O ,/O and/O he/O heard/O a/O mule/O 's/O raucous/O haw/O from/O the/O stable/O ,/O but/O otherwise/O the/O village/O was/O still/O ./O 
Here/O and/O there/O the/O glow/O of/O hearth/O fires/O shone/O through/O shuttered/O windows/O ,/O leaking/O between/O wooden/O slats/O ,/O but/O only/O a/O few/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mole/O 's/O Town/O was/O bigger/O than/O it/O seemed/O ,/O but/O three/O quarters/O of/O it/O was/O under/O the/O ground/O ,/O in/O deep/O warm/O cellars/O connected/O by/O a/O maze/O of/O tunnels/O ./O 
Even/O the/O whorehouse/O was/O down/O there/O ,/O nothing/O on/O the/O surface/O but/O a/O wooden/O shack/O no/O bigger/O than/O a/O privy/O ,/O with/O a/O red/O lantern/O hung/O over/O the/O door/O ./O 
On/O the/O Wall/O ,/O he/O 'd/O heard/O men/O call/O the/O whores/O \/O ``/O buried/O treasures/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O wondered/O whether/O any/O of/O his/O brothers/O in/O black/O were/O down/O there/O tonight/O ,/O mining/O ./O 
That/O was/O oathbreaking/O too/O ,/O yet/O no/O one/O seemed/O to/O care/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Not/O until/O he/O was/O well/O beyond/O the/O village/O did/O Jon/PERSON slow/O again/O ./O 
By/O then/O both/O he/O and/O the/O mare/O were/O damp/O with/O sweat/O ./O 
He/O dismounted/O ,/O shivering/O ,/O his/O burned/O hand/O aching/O ./O 
A/O bank/O of/O melting/O snow/O lay/O under/O the/O trees/O ,/O bright/O in/O the/O moonlight/O ,/O water/O trickling/O off/O to/O form/O small/O shallow/O pools/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON squatted/O and/O brought/O his/O hands/O together/O ,/O cupping/O the/O runoff/O between/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O snowmelt/O was/O icy/O cold/O ./O 
He/O drank/O ,/O and/O splashed/O some/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O until/O his/O cheeks/O tingled/O ./O 
His/O fingers/O were/O throbbing/O worse/O than/O they/O had/O in/O days/O ,/O and/O his/O head/O was/O pounding/O too/O ./O 
I/O am/O doing/O the/O right/O thing/O ,/O he/O told/O himself/O ,/O so/O why/O do/O I/O feel/O so/O bad/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O horse/O was/O well/O lathered/O ,/O so/O Jon/PERSON took/O the/O lead/O and/O walked/O her/O for/O a/O while/O ./O 
The/O road/O was/O scarcely/O wide/O enough/O for/O two/O riders/O to/O pass/O abreast/O ,/O its/O surface/O cut/O by/O tiny/O streams/O and/O littered/O with/O stone/O ./O 
That/O run/O had/O been/O truly/O stupid/O ,/O an/O invitation/O to/O a/O broken/O neck/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON wondered/O what/O had/O gotten/O into/O him/O ./O 
Was/O he/O in/O such/O a/O great/O rush/O to/O die/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Off/O in/O the/O trees/O ,/O the/O distant/O scream/O of/O some/O frightened/O animal/O made/O him/O look/O up/O ./O 
His/O mare/O whinnied/O nervously/O ./O 
Had/O his/O wolf/O found/O some/O prey/O ?/O 
He/O cupped/O his/O hands/O around/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O ,/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O only/O answer/O was/O a/O rush/O of/O wings/O behind/O him/O as/O an/O owl/O took/O flight/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Frowning/O ,/O Jon/PERSON continued/O on/O his/O way/O ./O 
He/O led/O the/O mare/O for/O half/O an/O hour/O ,/O until/O she/O was/O dry/O ./O 
Ghost/O did/O not/O appear/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON wanted/O to/O mount/O up/O and/O ride/O again/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O concerned/O about/O his/O missing/O wolf/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O you/O ?/O 
To/O me/O !/O 
Ghost/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Nothing/O in/O these/O woods/O could/O trouble/O a/O direwolf/O ,/O even/O a/O half-grown/O direwolf/O ,/O unless/O .../O no/O ,/O Ghost/PERSON was/O too/O smart/O to/O attack/O a/O bear/O ,/O and/O if/O there/O was/O a/O wolf/O pack/O anywhere/O close/O Jon/PERSON would/O have/O surely/O heard/O them/O howling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O should/O eat/O ,/O he/O decided/O ./O 
Food/O would/O settle/O his/O stomach/O and/O give/O Ghost/O the/O chance/O to/O catch/O up/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O danger/O yet/O ;/O Castle/O Black/O still/O slept/O ./O 
In/O his/O saddlebag/O ,/O he/O found/O a/O biscuit/O ,/O a/O piece/O of/O cheese/O ,/O and/O a/O small/O withered/O brown/O apple/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O brought/O salt/O beef/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O a/O rasher/O of/O bacon/O he/O 'd/O filched/O from/O the/O kitchens/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O save/O the/O meat/O for/O the/O morrow/O ./O 
After/O it/O was/O gone/O he/O 'd/O need/O to/O hunt/O ,/O and/O that/O would/O slow/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON sat/O under/O the/O trees/O and/O ate/O his/O biscuit/O and/O cheese/O while/O his/O mare/O grazed/O along/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
He/O kept/O the/O apple/O for/O last/O ./O 
It/O had/O gone/O a/O little/O soft/O ,/O but/O the/O flesh/O was/O still/O tart/O and/O juicy/O ./O 
He/O was/O down/O to/O the/O core/O when/O he/O heard/O the/O sounds/O :/O horses/O ,/O and/O from/O the/O north/O ./O 
Quickly/O Jon/PERSON leapt/O up/O and/O strode/O to/O his/O mare/O ./O 
Could/O he/O outrun/O them/O ?/O 
No/O ,/O they/O were/O too/O close/O ,/O they/O 'd/O hear/O him/O for/O a/O certainty/O ,/O and/O if/O they/O were/O from/O Castle/O Black/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O led/O the/O mare/O off/O the/O road/O ,/O behind/O a/O thick/O stand/O of/O grey-green/O sentinels/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Quiet/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O hushed/O voice/O ,/O crouching/O down/O to/O peer/O through/O the/O branches/O ./O 
If/O the/O gods/O were/O kind/O ,/O the/O riders/O would/O pass/O by/O ./O 
Likely/O as/O not/O ,/O they/O were/O only/O smallfolk/O from/O Mole/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Town/LOCATION ,/O farmers/O on/O their/O way/O to/O their/O fields/O ,/O although/O what/O they/O were/O doing/O out/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O night/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O listened/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O hooves/O growing/O steadily/O louder/O as/O they/O trotted/O briskly/O down/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
From/O the/O sound/O ,/O there/O were/O five/O or/O six/O of/O them/O at/O the/O least/O ./O 
Their/O voices/O drifted/O through/O the/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O .../O certain/O he/O came/O this/O way/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O ca/O n't/O be/O certain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O could/O have/O ridden/O east/O ,/O for/O all/O you/O know/O ./O 
Or/O left/O the/O road/O to/O cut/O through/O the/O woods/O ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O I/O 'd/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O dark/O ?/O 
Stupid/O ./O 
If/O you/O did/O n't/O fall/O off/O your/O horse/O and/O break/O your/O neck/O ,/O you/O 'd/O get/O lost/O and/O wind/O up/O back/O at/O the/O Wall/O when/O the/O sun/O came/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON sounded/O peeved/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O just/O ride/O south/O ,/O you/O can/O tell/O south/O by/O the/O stars/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O if/O the/O sky/O was/O cloudy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O I/O would/O n't/O go/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Another/O voice/O broke/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O where/O Id/O be/O if/O it/O was/O me/O ?/O 
I/O 'd/O be/O in/O Mole/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Town/LOCATION ,/O digging/O for/O buried/O treasure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Toad/PERSON 's/O shrill/O laughter/O boomed/O through/O the/O trees/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON 's/O mare/O snorted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Keep/O quiet/O ,/O all/O of/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Haider/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thought/O I/O heard/O something/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Where/O ?/O 
I/O did/O n't/O hear/O anything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O horses/O stopped/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O hear/O yourself/O fart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON insisted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Quiet/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O all/O fell/O silent/O ,/O listening/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON found/O himself/O holding/O his/O breath/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
He/O had/O n't/O gone/O to/O the/O Old/O Bear/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O n't/O gone/O to/O bed/O either/O ,/O he/O 'd/O woken/O the/O other/O boys/O ./O 
Damn/O them/O all/O ./O 
Come/O dawn/O ,/O if/O they/O were/O not/O in/O their/O beds/O ,/O they/O 'd/O be/O named/O deserters/O too/O ./O 
What/O did/O they/O think/O they/O were/O doing/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O hushed/O silence/O seemed/O to/O stretch/O on/O and/O on/O ./O 
From/O where/O Jon/PERSON crouched/O ,/O he/O could/O see/O the/O legs/O of/O their/O horses/O through/O the/O branches/O ./O 
Finally/O Pyp/O spoke/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O did/O you/O hear/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Haider/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O sound/O ,/O I/O thought/O it/O might/O have/O been/O a/O horse/O but/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O 's/O nothing/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Out/O of/O the/O corner/O of/O his/O eye/O ,/O Jon/PERSON glimpsed/O a/O pale/O shape/O moving/O through/O the/O trees/O ./O 
Leaves/O rustled/O ,/O and/O Ghost/PERSON came/O bounding/O out/O of/O the/O shadows/O ,/O so/O suddenly/O that/O Jon/PERSON 's/O mare/O started/O and/O gave/O a/O whinny/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Haider/PERSON shouted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O heard/O it/O too/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Traitor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O the/O direwolf/O as/O he/O swung/O up/O into/O the/O saddle/O ./O 
He/O turned/O the/O mare/O 's/O head/O to/O slide/O off/O through/O the/O trees/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O on/O him/O before/O he/O had/O gone/O ten/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON !/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON shouted/O after/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pull/O up/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O outrun/O us/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON wheeled/O around/O to/O face/O them/O ,/O drawing/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O back/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O wish/O to/O hurt/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O will/O if/O I/O have/O to/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O One/O against/O seven/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Haider/PERSON gave/O a/O signal/O ./O 
The/O boys/O spread/O out/O ,/O surrounding/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O want/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON demanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O want/O to/O take/O you/O back/O where/O you/O belong/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O belong/O with/O my/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 're/O your/O brothers/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 'll/O cut/O off/O your/O head/O if/O they/O catch/O you/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Toad/O put/O in/O with/O a/O nervous/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O so/O stupid/O ,/O it/O 's/O like/O something/O the/O Aurochs/O would/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O no/O oathbreaker/O ./O 
I/O said/O the/O words/O and/O I/O meant/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O did/O I./O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O you/O understand/O ?/O 
They/O murdered/O my/O father/O ./O 
It/O 's/O war/O ,/O my/O brother/O Robb/PERSON is/O fighting/O in/O the/O riverlands/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Pyp/PERSON solemnly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sam/PERSON told/O us/O everything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 're/O sorry/O about/O your/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O it/O does/O n't/O matter/O ./O 
Once/O you/O say/O the/O words/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O leave/O ,/O no/O matter/O what/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O to/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O fervently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O said/O the/O words/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O my/O watch/O begins/O ,/O you/O said/O it/O ./O 
It/O shall/O not/O end/O until/O my/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O live/O and/O die/O at/O my/O post/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON added/O ,/O nodding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O tell/O me/O the/O words/O ,/O I/O know/O them/O as/O well/O as/O you/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O angry/O now/O ./O 
Why/O could/O n't/O they/O let/O him/O go/O in/O peace/O ?/O 
They/O were/O only/O making/O it/O harder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O sword/O in/O the/O darkness/O ,/O \/O ''/O Haider/PERSON intoned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O watcher/O on/O the/O walls/O ,/O \/O ''/O piped/O Toad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON cursed/O them/O all/O to/O their/O faces/O ./O 
They/O took/O no/O notice/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON spurred/O his/O horse/O closer/O ,/O reciting/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O fire/O that/O Burns/PERSON against/O the/O cold/O ,/O the/O light/O that/O brings/O the/O dawn/O ,/O the/O horn/O that/O wakes/O the/O sleepers/O ,/O the/O shield/O that/O guards/O the/O realms/O of/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stay/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON warned/O him/O ,/O brandishing/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O mean/O it/O ,/O Pyp/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O were/O n't/O even/O wearing/O armor/O ,/O he/O could/O cut/O them/O to/O pieces/O if/O he/O had/O to/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Matthar/PERSON had/O circled/O behind/O him/O ./O 
He/O joined/O the/O chorus/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O pledge/O my/O life/O and/O honor/O to/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON kicked/O his/O mare/O ,/O spinning/O her/O in/O a/O circle/O ./O 
The/O boys/O were/O all/O around/O him/O now/O ,/O closing/O from/O every/O side/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O this/O night/O Haider/PERSON trotted/O in/O from/O the/O left/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O .../O and/O all/O the/O nights/O to/O come/O ,/O \/O ''/O finished/O Pyp/O ./O 
He/O reached/O over/O for/O Jon/PERSON 's/O reins/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O here/O are/O your/O choices/O ./O 
Kill/O me/O ,/O or/O come/O back/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON lifted/O his/O sword/O .../O and/O lowered/O it/O ,/O helpless/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damn/O you/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O we/O have/O to/O bind/O your/O hands/O ,/O or/O will/O you/O give/O us/O your/O word/O you/O 'll/O ride/O back/O peaceful/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Haider/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O run/O ,/O if/O that/O 's/O what/O you/O mean/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ghost/O moved/O out/O from/O under/O the/O trees/O and/O Jon/PERSON glared/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Small/O help/O you/O were/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
The/O deep/O red/O eyes/O looked/O at/O him/O knowingly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O had/O best/O hurry/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O 're/O not/O back/O before/O first/O light/O ,/O the/O Old/O Bear/O will/O have/O all/O our/O heads/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Of/O the/O ride/O back/O ,/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON remembered/O little/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O shorter/O than/O the/O journey/O south/O ,/O perhaps/O because/O his/O mind/O was/O elsewhere/O ./O 
Pyp/O set/O the/O pace/O ,/O galloping/O ,/O walking/O ,/O trotting/O ,/O and/O then/O breaking/O into/O another/O gallop/O ./O 
Mole/O 's/O Town/O came/O and/O went/O ,/O the/O red/O lantern/O over/O the/O brothel/O long/O extinguished/O ./O 
They/O made/O good/O time/O ./O 
Dawn/PERSON was/O still/O an/O hour/O off/O when/O Jon/PERSON glimpsed/O the/O towers/O of/O Castle/O Black/O ahead/O of/O them/O ,/O dark/O against/O the/O pale/O immensity/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O seem/O like/O home/O this/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O could/O take/O him/O back/O ,/O Jon/PERSON told/O himself/O ,/O but/O they/O could/O not/O make/O him/O stay/O ./O 
The/O war/O would/O not/O end/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O or/O the/O day/O after/O ,/O and/O his/O friends/O could/O not/O watch/O him/O day/O and/O night/O ./O 
He/O would/O bide/O his/O time/O ,/O make/O them/O think/O he/O was/O content/O to/O remain/O here/O .../O and/O then/O ,/O when/O they/O had/O grown/O lax/O ,/O he/O would/O be/O off/O again/O ./O 
Next/O time/O he/O would/O avoid/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
He/O could/O follow/O the/O Wall/O east/O ,/O perhaps/O all/O the/O way/O to/O the/O sea/O ,/O a/O longer/O route/O but/O a/O safer/O one/O ./O 
Or/O even/O west/O ,/O to/O the/O mountains/O ,/O and/O then/O south/O over/O the/O high/O passes/O ./O 
That/O was/O the/O wildling/O 's/O way/O ,/O hard/O and/O perilous/O ,/O but/O at/O least/O no/O one/O wouid/O follow/O him/O ./O 
He/O would/O n't/O stray/O within/O a/O hundred/O leagues/O of/O Winterfell/O or/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON awaited/O them/O in/O the/O old/O stables/O ,/O slumped/O on/O the/O ground/O against/O a/O bale/O of/O hay/O ,/O too/O anxious/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
He/O rose/O and/O brushed/O himself/O off/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O 'm/O glad/O they/O found/O you/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ,/O dismounting/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pyp/O hopped/O off/O his/O horse/O and/O looked/O at/O the/O lightening/O sky/O with/O disgust/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O us/O a/O hand/O bedding/O down/O the/O horses/O ,/O Sam/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O small/O boy/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O a/O long/O day/O before/O us/O ,/O and/O no/O sleep/O to/O face/O it/O on/O ,/O thanks/O to/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O day/O broke/O ,/O Jon/PERSON walked/O to/O the/O kitchens/O as/O he/O did/O every/O dawn/O ./O 
Three-Finger/O Hobb/PERSON said/O nothing/O as/O he/O gave/O him/O the/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O breakfast/O ./O 
Today/O it/O was/O three/O brown/O eggs/O boiled/O hard/O ,/O with/O fried/O bread/O and/O ham/O steak/O and/O a/O bowl/O of/O wrinkled/O plums/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON carried/O the/O food/O back/O to/O the/O King/O 's/O Tower/O ./O 
He/O found/O Mormont/PERSON at/O the/O window/O seat/O ,/O writing/O ./O 
His/O raven/O was/O walking/O back/O and/O forth/O across/O his/O shoulders/O ,/O muttering/O ,/O \/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O bird/O shrieked/O when/O Jon/PERSON entered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Put/O the/O food/O on/O the/O table/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O said/O ,/O glancing/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O have/O some/O beer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON opened/O a/O shuttered/O window/O ,/O took/O the/O flagon/O of/O beer/O off/O the/O outside/O ledge/O ,/O and/O filled/O a/O horn/O ./O 
Hobb/PERSON had/O given/O him/O a/O lemon/O ,/O still/O cold/O from/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON crushed/O it/O in/O his/O fist/O ./O 
The/O juice/O trickled/O through/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON drank/O lemon/O in/O his/O beer/O every/O day/O ,/O and/O claimed/O that/O was/O why/O he/O still/O had/O his/O own/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Doubtless/O you/O loved/O your/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O when/O Jon/PERSON brought/O him/O his/O horn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O things/O we/O love/O destroy/O us/O every/O time/O ,/O lad/O ./O 
Remember/O when/O I/O told/O you/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O remember/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O sullenly/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O care/O to/O talk/O of/O his/O father/O 's/O death/O ,/O not/O even/O to/O Mormont/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O See/O that/O you/O never/O forget/O it/O ./O 
The/O hard/O truths/O are/O the/O ones/O to/O hold/O tight/O ./O 
Fetch/O me/O my/O plate/O ./O 
Is/O it/O ham/O again/O ?/O 
So/O be/O it/O ./O 
You/O look/O weary/O ./O 
Was/O your/O moonlight/O ride/O so/O tiring/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O throat/O was/O dry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Know/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O echoed/O from/O Mormont/LOCATION 's/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O they/O chose/O me/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O because/O I/O 'm/O dumb/O as/O a/O stump/O ,/O Snow/O ?/O 
Aemon/PERSON told/O me/O you/O 'd/O go/O ./O 
I/O told/O him/O you/O 'd/O be/O back/O ./O 
I/O know/O my/O men/O .../O and/O my/O boys/O too/O ./O 
Honor/O set/O you/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O .../O and/O honor/O brought/O you/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O friends/O brought/O me/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O I/O say/O it/O was/O your/O honor/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON inspected/O his/O plate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O killed/O my/O father/O ./O 
Did/O you/O expect/O me/O to/O do/O nothing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O we/O expected/O you/O to/O do/O just/O as/O you/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON tried/O a/O plum/O ,/O spit/O out/O the/O pit/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ordered/O a/O watch/O kept/O over/O you./O ,/O You/O were/O seen/O leaving/O ./O 
If/O your/O brothers/O had/O not/O fetched/O you/O back/O ,/O you/O would/O have/O been/O taken/O along/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O not/O by/O friends/O ./O 
Unless/O you/O have/O a/O horse/O with/O wings/O like/O a/O raven/O ./O 
Do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON felt/O like/O a/O fool/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pity/O ,/O we/O could/O use/O a/O horse/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON stood/O tall/O ./O 
He/O told/O himself/O that/O he/O would/O die/O well/O ;/O that/O much/O he/O could/O do/O ,/O at/O the/O least/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O the/O penalty/O for/O desertion/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O afraid/O to/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Die/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O raven/O cried/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O live/O ,/O I/O hope/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ,/O cutting/O his/O ham/O with/O a/O dagger/O and/O feeding/O a/O bite/O to/O the/O bird/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O not/O deserted-yet/O ./O 
Here/O you/O stand/O ./O 
If/O we/O beheaded/O every/O boy/O who/O rode/O to/O Mole/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Town/LOCATION in/O the/O night/O ,/O only/O ghosts/O would/O guard/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Yet/O maybe/O you/O mean/O to/O flee/O again/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O or/O a/O fortnight/O from/O now/O ./O 
Is/O that/O it/O ?/O 
Is/O that/O your/O hope/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON kept/O silent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O thought/O so/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/O peeled/O the/O shell/O off/O a/O boiled/O egg/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O father/O is/O dead/O ,/O lad/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O you/O can/O bring/O him/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O answered/O ,/O sullen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 've/O seen/O the/O dead/O come/O back/O ,/O you/O and/O me/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O not/O something/O I/O care/O to/O see/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O ate/O the/O egg/O in/O two/O bites/O and/O flicked/O a/O bit/O of/O shell/O out/O from/O between/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O is/O in/O the/O field/O with/O all/O the/O power/O of/O the/O north/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Any/O one/O of/O his/O lords/O bannermen/O commands/O more/O swords/O than/O you/O 'll/O find/O in/O all/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
Why/O do/O you/O imagine/O that/O they/O need/O your/O help/O ?/O 
Are/O you/O such/O a/O mighty/O warrior/O ,/O or/O do/O you/O carry/O a/O grumkin/O in/O your/O pocket/O to/O magic/O up/O your/O sword/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O no/O answer/O for/O him/O ./O 
The/O raven/O was/O pecking/O at/O an/O egg/O ,/O breaking/O the/O shell/O ./O 
Pushing/O his/O beak/O through/O the/O hole/O ,/O he/O pulled/O out/O morsels/O of/O white/O and/O yoke/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O not/O the/O only/O one/O touched/O by/O this/O war/O ./O 
Like/O as/O not/O ,/O my/O sister/O is/O marching/O in/O your/O brother/O 's/O host/O ,/O her/O and/O those/O daughters/O of/O hers/O ,/O dressed/O in/O men/O 's/O mail/O ./O 
Maege/O is/O a/O hoary/O old/O snark/O ,/O stubborn/O ,/O short-tempered/O ,/O and/O willful/O ./O 
Truth/O be/O told/O ,/O I/O can/O hardly/O stand/O to/O be/O around/O the/O wretched/O woman/O ,/O but/O that/O does/O not/O mean/O my/O love/O for/O her/O is/O any/O less/O than/O the/O love/O you/O bear/O your/O half/O sisters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Frowning/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON took/O his/O last/O egg/O and/O squeezed/O it/O in/O his/O fist/O until/O the/O shell/O crunched/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Or/O perhaps/O it/O does/O ./O 
Be/O that/O as/O it/O may/O ,/O I/O 'd/O still/O grieve/O if/O she/O were/O slain/O ,/O yet/O you/O do/O n't/O see/O me/O running/O off/O ./O 
I/O said/O the/O words/O ,/O just/O as/O you/O did/O ./O 
My/O place/O is/O here/O .../O where/O is/O yours/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O I/O have/O no/O place/O ,/O Jon/PERSON wanted/O to/O say/O ,/O I/O 'm/O a/O bastard/O ,/O I/O have/O no/O rights/O ,/O no/O name/O ,/O no/O mother/O ,/O and/O now/O not/O even/O a/O father/O ./O 
The/O words/O would/O not/O come/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O cold/O winds/O are/O rising/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
Beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O the/O shadows/O lengthen/O ./O 
Cotter/PERSON Pyke/PERSON writes/O of/O vast/O herds/O of/O elk/O ,/O streaming/O south/O and/O east/O toward/O the/O sea/O ,/O and/O mammoths/O as/O well/O ./O 
He/O says/O one/O of/O his/O men/O discovered/O huge/O ,/O misshapen/O footprints/O not/O three/O leagues/O from/O Eastwatch/LOCATION ./O 
Rangers/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Tower/O have/O found/O whole/O villages/O abandoned/O ,/O and/O at/O night/O Ser/PERSON Denys/PERSON says/O they/O see/O fires/O in/O the/O mountains/O ,/O huge/O blazes/O that/O burn/O from/O dusk/O till/O dawn/O ./O 
Quorin/PERSON Halfhand/PERSON took/O a/O captive/O in/O the/O depths/O of/O the/O Gorge/O ,/O and/O the/O man/O swears/O that/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON is/O massing/O all/O his/O people/O in/O some/O new/O ,/O secret/O stronghold/O he/O 's/O found/O ,/O to/O what/O end/O the/O gods/O only/O know/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O your/O uncle/O Benjen/PERSON was/O the/O only/O ranger/O we/O 've/O lost/O this/O past/O year/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ben/PERSON Jen/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O squawked/O ,/O bobbing/O its/O head/O ,/O bits/O of/O egg/O dribbling/O from/O its/O beak/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ben/PERSON Jen/PERSON ./O 
Ben/PERSON Jen/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
There/O had/O been/O others/O ./O 
Too/O many/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O your/O brother/O 's/O war/O is/O more/O important/O than/O ours/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O old/O man/O barked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON chewed/O his/O lip/O ./O 
The/O raven/O flapped/O its/O wings/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O War/O ,/O war/O ,/O war/O ,/O war/O ,/O \/O ''/O it/O sang/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O save/O us/O ,/O boy/O ,/O you/O 're/O not/O blind/O and/O you/O 're/O not/O stupid/O ./O 
When/O dead/O men/O come/O hunting/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O do/O you/O think/O it/O matters/O who/O sits/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON had/O not/O thought/O of/O it/O that/O way/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O lord/O father/O sent/O you/O to/O us/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
Why/O ,/O who/O can/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
Why/O ?/O 
Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O raven/O called/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O I/O know/O is/O that/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O flows/O in/O the/O veins/O of/O the/O Starks/O ./O 
The/O First/O Men/O built/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O said/O they/O remember/O things/O otherwise/O forgotten/O ./O 
And/O that/O beast/O of/O yours/O .../O he/O led/O us/O to/O the/O wights/O ,/O warned/O you/O of/O the/O dead/O man/O on/O the/O steps/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON would/O doubtless/O call/O that/O happenstance/O ,/O yet/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON is/O dead/O and/O I/O 'm/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON stabbed/O a/O chunk/O of/O ham/O with/O the/O point/O of/O his/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O you/O were/O meant/O to/O be/O here/O ,/O and/O I/O want/O you/O and/O that/O wolf/O of/O yours/O with/O us/O when/O we/O go/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O words/O sent/O a/O chill/O of/O excitement/O down/O Jon/PERSON 's/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O Wall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O heard/O me/O ./O 
I/O mean/O to/O find/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O alive/O or/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O chewed/O and/O swallowed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O sit/O here/O meekly/O and/O wait/O for/O the/O snows/O and/O the/O ice/O winds/O ./O 
We/O must/O know/O what/O is/O happening/O ./O 
This/O time/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O will/O ride/O in/O force/O ,/O against/O the/O King-beyond-the-Wall/O ,/O the/O Others/O ,/O and/O anything/O else/O that/O may/O be/O out/O there/O ./O 
I/O mean/O to/O command/O them/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pointed/O his/O dagger/O at/O Jon/PERSON 's/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O custom/O ,/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O steward/O is/O his/O squire/O as/O well/O .../O but/O I/O do/O not/O care/O to/O wake/O every/O dawn/O wondering/O if/O you/O 've/O run/O off/O again/O ./O 
So/O I/O will/O have/O an/O answer/O from/O you/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ,/O and/O I/O will/O have/O it/O now/O ./O 
Are/O you/O a/O brother/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O .../O or/O only/O a/O bastard/O boy/O who/O wants/O to/O play/O at/O war/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON straightened/O himself/O and/O took/O a/O long/O deep/O breath/O ./O 
Forgive/O me/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON ,/O Arya/PERSON ,/O Bran/O .../O forgive/O me/O ,/O I/O can/O not/O help/O you/O ./O 
He/O has/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ./O 
This/O is/O my/O place/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O .../O yours/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Your/O man/O ./O 
I/O swear/O it/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O run/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Good/O ./O 
Now/O go/O put/O on/O your/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
