-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Daenerys/O Targaryen/O wed/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON with/O fear/O and/O barbaric/O splendor/O in/O a/O field/O beyond/O the/O walls/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O for/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON believed/O that/O all/O things/O of/O importance/O in/O a/O man/O 's/O life/O must/O be/O done/O beneath/O the/O open/O sky/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON had/O called/O his/O khalasar/O to/O attend/O him/O and/O they/O had/O come/O ,/O forty/O thousand/O Dothraki/O warriors/O and/O uncounted/O numbers/O of/O women/O ,/O children/O ,/O and/O slaves/O ./O 
Outside/O the/O city/O walls/O they/O camped/O with/O their/O vast/O herds/O ,/O raising/O palaces/O of/O woven/O grass/O ,/O eating/O everything/O in/O sight/O ,/O and/O making/O the/O good/O folk/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION more/O anxious/O with/O every/O passing/O day/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O fellow/O magisters/O ;/O have/O doubled/O the/O size/O of/O the/O city/O guard/O ,/O \/O ''/O Illyrio/PERSON told/O them/O over/O platters/O of/O honey/O duck/O and/O orange/O snap/O peppers/O one/O night/O at/O the/O manse/O that/O had/O been/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O ./O 
The/O khal/O had/O joined/O his/O khalasar/O ,/O his/O estate/O given/O over/O to/O Daenerys/PERSON and/O her/O brother/O until/O the/O wedding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Best/O we/O get/O Princess/O Daenerys/PERSON wedded/O quickly/O before/O they/O hand/O half/O the/O wealth/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION away/O to/O sellswords/O and/O bravos/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON jested/O ./O 
The/O exile/O had/O offered/O her/O brother/O his/O sword/O the/O night/O Dany/PERSON had/O been/O sold/O to/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ;/O Viserys/PERSON had/O accepted/O eagerly/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON had/O been/O their/O constant/O companion/O ever/O since/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON laughed/O lightly/O through/O his/O forked/O beard/O ,/O but/O Viserys/PERSON did/O not/O so/O much/O as/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O can/O have/O her/O tomorrow/O ,/O if/O he/O likes/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O brother/O said/O ./O 
He/O glanced/O over/O at/O Dany/PERSON ,/O and/O she/O lowered/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O long/O as/O he/O pays/O the/O price/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Illyrio/PERSON waved/O a/O languid/O hand/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O rings/O glittering/O on/O his/O fat/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O told/O you/O ,/O all/O is/O settled/O ./O 
Trust/O me/O ./O 
The/O khal/O has/O promised/O you/O a/O crown/O ,/O and/O you/O shall/O have/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O but/O when/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O the/O khal/O chooses/O ,/O \/O ''/O Illyrio/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O will/O have/O the/O girl/O first/O ,/O and/O after/O they/O are/O wed/O he/O must/O make/O his/O procession/O across/O the/O plains/O and/O present/O her/O to/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O at/O Vaes/PERSON Dolthrak/PERSON ./O 
After/O that/O ,/O perhaps/O ./O 
If/O the/O omens/O favor/O war/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O seethed/O with/O impatience/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O piss/O on/O Dothraki/O omens/O ./O 
The/O Usurper/O sits/O on/O my/O father/O 's/O throne/O ./O 
How/O long/O must/O I/O wait/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Illyrio/PERSON gave/O a/O massive/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O waited/O most/O of/O your/O life/O ,/O great/O king/O ./O 
What/O is/O another/O few/O months/O ,/O another/O few/O years/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O traveled/O as/O far/O east/O as/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ,/O nodded/O in/O agreement/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O counsel/O you/O to/O be/O patient/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O are/O true/O to/O their/O word/O ,/O but/O they/O do/O things/O in/O their/O own/O time/O ./O 
A/O lesser/O man/O may/O beg/O a/O favor/O from/O the/O khal/O ,/O but/O must/O never/O presume/O to/O berate/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O bristled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Guard/O your/O tongue/O ,/O Mormont/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O have/O it/O out/O ./O 
I/O am/O no/O lesser/O man/O ,/O I/O am/O the/O rightful/O Lord/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
The/O dragon/O does/O not/O beg/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON lowered/O his/O eyes/O respectfully/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON smiled/O enigmatically/O and/O tore/O a/O wing/O from/O the/O duck/O ./O 
Honey/O and/O grease/O ran/O over/O his/O fingers/O and/O dripped/O down/O into/O his/O beard/O as/O he/O nibbled/O at/O the/O tender/O meat/O ./O 
There/O are/O no/O more/O dragons/O ,/O Dany/PERSON thought/O ,/O staring/O at/O her/O brother/O ,/O though/O she/O did/O not/O dare/O say/O it/O aloud/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O that/O night/O she/O dreamt/O of/O one/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON was/O hitting/O her/O ,/O hurting/O her/O ./O 
She/O was/O naked/O ,/O clumsy/O with/O fear/O ./O 
She/O ran/O from/O him/O ,/O but/O her/O body/O seemed/O thick/O and/O ungainly/O ./O 
He/O struck/O her/O again/O ./O 
She/O ''/O ,/O ``/O stumbled/O and/O fell/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O woke/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O screamed/O as/O he/O kicked/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O woke/O the/O dragon/O ,/O you/O woke/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O thighs/O were/O slick/O with/O blood/O ./O 
She/O closed/O her/O eyes/O and/O whimpered/O ./O 
As/O if/O in/O answer/O ,/O there/O was/O a/O hideous/O ripping/O sound/O and/O the/O crackling/O of/O some/O great/O fire/O ./O 
When/O she/O looked/O again/O ,/O Viserys/PERSON was/O gone/O ,/O great/O columns/O of/O flame/O rose/O all/O around/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O midst/O of/O them/O was/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
It/O turned/O its/O great/O head/O slowly/O ./O 
When/O its/O molten/O eyes/O found/O hers/O ,/O she/O woke/O ,/O shaking/O and/O covered/O with/O a/O fine/O sheen/O of/O sweat/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O been/O so/O afraid/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O .../O until/O the/O day/O of/O her/O wedding/O came/O at/O last/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O ceremony/O began/O at/O dawn/O and/O continued/O until/O dusk/O ,/O an/O endless/O day/O of/O drinking/O and/O feasting/O and/O fighting/O ./O 
A/O mighty/O earthen/O ramp/O had/O been/O raised/O amid/O the/O grass/O palaces/O ,/O and/O there/O Dany/PERSON was/O seated/O beside/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ,/O above/O the/O seething/O sea/O of/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
She/O had/O never/O seen/O so/O many/O people/O in/O one/O place/O ,/O nor/O people/O so/O strange/O and/O frightening/O ./O 
The/O horselords/O might/O put/O on/O rich/O fabrics/O and/O sweet/O perfumes/O when/O they/O visited/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O but/O out/O under/O the/O open/O sky/O they/O kept/O the/O old/O ways/O ./O 
Men/O and/O women/O alike/O wore/O painted/O leather/O vests/O over/O bare/O chests/O and/O horsehair/O leggings/O cinched/O by/O bronze/O medallion/O belts/O ,/O and/O the/O warriors/O greased/O their/O long/O braids/O with/O fat/O from/O the/O rendering/O pits/O ./O 
They/O gorged/O themselves/O on/O horseflesh/O roasted/O with/O honey/O and/O peppers/O ,/O drank/O themselves/O blind/O on/O fermented/O mare/O 's/O milk/O and/O Illyrio/PERSON 's/O fine/O wines/O ,/O and/O spat/O jests/O at/O each/O other/O across/O the/O fires/O ,/O their/O voices/O harsh/O and/O alien/O in/O Dany/PERSON 's/O ears/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON was/O seated/O just/O below/O her/O ,/O splendid/O in/O a/O new/O black/O wool/O tunic/O with/O a/O scarlet/O dragon/O on/O the/O chest/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Jo/PERSON rah/O sat/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Theirs/O was/O a/O place/O of/O high/O honor/O ,/O just/O below/O the/O khal/O 's/O own/O bloodriders/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON could/O see/O the/O anger/O in/O her/O brother/O 's/O lilac/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O like/O sitting/O beneath/O her/O ,/O and/O he/O fumed/O when/O the/O slaves/O offered/O each/O dish/O first/O to/O the/O khal/O and/O his/O bride/O ,/O and/O served/O him/O from/O the/O portions/O they/O refused/O ./O 
He/O could/O do/O nothing/O but/O nurse/O his/O resentment/O ,/O so/O nurse/O it/O he/O did/O ,/O his/O mood/O growing/O blacker/O by/O the/O hour/O at/O each/O insult/O to/O his/O person/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON had/O never/O felt/O so/O alone/O as/O she/O did/O seated/O in/O the/O midst/O of/O that/O vast/O horde/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O had/O told/O her/O to/O smile/O ,/O and/O so/O she/O smiled/O until/O her/O face/O ached/O and/O the/O tears/O came/O unbidden/O to/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O did/O her/O best/O to/O hide/O them/O ,/O knowing/O how/O angry/O Viserys/PERSON would/O be/O if/O he/O saw/O her/O crying/O ,/O terrified/O of/O how/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON might/O react/O ./O 
Food/O was/O brought/O to/O her/O ,/O steaming/O joints/O of/O meat/O and/O thick/O black/O sausages/O and/O Dothraki/PERSON blood/O pies/O ,/O and/O later/O fruits/O and/O sweetgrass/O stews/O and/O delicate/O pastries/O from/O the/O kitchens/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O but/O she/O waved/O it/O all/O away/O ./O 
Her/O stomach/O was/O a/O roil/O ,/O and/O she/O knew/O she/O could/O keep/O none/O of/O it/O down/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O one/O to/O talk/O to/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON shouted/O commands/O and/O jests/O down/O to/O his/O bloodriders/O ,/O and/O laughed/O at/O their/O replies/O ,/O but/O he/O scarcely/O glanced/O at/O Dany/PERSON beside/O him/O ./O 
They/O had/O no/O common/O language/O ./O 
Dothraki/PERSON was/O incomprehensible/O to/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O khal/O knew/O only/O a/O few/O words/O of/O the/O bastard/O Valyrian/O of/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ,/O and/O none/O at/O all/O of/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
She/O would/O even/O have/O welcomed/O the/O conversation/O of/O Illyrio/LOCATION and/O her/O brother/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O too/O far/O below/O to/O hear/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O So/O she/O sat/O in/O her/O wedding/O silks/O ,/O nursing/O a/O cup/O of/O honeyed/O wine/O ,/O afraid/O to/O eat/O ,/O talking/O silently/O to/O herself/O ./O 
I/O am/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
I/O am/O Daenerys/PERSON Stormborn/PERSON ,/O Princess/O of/O Dragonstone/LOCATION ,/O of/O the/O blood/O and/O seed/O of/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sun/O was/O only/O a/O quarter/O of/O the/O way/O up/O the/O sky/O when/O she/O saw/O her/O first/O man/O die/O ./O 
Drums/O were/O beating/O as/O some/O of/O the/O women/O danced/O for/O the/O khal/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON watched/O without/O expression/O ,/O but/O his/O eyes/O followed/O their/O movements/O ,/O and/O from/O time/O to/O time/O he/O would/O toss/O down/O a/O bronze/O medallion/O for/O the/O women/O to/O fight/O over/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O warriors/O were/O watching/O too/O ./O 
One/O of/O them/O finally/O stepped/O into/O the/O circle/O ,/O grabbed/O a/O dancer/O by/O the/O arm/O ,/O pushed/O her/O down/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O and/O mounted/O her/O right/O there/O ,/O as/O a/O stallion/O mounts/O a/O mare/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON had/O told/O her/O that/O might/O happen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O mate/O like/O the/O animals/O in/O their/O herds/O ./O 
There/O is/O no/O privacy/O in/O a/O khalasar/O ,/O and/O they/O do/O not/O understand/O sin/O or/O shame/O as/O we/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON looked/O away/O from/O the/O coupling/O ,/O frightened/O when/O she/O realized/O what/O was/O happening/O ,/O but/O a/O second/O warrior/O stepped/O forward/O ,/O and/O a/O third/O ,/O and/O soon/O there/O was/O no/O way/O to/O avert/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Then/O two/O men/O seized/O the/O same/O woman/O ./O 
She/O heard/O a/O shout/O ,/O saw/O a/O shove/O ,/O and/O in/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O the/O arakhs/O were/O out/O ,/O long/O razor-sharp/O blades/O ,/O half/O sword/O and/O half/O scythe/O ./O 
A/O dance/O of/O death/O began/O as/O the/O warriors/O circled/O and/O slashed/O ,/O leaping/O toward/O each/O other/O ,/O whirling/O the/O blades/O around/O their/O heads/O ,/O shrieking/O insults/O at/O each/O clash/O ./O 
No/O one/O made/O a/O move/O to/O interfere/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O ended/O as/O quickly/O as/O it/O began/O ./O 
The/O arakhs/O shivered/O together/O faster/O than/O Dany/PERSON could/O follow/O ,/O one/O man/O missed/O a/O step/O ,/O the/O other/O swung/O his/O blade/O in/O a/O flat/O arc/O ./O 
Steel/O bit/O into/O flesh/O just/O above/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON '/O s/O waist/O ,/O and/O opened/O him/O from/O backbone/O to/O belly/O button/O ,/O spilling/O his/O entrails/O into/O the/O dust/O ./O 
As/O the/O loser/O died/O ,/O the/O winner/O took/O hold/O of/O the/O nearest/O woman-not/O even/O the/O one/O they/O had/O been/O quarreling/O over-and/O had/O her/O there/O and/O then/O ./O 
Slaves/O carried/O off/O the/O body/O ,/O and/O the/O dancing/O resumed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON had/O warned/O Dany/PERSON about/O this/O too/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O Dothraki/O wedding/O without/O at/O least/O three/O deaths/O is/O deemed/O a/O dull/O affair/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O had/O said/O ./O 
Her/O wedding/O must/O have/O been/O especially/O blessed/O ;/O before/O the/O day/O was/O over/O ,/O a/O dozen/O men/O had/O died/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O the/O hours/O passed/O ,/O the/O terror/O grew/O in/O Dany/PERSON ,/O until/O it/O was/O all/O she/O could/O do/O not/O to/O scream/O ./O 
She/O was/O afraid/O of/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O whose/O ways/O seemed/O alien/O and/O monstrous/O ,/O as/O if/O they/O were/O beasts/O in/O human/O skins/O and/O not/O true/O men/O at/O all/O ./O 
She/O was/O afraid/O of/O her/O brother/O ,/O of/O what/O he/O might/O do/O if/O she/O failed/O him/O ./O 
Most/O of/O all/O ,/O she/O was/O afraid/O of/O what/O would/O happen/O tonight/O under/O the/O stars/O ,/O when/O her/O brother/O gave/O her/O up/O to/O the/O hulking/O giant/O who/O sat/O drinking/O beside/O her/O with/O a/O face/O as/O still/O and/O cruel/O as/O a/O bronze/O mask/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O at/O last/O the/O sun/O was/O low/O in/O the/O sky/O ,/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON clapped/O his/O hands/O together/O ,/O and/O the/O drums/O and/O the/O shouting/O and/O feasting/O came/O to/O a/O sudden/O halt/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON stood/O and/O pulled/O Dany/PERSON to/O her/O feet/O beside/O him/O ./O 
It/O was/O time/O for/O her/O bride/O gifts/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O after/O the/O gifts/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O after/O the/O sun/O had/O gone/O down/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O time/O for/O the/O first/O ride/O and/O the/O consummation/O of/O her/O marriage/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON tried/O to/O put/O the/O thought/O aside/O ,/O but/O it/O would/O not/O leave/O her/O ./O 
She/O hugged/O herself/O to/O try/O to/O keep/O from/O shaking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O brother/O Viserys/PERSON gifted/O her/O with/O three/O handmaids/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON knew/O they/O had/O cost/O him/O nothing/O ;/O Illyrio/PERSON no/O doubt/O had/O provided/O the/O girls/O ./O 
Irri/PERSON and/O Jhiqui/PERSON were/O copper-skinned/O Dothraki/PERSON with/O black/O hair/O and/O almond/O shaped/O eyes/O ,/O Doreah/PERSON a/O fair-haired/O ,/O blue-eyed/O Lysene/PERSON girl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O are/O no/O common/O servants/O ,/O sweet/O sister/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O brother/O told/O her/O as/O they/O were/O brought/O forward/O one/O by/O one/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Illyrio/PERSON and/O I/O selected/O them/O personally/O for/O you/O ./O 
Irri/ORGANIZATION will/O teach/O you/O riding/O ,/O Jhiqui/PERSON the/O Dothraki/O tongue/O ,/O and/O Doreah/PERSON will/O instruct/O you/O in/O the/O womanly/O arts/O of/O love/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O thinly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O 's/O very/O good/O ,/O Illyrio/PERSON and/O I/O can/O both/O swear/O to/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON apologized/O for/O his/O gift/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O a/O small/O thing/O ,/O my/O princess/O ,/O but/O all/O a/O poor/O exile/O could/O afford/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O laid/O a/O small/O stack/O of/O old/O books/O before/O her/O ./O 
They/O were/O histories/O and/O songs/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O she/O saw/O ,/O written/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ./O 
She/O thanked/O him/O with/O all/O her/O heart/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON murmured/O a/O command/O ,/O and/O four/O burly/O slaves/O hurried/O forward/O ,/O bearing/O between/O them/O a/O great/O cedar/O chest/O bound/O in/O bronze/O ./O 
When/O she/O opened/O it/O ,/O she/O found/O piles/O of/O the/O finest/O velvets/O and/O damasks/O the/O Free/O Cities/O could/O produce/O .../O and/O resting/O on/O top/O ,/O nestled/O in/O the/O soft/O cloth/O ,/O three/O huge/O eggs/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON gasped/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O most/O beautiful/O things/O she/O had/O ever/O seen/O ,/O each/O different/O than/O the/O others/O ,/O patterned/O in/O such/O rich/O colors/O that/O at/O first/O she/O thought/O they/O were/O crusted/O with/O jewels/O ,/O and/O so/O large/O it/O took/O both/O of/O her/O hands/O to/O hold/O one/O ./O 
She/O lifted/O it/O delicately/O ,/O expecting/O that/O it/O would/O be/O made/O of/O some/O fine/O porcelain/O or/O delicate/O enamel/O ,/O or/O even/O blown/O glass/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O much/O heavier/O than/O that/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O were/O all/O of/O solid/O stone/O ./O 
The/O surface/O of/O the/O shell/O was/O covered/O with/O tiny/O scales/O ,/O and/O as/O she/O turned/O the/O egg/O between/O her/O fingers/O ,/O they/O shimmered/O like/O polished/O metal/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O setting/O sun/O ./O 
One/O egg/O was/O a/O deep/O green/O ,/O with/O burnished/O bronze/O flecks/O that/O came/O and/O went/O depending/O on/O how/O Dany/PERSON turned/O it/O ./O 
Another/O was/O pale/O cream/O streaked/O with/O gold/O ./O 
The/O last/O was/O black/O ,/O as/O black/O as/O a/O midnight/O sea/O ,/O yet/O alive/O with/O scarlet/O ripples/O and/O swirls/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O they/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ,/O her/O voice/O hushed/O and/O full/O of/O wonder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dragon/O 's/O eggs/O ,/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Lands/O beyond/O Asshai/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O eons/O have/O turned/O them/O to/O stone/O ,/O yet/O still/O they/O burn/O bright/O with/O beauty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O shall/O treasure/O them/O always/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON had/O heard/O tales/O of/O such/O eggs/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O never/O seen/O one/O ,/O nor/O thought/O to/O see/O one/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O truly/O magnificent/O gift/O ,/O though/O she/O knew/O that/O Illyrio/PERSON could/O afford/O to/O be/O lavish/O ./O 
He/O had/O collected/O a/O fortune/O in/O horses/O and/O slaves/O for/O his/O part/O in/O selling/O her/O to/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O khal/O 's/O bloodriders/O offered/O her/O the/O traditional/O three/O weapons/O ,/O and/O splendid/O weapons/O they/O were/O ./O 
Haggo/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O great/O leather/O whip/O with/O a/O silver/O handle/O ,/O Cohollo/PERSON a/O magnificent/O arakh/O chased/O in/O gold/O ,/O and/O Qotho/O a/O double-curved/O dragonbone/O bow/O taller/O than/O she/O was/O ./O 
Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O the/O traditional/O refusals/O for/O these/O offerings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O a/O gift/O worthy/O of/O a/O great/O warrior/O ,/O O/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O and/O I/O am/O but/O a/O woman/O ./O 
Let/O my/O lord/O husband/O bear/O these/O in/O my/O stead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O so/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON too/O received/O his/O \/O ``/O bride/O gifts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Other/O gifts/O she/O was/O given/O in/O plenty/O by/O other/O Dothraki/O :/O slippers/O and/O jewels/O and/O silver/O rings/O for/O her/O hair/O ,/O medallion/O belts/O and/O painted/O vests/O and/O soft/O furs/O ,/O sandsilks/O and/O jars/O of/O scent/O ,/O needles/O and/O feathers/O and/O tiny/O bottles/O of/O purple/O glass/O ,/O and/O a/O gown/O made/O from/O the/O skin/O of/O a/O thousand/O mice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O handsome/O gift/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON said/O of/O the/O last/O ,/O after/O he/O had/O told/O her/O what/O it/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Most/O lucky/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O gifts/O mounted/O up/O around/O her/O in/O great/O piles/O ,/O more/O gifts/O than/O she/O could/O possibly/O imagine/O ,/O more/O gifts/O than/O she/O could/O want/O or/O use/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O last/O of/O all/O ,/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON brought/O forth/O his/O own/O bride/O gift/O to/O her/O ./O 
An/O expectant/O hush/O rippled/O out/O from/O the/O center/O of/O the/O camp/O as/O he/O left/O her/O side/O ,/O growing/O until/O it/O had/O swallowed/O the/O whole/O ''/O ,/O ``/O khalasar/O ./O 
When/O he/O returned/O ,/O the/O dense/O press/O of/O Dothraki/O gift-givers/O parted/O before/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O led/O the/O horse/O to/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O was/O a/O young/O filly/O ,/O spirited/O and/O splendid/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON knew/O just/O enough/O about/O horses/O to/O know/O that/O this/O was/O no/O ordinary/O animal/O ./O 
There/O was/O something/O about/O her/O that/O took/O the/O breath/O away/O ./O 
She/O was/O grey/O as/O the/O winter/O sea/O ,/O with/O a/O mane/O like/O silver/O smoke/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hesitantly/O she/O reached/O out/O and/O stroked/O the/O horse/O 's/O neck/O ,/O ran/O her/O fingers/O through/O the/O silver/O of/O her/O mane/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON said/O something/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION and/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON translated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Silver/O for/O the/O silver/O of/O your/O hair/O ,/O the/O khal/O says/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O beautiful/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON murmured/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O is/O the/O pride/O of/O the/O khalasar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Illyrio/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Custom/O decrees/O that/O the/O khaleesi/O must/O ride/O a/O mount/O worthy/O of/O her/O place/O by/O the/O side/O of/O the/O khal/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON stepped/O forward/O and/O put/O his/O hands/O on/O her/O waist/O ./O 
He/O lifted/O her/O up/O as/O easily/O as/O if/O she/O were/O a/O child/O and/O set/O her/O on/O the/O thin/O Dothraki/O saddle/O ,/O so/O much/O smaller/O than/O the/O ones/O she/O was/O used/O to/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON sat/O there/O uncertain/O for/O a/O moment/O ./O 
No/O one/O had/O told/O her/O about/O this/O part/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O should/O I/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O Illyrio/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O Ser/PERSON Jo/PERSON rah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON who/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O the/O reins/O and/O ride/O ./O 
You/O need/O not/O go/O far/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Nervously/O Dany/PERSON gathered/O the/O reins/O in/O her/O hands/O and/O slid/O her/O feet/O into/O the/O short/O stirrups/O ./O 
She/O was/O only/O a/O fair/O rider/O ;/O she/O had/O spent/O far/O more/O time/O traveling/O by/O ship/O and/O wagon/O and/O palanquin/O than/O by/O horseback/O ./O 
Praying/O that/O she/O would/O not/O fall/O off/O and/O disgrace/O herself/O ,/O she/O gave/O the/O filly/O the/O lightest/O and/O most/O timid/O touch/O with/O her/O knees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O for/O the/O first/O time/O in/O hours/O ,/O she/O forgot/O to/O be/O afraid/O ./O 
Or/O perhaps/O it/O was/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ever/O ./O 
The/O silver-grey/O filly/O moved/O with/O a/O smooth/O and/O silken/O gait/O ,/O and/O the/O crowd/O parted/O for/O her/O ,/O every/O eye/O upon/O them/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON found/O herself/O moving/O faster/O than/O she/O had/O intended/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O it/O was/O exciting/O rather/O than/O terrifying/O ./O 
The/O horse/O broke/O into/O a/O trot/O ,/O and/O she/O smiled/O ./O 
Dothraki/PERSON scrambled/O to/O clear/O a/O path/O ./O 
The/O slightest/O pressure/O with/O her/O legs/O ,/O the/O lightest/O touch/O on/O the/O reins/O ,/O and/O the/O filly/O responded/O ./O 
She/O sent/O it/O into/O a/O gallop/O ,/O and/O now/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON were/O hooting/O and/O laughing/O and/O shouting/O at/O her/O as/O they/O jumped/O out/O of/O her/O way/O ./O 
As/O she/O turned/O to/O ride/O back/O ,/O a/O firepit/O loomed/O ahead/O ,/O directly/O in/O her/O path/O ./O 
They/O were/O hemmed/O in/O on/O either/O side/O ,/O with/O no/O room/O to/O stop/O ./O 
A/O daring/O she/O had/O never/O known/O filled/O Daenerys/PERSON then/O ,/O and/O she/O gave/O the/O filly/O her/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O silver/O horse/O leapt/O the/O flames/O as/O if/O she/O had/O wings/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O pulled/O up/O before/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON ,/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Tell/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON that/O he/O has/O given/O me/O the/O wind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O fat/O Pentoshi/PERSON stroked/O his/O yellow/O beard/O as/O he/O repeated/O her/O words/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ,/O and/O Dany/PERSON saw/O her/O new/O husband/O smile/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O last/O sliver/O of/O sun/O vanished/O behind/O the/O high/O walls/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION to/O the/O west/O just/O then/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON had/O lost/O all/O track/O of/O time/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON commanded/O his/O bloodriders/O to/O bring/O forth/O his/O own/O horse/O ,/O a/O lean/O red/O stallion/O ./O 
As/O the/O khal/O was/O saddling/O the/O horse/O ,/O Viserys/PERSON slid/O close/O to/O Dany/PERSON on/O her/O silver/O ,/O dug/O his/O fingers/O into/O her/O leg/O ,/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Please/O him/O ,/O sweet/O sister/O ,/O or/O I/O swear/O ,/O you/O will/O see/O the/O dragon/O wake/O as/O it/O has/O never/O woken/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O fear/O came/O back/O to/O her/O then/O ,/O with/O her/O brother/O 's/O words/O ./O 
She/O felt/O like/O a/O child/O once/O more/O ,/O only/O thirteen/O and/O all/O alone/O ,/O not/O ready/O for/O what/O was/O about/O to/O happen/O to/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O rode/O out/O together/O as/O the/O stars/O came/O out/O ,/O leaving/O the/O khalasar/O and/O the/O grass/O palaces/O behind/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON spoke/O no/O word/O to/O her/O ,/O but/O drove/O his/O stallion/O at/O a/O hard/O trot/O through/O the/O gathering/O dusk/O ./O 
The/O tiny/O silver/O bells/O in/O his/O long/O braid/O rang/O softly/O as/O he/O rode/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O aloud/O as/O she/O followed/O ,/O trying/O to/O keep/O her/O courage/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O dragon/O was/O never/O afraid/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O she/O could/O not/O say/O how/O far/O or/O how/O long/O they/O had/O ridden/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O full/O dark/O when/O they/O stopped/O at/O a/O grassy/O place/O beside/O a/O small/O stream/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON swung/O off/O his/O horse/O and/O lifted/O her/O down/O from/O hers/O ./O 
She/O felt/O as/O fragile/O as/O glass/O in/O his/O hands/O ,/O her/O limbs/O as/O weak/O as/O water/O ./O 
She/O stood/O there/O helpless/O and/O trembling/O in/O her/O wedding/O silks/O while/O he/O secured/O the/O horses/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O turned/O to/O look/O at/O her/O ,/O she/O began/O to/O cry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON stared/O at/O her/O tears/O ,/O his/O face/O strangely/O empty/O of/O expression/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O lifted/O his/O hand/O and/O rubbed/O away/O the/O tears/O roughly/O with/O a/O callused/O thumb/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O speak/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O in/O wonder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Perhaps/O he/O had/O only/O that/O word/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O one/O word/O more/O than/O she/O had/O known/O he/O had/O ,/O and/O somehow/O it/O made/O her/O feel/O a/O little/O better/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON touched/O her/O hair/O lightly/O ,/O sliding/O the/O silver-blond/O strands/O between/O his/O fingers/O and/O murmuring/O softly/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
Dany/PERSON did/O not/O understand/O the/O words/O ,/O yet/O there/O was/O warmth/O in/O the/O tone/O ,/O a/O tenderness/O she/O had/O never/O expected/O from/O this/O man/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O put/O his/O finger/O under/O her/O chin/O and/O lifted/O her/O head/O ,/O so/O she/O was/O looking/O up/O into/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Drogo/PERSON towered/O over/O her/O as/O he/O towered/O over/O everyone/O ./O 
Taking/O her/O lightly/O under/O the/O arms/O ,/O he/O lifted/O her/O and/O seated/O her/O on/O a/O rounded/O rock/O beside/O the/O stream/O ./O 
Then/O he/O sat/O on/O the/O ground/O facing/O her/O ,/O legs/O crossed/O beneath/O him/O ,/O their/O faces/O finally/O at/O a/O height/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O the/O only/O word/O you/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON did/O not/O reply/O ./O 
His/O long/O heavy/O braid/O was/O coiled/O in/O the/O dirt/O beside/O him/O ./O 
He/O pulled/O it/O over/O his/O right/O shoulder/O and/O began/O to/O remove/O the/O bells/O from/O his/O hair/O ,/O one/O by/O one/O ./O 
After/O a/O moment/O Dany/PERSON leaned/O forward/O to/O help/O ./O 
When/O they/O were/O done/O ,/O Drogo/PERSON gestured/O ./O 
She/O understood/O ./O 
Slowly/O ,/O carefully/O ,/O she/O began/O to/O undo/O his/O braid/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O took/O a/O long/O time/O ./O 
All/O the/O while/O he/O sat/O there/O silently/O ,/O watching/O her/O ./O 
When/O she/O was/O done/O ,/O he/O shook/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O his/O hair/O spread/O out/O behind/O him/O like/O a/O river/O of/O darkness/O ,/O oiled/O and/O gleaming/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O seen/O hair/O so/O long/O ,/O so/O black/O ,/O so/O thick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O it/O was/O his/O turn/O ./O 
He/O began/O to/O undress/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O fingers/O were/O deft/O and/O strangely/O tender/O ./O 
He/O removed/O her/O silks/O one/O by/O one/O ,/O carefully/O ,/O while/O Dany/PERSON sat/O unmoving/O ,/O silent/O ,/O looking/O at/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
When/O he/O bared/O her/O small/O breasts/O ,/O she/O could/O not/O help/O herself/O ./O 
She/O averted/O her/O eyes/O and/O covered/O herself/O with/O her/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O pulled/O her/O hands/O away/O from/O her/O breasts/O ,/O gently/O but/O firmly/O ,/O then/O lifted/O her/O face/O again/O to/O make/O her/O look/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O repeated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O echoed/O back/O at/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O stood/O her/O up/O then/O and/O pulled/O her/O close/O to/O remove/O the/O last/O of/O her/O silks/O ./O 
The/O night/O air/O was/O chilly/O on/O her/O bare/O skin/O ./O 
She/O shivered/O ,/O and/O gooseflesh/O covered/O her/O arms/O and/O legs/O ./O 
She/O was/O afraid/O ''/O ,/O ``/O of/O what/O would/O come/O next/O ,/O but/O for/O a/O while/O nothing/O happened/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON sat/O with/O his/O legs/O crossed/O ,/O looking/O at/O her/O ,/O drinking/O in/O her/O body/O with/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O a/O while/O he/O began/O to/O touch/O her/O ./O 
Lightly/O at/O first/O ,/O then/O harder/O ./O 
She/O could/O sense/O the/O fierce/O strength/O in/O his/O hands/O ,/O but/O he/O never/O hurt/O her/O ./O 
He/O held/O her/O hand/O in/O his/O own/O and/O brushed/O her/O fingers/O ,/O one/O by/O one/O ./O 
He/O ran/O a/O hand/O gently/O down/O her/O leg/O ./O 
He/O stroked/O her/O face/O ,/O tracing/O the/O curve/O of/O her/O ears/O ,/O running/O a/O finger/O gently/O around/O her/O mouth/O ./O 
He/O put/O both/O hands/O in/O her/O hair/O and/O combed/O it/O with/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
He/O turned/O her/O around/O ,/O massaged/O her/O shoulders/O ,/O slid/O a/O knuckle/O down/O the/O path/O of/O her/O spine/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O as/O if/O hours/O passed/O before/O his/O hands/O finally/O went/O to/O her/O breasts/O ./O 
He/O stroked/O the/O soft/O skin/O underneath/O until/O it/O tingled/O ./O 
He/O circled/O her/O nipples/O with/O his/O thumbs/O ,/O pinched/O them/O between/O thumb/O and/O forefinger/O ,/O then/O began/O to/O pull/O at/O her/O ,/O very/O lightly/O at/O first/O ,/O then/O more/O insistently/O ,/O until/O her/O nipples/O stiffened/O and/O began/O to/O ache/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O stopped/O then/O ,/O and/O drew/O her/O down/O onto/O his/O lap/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON was/O flushed/O and/O breathless/O ,/O her/O heart/O fluttering/O in/O her/O chest/O ./O 
He/O cupped/O her/O face/O in/O his/O huge/O hands/O and/O looked/O into/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O and/O she/O knew/O it/O was/O a/O question/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O took/O his/O hand/O and/O moved/O it/O down/O to/O the/O wetness/O between/O her/O thighs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O as/O she/O put/O his/O finger/O inside/O her/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
