-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Of/O all/O the/O rooms/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION 's/O Great/O Keep/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON 's/O bedchambers/O were/O the/O hottest/O ./O 
She/O seldom/O had/O to/O light/O a/O fire/O ./O 
The/O castle/O had/O been/O built/O over/O natural/O hot/O springs/O ,/O and/O the/O scalding/O waters/O rushed/O through/O its/O walls/O and/O chambers/O like/O blood/O through/O a/O man/O 's/O body/O ,/O driving/O the/O chill/O from/O the/O stone/O halls/O ,/O filling/O the/O glass/O gardens/O with/O a/O moist/O warmth/O ,/O keeping/O the/O earth/O from/O freezing/O ./O 
Open/O pools/O smoked/O day/O and/O night/O in/O a/O dozen/O small/O courtyards/O ./O 
That/O was/O a/O little/O thing/O ,/O in/O summer/O ;/O in/O winter/O ,/O it/O was/O the/O difference/O between/O life/O and/O death/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O 's/O bath/O was/O always/O hot/O and/O steaming/O ,/O and/O her/O walls/O warm/O to/O the/O touch/O ./O 
The/O warmth/O reminded/O her/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O of/O days/O in/O the/O sun/O with/O Lysa/PERSON and/O Edmure/PERSON ,/O but/O Ned/PERSON could/O never/O abide/O the/O heat/O ./O 
The/O Starks/PERSON were/O made/O for/O the/O cold/O ,/O he/O would/O tell/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O would/O laugh/O and/O tell/O him/O in/O that/O case/O they/O had/O certainly/O built/O their/O castle/O in/O the/O wrong/O place/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O So/O when/O they/O had/O finished/O ,/O Ned/PERSON rolled/O off/O and/O climbed/O from/O her/O bed/O ,/O as/O he/O had/O a/O thousand/O times/O before/O ./O 
He/O crossed/O the/O room/O ,/O pulled/O back/O the/O heavy/O tapestries/O ,/O and/O threw/O open/O the/O high/O narrow/O windows/O one/O by/O one/O ,/O letting/O the/O night/O air/O into/O the/O chamber/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O wind/O swirled/O around/O him/O as/O he/O stood/O facing/O the/O dark/O ,/O naked/O and/O empty-handed/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON pulled/O the/O furs/O to/O her/O chin/O and/O watched/O him/O ./O 
He/O looked/O somehow/O smaller/O and/O more/O vulnerable/O ,/O like/O the/O youth/O she/O had/O wed/O in/O the/O sept/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O fifteen/O long/O years/O gone/O ./O 
Her/O loins/O still/O ached/O from/O the/O urgency/O of/O his/O lovemaking/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O good/O ache/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O his/O seed/O within/O her/O ./O 
She/O prayed/O that/O it/O might/O quicken/O there/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O three/O years/O since/O Rickon/PERSON ./O 
She/O was/O not/O too/O old/O ./O 
She/O could/O give/O him/O another/O son/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O refuse/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O as/O he/O turned/O back/O to/O her/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O haunted/O ,/O his/O voice/O thick/O with/O doubt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON sat/O up/O in/O the/O bed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O can/O not/O ./O 
You/O must/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O duties/O are/O here/O in/O the/O north/O ./O 
I/O have/O no/O wish/O to/O be/O Robert/PERSON 's/O Hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O not/O understand/O that/O ./O 
He/O is/O a/O king/O now/O ,/O and/O kings/O are/O not/O like/O other/O men/O ./O 
If/O you/O refuse/O to/O serve/O him/O ,/O he/O will/O wonder/O why/O ,/O and/O sooner/O or/O later/O he/O will/O begin/O to/O suspect/O that/O you/O oppose/O him/O ./O 
Ca/O n't/O you/O see/O the/O danger/O that/O would/O put/O us/O in/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ,/O refusing/O to/O believe/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON would/O never/O harm/O me/O or/O any/O of/O mine/O ./O 
We/O were/O closer/O than/O brothers/O ./O 
He/O loves/O me/O ./O 
If/O I/O refuse/O him/O ,/O he/O will/O roar/O and/O curse/O and/O bluster/O ,/O and/O in/O a/O week/O we/O will/O laugh/O about/O it/O together/O ./O 
I/O know/O the/O man/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O knew/O the/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O is/O a/O stranger/O to/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON remembered/O the/O direwolf/O dead/O in/O the/O snow/O ,/O the/O broken/O antler/O lodged/O deep/O in/O her/O throat/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O make/O him/O see/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pride/O is/O everything/O to/O a/O king/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON came/O all/O this/O way/O to/O see/O you/O ,/O to/O bring/O you/O these/O great/O honors/O ,/O you/O can/O not/O throw/O them/O back/O in/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Honors/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON laughed/O bitterly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O his/O eyes/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O in/O yours/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O in/O mine/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O blazed/O ,/O angry/O now/O ./O 
Why/O could/O n't/O he/O see/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O He/O offers/O his/O own/O son/O in/O marriage/O to/O our/O daughter/O ,/O what/O else/O would/O you/O call/O that/O ?/O 
Sansa/O might/O someday/O be/O queen/O ./O 
Her/O sons/O could/O rule/O from/O the/O Wall/O to/O the/O mountains/O of/O Dome/LOCATION ./O 
What/O is/O so/O wrong/O with/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O Sansa/O is/O only/O eleven/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Joffrey/O .../O Joffrey/O is/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O finished/O for/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O crown/O prince/O ,/O and/O heir/O to/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ./O 
And/O I/O was/O only/O twelve/O when/O my/O father/O promised/O me/O to/O your/O brother/O Brandon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O brought/O a/O bitter/O twist/O to/O Ned/PERSON 's/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Brandon/PERSON ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
Brandon/PERSON would/O know/O what/O to/O do/O ./O 
He/O always/O did/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O meant/O for/O Brandon/PERSON ./O 
You/O ,/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O everything/O ./O 
He/O was/O born/O to/O be/O a/O King/O 's/O Hand/O and/O a/O father/O to/O queens/O ./O 
I/O never/O asked/O for/O this/O cup/O to/O pass/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O Brandon/PERSON is/O dead/O ,/O and/O the/O cup/O has/O passed/O ,/O and/O you/O must/O drink/O from/O it/O ,/O like/O it/O or/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON turned/O away/O from/O her/O ,/O back/O to/O the/O night/O ./O 
He/O stood/O staring/O out/O in/O the/O darkness/O ,/O watching/O the/O moon/O and/O the/O stars/O perhaps/O ,/O or/O perhaps/O the/O sentries/O on/O the/O wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON softened/O then/O ,/O to/O see/O his/O pain/O ./O 
Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O married/O her/O in/O Brandon/PERSON 's/O place/O ,/O as/O custom/O decreed/O ,/O but/O the/O shadow/O of/O his/O dead/O brother/O still/O lay/O between/O them/O ,/O as/O did/O the/O other/O ,/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O woman/O he/O would/O not/O name/O ,/O the/O woman/O who/O had/O borne/O him/O his/O bastard/O son/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O was/O about/O to/O go/O to/O him/O when/O the/O knock/O came/O at/O the/O door/O ,/O loud/O and/O unexpected/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON turned/O ,/O frowning/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Desmond/O 's/O voice/O came/O through/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON is/O without/O and/O begs/O urgent/O audience/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O told/O him/O I/O had/O left/O orders/O not/O to/O be/O disturbed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
He/O insists/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O well/O ./O 
Send/O him/O in/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O crossed/O to/O the/O wardrobe/O and/O slipped/O on/O a/O heavy/O robe/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON realized/O suddenly/O how/O cold/O it/O had/O become/O ./O 
She/O sat/O up/O in/O bed/O and/O pulled/O the/O furs/O to/O her/O chin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O we/O should/O close/O the/O windows/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O suggested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON nodded/O absently/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON was/O shown/O in/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O maester/O was/O a/O small/O grey/O man/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O grey/O ,/O and/O quick/O ,/O and/O saw/O much/O ./O 
His/O hair/O was/O grey/O ,/O what/O little/O the/O years/O had/O left/O him/O ./O 
His/O robe/O was/O grey/O wool/O ,/O trimmed/O with/O white/O fur/O ,/O the/O Stark/O colors/O ./O 
Its/O great/O floppy/O sleeves/O had/O pockets/O hidden/O inside/O ./O 
Luwin/PERSON was/O always/O tucking/O things/O into/O those/O sleeves/O and/O producing/O other/O things/O from/O them/O :/O books/O ,/O messages/O ,/O strange/O artifacts/O ,/O toys/O for/O the/O children/O ./O 
With/O all/O he/O kept/O hidden/O in/O his/O sleeves/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O surprised/O that/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON could/O lift/O his/O arms/O at/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O maester/O waited/O until/O the/O door/O had/O closed/O behind/O him/O before/O he/O spoke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O pardon/O for/O disturbing/O your/O rest/O ./O 
I/O have/O been/O left/O a/O message/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O looked/O irritated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Been/O left/O ?/O 
By/O whom/O ?/O 
Has/O there/O been/O a/O rider/O ?/O 
I/O was/O not/O told/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O rider/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Only/O a/O carved/O wooden/O box/O ,/O left/O on/O a/O table/O in/O my/O observatory/O while/O I/O napped/O ./O 
My/O servants/O saw/O no/O one/O ,/O but/O it/O must/O have/O been/O brought/O by/O someone/O in/O the/O king/O 's/O party/O ./O 
We/O have/O had/O no/O other/O visitors/O from/O the/O south/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wooden/O box/O ,/O you/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Inside/O was/O a/O fine/O new/O lens/O for/O the/O observatory/O ,/O from/O Myr/ORGANIZATION by/O the/O look/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O lenscrafters/O of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION are/O without/O equal/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ./O 
He/O had/O little/O patience/O for/O this/O sort/O of/O thing/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O lens/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O has/O that/O to/O do/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O asked/O the/O same/O question/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Clearly/O there/O was/O more/O to/O this/O than/O the/O seeming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Under/O the/O heavy/O weight/O of/O her/O furs/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON shivered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O lens/O is/O an/O instrument/O to/O help/O us/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Indeed/O it/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O fingered/O the/O collar/O of/O his/O order/O ;/O a/O heavy/O chain/O worn/O tight/O around/O the/O neck/O beneath/O his/O robe/O ,/O each/O link/O forged/O from/O a/O different/O metal/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O feel/O dread/O stirring/O inside/O her/O once/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O that/O they/O would/O have/O us/O see/O more/O clearly/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O very/O thing/O I/O asked/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON drew/O a/O tightly/O rolled/O paper/O out/O of/O his/O sleeve/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O found/O the/O true/O message/O concealed/O within/O a/O false/O bottom/O when/O I/O dismantled/O the/O box/O the/O lens/O had/O come/O in/O ,/O but/O it/O is/O not/O for/O my/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON held/O out/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O have/O it/O ,/O then/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Luwin/PERSON did/O not/O stir/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pardons/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
The/O message/O is/O not/O for/O you/O either/O ./O 
It/O is/O marked/O for/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON ,/O and/O her/O alone/O ./O 
May/O I/O approach/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O ,/O not/O trusting/O to/O speak/O ./O 
The/O maester/O placed/O the/O paper/O on/O the/O table/O beside/O the/O bed/O ./O 
It/O was/O sealed/O with/O a/O small/O blob/O of/O blue/O wax/O ./O 
Luwin/PERSON bowed/O and/O began/O to/O retreat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stay/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON commanded/O him/O ./O 
His/O voice/O was/O grave/O ./O 
He/O looked/O at/O Catelyn/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
My/O lady/O ,/O you/O 're/O shaking/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O afraid/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O admitted/O ./O 
She/O reached/O out/O and/O took/O the/O letter/O in/O trembling/O hands/O ./O 
The/O furs/O dropped/O away/O from/O her/O nakedness/O ,/O forgotten/O ./O 
In/O the/O blue/O wax/O was/O the/O moon-and-falcon/O seal/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Arryn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O from/O Lysa/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON looked/O at/O her/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O will/O not/O make/O us/O glad/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O grief/O in/O this/O message/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
I/O can/O feel/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ,/O his/O face/O darkening/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Open/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON broke/O the/O seal/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O eyes/O moved/O over/O the/O words/O ./O 
At/O first/O they/O made/O no/O sense/O to/O her/O ./O 
Then/O she/O remembered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON took/O no/O chances/O ./O 
When/O we/O were/O girls/O together/O ,/O we/O had/O a/O private/O language/O ,/O she/O and/O L/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O you/O read/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON admitted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O tell/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O I/O should/O withdraw/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O will/O need/O your/O counsel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O threw/O back/O the/O furs/O and/O climbed/O from/O the/O bed/O ./O 
The/O night/O air/O was/O as/O cold/O as/O the/O grave/O on/O her/O bare/O skin/O as/O she/O padded/O across/O the/O room/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON averted/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
Even/O Ned/PERSON looked/O shocked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lighting/O a/O fire/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
She/O found/O a/O dressing/O gown/O and/O shrugged/O into/O it/O ,/O then/O knelt/O over/O the/O cold/O hearth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maester/O Luwin/O -/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON has/O delivered/O all/O my/O children/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O time/O for/O false/O modesty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O slid/O the/O paper/O in/O among/O the/O kindling/O and/O placed/O the/O heavier/O logs/O on/O top/O of/O it/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON crossed/O the/O room/O ,/O took/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O ,/O and/O pulled/O her/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
He/O held/O her/O there/O ,/O his/O face/O inches/O from/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O tell/O me/O !/O 
What/O was/O this/O message/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON stiffened/O in/O his/O grasp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O warning/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O have/O the/O wits/O to/O hear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O searched/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Go/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON says/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON was/O murdered/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O fingers/O tightened/O on/O her/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O whom/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON released/O his/O hold/O on/O her/O arm/O ./O 
There/O were/O deep/O red/O marks/O on/O her/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
His/O voice/O was/O hoarse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O sister/O is/O sick/O with/O grief/O ./O 
She/O can/O not/O know/O what/O she/O is/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O knows/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON is/O impulsive/O ,/O yes/O ,/O but/O this/O message/O was/O carefully/O planned/O ,/O cleverly/O hidden/O ./O 
She/O knew/O it/O meant/O death/O if/O her/O letter/O fell/O into/O the/O wrong/O hands/O ./O 
To/O risk/O so/O much/O ,/O she/O must/O have/O had/O more/O than/O mere/O suspicion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON looked/O to/O her/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O we/O truly/O have/O no/O choice/O ./O 
You/O must/O be/O Robert/PERSON 's/O Hand/O ./O 
You/O must/O go/O south/O with/O him/O and/O learn/O the/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O saw/O at/O once/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O reached/O a/O very/O different/O conclusion/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O only/O truths/O I/O know/O are/O here/O ./O 
The/O south/O is/O a/O nest/O of/O adders/O I/O would/O do/O better/O to/O avoid/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Luwin/PERSON plucked/O at/O his/O chain/O collar/O where/O it/O had/O chafed/O the/O soft/O skin/O of/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O has/O great/O power/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Power/O to/O find/O the/O truth/O of/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON '/O s/O death/O ,/O to/O bring/O his/O killers/O to/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ./O 
Power/O to/O protect/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON and/O her/O son/O ,/O if/O the/O worst/O be/O true/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O glanced/O helplessly/O around/O the/O bedchamber/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O heart/O went/O out/O to/O him/O ,/O but/O she/O knew/O she/O could/O not/O take/O him/O in/O her/O arms/O just/O then/O ./O 
First/O the/O victory/O must/O be/O won/O ,/O for/O her/O children/O 's/O sake/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O say/O you/O love/O Robert/PERSON like/O a/O brother/O ./O 
Would/O you/O leave/O your/O brother/O surrounded/O by/O Lannisters/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O take/O both/O of/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON muttered/O darkly/O ./O 
He/O turned/O away/O from/O them/O and/O went/O to/O the/O window/O ./O 
She/O did/O not/O speak/O ,/O nor/O did/O the/O maester/O ./O 
They/O waited/O ,/O quiet/O ,/O while/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O a/O silent/O farewell/O to/O the/O home/O he/O loved/O ./O 
When/O he/O turned/O away/O from/O the/O window/O at/O last/O ,/O his/O voice/O was/O tired/O and/O full/O of/O melancholy/O ,/O and/O moisture/O glittered/O faintly/O in/O the/O corners/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O went/O south/O once/O ,/O to/O answer/O the/O summons/O of/O a/O king/O ./O 
He/O never/O came/O home/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O different/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O different/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O dully/O ./O 
He/O seated/O himself/O in/O a/O chair/O by/O the/O hearth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Catelyn/O ,/O you/O shall/O stay/O here/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O words/O were/O like/O an/O icy/O draft/O through/O her/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O suddenly/O afraid/O ./O 
Was/O this/O to/O be/O her/O punishment/O ?/O 
Never/O to/O see/O his/O face/O again/O ,/O nor/O to/O feel/O his/O arms/O around/O her/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O in/O words/O that/O would/O brook/O no/O argument/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O govern/O the/O north/O in/O my/O stead/O ,/O while/O I/O run/O Robert/PERSON 's/O errands/O ./O 
There/O must/O always/O be/O a/O Stark/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Robb/PERSON is/O fourteen/O ./O 
Soon/O enough/O ,/O he/O will/O be/O a/O man/O grown/O ./O 
He/O must/O learn/O to/O rule/O ,/O and/O I/O will/O not/O be/O here/O for/O him/O ./O 
Make/O him/O part/O of/O your/O councils/O ./O 
He/O must/O be/O ready/O when/O his/O time/O comes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O will/O ,/O not/O for/O many/O years/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON murmured/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O I/O trust/O you/O as/O I/O would/O my/O own/O blood/O ./O 
Give/O my/O wife/O your/O voice/O in/O all/O things/O great/O and/O small/O ./O 
Teach/O my/O son/O the/O things/O he/O needs/O to/O know/O ./O 
Winter/O is/O coming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON nodded/O gravely/O ./O 
Then/O silence/O fell/O ,/O until/O Catelyn/PERSON found/O her/O courage/O and/O asked/O the/O question/O whose/O answer/O she/O most/O dreaded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O of/O the/O other/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON stood/O ,/O and/O took/O her/O in/O his/O arms/O ,/O and/O held/O her/O face/O close/O to/O his/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rickon/O is/O very/O young/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O should/O stay/O here/O with/O you/O and/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
The/O others/O I/O would/O take/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O could/O not/O bear/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O trembling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O must/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O must/O wed/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O that/O is/O clear/O now/O ,/O we/O must/O give/O them/O no/O grounds/O to/O suspect/O our/O devotion/O ./O 
And/O it/O is/O past/O time/O that/O Arya/PERSON learned/O the/O ways/O of/O a/O southron/O court/O ./O 
In/O a/O few/O years/O she/O will/O be/O of/O an/O age/O to/O marry/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O would/O shine/O in/O the/O south/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O to/O herself/O ,/O and/O the/O gods/O knew/O that/O Arya/PERSON needed/O refinement/O ./O 
Reluctantly/O ,/O she/O let/O go/O of/O them/O in/O her/O heart/O ./O 
But/O not/O Bran/O ./O 
Never/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O please/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O for/O the/O love/O you/O bear/O me/O ,/O let/O Bran/O remain/O here/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
He/O is/O only/O seven/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O eight/O when/O my/O father/O sent/O me/O to/O foster/O at/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tells/O me/O there/O is/O bad/O feeling/O between/O Robb/PERSON and/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
That/O is/O not/O healthy/O ./O 
Bran/O can/O bridge/O that/O distance/O ./O 
He/O is/O a/O sweet/O boy/O ,/O quick/O to/O laugh/O ,/O easy/O to/O love/O ./O 
Let/O him/O grow/O up/O with/O the/O young/O princes/O ,/O let/O him/O become/O their/O friend/O as/O Robert/PERSON became/O mine/O ./O 
Our/O House/ORGANIZATION will/O be/O the/O safer/O for/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O right/O ;/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O it/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O make/O the/O pain/O any/O easier/O to/O bear/O ./O 
She/O would/O lose/O all/O four/O of/O them/O ,/O then/O :/O Ned/PERSON ,/O and/O both/O girls/O ,/O and/O her/O sweet/O ,/O loving/O Bran/O ./O 
Only/O Robb/PERSON and/O little/O Rickon/PERSON would/O be/O left/O to/O her/O ./O 
She/O felt/O lonely/O already/O ./O 
Winterfell/PERSON was/O such/O a/O vast/O place/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O him/O off/O the/O walls/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O bravely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O how/O Bran/O loves/O to/O climb/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON kissed/O the/O tears/O from/O her/O eyes/O before/O they/O could/O fall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O hard/O ,/O I/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O of/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON tensed/O at/O the/O mention/O of/O the/O name/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON felt/O the/O anger/O in/O her/O ,/O and/O pulled/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Many/O men/O fathered/O bastards/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O grown/O up/O with/O that/O knowledge/O ./O 
It/O came/O as/O no/O surprise/O to/O her/O ,/O in/O the/O first/O year/O of/O her/O marriage/O ,/O to/O learn/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O fathered/O a/O child/O on/O some/O girl/O chance/O met/O on/O campaign/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O man/O 's/O needs/O ,/O after/O all/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O spent/O that/O year/O apart/O ,/O Ned/PERSON off/O at/O war/O in/O the/O south/O while/O she/O remained/O safe/O in/O her/O father/O 's/O castle/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
Her/O thoughts/O were/O more/O of/O Robb/PERSON ,/O the/O infant/O at/O her/O breast/O ,/O than/O of/O the/O husband/O she/O scarcely/O knew/O ./O 
He/O was/O welcome/O to/O whatever/O solace/O he/O might/O find/O between/O battles/O ./O 
And/O if/O his/O seed/O quickened/O ,/O she/O expected/O he/O would/O see/O to/O the/O child/O 's/O needs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O did/O more/O than/O that/O ./O 
The/O Starks/PERSON were/O not/O like/O other/O men/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON brought/O his/O bastard/O home/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O called/O him/O \/O ``/O son/O \/O ''/O for/O all/O the/O north/O to/O see/O ./O 
When/O the/O wars/O were/O over/O at/O last/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON rode/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O Jon/PERSON and/O his/O wet/O nurse/O had/O already/O taken/O up/O residence/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O cut/O deep/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON would/O not/O speak/O of/O the/O mother/O ,/O not/O so/O much/O as/O a/O word/O ,/O but/O a/O castle/O has/O no/O secrets/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON heard/O her/O maids/O repeating/O tales/O they/O heard/O from/O the/O lips/O of/O her/O husband/O 's/O soldiers/O ./O 
They/O whispered/O of/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O the/O Sword/O of/O the/O Morning/O ,/O deadliest/O of/O the/O seven/O knights/O of/O Aerys/PERSON 's/O Kingsguard/O ,/O and/O of/O how/O their/O young/O lord/O had/O slain/O him/O in/O single/O combat/O ./O 
And/O ''/O ,/O ``/O they/O told/O how/O afterward/O Ned/PERSON had/O carried/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON 's/O sword/O back/O to/O the/O beautiful/O young/O sister/O who/O awaited/O him/O in/O a/O castle/O called/O Starfall/O on/O the/O shores/O of/O the/O Summer/O Sea/O ./O 
The/O Lady/O Ashara/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O tall/O and/O fair/O ,/O with/O haunting/O violet/O eyes/O ./O 
It/O had/O taken/O her/O a/O fortnight/O to/O marshal/O her/O courage/O ,/O but/O finally/O ,/O in/O bed/O one/O night/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O asked/O her/O husband/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ,/O asked/O him/O to/O his/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O only/O time/O in/O all/O their/O years/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O ever/O frightened/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Never/O ask/O me/O about/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O cold/O as/O ice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O my/O blood/O ,/O and/O that/O is/O all/O you/O need/O to/O know/O ./O 
And/O now/O I/O will/O learn/O where/O you/O heard/O that/O name/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O pledged/O to/O obey/O ;/O she/O told/O him/O ;/O and/O from/O that/O day/O on/O ,/O the/O whispering/O had/O stopped/O ,/O and/O Ashara/PERSON Dayne/PERSON 's/O name/O was/O never/O heard/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Whoever/O Jon/PERSON 's/O mother/O had/O been/O ,/O Ned/PERSON must/O have/O loved/O her/O fiercely/O ,/O for/O nothing/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O would/O persuade/O him/O to/O send/O the/O boy/O away/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O one/O thing/O she/O could/O never/O forgive/O him/O ./O 
She/O had/O come/O to/O love/O her/O husband/O with/O all/O her/O heart/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O never/O found/O it/O in/O her/O to/O love/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
She/O might/O have/O overlooked/O a/O dozen/O bastards/O for/O Ned/PERSON 's/O sake/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O were/O out/O of/O sight/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON was/O never/O out/O of/O sight/O ,/O and/O as/O he/O grew/O ,/O he/O looked/O more/O like/O Ned/PERSON than/O any/O of/O the/O trueborn/O sons/O she/O bore/O him/O ./O 
Somehow/O that/O made/O it/O worse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON must/O go/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O and/O Robb/PERSON are/O close/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O hoped/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O can/O not/O stay/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O cutting/O him/O off/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O your/O son/O ,/O not/O mine/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O have/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O hard/O ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O but/O no/O less/O the/O truth/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON would/O do/O the/O boy/O no/O kindness/O by/O leaving/O him/O here/O at/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O look/O Ned/PERSON gave/O her/O was/O anguished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O know/O I/O can/O not/O take/O him/O south/O ./O 
There/O will/O be/O no/O place/O for/O him/O at/O court/O ./O 
A/O boy/O with/O a/O bastard/O 's/O name/O .../O you/O know/O what/O they/O will/O say/O of/O him/O ./O 
He/O will/O be/O shunned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O armored/O her/O heart/O against/O the/O mute/O appeal/O in/O her/O husband/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O say/O your/O friend/O Robert/PERSON has/O fathered/O a/O dozen/O bastards/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O none/O of/O them/O has/O ever/O been/O seen/O at/O court/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON blazed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lannister/O woman/O has/O seen/O to/O that/O ./O 
How/O can/O you/O be/O so/O damnably/O cruel/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON ?/O 
He/O is/O only/O a/O boy/O ./O 
He/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O fury/O was/O on/O him/O ./O 
He/O might/O have/O said/O more/O ,/O and/O worse/O ,/O but/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON cut/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Another/O solution/O presents/O itself/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O voice/O quiet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O Benjen/PERSON came/O to/O me/O about/O Jon/PERSON a/O few/O days/O ago/O ./O 
It/O seems/O the/O boy/O aspires/O to/O take/O the/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O looked/O shocked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O asked/O to/O join/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O nothing/O ./O 
Let/O Ned/PERSON work/O it/O out/O in/O his/O own/O mind/O ;/O her/O voice/O would/O not/O be/O welcome/O now/O ./O 
Yet/O gladly/O would/O she/O have/O kissed/O the/O maester/O just/O then/O ./O 
His/O was/O the/O perfect/O solution/O ./O 
Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O a/O Sworn/O Brother/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON would/O be/O a/O son/O to/O him/O ,/O the/O child/O he/O would/O never/O have/O ./O 
And/O in/O time/O the/O boy/O would/O take/O the/O oath/O as/O well/O ./O 
He/O would/O father/O no/O sons/O who/O might/O someday/O contest/O with/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O own/O grandchildren/O for/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O great/O honor/O in/O service/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O even/O a/O bastard/O may/O rise/O high/O in/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON reflected/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O his/O voice/O was/O troubled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON is/O so/O young/O ./O 
If/O he/O asked/O this/O when/O he/O was/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O that/O would/O be/O one/O thing/O ,/O but/O a/O boy/O of/O fourteen/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O hard/O sacrifice/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O these/O are/O hard/O times/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
His/O road/O is/O no/O crueler/O than/O yours/O or/O your/O lady/O 's/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O of/O the/O three/O children/O she/O must/O lose/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O easy/O keeping/O silent/O then/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON turned/O away/O from/O them/O to/O gaze/O out/O the/O window/O ,/O his/O long/O face/O silent/O and/O thoughtful/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O sighed/O ,/O and/O turned/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Very/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O suppose/O it/O is/O for/O the/O best/O ./O 
I/O will/O speak/O to/O Ben/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O shall/O we/O tell/O Jon/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O maester/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O must/O ./O 
Preparations/O must/O be/O made/O ./O 
It/O will/O be/O a/O fortnight/O before/O we/O are/O ready/O to/O depart/O ./O 
I/O would/O sooner/O let/O Jon/PERSON enjoy/O these/O last/O few/O days/O ./O 
Summer/O will/O end/O soon/O enough/O ,/O and/O childhood/O as/O well/O ./O 
When/O the/O time/O comes/O ,/O I/O will/O tell/O him/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
