-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O walls/O of/O the/O throne/O room/O had/O been/O stripped/O bare/O ,/O the/O hunting/O tapestries/O that/O King/O Robert/PERSON loved/O taken/O down/O and/O stacked/O in/O the/O corner/O in/O an/O untidy/O heap/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Mandon/PERSON Moore/PERSON went/O to/O take/O his/O place/O under/O the/O throne/O beside/O two/O of/O his/O fellows/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
Sansa/O hovered/O by/O the/O door/O ,/O for/O once/O unguarded/O ./O 
The/O queen/O had/O given/O her/O freedom/O of/O the/O castle/O as/O a/O reward/O for/O being/O good/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O ,/O she/O was/O escorted/O everywhere/O she/O went/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Honor/O guards/O for/O my/O daughter-to-be/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O called/O them/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O not/O make/O Sansa/O feel/O honored/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Freedom/O ,/O of/O the/O castle/O \/O ''/O meant/O that/O she/O could/O go/O wherever/O she/O chose/O within/O the/O Red/O Keep/O so/O long/O as/O she/O promised/O not/O to/O go/O beyond/O the/O walls/O ,/O a/O promise/O Sansa/O had/O been/O more/O than/O willing/O to/O give/O ./O 
She/O could/O n't/O have/O gone/O beyond/O the/O walls/O anyway/O ./O 
The/O gates/O were/O watched/O day/O and/O night/O by/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON 's/O gold/O cloaks/O ,/O and/O Lannister/PERSON house/O guards/O were/O always/O about/O as/O well/O ./O 
Besides/O ,/O even/O if/O she/O could/O leave/O the/O castle/O ,/O where/O would/O she/O go/O ?/O 
It/O was/O enough/O that/O she/O could/O walk/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O pick/O flowers/O in/O Myrcella/LOCATION 's/O garden/O ,/O and/O visit/O the/O sept/O to/O pray/O for/O her/O father/O ./O 
Sometimes/O she/O prayed/O in/O the/O godswood/O as/O well/O ,/O since/O the/O Starks/PERSON kept/O the/O old/O gods/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O This/O was/O the/O first/O court/O session/O of/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O reign/O ,/O so/O Sansa/O looked/O about/O nervously/O ./O 
A/O line/O of/O Lannister/O house/O guards/O stood/O beneath/O the/O western/O windows/O ,/O a/O line/O of/O gold-cloaked/O City/O Watchmen/O beneath/O the/O east/O ./O 
Of/O smallfolk/O and/O commoners/O ,/O she/O saw/O no/O sign/O ,/O but/O under/O the/O gallery/O a/O cluster/O of/O lords/O great/O and/O small/O milled/O restlessly/O ./O 
There/O were/O no/O more/O than/O twenty/O ,/O where/O a/O hundred/O had/O been/O accustomed/O to/O wait/O upon/O King/O Robert/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O slipped/O in/O among/O them/O ,/O murmuring/O greetings/O as/O she/O worked/O her/O way/O toward/O the/O front/O ./O 
She/O recognized/O black-skinned/O Jalabhar/PERSON Xho/PERSON ,/O gloomy/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON Santagar/PERSON ,/O the/O Redwyne/O twins/O Horror/O and/O Slobber/O .../O only/O none/O of/O them/O seemed/O to/O recognize/O her/O ./O 
Or/O if/O they/O did/O ,/O they/O shied/O away/O as/O if/O she/O had/O the/O grey/O plague/O ./O 
Sickly/O Lord/O Gyles/PERSON covered/O his/O face/O at/O her/O approach/O and/O feigned/O a/O fit/O of/O coughing/O ,/O and/O when/O funny/O drunken/O Ser/PERSON Dontos/PERSON started/O to/O hail/O her/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON whispered/O in/O his/O ear/O and/O he/O turned/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O so/O many/O others/O were/O missing/O ./O 
Where/O had/O the/O rest/O of/O them/O gone/O ?/O 
Sansa/O wondered/O ./O 
Vainly/O ,/O she/O searched/O for/O friendly/O faces/O ./O 
Not/O one/O of/O them/O would/O meet/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
It/O was/O as/O if/O she/O had/O become/O a/O ghost/O ,/O dead/O before/O her/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O was/O seated/O alone/O at/O the/O council/O table/O ,/O seemingly/O asleep/O ,/O his/O hands/O clasped/O together/O atop/O his/O beard/O ./O 
She/O saw/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON hurry/O into/O the/O hall/O ,/O his/O feet/O making/O no/O sound/O ./O 
A/O moment/O later/O Lord/PERSON Baelish/PERSON entered/O through/O the/O tall/O doors/O in/O the/O rear/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
He/O chatted/O amiably/O with/O Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Dontos/PERSON as/O he/O made/O his/O way/O to/O the/O front/O ./O 
Butterflies/O fluttered/O nervously/O in/O Sansa/O '/O s/O stomach/O ./O 
I/O should/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
I/O have/O nothing/O to/O be/O afraid/O of/O ,/O it/O will/O all/O come/O out/O well/O ,/O Jo/PERSON ff/O loves/O me/O and/O the/O queen/O does/O too/O ,/O she/O said/O so/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O herald/O 's/O voice/O rang/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O hail/O His/O Grace/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON of/O the/O Houses/O Baratheon/O and/O Lannister/PERSON ,/O the/O First/O of/O his/O Name/O ,/O King/O of/O the/O Andals/O ,/O the/O Rhoynar/O ,/O and/O the/O First/O Men/O ,/O and/O Lord/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
All/O hail/O his/O lady/O mother/O ,/O Cersei/PERSON of/O House/ORGANIZATION Lannister/O ,/O Queen/O Regent/O ,/O Light/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O and/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O ,/O resplendent/O in/O white/O plate/O ,/O led/O them/O in/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Arys/PERSON Oakheart/PERSON escorted/O the/O queen/O ,/O while/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON Blount/PERSON walked/O beside/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O so/O six/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O were/O now/O in/O the/O hall/O ,/O all/O the/O White/LOCATION Swords/LOCATION save/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON alone/O ./O 
Her/O prince-no/O ,/O her/O king/O now/O !/O 
-/O took/O the/O steps/O of/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O two/O at/O a/O time/O ,/O while/O his/O mother/O was/O seated/O with/O the/O council/O ./O 
Jo/PERSON ff/O wore/O plush/O black/O velvets/O slashed/O with/O crimson/O ,/O a/O shimmering/O cloth-of-gold/O cape/O with/O a/O high/O collar/O ,/O and/O on/O his/O head/O a/O golden/O crown/O crusted/O with/O rubies/O and/O black/O diamonds/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O Joffrey/PERSON turned/O to/O look/O out/O over/O the/O hall/O ,/O his/O eye/O caught/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O ./O 
He/O smiled/O ,/O seated/O himself/O ,/O and/O spoke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O a/O king/O 's/O duty/O to/O punish/O the/O disloyal/O and/O reward/O those/O who/O are/O true/O ./O 
Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON ,/O I/O command/O you/O to/O read/O my/O decrees/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Pycelle/PERSON pushed/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
He/O was/O clad/O in/O a/O magnificent/O robe/O of/O thick/O red/O velvet/O ,/O with/O an/O ermine/O collar/O and/O shiny/O gold/O fastenings/O ./O 
From/O a/O drooping/O sleeve/O ,/O heavy/O with/O gilded/O scrollwork/O ,/O he/O drew/O a/O parchment/O ,/O unrolled/O it/O ,/O and/O began/O to/O read/O a/O long/O list/O of/O names/O ,/O commanding/O each/O in/O the/O name/O of/O king/O and/O council/O to/O present/O themselves/O and/O swear/O their/O fealty/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
Failing/O that/O ,/O they/O would/O be/O adjudged/O traitors/O ,/O their/O lands/O and/O titles/O forfeit/O to/O the/O throne/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O names/O he/O read/O made/O Sansa/O hold/O her/O breath/O ./O 
Lord/O Stannis/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ,/O his/O lady/O wife/O ,/O his/O daughter/O ./O 
Lord/O Renly/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ./O 
Both/O Lord/O Royces/O and/O their/O sons/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON ./O 
Lord/ORGANIZATION Mace/ORGANIZATION Tyre/ORGANIZATION 11/O ,/O his/O brothers/O ,/O uncles/O ,/O sons/O ./O 
The/O red/O priest/O ,/O Thoros/PERSON of/O Myr/O ./O 
Lord/O Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON ./O 
Lady/O Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON and/O her/O son/O ,/O the/O little/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON ,/O his/O brother/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON ,/O his/O son/O Ser/PERSON Edmure/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Bryce/PERSON Caron/PERSON of/O the/O Marches/O ./O 
Lord/O Tytos/PERSON Blackwood/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON and/O his/O heir/O Ser/O Stevron/O ./O 
Lord/O Karyl/PERSON Vance/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Jonos/PERSON Bracken/PERSON ./O 
Lady/O Sheila/PERSON Whent/PERSON ./O 
Doran/PERSON Martell/PERSON ,/O Prince/PERSON of/PERSON Dome/PERSON ,/O and/O all/O his/O sons/O ./O 
So/O many/O ,/O she/O thought/O as/O Pycelle/O read/O on/O and/O on/O ,/O it/O will/O take/O a/O whole/O flock/O of/O ravens/O to/O send/O out/O these/O commands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O at/O the/O end/O ,/O near/O last/O ,/O came/O the/O names/O Sansa/O had/O been/O dreading/O ./O 
Lady/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O Rickon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O Arya/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
Sansa/O stifled/O a/O gasp/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON ./O 
They/O wanted/O Arya/PERSON to/O present/O herself/O and/O swear/O an/O oath/O .../O it/O must/O mean/O her/O sister/O had/O fled/O on/O the/O galley/O ,/O she/O must/O be/O safe/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION by/O now/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O rolled/O up/O the/O list/O ,/O tucked/O it/O up/O his/O left/O sleeve/O ,/O and/O pulled/O another/O parchment/O from/O his/O right/O ./O 
He/O cleared/O his/O throat/O and/O resumed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O the/O place/O of/O the/O traitor/O Eddard/O Stark/O ,/O it/O is/O the/O wish/O of/O His/O Grace/O that/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION and/O Warden/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O take/O up/O the/O office/O of/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O to/O speak/O with/O his/O voice/O ,/O lead/O his/O armies/O against/O his/O enemies/O ,/O and/O carry/O out/O his/O royal/O will/O ./O 
So/O the/O king/O has/O decreed/O ./O 
The/O small/O council/O consents/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O place/O of/O the/O traitor/O Stannis/O Baratheon/O ,/O it/O is/O the/O wish/O of/O His/O Grace/O that/O his/O lady/O mother/O ,/O the/O Queen/O Regent/PERSON Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O ever/O been/O his/O staunchest/O support/O ,/O be/O seated/O upon/O his/O small/O council/O ,/O that/O she/O may/O help/O him/O rule/O wisely/O and/O with/O justice/O ./O 
So/O the/O king/O has/O decreed/O ./O 
The/O small/O council/O consents/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O heard/O a/O soft/O murmuring/O from/O the/O lords/O around/O her/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O quickly/O stilled/O ./O 
Pycelle/PERSON continued/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O also/O the/O wish/O of/O His/O Grace/O that/O his/O loyal/O servant/O ,/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON ,/O Commander/O of/O the/O City/ORGANIZATION Watch/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O be/O at/O once/O raised/O to/O the/O rank/O of/O lord/O and/O granted/O the/O ancient/O seat/O of/O Harrenhal/LOCATION with/O all/O its/O attendant/O lands/O and/O incomes/O ,/O and/O that/O his/O sons/O and/O grandsons/O shall/O hold/O ''/O ,/O ``/O these/O honors/O after/O him/O until/O the/O end/O of/O time/O ./O 
It/O is/O moreover/O his/O command/O that/O Lord/O Slynt/PERSON be/O seated/O immediately/O upon/O his/O small/O council/O ,/O to/O assist/O in/O the/O governance/O of/O the/O realm/O ./O 
So/O the/O king/O has/O decreed/O ./O 
The/O small/O council/O consents/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O glimpsed/O motion/O from/O the/O corner/O of/O her/O eye/O as/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON made/O his/O entrance/O ./O 
This/O time/O the/O muttering/O was/O louder/O and/O angrier/O ./O 
Proud/O lords/O whose/O houses/O went/O back/O thousands/O of/O years/O made/O way/O reluctantly/O for/O the/O balding/O ,/O frog-faced/O commoner/O as/O he/O marched/O past/O ./O 
Golden/O scales/O had/O been/O sewn/O onto/O the/O black/O velvet/O of/O his/O doublet/O and/O rang/O together/O softly/O with/O each/O step/O ./O 
His/O cloak/O was/O checked/O black/O -/O and-go/O Id/O satin/O ./O 
Two/O ugly/O boys/O who/O must/O have/O been/O his/O sons/O went/O before/O him/O ,/O struggling/O with/O the/O weight/O of/O a/O heavy/O metal/O shield/O as/O tall/O as/O they/O were/O ./O 
For/O his/O sigil/O he/O had/O taken/O a/O bloody/O spear/O ,/O gold/O on/O a/O night-black/O field/O ./O 
The/O sight/O of/O it/O raised/O goose/O prickles/O up/O and/O down/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O Lord/O Slynt/PERSON took/O his/O place/O ,/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O resumed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lastly/O ,/O in/O these/O times/O of/O treason/O and/O turmoil/O ,/O with/O our/O beloved/O Robert/PERSON so/O lately/O dead/O ,/O it/O is/O the/O view/O of/O the/O council/O that/O the/O life/O and/O safety/O of/O King/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON is/O of/O paramount/O importance/O He/O looked/O to/O the/O queen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O Selmy/O ,/O stand/O forth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O had/O been/O standing/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O as/O still/O as/O any/O statue/O ,/O but/O now/O he/O went/O to/O one/O knee/O and/O bowed/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O I/O am/O yours/O to/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rise/O ,/O Ser/O Barristan/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O may/O remove/O your/O helm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Standing/O ,/O the/O old/O knight/O took/O off/O his/O high/O white/O helm/O ,/O though/O he/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O understand/O why/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O served/O the/O realm/O long/O and/O faithfully/O ,/O good/O ser/O ,/O and/O every/O man/O and/O woman/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O owes/O you/O thanks/O ./O 
Yet/O now/O I/O fear/O your/O service/O is/O at/O an/O end/O ./O 
It/O is/O the/O wish/O of/O king/O and/O council/O that/O you/O lay/O down/O your/O heavy/O burden/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O .../O burden/O ?/O 
I/O fear/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O do/O not/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O new-made/O lord/O ,/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON ,/O spoke/O up/O ,/O his/O voice/O heavy/O and/O blunt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Her/O Grace/O is/O trying/O to/O tell/O you/O that/O you/O are/O relieved/O as/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O tall/O ,/O white-haired/O knight/O seemed/O to/O shrink/O as/O he/O stood/O there/O ,/O scarcely/O breathing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Kingsguard/O is/O a/O Sworn/O Brotherhood/O ./O 
Our/O vows/O are/O taken/O for/O life/O ./O 
Only/O death/O may/O relieve/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O his/O sacred/O trust/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Whose/O death/O ,/O Ser/O Barristan/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O queen/O 's/O voice/O was/O soft/O as/O silk/O ,/O but/O her/O words/O carried/O the/O whole/O length/O of/O the/O hall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yours/O ,/O or/O your/O king/O 's/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O let/O my/O father/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O accusingly/O from/O atop/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O too/O old/O to/O protect/O anybody/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O watched/O as/O the/O knight/O peered/O up/O at/O his/O new/O king/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O seen/O him/O look/O his/O years/O before/O ,/O yet/O now/O he/O did/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O chosen/O for/O the/O White/O Swords/O in/O my/O twenty-third/O year/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O I/O had/O ever/O dreamed/O ,/O from/O the/O moment/O I/O first/O took/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
I/O gave/O up/O all/O claim/O to/O my/O ancestral/O keep/O ./O 
The/O girl/O I/O was/O to/O wed/O married/O my/O cousin/O in/O my/O place/O ,/O I/O had/O no/O need/O of/O land/O or/O sons/O ,/O my/O life/O would/O be/O lived/O for/O the/O realm/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON Hightower/PERSON himself/O heard/O my/O vows/O .../O to/O ward/O the/O king/O with/O all/O my/O strength/O .../O to/O give/O my/O blood/O for/O his/O .../O I/O fought/O beside/O the/O White/ORGANIZATION Bull/ORGANIZATION and/O Prince/O Lewyn/PERSON of/O Dome/O .../O beside/O Ser/O Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O the/O Sword/O of/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Morning/O ./O 
Before/O I/O served/O your/O father/O ,/O I/O helped/O shield/O King/O Aerys/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O Jaehaerys/PERSON before/O him/O .../O three/O kings/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O all/O of/O them/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O time/O is/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON requires/O men/O around/O him/O who/O are/O young/O and/O strong/O ./O 
The/O council/O has/O determined/O that/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON will/O take/O your/O place/O as/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O Sworn/O Brothers/O of/O the/O White/O Swords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON said/O ,/O his/O voice/O hard/O with/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O false/O knight/O who/O profaned/O his/O blade/O with/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O king/O he/O had/O sworn/O to/O defend/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Have/O a/O care/O for/O your/O words/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O queen/O warned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O speaking/O of/O our/O beloved/O brother/O ,/O your/O king/O 's/O own/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON spoke/O ,/O gentler/O than/O the/O others/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O not/O unmindful/O of/O your/O service/O ,/O good/O ser/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON has/O generously/O agreed/O to/O grant/O you/O a/O handsome/O tract/O of/O land/O north/O of/O Lannisport/LOCATION ,/O beside/O the/O sea/O ,/O with/O gold/O and/O men/O sufficient/O to/O build/O you/O a/O stout/O keep/O ,/O and/O servants/O to/O see/O to/O your/O every/O need/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Barristan/O looked/O up/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O hall/O to/O die/O in/O ,/O and/O men/O to/O bury/O me/O ./O 
I/O thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lords/O .../O but/O I/O spit/O upon/O your/O pity/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O reached/O up/O and/O undid/O the/O clasps/O that/O held/O his/O cloak/O in/O place/O ,/O and/O the/O heavy/O white/O garment/O slithered/O from/O his/O shoulders/O to/O fall/O in/O a/O heap/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
His/O helmet/O dropped/O with/O a/O clang/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O a/O knight/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O them/O ./O 
He/O opened/O the/O silver/O fastenings/O of/O his/O breastplate/O and/O let/O that/O fall/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O die/O a/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O naked/O knight/O ,/O it/O would/O seem/O ,/O \/O ''/O quipped/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O all/O laughed/O then/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON on/O his/O throne/O ,/O and/O the/O lords/O standing/O attendance/O ,/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON and/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON and/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON and/O even/O the/O other/O men/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O the/O five/O who/O had/O been/O his/O brothers/O until/O a/O moment/O ago/O ./O 
Surely/O that/O must/O have/O hurt/O the/O most/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON thought/O ./O 
Her/O heart/O went/O out/O to/O the/O gallant/O old/O man/O as/O he/O stood/O shamed/O and/O red-faced/O ,/O too/O angry/O to/O speak/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O drew/O his/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O heard/O someone/O gasp/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON moved/O forward/O to/O confront/O him/O ,/O but/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON froze/O them/O in/O place/O with/O a/O look/O that/O dripped/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O no/O fear/O ,/O sers/O ,/O your/O king/O is/O safe/O .../O no/O thanks/O to/O you/O ./O 
Even/O now/O ,/O I/O could/O cut/O through/O the/O five/O of/O you/O as/O easy/O as/O a/O dagger/O cuts/O cheese/O ./O 
If/O you/O would/O serve/O under/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O not/O a/O one/O of/O you/O is/O fit/O to/O wear/O the/O white/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O flung/O his/O sword/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
Melt/O it/O down/O and/O add/O it/O to/O the/O others/O ,/O if/O you/O like/O ./O 
It/O will/O do/O you/O more/O good/O than/O the/O swords/O in/O the/O hands/O of/O these/O five/O ./O 
Perhaps/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON will/O chance/O to/O sit/O on/O it/O when/O he/O takes/O your/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O took/O the/O long/O way/O out/O ,/O his/O steps/O ringing/O loud/O against/O the/O floor/O and/O echoing/O off/O the/O bare/O stone/O walls/O ./O 
Lords/O and/O ladies/O parted/O to/O let/O him/O pass/O ./O 
Not/O until/O the/O pages/O had/O closed/O the/O great/O oak-and/O -/O bronze/O doors/O behind/O him/O did/O Sansa/PERSON hear/O sounds/O again/O :/O soft/O voices/O ,/O uneasy/O stirrings/O ,/O the/O shuffle/O of/O papers/O from/O the/O council/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O called/O me/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O peevishly/O ,/O sounding/O younger/O than/O his/O years/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O talked/O about/O my/O uncle/O Stannis/PERSON too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Idle/O talk/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON the/O eunuch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Without/O meaning/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O could/O be/O making/O plots/O with/O my/O uncles/O ./O 
I/O want/O him/O seized/O and/O questioned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O No/O one/O moved/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON raised/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O said/O ,/O I/O want/O him/O seized/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON rose/O from/O the/O council/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O gold/O cloaks/O will/O see/O to/O it/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Janos/PERSON strode/O from/O the/O hall/O ,/O his/O ugly/O sons/O double-stepping/O to/O keep/O up/O as/O they/O lugged/O the/O great/O metal/O shield/O with/O the/O arms/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Slynt/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Little/O finger/O reminded/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O might/O resume/O ,/O the/O seven/O are/O now/O six/O ./O 
We/O find/O ourselves/O in/O need/O of/O a/O new/O sword/O for/O your/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O them/O ,/O Mother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O king/O and/O council/O have/O determined/O that/O no/O man/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O is/O more/O fit/O to/O guard/O and/O protect/O His/O Grace/O than/O his/O sworn/O shield/O ,/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O do/O you/O like/O that/O ,/O dog/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O 's/O scarred/O face/O was/O hard/O to/O read/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O long/O moment/O to/O consider/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O not/O ?/O 
I/O have/O no/O lands/O nor/O wife/O to/O forsake/O ,/O and/O who/O 'd/O care/O if/O I/O did/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O burned/O side/O of/O his/O mouth/O twisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O I/O warn/O you/O ,/O I/O 'll/O say/O no/O knight/O 's/O vows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Sworn/O Brothers/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O have/O always/O been/O knights/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON said/O firmly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Until/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Hound/PERSON said/O in/O his/O deep/O rasp/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Boros/PERSON fell/O silent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O king/O 's/O herald/O moved/O forward/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON realized/O the/O moment/O was/O almost/O at/O hand/O ./O 
She/O smoothed/O down/O the/O cloth/O of/O her/O skirt/O nervously/O ./O 
She/O was/O dressed/O in/O mourning/O ,/O as/O a/O sign/O of/O respect/O for/O the/O dead/O king/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O taken/O special/O care/O to/O make/O herself/O beautiful/O ./O 
Her/O gown/O was/O the/O ivory/O silk/O that/O the/O queen/O had/O given/O her/O ,/O the/O one/O Arya/PERSON had/O ruined/O ,/O but/O she/O 'd/O had/O them/O dye/O it/O black/O and/O you/O could/O n't/O see/O the/O stain/O at/O all/O ./O 
She/O had/O fretted/O over/O her/O jewelry/O for/O hours/O and/O finally/O decided/O upon/O the/O elegant/O simplicity/O of/O a/O plain/O silver/O chain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O herald/O 's/O voice/O boomed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O any/O man/O in/O this/O hall/O has/O other/O matters/O to/O set/O before/O His/O Grace/O ,/O let/O him/O speak/O now/O or/O go/O forth/O and/O hold/O his/O silence/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O quailed/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ,/O I/O must/O do/O it/O now/O ./O 
Gods/O give/O me/O courage/O ./O 
She/O took/O one/O step/O ,/O then/O another/O ./O 
Lords/O and/O knights/O stepped/O aside/O silently/O to/O let/O her/O pass/O ,/O and/O she/O felt/O the/O weight/O of/O their/O eyes/O on/O her/O ./O 
I/O must/O be/O as/O strong/O as/O my/O lady/O mother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O in/O a/O soft/O ,/O tremulous/O voice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O height/O of/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O gave/O Joffrey/PERSON a/O better/O vantage/O point/O than/O anyone/O else/O in/O the/O hall/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O first/O to/O see/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O forward/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ,/O smiling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O smile/O emboldened/O her/O ,/O made/O her/O feel/O beautiful/O and/O strong/O ./O 
He/O does/O love/O me/O ,/O he/O does/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON lifted/O her/O head/O and/O walked/O toward/O him/O ,/O not/O too/O slow/O and/O not/O too/O fast/O ./O 
She/O must/O not/O let/O them/O see/O how/O nervous/O she/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lady/O Sansa/O ,/O of/O House/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O herald/O cried/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O stopped/O under/O the/O throne/O ,/O at/O the/O spot/O where/O Ser/O Barristan/O 's/O white/O cloak/O lay/O puddled/O on/O the/O floor/O beside/O his/O helm/O and/O breastplate/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O some/O business/O for/O king/O and/O council/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O queen/O asked/O from/O the/O council/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O knelt/O on/O the/O cloak/O ,/O so/O as/O not/O to/O spoil/O her/O gown/O ,/O and/O looked/O up/O at/O her/O prince/O on/O his/O fearsome/O black/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O it/O please/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O I/O ask/O mercy/O for/O my/O father/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O practiced/O the/O words/O a/O hundred/O times/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O queen/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O you/O disappoint/O me/O ./O 
What/O did/O I/O tell/O you/O about/O traitor/O 's/O blood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O has/O committed/O grave/O and/O terrible/O crimes/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O intoned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O poor/O sad/O thing/O ,/O \/O ''/O sighed/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O is/O only/O a/O babe/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O she/O does/O not/O know/O what/O she/O asks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O eyes/O only/O for/O Joffrey/O ./O 
He/O must/O listen/O to/O me/O ,/O he/O must/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
The/O king/O shifted/O on/O his/O seat/O ,/O \/O ``/O Let/O her/O speak/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O commanded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O hear/O what/O she/O says/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/O smiled/O ,/O a/O shy/O secret/O smile/O ,/O just/O for/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O listening/O ./O 
She/O knew/O he/O would/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Treason/O is/O a/O noxious/O weed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON declared/O solemnly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O must/O be/O torn/O up/O ,/O root/O and/O stem/O and/O seed/O ,/O lest/O new/O traitors/O sprout/O from/O every/O roadside/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O deny/O your/O father/O 's/O crime/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O my/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON knew/O better/O than/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O he/O must/O be/O punished/O ./O 
All/O I/O ask/O is/O mercy/O ./O 
I/O know/O my/O lord/O father/O must/O regret/O what/O he/O did/O ./O 
He/O was/O King/O Robert/PERSON 's/O friend/O and/O he/O loved/O him/O ,/O you/O all/O know/O he/O loved/O him/O ./O 
He/O never/O wanted/O to/O be/O Hand/O until/O the/O king/O asked/O him/O ./O 
They/O must/O have/O lied/O to/O him/O ./O 
Lord/O Renly/O or/O Lord/O Stannis/O or/O .../O or/O somebody/O ,/O they/O must/O have/O lied/O ,/O otherwise/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON leaned/O forward/O ,/O hands/O grasping/O the/O arms/O of/O the/O throne/O ./O 
Broken/O sword/O points/O fanned/O out/O between/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O said/O I/O was/O n't/O the/O king/O ./O 
Why/O did/O he/O say/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O leg/O was/O broken/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON replied/O eagerly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O hurt/O ever/O so/O much/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON was/O giving/O him/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O and/O they/O say/O that/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O fills/O your/O head/O with/O clouds/O ./O 
Otherwise/O he/O would/O never/O have/O said/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O A/O child/O 's/O -/O faith/O .../O such/O sweet/O innocence/O .../O and/O yet/O ,/O they/O say/O wisdom/O oft/O comes/O from/O the/O mouths/O of/O babes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Treason/O is/O treason/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pycelle/PERSON replied/O at/O once/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON rocked/O restlessly/O on/O the/O throne/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cersei/O Lannister/O considered/O Sansa/O thoughtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON were/O to/O confess/O his/O crime/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O at/O last/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O would/O know/O he/O had/O repented/O his/O folly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON pushed/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON thought/O ,/O please/O ,/O please/O ,/O be/O the/O king/O I/O know/O you/O are/O ,/O good/O and/O kind/O and/O noble/O ,/O please/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O any/O more/O to/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O .../O that/O as/O you/O love/O me/O ,/O you/O do/O me/O this/O kindness/O ,/O my/O prince/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O King/O Joffrey/PERSON looked/O her/O up/O and/O down/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O sweet/O words/O have/O moved/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O gallantly/O ,/O nodding/O ,/O as/O if/O to/O say/O all/O would/O be/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O do/O as/O you/O ask/O .../O but/O first/O your/O father/O has/O to/O confess/O ./O 
He/O has/O to/O confess/O and/O say/O that/O I/O 'm/O the/O king/O ,/O or/O there/O will/O be/O no/O mercy/O for/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O said/O ,/O heart/O soaring/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O know/O he/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
