-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O you/O should/O have/O sent/O word/O of/O your/O coming/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON Waynwood/PERSON told/O her/O as/O their/O horses/O climbed/O the/O pass/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O would/O have/O sent/O an/O escort/O ./O 
The/O high/O road/O is/O not/O as/O safe/O as/O it/O once/O was/O ,/O for/O a/O party/O as/O small/O as/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O learned/O that/O to/O our/O sorrow/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
Sometimes/O she/O felt/O as/O though/O her/O heart/O had/O turned/O to/O stone/O ;/O six/O brave/O men/O had/O died/O to/O bring/O her/O this/O far/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O not/O even/O find/O it/O in/O her/O to/O weep/O for/O them/O ./O 
Even/O their/O names/O were/O fading/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O clansmen/O harried/O us/O day/O and/O night/O ./O 
We/O lost/O three/O men/O in/O the/O first/O attack/O ,/O and/O two/O more/O in/O the/O second/O ,/O and/O Lannister/PERSON 's/O serving/O man/O died/O of/O a/O fever/O when/O his/O wounds/O festered/O ./O 
When/O we/O heard/O your/O men/O approaching/O ,/O I/O thought/O us/O doomed/O for/O certain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O had/O drawn/O up/O for/O a/O last/O desperate/O fight/O ,/O blades/O in/O hand/O and/O backs/O to/O the/O rock/O ./O 
The/O dwarf/O had/O been/O whetting/O the/O edge/O of/O his/O axe/O and/O making/O some/O mordant/O jest/O when/O Bronn/PERSON spotted/O the/O banner/O the/O riders/O carried/O before/O them/O ,/O the/O moon-and/O -/O falcon/O of/O House/O Arryn/O ,/O sky-blue/O and/O white/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O never/O seen/O a/O more/O welcome/O sight/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O clans/O have/O grown/O bolder/O since/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON died/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O stocky/O youth/O of/O twenty/O years/O ,/O earnest/O and/O homely/O ,/O with/O a/O wide/O nose/O and/O a/O shock/O of/O thick/O brown/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O it/O were/O up/O to/O me/O ,/O I/O would/O take/O a/O hundred/O men/O into/O the/O mountains/O ,/O root/O them/O out/O of/O their/O fastnesses/O ,/O and/O teach/O them/O some/O sharp/O lessons/O ,/O but/O your/O sister/O has/O forbidden/O it/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O even/O permit/O her/O knights/O to/O fight/O in/O the/O Hand/O 's/O tourney/O ./O 
She/O wants/O all/O our/O swords/O kept/O close/O to/O home/O ,/O to/O defend/O the/O Vale/O .../O against/O what/O ,/O no/O one/O is/O certain/O ./O 
Shadows/O ,/O some/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O at/O her/O anxiously/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O suddenly/O remembered/O who/O she/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O I/O have/O not/O spoken/O out/O of/O turn/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
I/O meant/O no/O offense/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Frank/O talk/O does/O not/O offend/O me/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O what/O her/O sister/O feared/O ./O 
Not/O shadows/O ,/O Lannisters/PERSON ,/O she/O thought/O to/O herself/O ,/O glancing/O back/O to/O where/O the/O dwarf/O rode/O beside/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
The/O two/O of/O them/O had/O grown/O thick/O as/O thieves/O since/O Chiggen/PERSON had/O died/O ./O 
The/O little/O man/O was/O more/O cunning/O than/O she/O liked/O ./O 
When/O they/O had/O entered/O the/O mountains/O ,/O he/O had/O been/O her/O captive/O ,/O bound/O and/O helpless/O ./O 
What/O was/O he/O now/O ?/O 
Her/O captive/O still/O ,/O yet/O he/O rode/O along/O with/O a/O dirk/O through/O his/O belt/O and/O an/O axe/O strapped/O to/O his/O saddle/O ,/O wearing/O the/O shadowskin/O cloak/O he/O 'd/O won/O dicing/O with/O the/O singer/O and/O the/O chainmail/O hauberk/O he/O 'd/O taken/O off/O Chiggen/PERSON 's/O corpse/O ./O 
Two/O score/O men/O flanked/O the/O dwarf/O and/O the/O rest/O of/O her/O ragged/O band/O ,/O knights/O and/O men-at-arms/O in/O service/O to/O her/O sister/O Lysa/PERSON and/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O young/O son/O ,/O and/O yet/O Tyrion/PERSON betrayed/O no/O hint/O of/O fear/O ./O 
Could/O I/O be/O wrong/O ?/O 
Catelyn/PERSON wondered/O ,/O not/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
Could/O he/O be/O innocent/O after/O all/O ,/O of/O Bran/O and/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON and/O all/O the/O rest/O ?/O 
And/O if/O he/O was/O ,/O what/O did/O that/O make/O her/O ?/O 
Six/O men/O had/O died/O to/O bring/O him/O here/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Resolute/O ,/O she/O pushed/O her/O doubts/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O we/O reach/O your/O keep/O ,/O I/O would/O take/O it/O kindly/O if/O you/O could/O send/O for/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON at/O once/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON is/O feverish/O from/O his/O wounds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O More/O than/O once/O she/O had/O feared/O the/O gallant/O old/O knight/O would/O not/O survive/O the/O journey/O ./O 
Toward/O the/O end/O he/O could/O scarcely/O sit/O his/O horse/O ,/O and/O Bronn/PERSON had/O urged/O her/O to/O leave/O him/O to/O his/O fate/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O not/O hear/O of/O it/O ./O 
They/O had/O tied/O him/O in/O the/O saddle/O instead/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O commanded/O Marillion/PERSON the/O singer/O to/O watch/O over/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON hesitated/O before/O he/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON has/O commanded/O the/O maester/O to/O remain/O at/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION at/O all/O times/O ,/O to/O care/O for/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O a/O septon/O at/O the/O gate/O who/O tends/O to/O our/O wounded/O ./O 
He/O can/O see/O to/O your/O man/O 's/O hurts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O more/O faith/O in/O a/O maester/O 's/O learning/O than/O a/O septon/O 's/O prayers/O ./O 
She/O was/O about/O to/O say/O as/O much/O when/O she/O saw/O the/O battlements/O ahead/O ,/O long/O parapets/O built/O into/O the/O very/O stone/O of/O the/O mountains/O on/O either/O side/O of/O them/O ./O 
Where/O the/O pass/O shrank/O to/O a/O narrow/O defile/O scarce/O wide/O enough/O for/O four/O men/O to/O ride/O abreast/O ,/O twin/O watchtowers/O clung/O to/O the/O rocky/O slopes/O ,/O joined/O by/O a/O covered/O bridge/O of/O weathered/O grey/O stone/O that/O arched/O above/O the/O road/O ./O 
Silent/O faces/O watched/O from/O arrow/O slits/O in/O tower/O ,/O battlements/O ,/O and/O bridge/O ./O 
When/O they/O had/O climbed/O almost/O to/O the/O top/O ,/O a/O knight/O rode/O out/O to/O meet/O them/O ./O 
His/O horse/O and/O his/O armor/O were/O grey/O ,/O but/O his/O cloak/O was/O the/O rippling/O blue-and-red/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O and/O a/O shiny/O black/O fish/O ,/O wrought/O in/O gold/O and/O obsidian/O ,/O pinned/O its/O folds/O against/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O would/O pass/O the/O Bloody/O Gate/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON Waynwood/PERSON ,/O with/O the/O Lady/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON and/O her/O companions/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O young/O knight/O answered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Knight/O of/O the/O Gate/O lifted/O his/O visor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thought/O the/O lady/O looked/O familiar/O ./O 
You/O are/O far/O from/O home/O ,/O little/O Cat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O ,/O Uncle/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O smiling/O despite/O all/O she/O had/O been/O through/O ./O 
Hearing/O that/O hoarse/O ,/O smoky/O voice/O again/O took/O her/O back/O twenty/O years/O ,/O to/O the/O days/O of/O her/O childhood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O home/O is/O at/O my/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O gruffly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O home/O is/O in/O my/O heart/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O off/O your/O helm/O ./O 
I/O would/O look/O on/O your/O face/O again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O years/O have/O not/O improved/O it/O ,/O I/O fear/O ,/O \/O ''/O Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON said/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O lifted/O off/O the/O helm/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O that/O he/O lied/O ./O 
His/O features/O were/O lined/O and/O weathered/O ,/O and/O time/O had/O stolen/O the/O auburn/O from/O his/O hair/O and/O left/O him/O only/O grey/O ,/O but/O the/O smile/O was/O the/O same/O ,/O and/O the/O bushy/O eyebrows/O fat/O as/O caterpillars/O ,/O and/O the/O laughter/O in/O his/O deep/O blue/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O Lysa/PERSON know/O you/O were/O coming/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O time/O to/O send/O word/O ahead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
The/O others/O were/O coming/O up/O behind/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O we/O ride/O before/O the/O storm/O ,/O Uncle/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O May/O we/O enter/O the/O Vale/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON asked/O ./O 
The/O Waynwoods/O were/O ever/O ones/O for/O ceremony/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O name/O of/O Robert/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O Defender/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O True/O Warden/O of/O the/O East/LOCATION ,/O I/O bid/O you/O enter/O freely/O ,/O and/O charge/O you/O to/O keep/O his/O peace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O so/O she/O rode/O behind/O him/O ,/O beneath/O the/O shadow/O of/O the/O Bloody/O Gate/O where/O a/O dozen/O armies/O had/O dashed/O themselves/O to/O pieces/O in/O the/O Age/O of/O Heroes/O ./O 
On/O the/O far/O side/O of/O the/O stoneworks/O ,/O the/O mountains/O opened/O up/O suddenly/O upon/O a/O vista/O of/O green/O fields/O ,/O blue/O sky/O ,/O and/O snowcapped/O mountains/O that/O took/O her/O breath/O away/O ./O 
The/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION bathed/O in/O the/O morning/O light/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O stretched/O before/O them/O to/O the/O misty/O cast/O ,/O a/O tranquil/O land/O of/O rich/O black/O soil/O ,/O wide/O slow-moving/O rivers/O ,/O and/O hundreds/O of/O small/O lakes/O that/O shone/O like/O mirrors/O in/O the/O sun/O ,/O protected/O on/O all/O sides/O by/O its/O sheltering/O peaks/O ./O 
Wheat/O and/O corn/O and/O barley/O grew/O high/O in/O its/O fields/O ,/O and/O even/O in/O Highgarden/LOCATION the/O pumpkins/O were/O no/O larger/O nor/O the/O fruit/O any/O sweeter/O than/O here/O ./O 
They/O stood/O at/O the/O western/O end/O of/O the/O valley/O ,/O where/O the/O high/O road/O crested/O the/O last/O pass/O and/O began/O its/O winding/O descent/O to/O the/O bottomlands/O two/O miles/O below/O ./O 
The/O Vale/O was/O narrow/O here/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O a/O half/O day/O 's/O ride/O across/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O and/O the/O northern/O mountains/O seemed/O so/O close/O that/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O almost/O reach/O out/O and/O touch/O them/O ./O 
Looming/O over/O them/O all/O was/O the/O jagged/O peak/O called/O the/O Giant/O 's/O Lance/PERSON ,/O a/O mountain/O that/O even/O mountains/O looked/O up/O to/O ,/O its/O head/O lost/O in/O icy/O mists/O three/O and/O a/O half/O miles/O above/O the/O valley/O floor/O ./O 
Over/O its/O massive/O western/O shoulder/O flowed/O the/O ghost/O torrent/O of/O Alyssa/PERSON 's/O Tears/O ./O 
Even/O from/O this/O distance/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O make/O out/O the/O shining/O silver/O thread/O ,/O bright/O against/O the/O dark/O stone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O her/O uncle/O saw/O that/O she/O had/O stopped/O ,/O he/O moved/O his/O horse/O closer/O and/O pointed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O there/O ,/O beside/O Alyssa/PERSON 's/O Tears/O ./O 
All/O you/O can/O see/O from/O here/O is/O a/O flash/O of/O white/O every/O now/O and/O then/O ,/O if/O you/O look/O hard/O and/O the/O sun/O hits/O the/O walls/O just/O right/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Seven/O towers/O ,/O Ned/PERSON had/O told/O her/O ,/O like/O white/O daggers/O thrust/O into/O the/O belly/O of/O the/O sky/O ,/O so/O high/O you/O can/O stand/O on/O the/O parapets/O and/O look/O down/O on/O the/O clouds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O long/O a/O ride/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O can/O be/O at/O the/O mountain/O by/O evenfall/O ,/O \/O ''/O Uncle/PERSON Brynden/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O the/O climb/O will/O take/O another/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON spoke/O up/O from/O behind/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O fear/O I/O can/O go/O no/O farther/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O face/O sagged/O beneath/O his/O ragged/O ,/O newgrown/O whiskers/O ,/O and/O he/O looked/O so/O weary/O Catelyn/PERSON feared/O he/O might/O fall/O off/O his/O horse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nor/O should/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O done/O all/O I/O could/O have/O asked/O of/O you/O ,/O and/O a/O hundred/O times/O more/O ./O 
My/O uncle/O will/O see/O me/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
Lannister/O must/O come/O with/O me/O ,/O but/O there/O is/O no/O reason/O that/O you/O and/O the/O others/O should/O not/O rest/O here/O and/O recover/O your/O strength/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O should/O be/O honored/O to/O have/O them/O to/O guest/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON said/O with/O the/O grave/O courtesy/O of/O the/O young/O ./O 
Beside/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O only/O Bronn/LOCATION ,/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON ,/O and/O Marillion/O the/O singer/O remained/O of/O the/O party/O that/O had/O ridden/O with/O her/O from/O the/O inn/O by/O the/O crossroads/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON said/O ,/O riding/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O beg/O you/O allow/O me/O to/O accompany/O you/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O to/O see/O the/O end/O of/O the/O tale/O as/O I/O saw/O its/O beginnings/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O boy/O sounded/O haggard/O ,/O yet/O strangely/O determined/O ;/O he/O had/O a/O fevered/O shine/O to/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O never/O asked/O the/O singer/O to/O ride/O with/O them/O ;/O that/O choice/O he/O had/O made/O himself/O ,/O and/O how/O he/O had/O come/O to/O survive/O the/O journey/O when/O so/O many/O braver/O men/O lay/O dead/O and/O unburied/O behind/O them/O ,/O she/O could/O never/O say/O ./O 
Yet/O here/O he/O was/O ,/O with/O a/O scruff/O of/O beard/O that/O made/O him/O look/O almost/O a/O man/O ./O 
Perhaps/O she/O owed/O him/O something/O for/O having/O come/O this/O far/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Very/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O come/O as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O liked/O that/O less/O well/O ./O 
Without/O Bronn/PERSON she/O would/O never/O have/O reached/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O she/O knew/O ;/O the/O sellsword/O was/O as/O fierce/O a/O fighter/O as/O she/O had/O ever/O seen/O ,/O and/O his/O sword/O had/O helped/O cut/O them/O through/O to/O safety/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O for/O all/O that/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON misliked/O the/O man/O ./O 
Courage/O he/O had/O ,/O and/O strength/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O kindness/O in/O him/O ,/O and/O little/O loyalty/O ./O 
And/O she/O had/O seen/O him/O riding/O beside/O Lannister/LOCATION far/O too/O often/O ,/O talking/O in/O low/O voices/O and/O laughing/O at/O some/O private/O joke/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O preferred/O to/O separate/O him/O from/O the/O dwarf/O here/O and/O now/O ,/O but/O having/O agreed/O that/O Marillion/PERSON might/O continue/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O no/O gracious/O way/O to/O deny/O that/O same/O right/O to/O Bronn/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O although/O she/O noted/O that/O he/O had/O not/O actually/O asked/O her/O permission/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Willis/PERSON Wode/PERSON remained/O with/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O a/O soft-spoken/O septon/O fussing/O over/O their/O wounds/O ./O 
Their/O horses/O were/O left/O behind/O as/O well/O ,/O poor/O ragged/O things/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Donnel/PERSON promised/O to/O send/O birds/O ''/O ,/O ``/O ahead/O to/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O the/O Gates/O of/O the/O Moon/O with/O the/O word/O of/O their/O coming/O ./O 
Fresh/O mounts/O were/O brought/O forth/O from/O the/O stables/O ,/O surefooted/O mountain/O stock/O with/O shaggy/O coats/O ,/O and/O within/O the/O hour/O they/O set/O forth/O once/O again/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON rode/O beside/O her/O uncle/O as/O they/O began/O the/O descent/O to/O the/O valley/O floor/O ./O 
Behind/O came/O Bronn/LOCATION ,/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O Marillion/O ,/O and/O six/O of/O Brynden/PERSON 's/O men/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Not/O until/O they/O were/O a/O third/O of/O the/O way/O down/O the/O mountain/O path/O ,/O well/O out/O of/O earshot/O of/O the/O others/O ,/O did/O Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON turn/O to/O her/O and/O say/O ,/O \/O ``/O So/O ,/O child/O ./O 
Tell/O me/O about/O this/O storm/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O been/O a/O child/O in/O many/O years/O ,/O Uncle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O but/O she/O told/O him/O nonetheless/O ./O 
It/O took/O longer/O than/O she/O would/O have/O believed/O to/O tell/O it/O all/O ,/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O letter/O and/O Bran/O 's/O fall/O ,/O the/O assassin/O 's/O dagger/O and/O Littlefinger/PERSON and/O her/O chance/O meeting/O with/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON in/O the/O crossroadsinn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O listened/O silently/O ,/O heavy/O brows/O shadowing/O his/O eyes/O as/O his/O frown/O grew/O deeper/O ./O 
Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON had/O always/O known/O how/O to/O listen/O .../O to/O anyone/O but/O her/O father/O ./O 
He/O was/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON 's/O brother/O ,/O younger/O by/O five/O years/O ,/O but/O the/O two/O of/O them/O had/O been/O at/O war/O as/O far/O back/O as/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O remember/O ./O 
During/O one/O of/O their/O louder/O quarrels/O ,/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O eight/O ,/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON had/O called/O Brynden/PERSON \/O ``/O the/O black/O goat/O of/O the/O Tully/O flock/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Laughing/O ,/O Brynden/PERSON had/O pointed/O out/O that/O the/O sigil/O of/O their/O house/O was/O a/O leaping/O trout/O ,/O so/O he/O ought/O to/O be/O a/O black/O fish/O rather/O than/O a/O black/O goat/O ,/O and/O from/O that/O day/O forward/O he/O had/O taken/O it/O as/O his/O personal/O emblem/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O war/O had/O not/O ended/O until/O the/O day/O she/O and/O Lysa/PERSON had/O been/O wed./O ./O 
It/O was/O at/O their/O wedding/O feast/O that/O Brynden/PERSON told/O his/O brother/O he/O was/O leaving/O Riverrun/PERSON to/O serve/O Lysa/PERSON and/O her/O new/O husband/O ,/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
Lord/O Hoster/PERSON had/O not/O spoken/O his/O brother/O 's/O name/O since/O ,/O from/O what/O Edmure/PERSON told/O her/O in/O his/O infrequent/O letters/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Nonetheless/O ,/O during/O all/O those/O years/O of/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O girlhood/O ,/O it/O had/O been/O Brynden/PERSON the/O Blackfish/O to/O whom/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON 's/O children/O had/O run/O with/O their/O tears/O and/O their/O tales/O ,/O when/O Father/O was/O too/O busy/O and/O Mother/O too/O ill/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON ,/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O Edmure/O .../O and/O yes/O ,/O even/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON ,/O their/O father/O 's/O ward/O .../O he/O had/O listened/O to/O them/O all/O patiently/O ,/O as/O he/O listened/O now/O ,/O laughing/O at/O their/O triumphs/O and/O sympathizing/O with/O their/O childish/O misfortunes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O was/O done/O ,/O her/O uncle/O remained/O silent/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O as/O his/O horse/O negotiated/O the/O steep/O ,/O rocky/O trail/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O father/O must/O be/O told/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O Lannisters/O should/O march/O ,/O Winterfell/LOCATION is/O remote/O and/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION walled/O up/O behind/O its/O mountains/O ,/O but/O Riverrun/LOCATION lies/O right/O in/O their/O path/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O had/O the/O same/O fear/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O ask/O Maester/O Colemon/O to/O send/O a/O bird/O when/O we/O reach/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O other/O messages/O to/O send/O as/O well/O ;/O the/O commands/O that/O Ned/PERSON had/O given/O her/O for/O his/O bannermen/O ,/O to/O ready/O the/O defenses/O of/O the/O north/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O the/O mood/O in/O the/O Vale/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Angry/O ,/O \/O ''/O Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON was/O much/O loved/O ,/O and/O the/O insult/O was/O keenly/O felt/O when/O the/O king/O named/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON to/O an/O office/O the/O Arryns/O had/O held/O for/O near/O three/O hundred/O years/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON has/O commanded/O us/O to/O call/O her/O son/O the/O True/O Warden/O of/O the/O East/LOCATION ,/O but/O no/O one/O is/O fooled/O ./O 
Nor/O is/O your/O sister/O alone/O in/O wondering/O at/O the/O manner/O of/O the/O Hand/O 's/O death/O ./O 
None/O dare/O say/O Jon/PERSON was/O murdered/O ,/O not/O openly/O ,/O but/O suspicion/O casts/O a/O long/O shadow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O gave/O Catelyn/PERSON a/O look/O ,/O his/O mouth/O tight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O there/O is/O the/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O boy/O ?/O 
What/O of/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O ducked/O her/O head/O as/O they/O passed/O under/O a/O low/O overhang/O of/O rock/O ,/O and/O around/O a/O sharp/O turn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O 's/O voice/O was/O troubled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Six/O years/O old/O ,/O sickly/O ,/O and/O prone/O to/O weep/O if/O you/O take/O his/O dolls/O away/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O trueborn/O heir/O ,/O by/O all/O the/O gods/O ,/O yet/O there/O are/O some/O who/O say/O he/O is/O too/O weak/O to/O sit/O his/O father/O 's/O seat/O ,/O Nestor/PERSON Royce/PERSON has/O been/O high/O steward/O these/O past/O fourteen/O years/O ,/O while/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON served/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O and/O many/O whisper/O that/O he/O should/O rule/O until/O the/O boy/O comes/O of/O age/O ./O 
Others/O believe/O that/O Lysa/PERSON must/O marry/O again/O ,/O and/O soon/O ./O 
Already/O the/O suitors/O gather/O like/O crows/O on/O a/O battlefield/O ./O 
The/O Eyrie/O is/O full/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O might/O have/O expected/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O there/O ;/O Lysa/PERSON was/O still/O young/O ,/O and/O the/O kingdom/O of/O Mountain/LOCATION and/O Vale/ORGANIZATION made/O a/O handsome/O wedding/O gift/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O Lysa/PERSON take/O another/O husband/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O says/O yes/O ,/O provided/O she/O finds/O a/O man/O who/O suits/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O she/O has/O already/O rejected/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON and/O a/O dozen/O other/O suitable/O men/O ./O 
She/O swears/O that/O this/O time/O she/O will/O choose/O her/O lord/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O of/O all/O people/O can/O scarce/O fault/O her/O for/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Brynden/O snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nor/O do/O I/O ,/O but/O .../O it/O seems/O to/O me/O Lysa/PERSON is/O only/O playing/O at/O courtship/O ./O 
She/O enjoys/O the/O sport/O ,/O but/O I/O believe/O your/O sister/O intends/O to/O rule/O herself/O until/O her/O boy/O is/O old/O enough/O to/O be/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O in/O truth/O as/O well/O as/O name/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O woman/O can/O rule/O as/O wisely/O as/O a/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O tight/O woman/O can/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O uncle/O said/O with/O a/O sideways/O glance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Make/O no/O mistake/O ,/O Cat/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON is/O not/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O hesitated/O a/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O I/O fear/O you/O may/O not/O find/O your/O sister/O as/O helpful/O as/O you/O would/O like/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O was/O puzzled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O mean/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lysa/PERSON who/O came/O back/O from/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O is/O not/O the/O same/O girl/O who/O went/O south/O when/O her/O husband/O was/O named/O Hand/O ./O 
Those/O years/O were/O hard/O for/O her/O ./O 
You/O must/O know/O ./O 
Lord/O Arryn/PERSON was/O a/O dutiful/O husband/O ,/O but/O their/O marriage/O was/O made/O from/O politics/O ,/O not/O passion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O was/O my/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O began/O the/O same/O ,/O but/O your/O ending/O has/O been/O happier/O than/O your/O sister/O 's/O ./O 
Two/O babes/O stillborn/O ,/O twice/O as/O many/O miscarriages/O ,/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O death/O .../O Catelyn/O ,/O the/O gods/O gave/O Lysa/PERSON only/O the/O one/O child/O ,/O and/O he/O is/O all/O your/O sister/O lives/O for/O now/O ,/O poor/O boy/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O she/O fled/O rather/O than/O see/O him/O handed/O over/O to/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
Your/O sister/O is/O afraid/O ,/O child/O ,/O and/O the/O Lannisters/O are/O what/O she/O fears/O most/O ./O 
She/O ran/O to/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O stealing/O away/O from/O the/O Red/O Keep/O like/O a/O thief/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O and/O all/O to/O snatch/O her/O son/O out/O of/O the/O lion/O 's/O mouth/O .../O and/O now/O you/O have/O brought/O the/O lion/O to/O her/O door/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O chains/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
A/O crevasse/O yawned/O on/O her/O right/O ,/O falling/O away/O into/O darkness/O ./O 
She/O reined/O up/O her/O horse/O and/O picked/O her/O way/O along/O step/O by/O careful/O step/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O uncle/O glanced/O back/O ,/O to/O where/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O making/O his/O slow/O descent/O behind/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O an/O axe/O on/O his/O saddle/O ,/O a/O dirk/O at/O his/O belt/O ,/O and/O a/O sellsword/O that/O trails/O after/O him/O like/O a/O hungry/O shadow/O ./O 
Where/O are/O the/O chains/O ,/O sweet/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O shifted/O uneasily/O in/O her/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O is/O here/O ,/O and/O not/O by/O choice/O ./O 
Chains/O or/O no/O ,/O he/O is/O my/O prisoner/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON will/O want/O him/O to/O answer/O for/O his/O crimes/O no/O less/O than/O I/O ./O 
It/O was/O her/O own/O lord/O husband/O the/O Lannisters/O murdered/O ,/O and/O her/O own/O letter/O that/O first/O warned/O us/O against/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Brynden/O Blackfish/O gave/O her/O a/O weary/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O you/O are/O right/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sighed/O ,/O in/O tones/O that/O said/O she/O was/O wrong/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sun/O was/O well/O to/O the/O west/O by/O the/O time/O the/O slope/O began/O to/O flatten/O beneath/O the/O hooves/O of/O their/O horses/O ./O 
The/O road/O widened/O and/O grew/O straight/O ,/O and/O for/O the/O first/O time/O Catelyn/PERSON noticed/O wildflowers/O and/O grasses/O growing/O ./O 
Once/O they/O reached/O the/O valley/O floor/O ,/O the/O going/O was/O faster/O and/O they/O made/O good/O time/O ,/O cantering/O through/O verdant/O greenwoods/O and/O sleepy/O little/O hamlets/O ,/O past/O orchards/O and/O golden/O wheat/O fields/O ,/O splashing/O across/O a/O dozen/O sunlit/O streams/O ./O 
Her/O uncle/O sent/O a/O standard-bearer/O ahead/O of/O them/O ,/O a/O double/O banner/O flying/O from/O his/O staff/O ;/O the/O moon-and/O -/O falcon/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Arryn/O on/O high/O ,/O and/O below/O it/O his/O own/O black/O fish/O ./O 
Farm/O wagons/O and/O merchants/O '/O carts/O and/O riders/O from/O lesser/O houses/O moved/O aside/O to/O let/O them/O pass/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O so/O ,/O it/O was/O full/O dark/O before/O they/O reached/O the/O stout/O castle/O that/O stood/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O Giant/O 's/O Lance/PERSON ./O 
Torches/O flickered/O atop/O its/O ramparts/O ,/O and/O the/O horned/O moon/O danced/O upon/O the/O dark/O waters/O of/O its/O moat/O ./O 
The/O drawbridge/O was/O up/O and/O the/O portcullis/O down/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O lights/O burning/O in/O the/O gatehouse/O and/O spilling/O from/O the/O windows/O of/O the/O square/O towers/O beyond/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Gates/O of/O the/O Moon/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O uncle/O said/O as/O the/O party/O drew/O rein/O ./O 
His/O standard-bearer/O rode/O to/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O moat/O to/O hail/O the/O men/O in/O the/O gatehouse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON 's/O seat/O ./O 
He/O should/O be/O expecting/O us/O ./O 
Look/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON raised/O her/O eyes/O ,/O up/O and/O up/O and/O up/O ./O 
At/O first/O all/O she/O saw/O was/O stone/O and/O trees/O ,/O the/O looming/O mass/O of/O the/O great/O mountain/O shrouded/O in/O night/O ,/O as/O black/O as/O a/O starless/O sky/O ./O 
Then/O she/O noticed/O the/O glow/O of/O distant/O fires/O well/O above/O them/O ;/O a/O tower/O keep/O ,/O built/O upon/O the/O steep/O side/O of/O the/O mountain/O ,/O its/O lights/O like/O orange/O eyes/O staring/O down/O from/O above/O ./O 
Above/O that/O was/O another/O ,/O higher/O and/O more/O distant/O ,/O and/O still/O higher/O a/O third/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O a/O flickering/O spark/O in/O the/O sky/O ./O 
And/O finally/O ,/O up/O where/O the/O falcons/O soared/O ,/O a/O flash/O of/O white/O in/O the/O moonlight/O ./O 
Vertigo/PERSON washed/O over/O her/O as/O she/O stared/O upward/O at/O the/O pale/O towers/O ,/O so/O far/O above/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Eyrie/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O heard/O Marillion/O murmur/O ,/O awed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sharp/O voice/O of/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O broke/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Arryns/O must/O not/O be/O overfond/O of/O company/O ./O 
If/O you/O 're/O planning/O to/O make/O us/O climb/O that/O mountain/O in/O the/O dark/O ,/O I/O 'd/O rather/O you/O kill/O me/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 'll/O spend/O the/O night/O here/O and/O make/O the/O ascent/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Brynden/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O scarcely/O wait/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O do/O we/O get/O up/O there/O ?/O 
I/O 've/O no/O experience/O at/O riding/O goats/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mules/O ,/O \/O ''/O Brynden/PERSON said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O steps/O carved/O into/O the/O mountain/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O told/O her/O about/O them/O when/O he/O talked/O of/O his/O youth/O here/O with/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON and/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O too/O dark/O to/O see/O them/O ,/O but/O the/O steps/O are/O there/O ./O 
Too/O steep/O and/O narrow/O for/O horses/O ,/O but/O mules/O can/O manage/O them/O most/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
The/O path/O is/O guarded/O by/O three/O waycastles/O ,/O Stone/O and/O Snow/O and/O Sky/O ./O 
The/O mules/O will/O take/O us/O as/O far/O up/O as/O Sky/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O glanced/O up/O doubtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O beyond/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Brynden/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Beyond/O that/O ,/O the/O path/O is/O too/O steep/O even/O for/O mules/O ./O 
We/O ascend/O on/O foot/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
Or/O perchance/O you/O 'd/O prefer/O to/O ride/O a/O basket/O ./O 
The/O Eyrie/O clings/O to/O the/O mountain/O directly/O above/O Sky/O ,/O and/O in/O its/O cellars/O are/O six/O great/O winches/O with/O long/O iron/O chains/O to/O draw/O supplies/O up/O from/O below/O ./O 
If/O you/O prefer/O ,/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION ,/O I/O can/O arrange/O for/O you/O to/O ride/O up/O with/O the/O bread/O and/O beer/O and/O apples/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O gave/O a/O bark/O of/O laughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O were/O a/O pumpkin/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Alas/O ,/O my/O lord/O father/O would/O no/O doubt/O be/O most/O chagrined/O if/O his/O son/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION went/O to/O his/O fate/O like/O a/O load/O of/O turnips/O ./O 
If/O you/O ascend/O on/O foot/O ,/O I/O fear/O I/O must/O do/O the/O same/O ./O 
We/O Lannisters/O do/O have/O a/O certain/O pride/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pride/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON snapped/O ./O 
His/O mocking/O tone/O and/O easy/O manner/O made/O her/O angry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arrogance/O ,/O some/O might/O call/O it/O ./O 
Arrogance/O and/O avarice/O and/O lust/O for/O power/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O is/O undoubtedly/O arrogant/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O is/O the/O soul/O of/O avarice/O ,/O and/O my/O sweet/O sister/O Cersei/PERSON lusts/O for/O power/O with/O every/O waking/O breath/O ./O 
I/O ,/O however/O ,/O am/O innocent/O as/O a/O little/O lamb/O ./O 
Shall/O I/O bleat/O for/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O grinned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O drawbridge/O came/O creaking/O down/O before/O she/O could/O reply/O ,/O and/O they/O heard/O the/O sound/O of/O oiled/O chains/O as/O the/O portcullis/O was/O drawn/O up/O ./O 
Men-at-arms/O carried/O burning/O brands/O out/O to/O light/O their/O way/O ,/O and/O her/O uncle/O led/O them/O across/O the/O moat/O ./O 
Lord/O Nestor/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O High/O Steward/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION and/O Keeper/O of/O the/O Gates/O of/O the/O Moon/O ,/O was/O waiting/O in/O the/O yard/O to/O greet/O them/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O his/O knights/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O bowing/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O massive/O ,/O barrel-chested/O man/O ,/O and/O his/O bow/O was/O clumsy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON dismounted/O to/O stand/O before/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O knew/O the/O man/O only/O by/O reputation/O ;/O Bronze/PERSON Yohn/PERSON 's/O cousin/O ,/O from/O a/O lesser/O branch/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Royce/O ,/O yet/O still/O a/O formidable/O lord/O in/O his/O own/O right/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O had/O a/O long/O and/O tiring/O journey/O ./O 
I/O would/O beg/O the/O hospitality/O of/O your/O roof/O tonight/O ,/O if/O I/O might/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O roof/O is/O yours/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON returned/O gruffly/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O your/O sister/O the/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON has/O sent/O down/O word/O from/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
She/O wishes/O to/O see/O you/O at/O once/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O your/O party/O will/O be/O housed/O here/O and/O sent/O up/O at/O first/O light/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O uncle/O swung/O off/O his/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O madness/O is/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O bluntly/O ./O 
Brynden/PERSON Tully/PERSON had/O never/O been/O a/O man/O to/O blunt/O the/O edge/O of/O his/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O night/O ascent/O ,/O with/O the/O moon/O not/O even/O full/O ?/O 
Even/O Lysa/PERSON should/O know/O that/O 's/O an/O invitation/O to/O a/O broken/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O mules/O know/O the/O way/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O wiry/O girl/O of/O seventeen/O or/O eighteen/O years/O stepped/O up/O beside/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON ./O 
Her/O dark/O hair/O was/O cropped/O short/O and/O straight/O around/O her/O head/O ,/O and/O she/O wore/O riding/O leathers/O and/O a/O light/O shirt/O of/O silvered/O ringmail/O ./O 
She/O bowed/O to/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O more/O gracefully/O than/O her/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O no/O harm/O will/O come/O to/O you/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O my/O honor/O to/O take/O you/O up/O ./O 
I/O 've/O made/O the/O dark/O climb/O a/O hundred/O times/O ./O 
Mychel/PERSON says/O my/O father/O must/O have/O been/O a/O goat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O sounded/O so/O cocky/O that/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O to/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O a/O name/O ,/O child/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mya/PERSON Stone/PERSON ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O girl/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O did/O not/O please/O her/O ;/O it/O was/O an/O effort/O for/O Catelyn/LOCATION to/O keep/O the/O smile/O on/O her/O face/O ./O 
Stone/O was/O a/O bastard/O 's/O name/O in/O the/O Vale/O ,/O as/O Snow/O was/O in/O the/O north/O ,/O and/O Flowers/O in/O Highgarden/LOCATION ;/O in/O each/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O custom/O had/O fashioned/O a/O surname/O for/O children/O born/O with/O no/O names/O of/O their/O own/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O nothing/O against/O this/O girl/O ,/O but/O suddenly/O she/O could/O not/O help/O but/O think/O of/O Ned/PERSON 's/O bastard/O ''/O ,/O ``/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O the/O thought/O made/O her/O angry/O and/O guilty/O ,/O both/O at/O once/O ./O 
She/O struggled/O to/O find/O words/O for/O a/O reply/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON filled/O the/O silence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mya/PERSON 's/O a/O clever/O girl/O ,/O and/O if/O she/O vows/O she/O will/O bring/O you/O safely/O to/O the/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON ,/O I/O believe/O her/O ./O 
She/O has/O not/O failed/O me/O yet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O I/O put/O myself/O in/O your/O hands/O ,/O Mya/PERSON Stone/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON ,/O I/O charge/O you/O to/O keep/O a/O close/O guard/O on/O my/O prisoner/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O I/O charge/O you/O to/O bring/O the/O prisoner/O a/O cup/O of/O wine/O and/O a/O nicely/O crisped/O capon/O ,/O before/O he/O dies/O of/O hunger/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O girl/O would/O be/O pleasant/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O I/O suppose/O that/O 's/O too/O much/O to/O ask/O of/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O sellsword/O Bronn/PERSON laughed/O aloud/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Nestor/PERSON ignored/O the/O banter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O so/O it/O will/O be/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Only/O then/O did/O he/O look/O at/O the/O dwarf/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O our/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O to/O a/O tower/O cell/O ,/O and/O bring/O him/O meat/O and/O mead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O her/O leave/O of/O her/O uncle/O and/O the/O others/O as/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O led/O off/O ,/O then/O followed/O the/O bastard/O girl/O through/O the/O castle/O ./O 
Two/O mules/O were/O waiting/O in/O the/O upper/O bailey/O ,/O saddled/O and/O ready/O ./O 
Mya/PERSON helped/O her/O mount/O one/O while/O a/O guardsman/O in/O a/O sky-blue/O cloak/O opened/O the/O narrow/O postern/O gate/O ./O 
Beyond/O was/O dense/O forest/O of/O pine/O and/O spruce/O ,/O and/O the/O mountain/O like/O a/O black/O wall/O ,/O but/O the/O steps/O were/O there/O ,/O chiseled/O deep/O into/O the/O rock/O ,/O ascending/O into/O the/O sky/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Some/O people/O find/O it/O easier/O if/O they/O close/O their/O eyes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON said/O as/O she/O led/O the/O mules/O through/O the/O gate/O into/O the/O dark/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O they/O get/O frightened/O or/O dizzy/O ,/O sometimes/O they/O hold/O on/O to/O the/O mule/O too/O tight/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O like/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O born/O a/O Tully/O and/O wed/O to/O a/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O frighten/O easily/O ./O 
Do/O you/O plan/O to/O light/O a/O torch/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O steps/O were/O black/O as/O pitch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O girl/O made/O a/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Torches/O just/O blind/O you/O ./O 
On/O a/O clear/O night/O like/O this/O ,/O the/O moon/O and/O the/O stars/O are/O enough/O ./O 
Mychel/PERSON says/O I/O have/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O owl/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O mounted/O and/O urged/O her/O mule/O up/O the/O first/O step/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON 's/O animal/O followed/O of/O its/O own/O accord/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O mentioned/O Mychel/O before/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O mules/O set/O the/O pace/O ,/O slow/O but/O steady/O ./O 
She/O was/O perfectly/O content/O with/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mychel/O 's/O my/O love/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON explained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mychel/O Redfort/O ./O 
He/O 's/O squire/O to/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON ./O 
We/O 're/O to/O wed/O as/O soon/O as/O he/O becomes/O a/O knight/O ,/O next/O year/O or/O the/O year/O after/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O sounded/O so/O like/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O so/O happy/O and/O innocent/O with/O her/O dreams/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON smiled/O ,/O but/O the/O smile/O was/O tinged/O with/O sadness/O ./O 
The/O Redforts/O were/O an/O old/O name/O in/O the/O Vale/LOCATION ,/O she/O knew/O ,/O with/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O in/O their/O veins/O ./O 
His/O love/O she/O might/O be/O ,/O but/O no/O Redfort/O would/O ever/O wed/O a/O bastard/O ./O 
His/O family/O would/O arrange/O a/O more/O suitable/O match/O for/O him/O ,/O to/O a/O Corbray/O or/O a/O Waynwood/O or/O a/O Royce/O ,/O or/O perhaps/O a/O daughter/O of/O some/O greater/O house/O outside/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
If/O Mychel/PERSON Redfort/PERSON laid/O with/O this/O girl/O at/O all/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O on/O the/O wrong/O side/O of/O the/O sheet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O ascent/O was/O easier/O than/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O dared/O hope/O ./O 
The/O trees/O pressed/O close/O ,/O leaning/O over/O the/O path/O to/O make/O a/O rustling/O green/O roof/O that/O shut/O out/O even/O the/O moon/O ,/O so/O it/O seemed/O as/O though/O they/O were/O moving/O up/O a/O long/O black/O tunnel/O ./O 
But/O the/O mules/O were/O surefooted/O and/O tireless/O ,/O and/O Mya/PERSON Stone/PERSON did/O indeed/O seem/O blessed/O with/O night-eyes/O ./O 
They/O plodded/O upward/O ,/O winding/O their/O way/O back/O and/O forth/O across/O the/O face/O of/O the/O mountain/O as/O the/O steps/O twisted/O and/O turned/O ./O 
A/O thick/O layer/O of/O fallen/O needles/O carpeted/O the/O path/O ,/O so/O the/O shoes/O of/O their/O mules/O made/O only/O the/O softest/O sound/O on/O the/O rock/O ./O 
The/O quiet/O ''/O ,/O ``/O soothed/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O gentle/O rocking/O motion/O set/O Catelyn/PERSON to/O swaying/O in/O her/O saddle/O ./O 
Before/O long/O she/O was/O fighting/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Perhaps/O she/O did/O doze/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O for/O suddenly/O a/O massive/O ironbound/O gate/O was/O looming/O before/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stone/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON announced/O cheerily/O ,/O dismounting/O ./O 
Iron/O spikes/O were/O set/O along/O the/O tops/O of/O formidable/O stone/O walls/O ,/O and/O two/O fat/O round/O towers/O overtopped/O the/O keep/O ./O 
The/O gate/O swung/O open/O at/O Mya/PERSON 's/O shout/O ./O 
Inside/O ,/O the/O portly/O knight/O who/O commanded/O the/O waycastle/O greeted/O Mya/PERSON by/O name/O and/O offered/O them/O skewers/O of/O charred/O meat/O and/O onions/O still/O hot/O from/O the/O spit/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O not/O realized/O how/O hungry/O she/O was/O ./O 
She/O ate/O standing/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O as/O stablehands/O moved/O their/O saddles/O to/O fresh/O mules/O ./O 
The/O hot/O juices/O ran/O down/O her/O chin/O and/O dripped/O onto/O her/O cloak/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O too/O famished/O to/O care/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O it/O was/O up/O onto/O a/O new/O mule/O and/O out/O again/O into/O the/O starlight/O ./O 
The/O second/O part/O of/O the/O ascent/O seemed/O more/O treacherous/O to/O Catelyn/LOCATION ./O 
The/O trail/O was/O steeper/O ,/O the/O steps/O more/O worn/O ,/O and/O here/O and/O there/O littered/O with/O pebbles/O and/O broken/O stone/O ./O 
Mya/PERSON had/O to/O dismount/O a/O half-dozen/O times/O to/O move/O fallen/O rocks/O from/O their/O path/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O your/O mule/O to/O break/O a/O leg/O up/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON was/O forced/O to/O agree/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O altitude/O more/O now/O ./O 
The/O trees/O were/O sparser/O up/O here/O ,/O and/O the/O wind/O blew/O more/O vigorously/O ,/O sharp/O gusts/O that/O tugged/O at/O her/O clothing/O and/O pushed/O her/O hair/O into/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
From/O time/O to/O time/O the/O steps/O doubled/O back/O on/O themselves/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O see/O Stone/O below/O them/O ,/O and/O the/O Gates/O of/O the/O Moon/O farther/O down/O ,/O its/O torches/O no/O brighter/O than/O candles/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Snow/O was/O smaller/O than/O Stone/O ,/O a/O single/O fortified/O tower/O and/O a/O timber/O keep/O and/O stable/O hidden/O behind/O a/O low/O wall/O of/O unmortared/O rock/O ./O 
Yet/O it/O nestled/O against/O the/O Giant/O 's/O Lance/PERSON in/O such/O a/O way/O as/O to/O command/O the/O entire/O stone/O stair/O above/O the/O lower/O waycastle/O ./O 
An/O enemy/O intent/O on/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON would/O have/O to/O fight/O his/O way/O from/O Stone/O step/O by/O step/O ,/O while/O rocks/O and/O arrows/O rained/O down/O from/O Snow/O above/O ./O 
The/O commander/O ,/O an/O anxious/O young/O knight/O with/O a/O pockmarked/O face/O ,/O offered/O bread/O and/O cheese/O and/O the/O chance/O to/O warm/O themselves/O before/O his/O fire/O ,/O but/O Mya/PERSON declined/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O ought/O to/O keep/O going/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Again/O they/O were/O given/O fresh/O mules/O ./O 
Hers/O was/O white/O ./O 
Mya/PERSON smiled/O when/O she/O saw/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Whitey/PERSON 's/O a/O good/O one/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Sure/O of/O foot/O ,/O even/O on/O ice/O ,/O but/O you/O need/O to/O be/O careful/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O kick/O if/O he/O does/O n't/O like/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O white/O mule/O seemed/O to/O like/O Catelyn/PERSON ;/O there/O was/O no/O kicking/O ,/O thank/O the/O gods/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O ice/O either/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O grateful/O for/O that/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O mother/O says/O that/O hundreds/O of/O years/O ago/O ,/O this/O was/O where/O the/O snow/O began/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O always/O white/O above/O here/O ,/O and/O the/O ice/O never/O melted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O remember/O ever/O seeing/O snow/O this/O far/O down/O the/O mountain/O ,/O but/O maybe/O it/O was/O that/O way/O once/O ,/O in/O the/O olden/O times/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O So/O young/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O ,/O trying/O to/O remember/O if/O she/O had/O ever/O been/O like/O that/O ./O 
The/O girl/O had/O lived/O half/O her/O life/O in/O summer/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O all/O she/O knew/O ./O 
Winter/O is/O coming/O ,/O child/O ,/O she/O wanted/O to/O tell/O her/O ./O 
The/O words/O were/O on/O her/O lips/O ;/O she/O almost/O said/O them/O ./O 
Perhaps/O she/O was/O becoming/O a/O Stark/O at/O last/O ./O 
Above/O Snow/O ,/O the/O wind/O was/O a/O living/O thing/O ,/O howling/O around/O them/O like/O a/O wolf/O in/O the/O waste/O ,/O then/O falling/O off/O to/O nothing/O as/O if/O to/O lure/O them/O into/O complacency/O ./O 
The/O stars/O seemed/O brighter/O up/O here/O ,/O so/O close/O that/O she/O could/O almost/O touch/O them/O ,/O and/O the/O horned/O moon/O was/O huge/O in/O the/O clear/O black/O sky/O ./O 
As/O they/O climbed/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON found/O it/O was/O better/O to/O look/O up/O than/O down/O ./O 
The/O steps/O were/O cracked/O and/O ''/O ,/O ``/O broken/O from/O centuries/O of/O freeze/O and/O thaw/O and/O the/O tread/O of/O countless/O mules/O ,/O and/O even/O in/O the/O dark/O the/O heights/O put/O her/O heart/O in/O her/O throat/O ./O 
When/O they/O came/O to/O a/O high/O saddle/O between/O two/O spires/O of/O rock/O ,/O Mya/PERSON dismounted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O best/O to/O lead/O the/O mules/O over/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wind/O can/O be/O a/O little/O scary/O here/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O climbed/O stiffly/O from/O the/O shadows/O and/O looked/O at/O the/O path/O ahead/O ;/O twenty/O feet/O long/O and/O close/O to/O three/O feet/O wide/O ,/O but/O with/O a/O precipitous/O drop/O to/O either/O side/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O the/O wind/O shrieking/O ./O 
Mya/PERSON stepped/O lightly/O out/O ,/O her/O mule/O following/O as/O calmly/O as/O if/O they/O were/O crossing/O a/O bailey/O ./O 
It/O was/O her/O turn/O ./O 
Yet/O no/O sooner/O had/O she/O taken/O her/O first/O step/O than/O fear/O caught/O Catelyn/ORGANIZATION in/O its/O jaws/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O emptiness/O ,/O the/O vast/O black/O gulfs/O of/O air/O that/O yawned/O around/O her/O ./O 
She/O stopped/O ,/O trembling/O ,/O afraid/O to/O move/O ./O 
The/O wind/O screamed/O at/O her/O and/O wrenched/O at/O her/O cloak/O ,/O trying/O to/O pull/O her/O over/O the/O edge/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON edged/O her/O foot/O backward/O ,/O the/O most/O timid/O of/O steps/O ,/O but/O the/O mule/O was/O behind/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O not/O retreat/O ./O 
I/O am/O going/O to/O die/O here/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O cold/O sweat/O trickling/O down/O her/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON called/O across/O the/O gulf/O ./O 
The/O girl/O sounded/O a/O thousand/O leagues/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O well/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Tully/O Stark/O swallowed/O what/O remained/O of/O her/O pride/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O can/O not/O do/O this/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O you/O can/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O bastard/O girl/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O you/O can/O ./O 
Look/O how/O wide/O the/O path/O is/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O look/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O world/O seemed/O to/O be/O spinning/O around/O her/O ,/O mountain/O and/O sky/O and/O mules/O ,/O whirling/O like/O a/O child/O 's/O top/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON closed/O her/O eyes/O to/O steady/O her/O ragged/O breathing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O come/O back/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O move/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Moving/O was/O about/O the/O last/O thing/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O about/O to/O do/O ./O 
She/O listened/O to/O the/O skirling/O of/O the/O wind/O and/O the/O scuffling/O sound/O of/O leather/O on/O stone/O ./O 
Then/O Mya/PERSON was/O there/O ,/O taking/O her/O gently/O by/O the/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Keep/O your/O eyes/O closed/O if/O you/O like/O ./O 
Let/O go/O of/O the/O rope/O now/O ,/O Whitey/PERSON will/O take/O care/O of/O himself/O ./O 
Very/O good/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O lead/O you/O over/O ,/O it/O 's/O easy/O ,/O you/O 'll/O see/O ./O 
Give/O me/O a/O step/O now/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ,/O move/O your/O foot/O ,/O just/O slide/O it/O forward/O ./O 
See/O ./O 
Now/O another/O ./O 
Easy/O ./O 
You/O could/O run/O across/O ./O 
Another/O one/O ,/O go/O on/O ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O so/O ,/O foot/O by/O foot/O ,/O step/O by/O step/O ,/O the/O bastard/O girl/O led/O Catelyn/PERSON across/O ,/O blind/O and/O trembling/O ,/O while/O the/O white/O mule/O followed/O placidly/O behind/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O waycastle/O called/O Sky/O was/O no/O more/O than/O a/O high/O ,/O crescent-shaped/O wall/O of/O unmortared/O stone/O raised/O against/O the/O side/O of/O the/O mountain/O ,/O but/O even/O the/O topless/O towers/O of/O Valyria/LOCATION could/O not/O have/O looked/O more/O beautiful/O to/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ./O 
Here/O at/O last/O the/O snow/O crown/O began/O ;/O Sky/O 's/O weathered/O stones/O were/O rimed/O with/O frost/O ,/O and/O long/O spears/O of/O ice/O hung/O from/O the/O slopes/O above/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dawn/PERSON was/O breaking/O in/O the/O east/O as/O Mya/LOCATION Stone/LOCATION hallooed/O for/O the/O guards/O ,/O and/O the/O gates/O opened/O before/O them/O ./O 
Inside/O the/O walls/O there/O was/O only/O a/O series/O of/O ramps/O and/O a/O great/O tumble/O of/O boulders/O and/O stones/O of/O all/O sizes/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O it/O would/O be/O the/O easiest/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O to/O begin/O an/O avalanche/O from/O here/O ./O 
A/O mouth/O yawned/O in/O the/O rock/O face/O in/O front/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stables/O and/O barracks/O are/O in/O there/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O last/O part/O is/O inside/O the/O mountain/O ./O 
It/O can/O be/O a/O little/O dark/O ,/O but/O at/O least/O you/O 're/O out/O of/O the/O wind/O ./O 
This/O is/O as/O far/O as/O the/O mules/O can/O go/O ./O 
Past/O here/O ,/O well/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O sort/O of/O chimney/O ,/O more/O like/O a/O stone/O ladder/O than/O proper/O steps/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O not/O too/O bad/O ./O 
Another/O hour/O and/O we/O 'll/O be/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O looked/O up/O ./O 
Directly/O overhead/O ,/O pale/O in/O the/O dawn/O light/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O the/O foundations/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
It/O could/O not/O be/O more/O than/O six/O hundred/O feet/O above/O them/O ./O 
From/O below/O it/O looked/O like/O a/O small/O white/O honeycomb/O ./O 
She/O remembered/O what/O her/O uncle/O had/O said/O of/O baskets/O and/O winches/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O may/O have/O their/O pride/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O Mya/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O but/O the/O Tullys/O are/O born/O with/O better/O sense/O ./O 
I/O have/O ridden/O all/O day/O and/O the/O best/O part/O of/O a/O night/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O to/O lower/O a/O basket/O ./O 
I/O shall/O ride/O with/O the/O turnips/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O sun/O was/O well/O above/O the/O mountains/O by/O the/O time/O Catelyn/O Stark/O finally/O reached/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
A/O stocky/O ,/O silver-haired/O man/O in/O a/O sky-blue/O cloak/O and/O hammered/O moon-and-falcon/O breastplate/O helped/O her/O from/O the/O basket/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON ,/O captain/O of/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O household/O guard/O ./O 
Beside/O him/O stood/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON ,/O thin/O and/O nervous/O ,/O with/O too/O little/O hair/O and/O too/O much/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O pleasure/O is/O as/O great/O as/O it/O is/O unanticipated/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON bobbed/O his/O head/O in/O agreement/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Indeed/O it/O is/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O indeed/O it/O is/O ./O 
I/O have/O sent/O word/O to/O your/O sister/O ./O 
She/O left/O orders/O to/O be/O awakened/O the/O instant/O you/O arrived/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O hope/O she/O had/O a/O good/O night/O 's/O rest/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O with/O a/O certain/O bite/O in/O her/O tone/O that/O seemed/O to/O go/O unnoticed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O men/O escorted/O her/O from/O the/O winch/O room/O up/O a/O spiral/O stair/O ./O 
The/O Eyrie/O was/O a/O small/O castle/O by/O the/O standards/O of/O the/O great/O houses/O ;/O seven/O slender/O white/O towers/O bunched/O as/O tightly/O as/O arrows/O in/O a/O quiver/O on/O a/O shoulder/O of/O the/O great/O mountain/O ./O 
It/O had/O no/O need/O of/O stables/O nor/O smithys/O nor/O kennels/O ,/O but/O Ned/PERSON said/O its/O granary/O was/O as/O large/O as/O Winterfell/ORGANIZATION 's/O ,/O and/O its/O towers/O could/O house/O five/O hundred/O men/O ./O 
Yet/O it/O seemed/O strangely/O deserted/O to/O Catelyn/PERSON as/O she/O passed/O through/O it/O ,/O its/O pale/O stone/O halls/O echoing/O and/O empty/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON was/O waiting/O alone/O in/O her/O solar/O ,/O still/O clad/O in/O her/O bed/O robes/O ./O 
Her/O long/O auburn/O hair/O tumbled/O unbound/O across/O bare/O white/O shoulders/O and/O down/O her/O back/O ./O 
A/O maid/O stood/O behind/O her/O ,/O brushing/O out/O the/O night/O 's/O tangles/O ,/O but/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON entered/O ,/O her/O sister/O rose/O to/O her/O feet/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cat/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O Cat/O ,/O how/O good/O it/O is/O to/O see/O you/O ./O 
My/O sweet/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O ran/O across/O the/O chamber/O and/O wrapped/O her/O sister/O in/O her/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O long/O it/O has/O been/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON murmured/O against/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O how/O very/O very/O long/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O had/O been/O five/O years/O ,/O in/O truth/O ;/O five/O cruel/O years/O ,/O for/O Lysa/PERSON ./O 
They/O had/O taken/O their/O toll/O ./O 
Her/O sister/O was/O two/O years/O the/O younger/O ,/O yet/O she/O looked/O older/O now/O ./O 
Shorter/O than/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O Lysa/PERSON had/O grown/O thick/O of/O body/O ,/O pale/O and/O puffy/O of/O face/O ./O 
She/O had/O the/O blue/O eyes/O of/O the/O Tullys/O ,/O but/O hers/O were/O pale/O and/O watery/O ,/O never/O still/O ./O 
Her/O small/O mouth/O had/O turned/O petulant/O ./O 
As/O Catelyn/PERSON held/O her/O ,/O she/O remembered/O the/O slender/O ,/O high-breasted/O girl/O who/O 'd/O waited/O beside/O her/O that/O day/O in/O the/O sept/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
How/O lovely/O and/O full/O of/O hope/O she/O had/O been/O ./O 
All/O that/O remained/O of/O her/O sister/O 's/O beauty/O was/O the/O great/O fall/O of/O thick/O auburn/O hair/O that/O cascaded/O to/O her/O waist/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O look/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/O lied/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O .../O tired/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O sister/O broke/O the/O embrace/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tired/O ./O 
Yes/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O seemed/O to/O notice/O the/O others/O then/O ;/O her/O maid/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Leave/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wish/O to/O speak/O to/O my/O sister/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O held/O Catelyn/PERSON 's/O hand/O as/O they/O withdrew/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O .../O and/O dropped/O it/O the/O instant/O the/O door/O closed/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON saw/O her/O face/O change/O ./O 
It/O was/O as/O if/O the/O sun/O had/O gone/O behind/O a/O cloud/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O taken/O leave/O of/O your/O senses/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON snapped/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O bring/O ''/O ,/O ``/O him/O here/O ,/O without/O a/O word/O of/O permission/O ,/O without/O so/O much/O as/O a/O warning/O ,/O to/O drag/O us/O into/O your/O quarrels/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O quarrels/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O scarce/O believe/O what/O she/O was/O hearing/O ./O 
A/O great/O fire/O burned/O in/O the/O hearth/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O trace/O of/O warmth/O in/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O your/O quarrels/O first/O ,/O sister/O ./O 
It/O was/O you/O who/O sent/O me/O that/O cursed/O letter/O ,/O you/O who/O wrote/O that/O the/O Lannisters/O had/O murdered/O your/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O warn/O you/O ,/O so/O you/O could/O stay/O away/O from/O them/O !/O 
I/O never/O meant/O to/O fight/O them/O !/O 
Gods/O ,/O Cat/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O what/O you/O 've/O done/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O a/O small/O voice/O said/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON whirled/O ,/O her/O heavy/O robe/O swirling/O around/O her/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O stood/O in/O the/O doorway/O ,/O clutching/O a/O ragged/O cloth/O doll/O and/O looking/O at/O them/O with/O large/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O painfully/O thin/O child/O ,/O small/O for/O his/O age/O and/O sickly/O all/O his/O days/O ,/O and/O from/O time/O to/O time/O he/O trembled/O ./O 
The/O shaking/O sickness/O ,/O the/O maesters/O called/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O heard/O voices/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Small/O wonder/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O ;/O Lysa/PERSON had/O almost/O been/O shouting/O ./O 
Still/O ,/O her/O sister/O looked/O daggers/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O your/O aunt/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O baby/O ./O 
My/O sister/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
Do/O you/O remember/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O boy/O glanced/O at/O her/O blankly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O blinking/O ,/O though/O he/O had/O been/O less/O than/O a/O year/O old/O the/O last/O time/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O seen/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON seated/O herself/O near/O the/O fire/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Come/O to/O Mother/O ,/O my/O sweet/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O straightened/O his/O bedclothes/O and/O fussed/O with/O his/O fine/O brown/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O n't/O he/O beautiful/O ?/O 
And/O strong/O too/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O believe/O the/O things/O you/O hear/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knew/O ./O 
The/O seed/O is/O strong/O ,/O he/O told/O me/O ./O 
His/O last/O words/O ./O 
He/O kept/O saying/O Robert/PERSON 's/O name/O ,/O and/O he/O grabbed/O my/O arm/O so/O hard/O he/O left/O marks/O ./O 
Tell/O them/O ,/O the/O seed/O is/O strong/O ./O 
His/O seed/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O everyone/O to/O know/O what/O a/O good/O strong/O boy/O my/O baby/O was/O going/O to/O be/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O if/O you/O 're/O right/O about/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O all/O the/O more/O reason/O we/O must/O act/O quickly/O ./O 
We/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O in/O front/O of/O the/O baby/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O a/O delicate/O temper/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O ,/O sweet/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O boy/O is/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O Defender/O of/O the/O Vale/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON reminded/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O these/O are/O no/O times/O for/O delicacy/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON thinks/O it/O may/O come/O to/O war/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Quiet/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON snapped/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O scaring/O the/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Little/O Robert/PERSON took/O a/O quick/O peek/O over/O his/O shoulder/O at/O Catelyn/LOCATION and/O began/O to/O tremble/O ./O 
His/O doll/O fell/O to/O the/O rushes/O ,/O and/O he/O pressed/O himself/O against/O his/O mother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ,/O my/O sweet/O baby/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O 's/O here/O ,/O nothing/O will/O hurt/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O opened/O her/O robe/O and/O drew/O out/O a/O pale/O ,/O heavy/O breast/O ,/O tipped/O with/O red/O ./O 
The/O boy/O grabbed/O for/O it/O eagerly/O ,/O buried/O his/O face/O against/O her/O chest/O ,/O and/O began/O to/O suck/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON stroked/O his/O hair/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON was/O at/O a/O loss/O for/O words/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Anyn/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O she/O thought/O incredulously/O ./O 
She/O remembered/O her/O own/O baby/O ,/O three-year-old/O Rickon/PERSON ,/O half/O the/O age/O of/O this/O boy/O and/O five/O times/O as/O fierce/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION were/O restive/O ./O 
For/O the/O first/O time/O she/O understood/O why/O the/O king/O had/O tried/O to/O take/O the/O child/O away/O from/O his/O mother/O to/O foster/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 're/O safe/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON was/O saying/O ./O 
Whether/O to/O her/O or/O to/O the/O boy/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O not/O sure/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O a/O fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ,/O the/O anger/O rising/O in/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O is/O safe/O ./O 
If/O you/O think/O hiding/O here/O will/O make/O the/O Lannisters/O forget/O you/O ,/O you/O are/O sadly/O mistaken/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON covered/O her/O boy/O 's/O ear/O with/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O if/O they/O could/O bring/O an/O army/O through/O the/O mountains/O and/O past/O the/O Bloody/O Gate/O ,/O the/O Eyrie/O is/O impregnable/O ./O 
You/O saw/O for/O yourself/O ./O 
No/O enemy/O could/O ever/O reach/O us/O up/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON wanted/O to/O slap/O her/O ./O 
Uncle/O Brynden/PERSON had/O tried/O to/O warn/O her/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O castle/O is/O impregnable/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O one/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Everyone/O says/O so/O ./O 
The/O only/O thing/O is/O ,/O what/O am/O I/O to/O do/O with/O this/O Imp/O you/O have/O brought/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O he/O a/O bad/O man/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON asked/O ,/O his/O mother/O 's/O breast/O popping/O from/O his/O mouth/O ,/O the/O nipple/O wet/O and/O red/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O very/O bad/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON told/O him/O as/O she/O covered/O herself/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O Mother/O wo/O n't/O let/O him/O harm/O my/O little/O baby/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Make/O him/O fly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O eagerly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON stroked/O her/O son/O 's/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O we/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O murmured/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O that/O is/O just/O what/O we/O will/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
