-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O woods/O were/O full/O of/O whispers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Moonlight/O winked/O on/O the/O tumbling/O waters/O of/O the/O stream/O below/O as/O it/O wound/O its/O rocky/O way/O along/O the/O floor/O of/O the/O valley/O ./O 
Beneath/O the/O trees/O ,/O warhorses/O whickered/O softly/O and/O pawed/O at/O the/O moist/O ,/O leafy/O ground/O ,/O while/O men/O made/O nervous/O jests/O in/O hushed/O voices/O ./O 
Now/O and/O again/O ,/O she/O heard/O the/O chink/O of/O spears/O ,/O the/O faint/O metallic/O slither/O of/O chain/O mail/O ,/O but/O even/O those/O sounds/O were/O muffled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O should/O not/O be/O long/O now/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O had/O asked/O for/O the/O honor/O of/O protecting/O her/O in/O the/O battle/O to/O come/O ;/O it/O was/O his/O right/O ,/O as/O WinterfelPs/O captain/O of/O guards/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON had/O not/O refused/O it/O to/O him/O ./O 
She/O had/O thirty/O men/O around/O her/O ,/O charged/O to/O keep/O her/O unharmed/O and/O see/O her/O safely/O home/O to/O Winterfell/O if/O the/O fighting/O went/O against/O them/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON had/O wanted/O fifty/O ;/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O insisted/O that/O ten/O would/O be/O enough/O ,/O that/O he/O would/O need/O every/O sword/O for/O the/O fight/O ./O 
They/O made/O their/O peace/O at/O thirty/O ,/O neither/O happy/O with/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O come/O when/O it/O comes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
When/O it/O came/O ,/O she/O knew/O it/O would/O mean/O death/O ./O 
Hal/PERSON 's/O death/O perhaps/O .../O or/O hers/O ,/O or/O Robb/PERSON 's/O ./O 
No/O one/O was/O safe/O ./O 
No/O life/O was/O certain/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON was/O content/O to/O wait/O ,/O to/O listen/O to/O the/O whispers/O in/O the/O woods/O and/O the/O faint/O music/O of/O the/O brook/O ,/O to/O feel/O the/O warm/O wind/O in/O her/O hair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O was/O no/O stranger/O to/O waiting/O ,/O after/O all/O ./O 
Her/O men/O had/O always/O made/O her/O wait/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Watch/O for/O me/O ,/O little/O cat/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O would/O always/O tell/O her/O ,/O when/O he/O rode/O off/O to/O court/O or/O fair/O or/O battle/O ./O 
And/O she/O would/O ,/O standing/O patiently/O on/O the/O battlements/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION as/O the/O waters/O of/O the/O Red/O Fork/O and/O the/O Tumblestone/O flowed/O by/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O always/O come/O when/O he/O said/O he/O would/O ,/O and/O days/O would/O ofttimes/O pass/O as/O Catelyn/PERSON stood/O her/O vigil/O ,/O peering/O out/O between/O crenels/O and/O through/O arrow/O loops/O until/O she/O caught/O a/O glimpse/O of/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON on/O his/O old/O brown/O gelding/O ,/O trotting/O along/O the/O rivershore/O toward/O the/O landing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O you/O watch/O for/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O 'd/O ask/O when/O he/O bent/O to/O bug/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O you/O ,/O little/O cat/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O bid/O her/O wait/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O not/O be/O long/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O had/O vowed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O will/O be/O wed/O on/O my/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Yet/O when/O the/O day/O came/O at/O last/O ,/O it/O was/O his/O brother/O Eddard/PERSON who/O stood/O beside/O her/O in/O the/O sept./O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O lingered/O scarcely/O a/O fortnight/O with/O his/O new/O bride/O before/O he/O too/O had/O ridden/O off/O to/O war/O with/O promises/O on/O his/O lips/O ./O 
At/O least/O he/O had/O left/O her/O with/O more/O than/O words/O ;/O he/O had/O given/O her/O a/O son/O ./O 
Nine/O moons/O had/O waxed/O and/O waned/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON had/O been/O born/O in/O Riverrun/LOCATION while/O his/O father/O still/O warred/O in/O the/O south/O ./O 
She/O had/O brought/O him/O forth/O in/O blood/O and/O pain/O ,/O not/O knowing/O whether/O Ned/PERSON would/O ever/O see/O him/O ./O 
Her/O son/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O so/O small/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O now/O it/O was/O for/O Robb/PERSON that/O she/O waited/O .../O for/O Robb/PERSON ,/O and/O for/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O the/O gilded/O knight/O who/O men/O said/O had/O never/O learned/O to/O wait/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O is/O restless/O ,/O and/O quick/O to/O anger/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O uncle/O Brynden/PERSON had/O told/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
And/O he/O had/O wagered/O their/O lives/O and/O their/O best/O hope/O of/O victory/O on/O the/O truth/O of/O what/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O If/O Robb/PERSON was/O frightened/O ,/O he/O gave/O no/O sign/O of/O it/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON watched/O her/O son/O as/O he/O moved/O among/O the/O men/O ,/O touching/O one/O on/O the/O shoulder/O ,/O sharing/O a/O jest/O with/O another/O ,/O helping/O a/O third/O to/O gentle/O an/O anxious/O horse/O ./O 
His/O armor/O clinked/O softly/O when/O he/O moved/O ./O 
Only/O his/O head/O was/O bare/O ./O 
Catelyn/O ''/O ,/O ``/O watched/O a/O breeze/O stir/O his/O auburn/O hair/O ,/O so/O like/O her/O own/O ,/O and/O wondered/O when/O her/O son/O had/O grown/O so/O big/O ./O 
Fifteen/O ,/O and/O near/O as/O tall/O as/O she/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Let/O him/O grow/O taller/O ,/O she/O asked/O the/O gods/O ./O 
Let/O him/O know/O sixteen/O ,/O and/O twenty/O ,/O and/O fifty/O ./O 
Let/O him/O grow/O as/O tall/O as/O his/O father/O ,/O and/O hold/O his/O own/O son/O in/O his/O arms/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O please/O ,/O please/O ./O 
As/O she/O watched/O him/O ,/O this/O tall/O young/O man/O with/O the/O new/O beard/O and/O the/O direwo/O If/O prowling/O at/O his/O heels/O ,/O all/O she/O could/O see/O was/O the/O babe/O they/O had/O laid/O at/O her/O breast/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O so/O long/O ago/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O night/O was/O warm/O ,/O but/O the/O thought/O of/O Riverrun/PERSON was/O enough/O to/O make/O her/O shiver/O ./O 
Where/O are/O they/O ?/O 
she/O wondered/O ./O 
Could/O her/O uncle/O have/O been/O wrong/O ?/O 
So/O much/O rested/O on/O the/O truth/O of/O what/O he/O had/O told/O them/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON had/O given/O the/O Blackfish/O three/O hundred/O picked/O men/O ,/O and/O sent/O them/O ahead/O to/O screen/O his/O march/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON does/O not/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON said/O when/O he/O rode/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O stake/O my/O life/O on/O that/O ./O 
No/O bird/O has/O reached/O him/O ,/O my/O archers/O have/O seen/O to/O that/O ./O 
We/O 've/O seen/O a/O few/O of/O his/O outriders/O ,/O but/O those/O that/O saw/O us/O did/O not/O live/O to/O tell/O of/O it/O ./O 
He/O ought/O to/O have/O sent/O out/O more/O ./O 
He/O does/O not/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O large/O is/O his/O host/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O her/O son/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Twelve/O thousand/O foot/O ,/O scattered/O around/O the/O castle/O in/O three/O separate/O camps/O ,/O with/O the/O rivers/O between/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O uncle/O said/O ,/O with/O the/O craggy/O smile/O she/O remembered/O so/O well/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O other/O way/O to/O besiege/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O yet/O still/O ,/O that/O will/O be/O their/O undoing/O ./O 
Two/O or/O three/O thousand/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O has/O us/O three/O to/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O True/O enough/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O there/O is/O one/O thing/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON lacks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Patience/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Their/O host/O was/O greater/O than/O it/O had/O been/O when/O they/O left/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Lord/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON had/O brought/O his/O power/O out/O from/O Seagard/LOCATION to/O join/O them/O as/O they/O swept/O around/O the/O headwaters/O of/O the/O Blue/O Fork/O and/O galloped/O south/O ,/O and/O others/O had/O crept/O forth/O as/O well/O ,/O hedge/O knights/O and/O small/O lords/O and/O master/O less/O men-at-arms/O who/O had/O fled/O north/O when/O her/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON 's/O army/O was/O shattered/O beneath/O the/O walls/O of/O Riverrun/O ./O 
They/O had/O driven/O their/O horses/O as/O hard/O as/O they/O dared/O to/O reach/O this/O place/O before/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O word/O of/O their/O coming/O ,/O and/O now/O the/O hour/O was/O at/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON watched/O her/O son/O mount/O up/O ./O 
Olyvar/PERSON Frey/PERSON held/O his/O horse/O for/O him/O ,/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON 's/O son/O ,/O two/O years/O older/O than/O Robb/PERSON ,/O and/O ten/O years/O younger/O and/O more/O anxious/O ./O 
He/O strapped/O Robb/PERSON 's/O shield/O in/O place/O and/O handed/O up/O his/O helm/O ./O 
When/O he/O lowered/O it/O over/O the/O face/O she/O loved/O so/O well/O ,/O a/O tall/O young/O knight/O sat/O on/O his/O grey/O stallion/O where/O her/O son/O had/O been/O ./O 
It/O was/O dark/O among/O the/O trees/O ,/O where/O the/O moon/O did/O not/O reach/O ./O 
When/O Robb/PERSON turned/O his/O head/O to/O look/O at/O her/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O only/O black/O inside/O his/O visor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O must/O ride/O down/O the/O line/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O says/O you/O should/O let/O the/O men/O see/O you/O before/O a/O battle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O them/O see/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O give/O them/O courage/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O who/O will/O give/O me/O courage/O ?/O 
she/O wondered/O ,/O yet/O she/O kept/O her/O silence/O and/O made/O herself/O smile/O for/O him/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON turned/O the/O big/O grey/O stallion/O and/O walked/O him/O slowly/O away/O from/O her/O ,/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON shadowing/O his/O steps/O ./O 
Behind/O him/O his/O battle/O guard/O formed/O up/O ./O 
When/O he/O 'd/O forced/O Catelyn/PERSON to/O accept/O her/O protectors/O ,/O she/O had/O insisted/O that/O he/O be/O guarded/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O the/O lords/O bannermen/O had/O agreed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Many/O of/O their/O sons/O had/O clamored/O for/O the/O honor/O of/O riding/O with/O the/O Young/PERSON Wolf/PERSON ,/O as/O they/O had/O taken/O to/O calling/O him/O ./O 
Torrhen/PERSON Karstark/PERSON and/O his/O brother/O Eddard/PERSON were/O among/O his/O thirty/O ,/O and/O Patrek/PERSON Mallister/PERSON ,/O Smalljon/O Umber/O ,/O Daryn/PERSON Hornwood/PERSON ,/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O no/O less/O than/O five/O of/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON 's/O vast/O brood/O ,/O along/O with/O older/O men/O like/O Ser/O Wendel/O Manderly/O and/O Robin/PERSON Flint/PERSON ./O 
One/O of/O his/O companions/O was/O even/O a/O woman/O :/O Dacey/PERSON Mormont/PERSON ,/O Lady/PERSON Maege/PERSON 's/O eldest/O daughter/O and/O heir/O to/O Bear/LOCATION Island/LOCATION ,/O a/O lanky/O sixfooter/O who/O had/O been/O given/O a/O morningstar/O at/O an/O age/O when/O most/O girls/O were/O given/O dolls/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O other/O lords/O muttered/O about/O that/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O not/O listen/O to/O their/O complaints/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O not/O about/O the/O honor/O of/O your/O houses/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O about/O keeping/O my/O son/O alive/O and/O whole/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O if/O it/O comes/O to/O that/O ,/O she/O wondered/O ,/O will/O thiny/O be/O enough/O ?/O 
Will/O six/O thousand/O be/O enough/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O bird/O called/O faintly/O in/O the/O distance/O ,/O a/O high/O sharp/O trill/O that/O felt/O like/O an/O icy/O hand/O on/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O neck/O ./O 
Another/O bird/O answered/O ;/O a/O third/O ,/O a/O fourth/O ./O 
She/O knew/O their/O call/O well/O enough/O ,/O from/O her/O years/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Snow/O shrikes/O ./O 
Sometimes/O you/O saw/O them/O in/O the/O deep/O of/O winter/O ,/O when/O the/O godswood/O was/O white/O and/O still/O ./O 
They/O were/O northern/O birds/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O are/O coming/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O coming/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hal/PERSON Mollen/PERSON whispered/O ./O 
He/O was/O always/O a/O man/O for/O stating/O the/O obvious/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O be/O with/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O nodded/O as/O the/O woods/O grew/O still/O around/O them/O ./O 
In/O the/O quiet/O she/O could/O hear/O them/O ,/O far/O off/O yet/O moving/O closer/O ;/O the/O tread/O of/O many/O horses/O ,/O the/O rattle/O of/O swords/O and/O spears/O and/O armor/O ,/O the/O murmur/O of/O human/O voices/O ,/O with/O here/O a/O laugh/O ,/O and/O there/O a/O curse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Eons/O seemed/O to/O come/O and/O go/O ./O 
The/O sounds/O grew/O louder/O ./O 
She/O heard/O more/O laughter/O ,/O a/O shouted/O command/O ,/O splashing/O as/O they/O crossed/O and/O recrossed/O the/O little/O stream/O ./O 
A/O horse/O snorted/O ./O 
A/O man/O swore/O ./O 
And/O then/O at/O last/O she/O saw/O him/O .../O only/O for/O an/O instant/O ,/O framed/O between/O the/O branches/O of/O the/O trees/O as/O she/O looked/O down/O at/O the/O valley/O floor/O ,/O yet/O she/O knew/O it/O was/O him/O ./O 
Even/O at/O a/O distance/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON was/O unmistakable/O ./O 
The/O moonlight/O had/O silvered/O his/O armor/O and/O the/O gold/O of/O his/O hair/O ,/O and/O turned/O his/O crimson/O cloak/O to/O black/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O wearing/O a/O helm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O there/O and/O he/O was/O gone/O again/O ,/O his/O silvery/O armor/O obscured/O by/O the/O trees/O once/O more/O ./O 
Others/O came/O behind/O him/O ,/O long/O columns/O of/O them/O ,/O knights/O and/O sworn/O swords/O and/O freeriders/O ,/O three/O quarters/O of/O the/O Lannister/O horse/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O no/O man/O for/O sitting/O in/O a/O tent/O while/O his/O carpenters/O build/O siege/O towers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON had/O promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O has/O ridden/O out/O with/O his/O knights/O thrice/O already/O ,/O to/O chase/O down/O raiders/O or/O storm/O a/O stubborn/O holdfast/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Nodding/O ,/O Robb/PERSON had/O studied/O the/O map/O her/O uncle/O had/O drawn/O him/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O taught/O him/O to/O read/O maps/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Raid/O him/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O pointing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O few/O hundred/O men/O ,/O no/O more/O ./O 
Tully/O banners/O ./O 
When/O he/O comes/O after/O you/O ,/O we/O will/O be/O waiting/O \/O ''/O -/O his/O finger/O moved/O an/O inch/O to/O the/O left/O -/O \/O ``/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Here/O was/O a/O hush/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O moonlight/O and/O shadows/O ,/O a/O thick/O carpet/O of/O dead/O leaves/O underfoot/O ,/O densely/O wooded/O ridges/O sloping/O gently/O down/O to/O the/O streambed/O ,/O the/O underbrush/O thinning/O as/O the/O ground/O fell/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Here/O was/O her/O son/O on/O his/O stallion/O ,/O glancing/O back/O at/O her/O one/O last/O time/O and/O lifting/O his/O sword/O in/O salute/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Here/O was/O the/O call/O of/O Maege/PERSON Mormont/PERSON 's/O warhorn/O ,/O a/O long/O low/O blast/O that/O rolled/O down/O the/O valley/O from/O the/O east/O ,/O to/O tell/O them/O that/O the/O last/O of/O Jaime/PERSON 's/O riders/O had/O entered/O the/O trap/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON threw/O back/O his/O head/O and/O howled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sound/O seemed/O to/O go/O right/O through/O Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O and/O she/O found/O herself/O shivering/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O terrible/O sound/O ,/O a/O frightening/O sound/O ,/O yet/O there/O was/O music/O in/O it/O too/O ./O 
For/O a/O second/O she/O felt/O something/O like/O pity/O for/O the/O Lannisters/O below/O ./O 
So/O this/O is/O what/O death/O sounds/O like/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O HAAroooooooooooooooooooooooo/O came/O the/O answer/O from/O the/O far/O ridge/O as/O the/O Greatjon/LOCATION winded/O his/O own/O horn/O ./O 
To/O east/O and/O west/O ,/O the/O trumpets/O of/O the/O Mallisters/O and/O Freys/PERSON blew/O vengeance/O ./O 
North/O ,/O where/O the/O valley/O narrowed/O and/O bent/O like/O a/O cocked/O elbow/O ,/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON 's/O warhorns/O added/O their/O own/O deep/O ,/O mournful/O voices/O to/O the/O dark/O chorus/O ./O 
Men/O were/O shouting/O and/O horses/O rearing/O in/O the/O stream/O below/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O whispering/O wood/O let/O out/O its/O breath/O all/O at/O once/O ,/O as/O the/O bowmen/O Robb/PERSON had/O hidden/O in/O the/O branches/O of/O the/O trees/O let/O fly/O their/O arrows/O and/O the/O night/O erupted/O with/O the/O screams/O of/O men/O and/O horses/O ./O 
All/O around/O her/O ,/O the/O riders/O raised/O their/O lances/O ,/O and/O the/O dirt/O and/O leaves/O that/O had/O buried/O the/O cruet/O bright/O points/O fell/O away/O to/O reveal/O the/O gleam/O of/O sharpened/O steel/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wintefell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O heard/O Robb/PERSON shout/O as/O the/O arrows/O sighed/O again/O ./O 
He/O moved/O away/O from/O her/O at/O a/O trot/O ,/O leading/O his/O men/O downhill/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON sat/O on/O her/O horse/O ,/O unmoving/O ,/O with/O Hal/PERSON Mollen/PERSON and/O her/O guard/O around/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O waited/O as/O she/O had/O waited/O before/O ,/O for/O Brandon/PERSON and/O Ned/PERSON and/O her/O father/O ./O 
She/O was/O high/O on/O the/O ridge/O ,/O and/O the/O trees/O hid/O most/O of/O what/O was/O going/O on/O beneath/O her/O ./O 
A/O heartbeat/O ,/O two/O ,/O four/O ,/O and/O suddenly/O it/O was/O as/O if/O she/O and/O her/O protectors/O were/O alone/O in/O the/O wood/O ./O 
The/O rest/O were/O melted/O away/O into/O the/O green/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O when/O she/O looked/O across/O the/O valley/O to/O the/O far/O ridge/O ,/O she/O saw/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON 's/O riders/O emerge/O from/O the/O darkness/O beneath/O the/O trees/O ./O 
They/O were/O in/O a/O long/O line/O ,/O an/O endless/O line/O ,/O and/O as/O they/O burst/O from/O the/O wood/O there/O was/O an/O instant/O ,/O the/O smallest/O part/O of/O a/O heartbeat/O ,/O when/O all/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O was/O the/O moonlight/O on/O the/O points/O of/O their/O lances/O ,/O as/O if/O a/O thousand/O willowisps/O were/O coming/O down/O the/O ridge/O ,/O wreathed/O in/O silver/O flame/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O she/O blinked/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O only/O men/O ,/O rushing/O down/O to/O kill/O or/O die/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Afterward/O ,/O she/O could/O not/O claim/O she/O had/O seen/O the/O battle/O ./O 
Yet/O she/O could/O hear/O ,/O and/O the/O valley/O rang/O with/O echoes/O ./O 
The/O crack/O of/O a/O broken/O lance/O ,/O the/O clash/O of/O swords/O ,/O the/O cries/O of/O \/O ``/O Lannister/O \/O ''/O and/O \/O ``/O Winterfell/O \/O ''/O and/O \/O ``/O Tully/O !/O 
Riverrun/PERSON and/O Tully/O !/O 
\/O ''/O When/O she/O realized/O there/O was/O no/O more/O to/O see/O ,/O she/O closed/O her/O eyes/O and/O listened/O ./O 
The/O battle/O came/O alive/O around/O her/O ./O 
She/O heard/O hoofbeats/O ,/O iron/O boots/O splashing/O in/O shallow/O water/O ,/O the/O woody/O sound/O of/O swords/O on/O oaken/O shields/O and/O the/O scrape/O of/O steel/O against/O steel/O ,/O the/O hiss/O of/O arrows/O ,/O the/O thunder/O of/O drums/O ,/O the/O terrified/O screaming/O of/O a/O thousand/O horses/O ./O 
Men/O shouted/O curses/O and/O begged/O for/O mercy/O ,/O and/O got/O it/O -LRB-/O or/O not/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O lived/O -LRB-/O or/O died/O -RRB-/O ./O 
The/O ridges/O seemed/O to/O play/O queer/O tricks/O with/O sound/O ./O 
Once/O she/O heard/O Robb/PERSON 's/O voice/O ,/O as/O clear/O as/O if/O he/O 'd/O been/O standing/O at/O her/O side/O ,/O calling/O ,/O \/O ``/O To/O me/O !/O 
To/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O And/O she/O heard/O his/O direwolf/O ,/O snarling/O and/O growling/O ,/O heard/O the/O snap/O of/O those/O long/O teeth/O ,/O the/O tearing/O of/O flesh/O ,/O shrieks/O of/O fear/O and/O pain/O from/O man/O and/O horse/O alike/O ./O 
Was/O there/O only/O one/O wolf/O ?/O 
It/O was/O hard/O to/O be/O certain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Little/O by/O little/O ,/O the/O sounds/O dwindled/O and/O died/O ,/O until/O at/O last/O there/O was/O only/O the/O wolf/O ./O 
As/O a/O red/O dawn/O broke/O in/O the/O east/O ,/O Grey/LOCATION Wind/LOCATION began/O to/O howl/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON came/O back/O to/O her/O on/O a/O different/O horse/O ,/O riding/O a/O piebald/O gelding/O in/O the/O place/O of/O the/O grey/O stallion/O he/O had/O taken/O down/O into/O the/O valley/O ./O 
The/O wolfs/O head/O on/O his/O shield/O was/O slashed/O half/O to/O pieces/O ,/O raw/O wood/O showing/O where/O deep/O gouges/O had/O been/O hacked/O in/O the/O oak/O ,/O but/O Robb/PERSON himself/O seemed/O unhurt/O ./O 
Yet/O when/O he/O came/O closer/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O that/O his/O mailed/O glove/O and/O the/O sleeve/O of/O his/O surcoat/O were/O black/O with/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O hurt/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON lifted/O his/O hand/O ,/O opened/O and/O closed/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O .../O Torrhen/O 's/O blood/O ,/O perhaps/O ,/O or/O He/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O know/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O mob/O of/O men/O followed/O him/O up/O the/O slope/O ,/O dirty/O and/O dented/O and/O grinning/O ,/O with/O Theon/PERSON and/O the/O Greatjon/PERSON at/O their/O head/O ./O 
Between/O them/O they/O dragged/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ./O 
They/O threw/O him/O down/O in/O front/O of/O her/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hal/PERSON announced/O ,/O unnecessarily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lannister/PERSON raised/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O from/O his/O knees/O ./O 
Blood/O ran/O down/O one/O cheek/O from/O a/O gash/O across/O his/O scalp/O ,/O but/O the/O pale/O light/O of/O dawn/O had/O put/O the/O glint/O of/O gold/O back/O in/O his/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O offer/O you/O my/O sword/O ,/O but/O I/O seem/O to/O have/O mislaid/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O your/O sword/O I/O want/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O me/O my/O father/O and/O my/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON ./O 
Give/O me/O my/O daughters/O ./O 
Give/O me/O my/O lord/O husband/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O I/O have/O mislaid/O them/O as/O well/O ,/O I/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O pity/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O coldly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Kill/O him/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON urged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O his/O head/O off/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O son/O answered/O ,/O peeling/O off/O his/O bloody/O glove/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O more/O use/O alive/O than/O dead/O ./O 
And/O my/O lord/O father/O never/O condoned/O the/O murder/O of/O prisoners/O after/O a/O battle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wise/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O honorable/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O him/O away/O and/O put/O him/O in/O irons/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O as/O my/O lady/O mother/O says/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON commanded/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O make/O certain/O there/O 's/O a/O strong/O guard/O around/O him/O ./O 
Lord/O Karstark/PERSON will/O want/O his/O head/O on/O a/O pike/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O he/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Greatjon/LOCATION agreed/O ,/O gesturing/O ./O 
Lannister/PERSON was/O led/O away/O to/O be/O bandaged/O and/O chained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O should/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON want/O him/O dead/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON looked/O away/O into/O the/O woods/O ,/O with/O the/O same/O brooding/O look/O that/O Ned/PERSON often/O got/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O .../O he/O killed/O them/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON 's/O sons/O ,/O \/O ''/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON explained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Both/O of/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Torrhen/O and/O Eddard/O ./O 
And/O Daryn/PERSON Hornwood/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O can/O fault/O Lannister/O on/O his/O courage/O ,/O \/O ''/O Glover/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O he/O saw/O that/O he/O was/O lost/O ,/O he/O rallied/O his/O retainers/O and/O fought/O his/O way/O up/O the/O valley/O ,/O hoping/O to/O reach/O Lord/O Robb/PERSON and/O cut/O him/O down/O ./O 
And/O almost/O did/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O mislaid/O his/O sword/O in/O Eddard/PERSON Karstark/PERSON 's/O neck/O ,/O after/O he/O took/O Torrhen/PERSON 's/O hand/O off/O and/O split/O Daryn/PERSON Hornwood/PERSON 's/O skull/O open/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O the/O time/O he/O was/O shouting/O for/O me/O ./O 
If/O they/O had/O n't/O tried/O to/O stop/O him/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O I/O should/O then/O be/O mourning/O in/O place/O of/O Lord/O Karstark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O men/O did/O what/O they/O were/O sworn/O to/O do/O ,/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
They/O died/O protecting/O their/O liege/O lord/O ./O 
Grieve/PERSON for/O them/O ./O 
Honor/O them/O for/O their/O valor/O ./O 
But/O not/O now/O ./O 
You/O have/O no/O time/O for/O grief/O ./O 
You/O may/O have/O lopped/O the/O head/O off/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O snake/O ,/O but/O three/O quarters/O of/O the/O body/O is/O still/O coiled/O around/O my/O father/O 's/O castle/O ./O 
We/O have/O won/O a/O battle/O ,/O not/O a/O war/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O such/O a/O battle/O !/O 
\/O ''/O said/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON eagerly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O the/O realm/O has/O not/O seen/O such/O a/O victory/O since/O the/O Field/O of/O Fire/O ./O 
I/O vow/O ,/O the/O Lannisters/PERSON lost/O ten/O men/O for/O every/O one/O of/O ours/O that/O fell/O ./O 
We/O 've/O taken/O close/O to/O a/O hundred/O knights/O captive/O ,/O and/O a/O dozen/O lords/O bannermen/O ./O 
Lord/O Westerling/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Bane/PERSON fort/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Garth/PERSON Greenfield/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Estren/PERSON ,/O Ser/O Tytos/O Brax/O ,/O Mallor/O the/O Dornishman/O .../O and/O three/O Lannisters/O besides/O Jaime/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O own/O nephews/O ,/O two/O of/O his/O sister/O 's/O sons/O and/O one/O of/O his/O dead/O brother/O 's/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON interrupted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O perchance/O taken/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ,/O Theon/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Greyjoy/PERSON answered/O ,/O brought/O up/O short/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Until/O you/O do/O ,/O this/O war/O is/O far/O from/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON raised/O his/O head/O and/O pushed/O his/O hair/O back/O out/O of/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O mother/O is/O right/O ./O 
We/O still/O have/O Riverrun/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
