-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O straw/O on/O the/O floor/O stank/O of/O urine/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O window/O ,/O no/O bed/O ,/O not/O even/O a/O slop/O bucket/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O walls/O of/O pale/O red/O stone/O festooned/O with/O patches/O of/O nitre/O ,/O a/O grey/O door/O of/O splintered/O wood/O ,/O four/O inches/O thick/O and/O studded/O with/O iron/O ./O 
He/O had/O seen/O them/O ,/O briefly/O ,/O a/O quick/O glimpse/O as/O they/O shoved/O him/O inside/O ./O 
Once/O the/O door/O had/O slammed/O shut/O ,/O he/O had/O seen/O no/O more/O ./O 
The/O dark/O was/O absolute/O ./O 
He/O had/O as/O well/O been/O blind/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Or/O dead/O ./O 
Buried/O with/O his/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O as/O his/O groping/O hand/O touched/O a/O cold/O stone/O wall/O ,/O his/O leg/O throbbing/O with/O every/O motion/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O the/O jest/O the/O king/O had/O shared/O in/O the/O crypts/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O as/O the/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O looked/O on/O with/O cold/O stone/O eyes/O ./O 
The/O king/O eats/O ,/O Robert/PERSON had/O said/O ,/O and/O the/O Hand/O takes/O the/O shit/O ./O 
How/O he/O had/O laughed/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O had/O gotten/O it/O wrong/O ./O 
The/O king/O dies/O ,/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON thought/O ,/O and/O the/O Hand/O is/O buried/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dungeon/O was/O under/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O deeper/O than/O he/O dared/O imagine/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O the/O old/O stories/O about/O Maegor/PERSON the/PERSON Cruel/PERSON ,/O who/O murdered/O all/O the/O masons/O who/O labored/O on/O his/O castle/O ,/O so/O they/O might/O never/O reveal/O its/O secrets/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O damned/O them/O all/O :/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O Janos/PERSON Slynt/PERSON and/O his/O gold/O cloaks/O ,/O the/O queen/O ,/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O Pycelle/LOCATION and/O Varys/O and/O Ser/O Barristan/O ,/O even/O Lord/O Renly/O ,/O Robert/PERSON 's/O own/O blood/O ,/O who/O had/O run/O when/O he/O was/O needed/O most/O ./O 
Yet/O in/O the/O end/O he/O blamed/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O cried/O to/O the/O darkness/O ,/O \/O ``/O thrice/O -/O damned/O blind/O fool/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Cersei/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O face/O seemed/O to/O float/O before/O him/O in/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
Her/O hair/O was/O full/O of/O sunlight/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O mockery/O in/O her/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O you/O play/O the/O game/O of/O thrones/O ,/O you/O win/O or/O you/O die/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON had/O played/O and/O lost/O ,/O and/O his/O men/O had/O paid/O the/O price/O of/O his/O folly/O with/O their/O life/O 's/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O thought/O of/O his/O daughters/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O wept/O gladly/O ,/O but/O the/O tears/O would/O not/O come/O ./O 
Even/O now/O ,/O he/O was/O a/O Stark/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O his/O grief/O and/O his/O rage/O froze/O hard/O inside/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O kept/O very/O still/O ,/O his/O leg/O did/O not/O hurt/O so/O much/O ,/O so/O he/O did/O his/O best/O to/O lie/O unmoving/O ./O 
For/O how/O long/O he/O could/O not/O say/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O sun/O and/O no/O moon/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O see/O to/O mark/O the/O walls/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON closed/O his/O eyes/O and/O opened/O them/O ;/O it/O made/O no/O difference/O ./O 
He/O slept/O and/O woke/O and/O slept/O again/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O know/O which/O was/O more/O painful/O ,/O the/O waking/O or/O the/O sleeping/O ./O 
When/O he/O slept/O ,/O he/O dreamed/O :/O dark/O disturbing/O dreams/O of/O blood/O and/O broken/O promises/O ./O 
When/O he/O woke/O ,/O there/O was/O nothing/O to/O do/O but/O think/O ,/O and/O his/O waking/O thoughts/O were/O worse/O than/O nightmares/O ./O 
The/O thought/O of/O Cat/O was/O as/O painful/O as/O a/O bed/O of/O nettles/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O where/O she/O was/O ,/O what/O she/O was/O doing/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O whether/O he/O would/O ever/O see/O her/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hours/O turned/O to/O days/O ,/O or/O so/O it/O seemed/O ./O 
He/O could/O feel/O a/O dull/O ache/O in/O his/O shattered/O leg/O ,/O an/O itch/O beneath/O the/O plaster/O ./O 
When/O he/O touched/O his/O thigh/O ,/O the/O flesh/O was/O hot/O to/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O only/O sound/O was/O his/O breathing/O ./O 
After/O a/O time/O ,/O he/O began/O to/O talk/O aloud/O ,/O just/O to/O hear/O a/O voice/O ./O 
He/O made/O plans/O to/O keep/O himself/O sane/O ,/O built/O castles/O of/O hope/O in/O the/O dark/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON 's/O brothers/O were/O out/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O raising/O armies/O at/O Dragonstone/LOCATION and/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ./O 
Alyn/PERSON and/O Harwin/PERSON would/O return/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O with/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O household/O guard/O once/O they/O had/O dealt/O with/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON would/O ''/O ,/O ``/O raise/O the/O north/O when/O the/O word/O reached/O her/O ,/O and/O the/O lords/O of/O river/O and/O mountain/O and/O Vale/PERSON would/O join/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O found/O himself/O thinking/O of/O Robert/PERSON more/O and/O more/O ./O 
He/O saw/O the/O king/O as/O he/O had/O been/O in/O the/O flower/O of/O his/O youth/O ,/O tall/O and/O handsome/O ,/O his/O great/O antlered/O helm/O on/O his/O head/O ,/O his/O warhammer/O in/O hand/O ,/O sitting/O his/O horse/O like/O a/O horned/O god/O ./O 
He/O heard/O his/O laughter/O in/O the/O dark/O ,/O saw/O his/O eyes/O ,/O blue/O and/O clear/O as/O mountain/O lakes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O at/O us/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robert/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O how/O did/O we/O come/O to/O this/O ?/O 
You/O here/O ,/O and/O me/O killed/O by/O a/O pig/O ./O 
We/O won/O a/O throne/O together/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O I/O failed/O you/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O Ned/PERSON thought/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O say/O the/O words/O ./O 
I/O lied/O to/O you/O ,/O hid/O the/O truth/O ./O 
I/O let/O them/O kill/O you/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O king/O heard/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O stiff-necked/O fool/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O muttered/O ,/O \/O ``/O too/O proud/O to/O listen/O ./O 
Can/O you/O eat/O pride/O ,/O Stark/O ?/O 
Will/O honor/O shield/O your/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Cracks/O ran/O down/O his/O face/O ,/O fissures/O opening/O in/O the/O flesh/O ,/O and/O he/O reached/O up/O and/O ripped/O the/O mask/O away/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O Robert/PERSON at/O all/O ;/O it/O was/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O grinning/O ,/O mocking/O him/O ./O 
When/O he/O opened/O his/O mouth/O to/O speak/O ,/O his/O lies/O turned/O to/O pale/O grey/O moths/O and/O took/O wing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON was/O half-asleep/O when/O the/O footsteps/O came/O down/O the/O hall/O ./O 
At/O first/O he/O thought/O he/O dreamt/O them/O ;/O it/O had/O been/O so/O long/O since/O he/O had/O heard/O anything/O but/O the/O sound/O of/O his/O own/O voice/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON was/O feverish/O by/O then/O ,/O his/O leg/O a/O dull/O agony/O ,/O his/O lips/O parched/O and/O cracked/O ./O 
When/O the/O heavy/O wooden/O door/O creaked/O open/O ,/O the/O sudden/O light/O was/O painful/O to/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O gaoler/O thrust/O a/O jug/O at/O him/O ./O 
The/O clay/O was/O cool/O and/O beaded/O with/O moisture/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON grasped/O it/O with/O both/O hands/O and/O gulped/O eagerly/O ./O 
Water/O ran/O from/O his/O mouth/O and/O dripped/O down/O through/O his/O beard/O ./O 
He/O drank/O until/O he/O thought/O he/O would/O be/O sick/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O long/O ./O 
./O 
?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O weakly/O when/O he/O could/O drink/O no/O more/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O gaoler/O was/O a/O scarecrow/O of/O a/O man/O with/O a/O rat/O 's/O face/O and/O frayed/O beard/O ,/O clad/O in/O a/O mail/O shirt/O and/O a/O leather/O half/O cape/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O talking/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O wrenched/O the/O jug/O from/O Ned/PERSON 's/O hands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O my/O daughters/O .../O \/O ''/O The/O door/O crashed/O shut/O ./O 
He/O blinked/O as/O the/O light/O vanished/O ,/O lowered/O his/O head/O to/O his/O chest/O ,/O and/O curled/O up/O on/O the/O straw/O ./O 
It/O no/O longer/O stank/O of/O urine/O and/O shit/O ./O 
It/O no/O longer/O smelled/O at/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O could/O no/O longer/O tell/O the/O difference/O between/O waking/O and/O sleeping/O ./O 
The/O memory/O came/O creeping/O upon/O him/O in/O the/O darkness/O ,/O as/O vivid/O as/O a/O dream/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O year/O of/O false/O spring/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O eighteen/O again/O ,/O down/O from/O the/O Eyrie/O to/O the/O tourney/O at/O Harrenhal/LOCATION ./O 
He/O could/O see/O the/O deep/O green/O of/O the/O grass/O ,/O and/O smell/O the/O pollen/O on/O the/O wind/O ./O 
Warm/O days/O and/O cool/O nights/O and/O the/O sweet/O taste/O of/O wine/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O Brandon/PERSON 's/O laughter/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON 's/O berserk/O valor/O in/O the/O melee/O ,/O the/O way/O he/O laughed/O as/O he/O unhorsed/O men/O left/O and/O right/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O a/O golden/O youth/O in/O scaled/O white/O armor/O ,/O kneeling/O on/O the/O grass/O in/O front/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O pavilion/O and/O making/O his/O vows/O to/O protect/O and/O defend/O King/O Aerys/O ./O 
Afterward/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Oswell/PERSON Whent/PERSON helped/O Jaime/PERSON to/O his/O feet/O ,/O and/O the/O White/O Bull/O himself/O ,/O Lord/O Commander/O Ser/PERSON Gerold/PERSON Hightower/PERSON ,/O fastened/O the/O snowy/O cloak/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O about/O his/O shoulders/O ./O 
All/O six/O White/O Swords/O were/O there/O to/O welcome/O their/O newest/O brother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O when/O the/O jousting/O began/O ,/O the/O day/O belonged/O to/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON ./O 
The/O crown/O prince/O wore/O the/O armor/O he/O would/O die/O in/O :/O gleaming/O black/O plate/O with/O the/O three-headed/O dragon/O of/O his/O House/O ''/O ,/O ``/O wrought/O in/O rubies/O on/O the/O breast/O ./O 
A/O plume/O of/O scarlet/O silk/O streamed/O behind/O him/O when/O he/O rode/O ,/O and/O it/O seemed/O no/O lance/O could/O touch/O him/O ./O 
Brandon/PERSON fell/O to/O him/O ,/O and/O Bronze/PERSON Yohn/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O and/O even/O the/O splendid/O Ser/PERSON Arthur/PERSON Dayne/PERSON ,/O the/O Sword/O of/O the/O Morning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON had/O been/O jesting/O with/O Jon/PERSON and/O old/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON as/O the/O prince/O circled/O the/O field/O after/O unhorsing/O Ser/O Barristan/O in/O the/O final/O tilt/O to/O claim/O the/O champion/O 's/O crown/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON remembered/O the/O moment/O when/O all/O the/O smiles/O died/O ,/O when/O Prince/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON urged/O his/O horse/O past/O his/O own/O wife/O ,/O the/O Dornish/O princess/O Elia/PERSON Martell/PERSON ,/O to/O lay/O the/O queen/O of/O beauty/O 's/O laurel/O in/O Lyanna/PERSON 's/O lap/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O it/O still/O :/O a/O crown/O of/O winter/O roses/O ,/O blue/O as/O frost/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON reached/O out/O his/O hand/O to/O grasp/O the/O flowery/O crown/O ,/O but/O beneath/O the/O pale/O blue/O petals/O the/O thorns/O lay/O hidden/O ./O 
He/O felt/O them/O clawing/O at/O his/O skin/O ,/O sharp/O and/O cruel/O ,/O saw/O the/O slow/O trickle/O of/O blood/O run/O down/O his/O fingers/O ,/O and/O woke/O ,/O trembling/O ,/O in/O the/O dark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Promise/O me/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O his/O sister/O had/O whispered/O from/O her/O bed/O of/O blood/O ./O 
She/O had/O loved/O the/O scent/O of/O winter/O roses/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O save/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON wept/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O going/O mad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O gods/O did/O not/O deign/O to/O answer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Each/O time/O the/O turnkey/O brought/O him/O water/O ,/O he/O told/O himself/O another/O day/O had/O passed/O ./O 
At/O first/O he/O would/O beg/O the/O man/O for/O some/O word/O of/O his/O daughters/O and/O the/O world/O beyond/O his/O cell/O ./O 
Grunts/O and/O kicks/O were/O his/O only/O replies/O ./O 
Later/O ,/O when/O the/O stomach/O cramps/O began/O ,/O he/O begged/O for/O food/O instead/O ./O 
It/O made/O no/O matter/O ;/O he/O was/O not/O fed/O ./O 
Perhaps/O the/O Lannisters/O meant/O for/O him/O to/O starve/O to/O death/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O himself/O ./O 
If/O Cersei/PERSON had/O wanted/O him/O dead/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O been/O cut/O down/O in/O the/O throne/O room/O with/O his/O men/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O him/O alive/O ./O 
Weak/O ,/O desperate/O ,/O yet/O alive/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON held/O her/O brother/O ;/O she/O dare/O not/O kill/O him/O or/O the/O Imp/PERSON 's/O life/O would/O be/O forfeit/O as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O outside/O his/O cell/O came/O the/O rattle/O of/O iron/O chains/O ./O 
As/O the/O door/O creaked/O open/O ,/O Ned/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O to/O the/O damp/O wall/O and/O pushed/O himself/O toward/O the/O light/O ./O 
The/O glare/O of/O a/O torch/O made/O him/O squint/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Food/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O croaked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wine/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O answered/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O the/O rat-faced/O man/O ;/O this/O gaoler/O was/O stouter/O ,/O shorter/O ,/O though/O he/O wore/O the/O same/O leather/O half/O cape/O and/O spiked/O steel/O cap/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O thrust/O a/O wineskin/O into/O Ned/PERSON 's/O hands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O voice/O was/O strangely/O familiar/O ,/O yet/O it/O took/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON a/O moment/O to/O place/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Varys/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O groggily/O when/O it/O came/O ./O 
He/O touched/O the/O man/O 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O .../O not/O dreaming/O this/O ./O 
You/O 're/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O 's/O plump/O cheeks/O were/O covered/O with/O a/O dark/O stubble/O of/O beard/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON felt/O the/O coarse/O hair/O with/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
Varys/PERSON had/O transformed/O himself/O into/O a/O grizzled/O turnkey/O ,/O reeking/O of/O sweat/O and/O sour/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O did/O you/O .../O what/O sort/O of/O magician/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O thirsty/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O hands/O fumbled/O at/O the/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O the/O same/O poison/O they/O gave/O Robert/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O wrong/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O sadly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Truly/O ,/O no/O one/O loves/O a/O eunuch/O ./O 
Give/O me/O the/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drank/O ,/O a/O trickle/O of/O red/O leaking/O from/O the/O corner/O of/O his/O plump/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O the/O equal/O of/O the/O vintage/O you/O offered/O me/O the/O night/O of/O the/O tourney/O ,/O but/O no/O more/O poisonous/O than/O most/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O concluded/O ,/O wiping/O his/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON tried/O a/O swallow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dregs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O felt/O as/O though/O he/O were/O about/O to/O bring/O the/O wine/O back/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O men/O must/O swallow/O the/O sour/O with/O the/O sweet/O ./O 
High/O lords/O and/O eunuchs/O alike/O ./O 
Your/O hour/O has/O come/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O daughters/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O younger/O girl/O escaped/O Ser/O Meryn/O and/O fled/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O been/O able/O to/O find/O her/O ./O 
Nor/O have/O the/O Lannisters/O ./O 
A/O kindness/O ,/O there/O ./O 
Our/O new/O king/O loves/O her/O not/O ./O 
Your/O older/O girl/O is/O still/O betrothed/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
Cersei/PERSON keeps/O her/O close/O ./O 
She/O came/O to/O court/O a/O few/O days/O ago/O to/O plead/O that/O you/O be/O spared/O ./O 
A/O pity/O you/O could/O n't/O have/O been/O there/O ,/O you/O would/O have/O been/O touched/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O leaned/O forward/O intently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O trust/O you/O realize/O that/O you/O are/O a/O dead/O man/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O queen/O will/O not/O kill/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
His/O head/O swam/O ;/O the/O wine/O was/O strong/O ,/O and/O it/O had/O been/O too/O long/O since/O he/O 'd/O eaten/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cat/O .../O Cat/O holds/O her/O brother/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O wrong/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O lost/O to/O her/O ,/O in/O any/O case/O ./O 
She/O let/O the/O Imp/O slip/O through/O her/O fingers/O ./O 
I/O expect/O he/O is/O dead/O by/O now/O ,/O somewhere/O in/O the/O Mountains/O of/O the/O Moon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O that/O is/O true/O ,/O slit/O my/O throat/O and/O have/O done/O with/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O dizzy/O from/O the/O wine/O ,/O tired/O and/O heartsick/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O blood/O is/O the/O last/O thing/O I/O desire/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O they/O slaughtered/O my/O guard/O ,/O you/O stood/O beside/O the/O queen/O and/O watched/O ,/O and/O said/O not/O a/O word/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O would/O again/O ./O 
I/O seem/O to/O recall/O that/O I/O was/O unarmed/O ,/O unarmored/O ,/O and/O surrounded/O by/O Lannister/O swords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O looked/O at/O him/O curiously/O ,/O tilting/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O was/O a/O young/O boy/O ,/O before/O I/O was/O cut/O ,/O I/O traveled/O with/O a/O troupe/O of/O mummers/O through/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
They/O taught/O me/O that/O each/O man/O has/O a/O role/O to/O play/O ,/O in/O life/O as/O well/O as/O mummery/O ./O 
So/O it/O is/O at/O court/O ./O 
The/O King/O 's/O Justice/O must/O be/O fearsome/O ,/O the/O master/O of/O coin/O must/O be/O frugal/O ,/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O must/O be/O valiant/O .../O and/O the/O master/O of/O whisperers/O must/O be/O sly/O and/O obsequious/O and/O without/O scruple/O ./O 
A/O courageous/O informer/O would/O be/O as/O useless/O as/O a/O cowardly/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O the/O wineskin/O back/O and/O drank/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON studied/O the/O eunuch/O 's/O face/O ,/O searching/O for/O truth/O beneath/O the/O mummer/O 's/O scars/O and/O false/O stubble/O ./O 
He/O tried/O some/O more/O wine/O ./O 
This/O time/O it/O went/O down/O easier/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O you/O free/O me/O from/O this/O pit/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O could/O .../O but/O will/O I/O ?/O 
No/O ./O 
Questions/O would/O be/O asked/O ,/O and/O the/O answers/O would/O lead/O back/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O expected/O no/O more/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O blunt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O eunuch/O has/O no/O honor/O ,/O and/O a/O spider/O does/O not/O enjoy/O the/O luxury/O of/O scruples/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O you/O at/O least/O consent/O to/O carry/O a/O message/O out/O for/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O would/O depend/O on/O the/O message/O ./O 
I/O will/O gladly/O provide/O you/O with/O paper/O and/O ink/O ,/O if/O you/O like/O ./O 
And/O when/O you/O have/O written/O what/O you/O will/O ,/O I/O will/O take/O the/O letter/O and/O read/O it/O ,/O and/O deliver/O it/O or/O not/O ,/O as/O best/O serves/O my/O own/O ends/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O own/O ends/O ./O 
What/O ends/O are/O those/O ,/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Peace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON replied/O without/O hesitation/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O there/O was/O one/O soul/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O who/O was/O truly/O desperate/O to/O keep/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON alive/O ,/O it/O was/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O fifteen/O years/O I/O protected/O him/O from/O his/O enemies/O ,/O but/O I/O could/O not/O protect/O him/O from/O his/O friends/O ./O 
What/O strange/O fit/O of/O madness/O led/O you/O to/O tell/O the/O queen/O that/O you/O had/O learned/O the/O truth/O of/O Joffrey/PERSON '/O s/O birth/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O madness/O of/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON admitted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Varys/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O To/O be/O sure/O ./O 
You/O are/O an/O honest/O and/O honorable/O man/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ./O 
Ofttimes/O I/O forget/O that/O ./O 
I/O have/O met/O so/O few/O of/O them/O in/O my/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O glanced/O around/O the/O cell/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O see/O what/O honesty/O and/O honor/O have/O won/O you/O ,/O I/O understand/O why/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O Stark/O laid/O his/O head/O back/O against/O the/O damp/O stone/O wall/O and/O closed/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
His/O leg/O was/O throbbing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O 's/O wine/O .../O did/O you/O question/O Lancel/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O indeed/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON gave/O him/O the/O wineskins/O ,/O and/O told/O him/O it/O was/O Robert/PERSON 's/O favorite/O vintage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O hunter/O lives/O a/O perilous/O life/O ./O 
If/O the/O boar/O had/O not/O done/O for/O Robert/PERSON ,/O it/O would/O have/O been/O a/O fall/O from/O a/O horse/O ,/O the/O bite/O of/O a/O wood/O adder/O ,/O an/O arrow/O gone/O astray/O .../O the/O forest/O is/O the/O abbatoir/O of/O the/O gods/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O wine/O that/O killed/O the/O king/O ./O 
It/O was/O your/O mercy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O feared/O as/O much/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O forgive/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O there/O are/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O expect/O they/O will/O ./O 
The/O queen/O would/O not/O have/O waited/O long/O in/O any/O case/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON was/O becoming/O unruly/O ,/O and/O she/O needed/O to/O be/O rid/O of/O him/O to/O free/O her/O hands/O to/O deal/O with/O his/O brothers/O ./O 
They/O are/O quite/O a/O pair/O ,/O Stannis/PERSON and/O Renly/O ./O 
The/O iron/O gauntlet/O and/O the/O silk/O glove/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O wiped/O his/O mouth/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O been/O foolish/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
You/O ought/O to/O have/O heeded/O Littlefinger/PERSON when/O he/O urged/O you/O to/O support/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O succession/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O .../O how/O could/O you/O know/O of/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O that/O need/O concern/O you/O ./O 
I/O also/O know/O that/O on/O the/O morrow/O the/O queen/O will/O pay/O you/O a/O visit/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Slowly/O Ned/PERSON raised/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cersei/O is/O frightened/O of/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O .../O but/O she/O has/O other/O enemies/O she/O fears/O even/O more/O ./O 
Her/O beloved/O Jaime/PERSON is/O fighting/O the/O river/O lords/O even/O now/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON sits/O in/O the/O Eyrie/O ,/O ringed/O in/O stone/O and/O steel/O ,/O and/O there/O is/O no/O love/O lost/O between/O her/O and/O the/O queen/O ./O 
In/O Dome/LOCATION ,/O the/O Martells/PERSON still/O brood/O on/O the/O murder/O of/O Princess/O Elia/PERSON and/O her/O babes/O ./O 
And/O now/O your/O son/O marches/O down/O the/O Neck/O with/O a/O northern/O host/O at/O his/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robb/PERSON is/O only/O a/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O aghast/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O boy/O with/O an/O army/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O only/O a/O boy/O ,/O as/O you/O say/O ./O 
The/O king/O 's/O brothers/O are/O the/O ones/O giving/O Cersei/PERSON sleepless/O nights/O .../O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON in/O particular/O ./O 
His/O claim/O is/O the/O true/O one/O ,/O he/O is/O known/O for/O his/O prowess/O as/O a/O battle/O commander/O ,/O and/O he/O is/O utterly/O without/O mercy/O ./O 
There/O is/O no/O creature/O on/O earth/O half/O so/O terrifying/O as/O a/O truly/O just/O man/O ./O 
No/O one/O knows/O what/O Stannis/PERSON has/O been/O doing/O on/O Dragonstone/O ,/O but/O I/O will/O wager/O you/O that/O he/O 's/O gathered/O more/O swords/O than/O seashells/O ./O 
So/O here/O is/O Cersei/PERSON '/O s/O nightmare/O :/O while/O her/O father/O and/O brother/O spend/O their/O power/O battling/O Starks/PERSON and/O Tullys/O ,/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON will/O land/O ,/O proclaim/O himself/O king/O ,/O and/O lop/O off/O her/O son/O 's/O curly/O blond/O head/O .../O and/O her/O own/O in/O the/O bargain/O ,/O though/O I/O truly/O believe/O she/O cares/O more/O about/O the/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stannis/O Baratheon/O is/O Robert/PERSON 's/O true/O heir/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O throne/O is/O his/O by/O rights/O ./O 
I/O would/O welcome/O his/O ascent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O tsked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cersei/O will/O not/O want/O to/O hear/O that/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O ./O 
Stannis/O may/O win/O the/O throne/O ,/O but/O only/O your/O rotting/O head/O will/O remain/O to/O cheer/O unless/O you/O guard/O that/O tongue/O of/O yours/O ./O 
Sansa/O begged/O so/O sweetly/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O a/O shame/O if/O you/O threw/O it/O all/O away/O ./O 
You/O are/O being/O given/O your/O life/O back/O ,/O if/O you/O 'll/O take/O it/O ./O 
Cersei/O is/O no/O fool/O ./O 
She/O knows/O a/O tame/O wolf/O is/O of/O more/O use/O than/O a/O dead/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O want/O me/O to/O serve/O the/O woman/O who/O murdered/O my/O king/O ,/O butchered/O my/O men/O ,/O and/O crippled/O my/O son/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON 's/O voice/O was/O thick/O with/O disbelief/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O you/O to/O serve/O the/O realm/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O the/O queen/O that/O you/O will/O confess/O your/O vile/O treason/O ,/O command/O your/O son/O to/O lay/O down/O his/O sword/O ,/O and/O proclaim/O Joffrey/PERSON as/O the/O true/O heir/O ./O 
Offer/O to/O denounce/O Stannis/O and/O Renly/PERSON as/O faithless/O usurpers/O ./O 
Our/O green-eyed/O lioness/O knows/O you/O are/O a/O man/O of/O honor/O ./O 
If/O you/O will/O give/O her/O the/O peace/O she/O needs/O and/O the/O time/O to/O deal/O with/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O and/O pledge/O to/O carry/O her/O secret/O to/O your/O grave/O ,/O I/O believe/O she/O will/O allow/O you/O to/O take/O the/O black/O and/O live/O out/O the/O rest/O of/O your/O days/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O with/O your/O brother/O and/O that/O baseborn/O son/O of/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O thought/O of/O Jon/PERSON filled/O Ned/PERSON with/O a/O sense/O of/O shame/O ,/O and/O a/O sorrow/O too/O deep/O for/O words/O ./O 
If/O only/O he/O could/O see/O the/O boy/O again/O ,/O sit/O and/O talk/O with/O him/O .../O pain/O shot/O through/O his/O broken/O leg/O ,/O beneath/O the/O filthy/O grey/O plaster/O of/O his/O cast/O ./O 
He/O winced/O ,/O his/O fingers/O opening/O and/O closing/O helplessly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O your/O own/O scheme/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O gasped/O out/O at/O Varys/LOCATION ,/O \/O ``/O or/O are/O you/O in/O league/O with/O Littlefinger/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O seemed/O to/O amuse/O the/O eunuch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O sooner/O wed/O the/O Black/O Goat/O of/O Qohor/O ./O 
Littlefinger/O is/O the/O second/O most/O devious/O man/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O I/O feed/O him/O choice/O whispers/O ,/O sufficient/O so/O that/O he/O thinks/O I/O am/O his/O .../O just/O as/O I/O allow/O Cersei/PERSON to/O believe/O I/O am/O hers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O just/O as/O you/O let/O me/O believe/O that/O you/O were/O mine/O ./O 
Tell/O me/O ,/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON ,/O who/O do/O you/O truly/O serve/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O smiled/O thinly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ,/O the/O realm/O ,/O my/O good/O lord/O ,/O how/O ever/O could/O you/O doubt/O that/O ?/O 
I/O swear/O it/O by/O my/O lost/O manhood/O ./O 
I/O serve/O the/O realm/O ,/O and/O the/O realm/O needs/O peace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O finished/O the/O last/O swallow/O of/O wine/O ,/O and/O tossed/O the/O empty/O skin/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O what/O is/O your/O answer/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ?/O 
Give/O me/O your/O word/O that/O you/O 'll/O tell/O the/O queen/O what/O she/O wants/O to/O hear/O when/O she/O comes/O calling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O I/O did/O ,/O my/O word/O would/O be/O as/O hollow/O as/O an/O empty/O suit/O of/O armor/O ./O 
My/O life/O is/O not/O so/O precious/O to/O me/O as/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pity/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O eunuch/O stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O your/O daughter/O 's/O life/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
How/O precious/O is/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O chill/O pierced/O Ned/PERSON 's/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O daughter/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Surely/O you/O did/O not/O think/O I/O 'd/O forgotten/O about/O your/O sweet/O innocent/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
The/O queen/O most/O certainly/O has/O not/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON pleaded/O ,/O his/O voice/O cracking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Varys/O ,/O gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O do/O as/O you/O like/O with/O me/O ,/O but/O leave/O my/O daughter/O out/O of/O your/O schemes/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON 's/O no/O more/O than/O a/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rhaenys/PERSON was/O a/O child/O too/O ./O 
Prince/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O daughter/O ./O 
A/O precious/O little/O thing/O ,/O younger/O than/O your/O girls/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O small/O black/O kitten/O she/O called/O Balerion/LOCATION ,/O did/O you/O know/O ?/O 
I/O always/O wondered/O what/O happened/O to/O him/O ./O 
Rhaenys/PERSON liked/O to/O pretend/O he/O was/O the/O true/O Balerion/LOCATION ,/O the/O Black/O Dread/O of/O old/O ,/O but/O I/O imagine/O the/O Lannisters/O taught/O her/O the/O difference/O between/O a/O kitten/O and/O a/O dragon/O quick/O enough/O ,/O the/O day/O they/O broke/O down/O her/O door/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Varys/PERSON gave/O a/O long/O weary/O sigh/O ,/O the/O sigh/O of/O a/O man/O who/O carried/O all/O the/O sadness/O of/O the/O world/O in/O a/O sack/O upon/O his/O shoulders/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O High/O Septon/O once/O told/O me/O that/O as/O we/O sin/O ,/O so/O do/O we/O suffer/O ./O 
If/O that/O 's/O true/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ,/O tell/O me/O .../O why/O is/O it/O always/O the/O innocents/O who/O suffer/O most/O ,/O when/O you/O high/O lords/O play/O your/O game/O of/O thrones/O ?/O 
Ponder/O it/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O ,/O while/O you/O wait/O upon/O the/O queen/O ./O 
And/O spare/O a/O thought/O for/O this/O as/O well/O :/O The/O next/O visitor/O who/O calls/O on/O you/O could/O bring/O you/O bread/O and/O cheese/O and/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O for/O your/O pain/O .../O or/O he/O could/O bring/O you/O Sansa/O 's/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O choice/O ,/O my/O dear/O lord/O Hand/O ,/O is/O entirely/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
