-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Othor/O ,/O \/O ''/O announced/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O beyond/O a/O doubt/O ./O 
And/O this/O one/O was/O Jafer/PERSON Flowers/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O the/O corpse/O over/O with/O his/O foot/O ,/O and/O the/O dead/O white/O face/O stared/O up/O at/O the/O overcast/O sky/O with/O blue/O ,/O blue/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O men/O ,/O both/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O My/O uncle/O 's/O men/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O numbly/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O how/O he/O 'd/O pleaded/O to/O ride/O with/O them/O ./O 
Gods/O ,/O I/O was/O such/O a/O green/O boy/O ./O 
If/O he/O had/O taken/O me/O ,/O it/O might/O be/O me/O lying/O here/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jafer/O 's/O right/O wrist/O ended/O in/O the/O ruin/O of/O torn/O flesh/O and/O splintered/O bone/O left/O by/O Ghost/O `/O sjaws/O ./O 
His/O right/O hand/O was/O floating/O in/O ajar/O of/O vinegar/O back/O in/O Maester/LOCATION Aemon/LOCATION 's/O tower/O ./O 
His/O left/O hand/O ,/O still/O at/O the/O end/O of/O his/O arm/O ,/O was/O as/O black/O as/O his/O cloak/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O have/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O muttered/O ./O 
He/O swung/O down/O from/O his/O garron/O ,/O handing/O his/O reins/O to/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
The/O morning/O was/O unnaturally/O warm/O ;/O beads/O of/O sweat/O dotted/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O broad/O forehead/O like/O dew/O on/O a/O melon/O ./O 
His/O horse/O was/O nervous/O ,/O rolling/O her/O eyes/O ,/O backing/O away/O from/O the/O dead/O men/O as/O far/O as/O her/O lead/O would/O allow/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON led/O her/O off/O a/O few/O paces/O ,/O fighting/O to/O keep/O her/O from/O bolting/O ./O 
The/O horses/O did/O not/O like/O the/O feel/O of/O this/O place/O ./O 
For/O that/O matter/O ,/O neither/O did/O Jon/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dogs/O liked/O it/O least/O of/O all/O ./O 
Ghost/O had/O led/O the/O party/O here/O ;/O the/O pack/O of/O hounds/O had/O been/O useless/O ./O 
When/O Bass/O the/O kennelmaster/O had/O tried/O to/O get/O them/O to/O take/O the/O scent/O from/O the/O severed/O hand/O ,/O they/O had/O gone/O wild/O ,/O yowling/O and/O barking/O ,/O fighting/O to/O get/O away/O ./O 
Even/O now/O they/O were/O snarling/O and/O whimpering/O by/O turns/O ,/O pulling/O at/O their/O leashes/O while/O Chett/PERSON cursed/O them/O for/O curs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O is/O only/O a/O wood/O ,/O Jon/PERSON told/O himself/O ,/O and/O they/O 're/O only/O dead/O men/O ./O 
He/O had/O seen/O dead/O men/O before/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Last/O night/O he/O had/O dreamt/O the/O Winterfell/O dream/O again/O ./O 
He/O was/O wandering/O the/O empty/O castle/O ,/O searching/O for/O his/O father/O ,/O descending/O into/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
Only/O this/O time/O the/O dream/O had/O gone/O further/O than/O before/O ./O 
In/O the/O dark/O he/O 'd/O heard/O the/O scrape/O of/O stone/O on/O stone/O ./O 
When/O he/O turned/O he/O saw/O that/O the/O vaults/O were/O opening/O ,/O one/O after/O the/O other/O ./O 
As/O the/O dead/O kings/O came/O stumbling/O from/O their/O cold/O black/O graves/O ,/O Jon/PERSON had/O woken/O in/O pitchdark/O ,/O his/O heart/O hammering/O ./O 
Even/O when/O Ghost/O leapt/O up/O on/O the/O bed/O to/O nuzzle/O at/O his/O face/O ,/O he/O could/O not/O shake/O his/O deep/O sense/O of/O terror/O ./O 
He/O dared/O not/O go/O back/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
Instead/O he/O had/O climbed/O the/O Wall/O and/O walked/O ,/O restless/O ,/O until/O he/O saw/O the/O light/O of/O the/O dawn/O off/O to/O the/O cast/O ./O 
It/O was/O only/O a/O dream/O ./O 
I/O am/O a/O brother/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O now/O ,/O not/O a/O frightened/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON huddled/O beneath/O the/O trees/O ,/O half-hidden/O behind/O the/O horses/O ./O 
His/O round/O fat/O face/O was/O the/O color/O of/O curdled/O milk/O ./O 
So/O far/O he/O had/O not/O lurched/O off/O to/O the/O woods/O to/O retch/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O not/O so/O much/O as/O glanced/O at/O the/O dead/O men/O either/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O look/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O miserably/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O to/O look/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O keeping/O his/O voice/O low/O so/O the/O others/O would/O not/O hear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON sent/O you/O to/O be/O his/O eyes/O ,/O did/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
What/O good/O are/O eyes/O if/O they/O 're/O shut/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O but/O .../O I/O 'm/O such/O a/O coward/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O on/O Sam/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O a/O dozen/O rangers/O with/O us/O ,/O and/O the/O dogs/O ,/O even/O Ghost/O ./O 
No/O one/O will/O hurt/O you/O ,/O Sam/PERSON ./O 
Go/O ahead/O and/O look/O ./O 
The/O first/O look/O is/O the/O hardest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON gave/O a/O tremulous/O nod/O ,/O working/O up/O his/O courage/O with/O a/O visible/O effort/O ./O 
Slowly/O he/O swiveled/O his/O head/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O widened/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON held/O his/O arm/O so/O he/O could/O not/O turn/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Jaremy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O asked/O gruffly/O ,/O \/O ``/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O six/O men/O with/O him/O when/O he/O rode/O from/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Where/O are/O the/O others/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jaremy/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O knew/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Plainly/O Mormont/O was/O not/O pleased/O with/O that/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Two/O of/O our/O brothers/O butchered/O almost/O within/O sight/O of/O the/O Wall/O ,/O yet/O your/O rangers/O heard/O nothing/O ,/O saw/O nothing/O ./O 
Is/O this/O what/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O has/O fallen/O to/O ?/O 
Do/O we/O still/O sweep/O these/O woods/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O we/O still/O mount/O watches/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O do/O ,/O but/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O man/O wears/O a/O hunting/O horn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON pointed/O at/O Othor/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Must/O I/O suppose/O that/O he/O died/O without/O sounding/O it/O ?/O 
Or/O have/O your/O rangers/O all/O gone/O deaf/O as/O well/O as/O blind/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jaremy/O bristled/O ,/O his/O face/O taut/O with/O anger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O horn/O was/O blown/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O or/O my/O rangers/O would/O have/O heard/O it/O ./O 
I/O do/O not/O have/O sufficient/O men/O to/O mount/O as/O many/O patrols/O as/O I/O should/O like/O .../O and/O since/O Benjen/PERSON was/O lost/O ,/O we/O have/O stayed/O closer/O to/O the/O Wall/O than/O we/O were/O wont/O to/O do/O before/O ,/O by/O your/O own/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O grunted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Well/O ./O 
Be/O that/O as/O it/O may/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O made/O an/O impatient/O gesture/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O how/O they/O died/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Squatting/O beside/O the/O dead/O man/O he/O had/O named/O Jafer/PERSON Flowers/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON grasped/O his/O head/O by/O the/O scalp/O ./O 
The/O hair/O came/O out/O between/O his/O fingers/O ,/O brittle/O as/O straw/O ./O 
The/O knight/O cursed/O and/O shoved/O at/O the/O face/O with/O the/O heel/O of/O his/O hand/O ./O 
A/O great/O gash/O in/O the/O side/O of/O the/O corpse/O 's/O neck/O opened/O like/O a/O mouth/O ,/O crusted/O with/O dried/O blood/O ./O 
Only/O a/O few/O ropes/O of/O pale/O tendon/O still/O attached/O the/O head/O to/O the/O neck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O was/O done/O with/O an/O axe/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aye/O ,/O \/O ''/O muttered/O Dywen/PERSON ,/O the/O old/O forester/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Belike/O the/O axe/O that/O Othor/O carried/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON could/O feel/O his/O breakfast/O churning/O in/O his/O belly/O ,/O but/O he/O pressed/O his/O lips/O together/O and/O made/O himself/O look/O at/O the/O second/O body/O ./O 
Othor/PERSON had/O been/O a/O big/O ugly/O man/O ,/O and/O he/O made/O a/O big/O ugly/O corpse/O ./O 
No/O axe/O was/O in/O evidence/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON remembered/O Othor/O ;/O he/O had/O been/O the/O one/O bellowing/O the/O bawdy/O song/O as/O the/O rangers/O rode/O out/O ./O 
His/O singing/O days/O were/O done/O ./O 
His/O flesh/O was/O blanched/O white/O as/O milk/O ,/O everywhere/O but/O his/O hands/O ./O 
His/O hands/O were/O black/O like/O Jafer/PERSON 's/O ./O 
Blossoms/O of/O hard/O cracked/O blood/O decorated/O the/O mortal/O wounds/O that/O covered/O him/O like/O a/O rash/O ,/O breast/O and/O groin/O and/O throat/O ./O 
Yet/O his/O eyes/O were/O still/O open/O ./O 
They/O stared/O up/O at/O the/O sky/O ,/O blue/O as/O sapphires/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Jaremy/O stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wildlings/O have/O axes/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/O rounded/O on/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O you/O believe/O this/O is/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON 's/O work/O ?/O 
This/O close/O to/O the/O Wall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O else/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON could/O have/O told/O him/O ./O 
He/O knew/O ,/O they/O all/O knew/O ,/O yet/O no/O man/O of/O them/O would/O say/O the/O words/O ./O 
The/O Others/O are/O only/O a/O story/O ,/O a/O tale/O to/O make/O children/O shiver/O ./O 
If/O they/O ever/O lived/O at/O all/O ,/O they/O are/O gone/O eight/O thousand/O years/O ./O 
Even/O the/O thought/O made/O him/O feel/O foolish/O ;/O he/O was/O a/O man/O grown/O now/O ,/O a/O black/O brother/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O not/O the/O boy/O who/O 'd/O once/O sat/O at/O Old/LOCATION Nan/LOCATION 's/O feet/O with/O Bran/O and/O Robb/PERSON and/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON gave/O a/O snort/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O come/O under/O wildling/O attack/O a/O half/O day/O 's/O ride/O from/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION ,/O he/O would/O have/O returned/O for/O more/O men/O ,/O chased/O the/O killers/O through/O all/O seven/O hells/O and/O brought/O me/O back/O their/O heads/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Unless/O he/O was/O slain/O as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON insisted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O words/O hurt/O ,/O even/O now/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O so/O long/O ,/O it/O seemed/O folly/O to/O cling/O to/O the/O hope/O that/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON was/O still/O alive/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON was/O nothing/O if/O not/O stubborn/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O has/O been/O close/O on/O half/O a/O year/O since/O Benjen/PERSON left/O us/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/O Jaremy/O went/O on/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O forest/O is/O vast/O ./O 
The/O wildlings/O might/O have/O fallen/O on/O him/O anywhere/O ./O 
I/O 'd/O wager/O these/O two/O were/O the/O last/O survivors/O of/O his/O party/O ,/O on/O their/O way/O back/O to/O us/O .../O but/O the/O enemy/O caught/O them/O before/O they/O could/O reach/O the/O safety/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
The/O corpses/O are/O still/O fresh/O ,/O these/O men/O can/O not/O have/O been/O dead/O more/O than/O a/O day/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON squeaked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O startled/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON 's/O nervous/O ,/O high-pitched/O voice/O was/O the/O last/O he/O would/O have/O expected/O to/O hear/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O was/O frightened/O of/O the/O officers/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON was/O not/O known/O for/O his/O patience/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O not/O ask/O for/O your/O views/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rykker/PERSON said/O coldly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O him/O speak/O ,/O ser/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON blurted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/O 's/O eyes/O flicked/O from/O Sam/PERSON to/O Jon/PERSON and/O back/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O lad/O has/O something/O to/O say/O ,/O I/O 'll/O hear/O him/O out/O ./O 
Come/O closer/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
We/O ca/O n't/O see/O you/O behind/O those/O horses/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON edged/O past/O Jon/PERSON and/O the/O garrons/O ,/O sweating/O profusely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O it/O .../O it/O ca/O n't/O be/O a/O day/O or/O .../O look/O .../O the/O blood/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON growled/O impatiently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O ,/O what/O of/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O soils/O his/O smallclothes/O at/O the/O sight/O of/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Chett/PERSON shouted/O out/O ,/O and/O the/O rangers/O laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON mopped/O at/O the/O sweat/O on/O his/O brow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O .../O you/O can/O see/O where/O Ghost/O .../O Jon/PERSON 's/O direwolf/O .../O you/O can/O see/O where/O he/O tore/O off/O that/O man/O 's/O hand/O ,/O and/O yet/O .../O the/O stump/O has/O n't/O bled/O ,/O look/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O waved/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O .../O L-lord/O Randyll/O ,/O he/O ,/O he/O made/O me/O watch/O him/O dress/O animals/O sometimes/O ,/O when/O .../O after/O .../O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O from/O side/O to/O side/O ,/O his/O chins/O quivering/O ./O 
Now/O that/O he/O had/O looked/O at/O the/O bodies/O ,/O he/O could/O not/O seem/O to/O look/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O fresh/O kill/O .../O the/O blood/O would/O still/O flow/O ,/O my/O lords/O ./O 
Later/O .../O later/O it/O would/O be/O clotted/O ,/O like/O a./O ./O 
./O 
a/O jelly/O ,/O thick/O and/O .../O and/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O was/O going/O to/O be/O sick/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O man/O .../O look/O at/O the/O wrist/O ,/O it/O 's/O all/O .../O crusty/O .../O dry/O .../O like/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON saw/O at/O once/O what/O Sam/PERSON meant/O ./O 
He/O could/O see/O the/O torn/O veins/O in/O the/O dead/O man/O 's/O wrist/O ,/O iron/O worms/O in/O the/O pale/O flesh/O ./O 
His/O blood/O was/O a/O black/O dust/O ./O 
Yet/O Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON was/O unconvinced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O they/O 'd/O been/O dead/O much/O longer/O than/O a/O day/O ,/O they/O 'd/O be/O ripe/O by/O now/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O even/O smell/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dywen/O ,/O the/O gnarled/O old/O forester/O who/O liked/O to/O boast/O that/O he/O could/O smell/O snow/O coming/O on/O ,/O sidled/O closer/O to/O the/O corpses/O and/O took/O a/O whiff/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O they/O 're/O no/O pansy/O flowers/O ,/O but/O .../O m/O `/O lord/O has/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ./O 
There/O 's/O no/O corpse/O stink/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O .../O they/O are/O n't/O rotting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON pointed/O ,/O his/O fat/O finger/O shaking/O only/O a/O little/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O ,/O there/O 's/O .../O there/O 's/O no/O maggots/O or/O .../O or/O .../O worms/O or/O anything/O .../O they/O 've/O been/O lying/O here/O in/O the/O woods/O ,/O but/O they/O .../O they/O have/O n't/O been/O chewed/O or/O eaten/O by/O animals/O .../O only/O Ghost/O .../O otherwise/O they/O 're/O .../O they/O 're/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Untouched/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Ghost/O is/O different/O ./O 
The/O dogs/O and/O the/O horses/O wo/O n't/O go/O near/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O rangers/O exchanged/O glances/O ;/O they/O could/O see/O it/O was/O true/O ,/O every/O man/O of/O them/O ./O 
Mormont/O frowned/O ,/O glancing/O from/O the/O corpses/O to/O the/O dogs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Chett/O ,/O bring/O the/O hounds/O closer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chett/O tried/O ,/O cursing/O ,/O yanking/O on/O the/O leashes/O ,/O giving/O one/O animal/O a/O lick/O of/O his/O boot/O ./O 
Most/O of/O the/O dogs/O just/O whimpered/O and/O planted/O their/O feet/O ./O 
He/O tried/O dragging/O one/O ./O 
The/O bitch/O resisted/O ,/O growling/O and/O squirming/O as/O if/O to/O escape/O her/O collar/O ./O 
Finally/O she/O lunged/O at/O him/O ./O 
Chett/PERSON dropped/O the/O leash/O and/O stumbled/O backward/O ./O 
The/O dog/O leapt/O over/O him/O and/O bounded/O off/O into/O the/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O .../O this/O is/O all/O wrong/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON Tarly/PERSON said/O earnestly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O blood/O .../O there/O 's/O bloodstains/O on/O their/O clothes/O ,/O and/O .../O and/O their/O flesh/O ,/O dry/O and/O hard/O ,/O but/O .../O there/O 's/O none/O on/O the/O ground/O ,/O or/O .../O anywhere/O ./O 
With/O those/O .../O those/O .../O those/O .../O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON made/O himself/O swallow/O ,/O took/O a/O deep/O breath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O those/O wounds/O .../O terrible/O wounds/O .../O there/O should/O be/O blood/O all/O over/O ./O 
Should/O n't/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dywen/PERSON sucked/O at/O his/O wooden/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Might/O be/O they/O did/O n't/O die/O here/O ./O 
Might/O be/O someone/O brought/O `/O ern/O and/O left/O `/O ern/O for/O us/O ./O 
A/O warning/O ,/O as/O like/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O old/O forester/O peered/O down/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O might/O be/O I/O 'm/O a/O fool/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O that/O Othor/O never/O had/O no/O blue/O eyes/O afore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jaremy/O looked/O startled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Neither/O did/O Flowers/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O blurted/O ,/O turning/O to/O stare/O at/O the/O dead/O man/O ./O 
A/O silence/O fell/O over/O the/O wood/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O all/O they/O heard/O was/O Sam/PERSON 's/O heavy/O breathing/O and/O the/O wet/O sound/O of/O Dywen/O sucking/O on/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON squatted/O beside/O Ghost/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Burn/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O someone/O whispered/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O rangers/O ;/O Jon/PERSON could/O not/O have/O said/O who/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O burn/O them/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O second/O voice/O urged/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O gave/O a/O stubborn/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O yet/O ./O 
I/O want/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON to/O have/O a/O look/O at/O them/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O bring/O them/O back/O to/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Some/O commands/O are/O more/O easily/O given/O than/O obeyed/O ./O 
They/O wrapped/O the/O dead/O men/O in/O cloaks/O ,/O but/O when/O Hake/PERSON and/O Dywen/PERSON tried/O to/O tie/O one/O onto/O a/O horse/O ,/O the/O animal/O went/O mad/O ,/O screaming/O and/O rearing/O ,/O lashing/O out/O with/O its/O hooves/O ,/O even/O biting/O at/O Ketter/PERSON when/O he/O ran/O to/O help/O ./O 
The/O rangers/O had/O no/O better/O luck/O with/O the/O other/O garrons/O ;/O not/O even/O the/O most/O placid/O wanted/O any/O part/O of/O these/O burdens/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O they/O were/O forced/O to/O hack/O off/O branches/O and/O fashion/O crude/O slings/O to/O carry/O the/O corpses/O back/O on/O foot/O ./O 
It/O was/O well/O past/O midday/O by/O the/O time/O they/O started/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O have/O these/O woods/O searched/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON commanded/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON as/O they/O set/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Every/O tree/O ,/O every/O rock/O ,/O every/O bush/O ,/O and/O every/O foot/O of/O muddy/O ground/O within/O ten/O leagues/O of/O here/O ./O 
Use/O all/O the/O men/O you/O have/O ,/O and/O if/O you/O do/O not/O have/O enough/O ,/O borrow/O hunters/O and/O foresters/O from/O the/O stewards/O ./O 
If/O Ben/PERSON and/O the/O others/O are/O out/O here/O ,/O dead/O or/O alive/O ,/O I/O will/O have/O them/O found/O ./O 
And/O if/O there/O is/O anyone/O else/O in/O these/O woods/O ,/O I/O will/O know/O of/O it/O ./O 
You/O are/O to/O track/O them/O and/O take/O them/O ,/O alive/O if/O possible/O ./O 
Is/O that/O understood/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O done/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O After/O that/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON rode/O in/O silence/O ,/O brooding/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON followed/O close/O behind/O him/O ;/O as/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O steward/O ,/O that/O was/O his/O place/O ./O 
The/O day/O was/O grey/O ,/O damp/O ,/O overcast/O ,/O the/O sort/O of/O day/O that/O made/O you/O wish/O for/O rain/O ./O 
No/O wind/O stirred/O the/O wood/O ;/O the/O air/O hung/O humid/O and/O heavy/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON 's/O clothes/O clung/O to/O his/O skin/O ./O 
It/O was/O warm/O ./O 
Too/O warm/O ./O 
The/O Wall/O was/O weeping/O copiously/O ,/O had/O been/O weeping/O for/O days/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O Jon/PERSON even/O imagined/O it/O was/O shrinking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O men/O called/O this/O weather/O spirit/O summer/O ,/O and/O said/O it/O meant/O the/O season/O was/O giving/O up/O its/O ghosts/O at/O last/O ./O 
After/O this/O the/O cold/O would/O come/O ,/O they/O warned/O ,/O and/O a/O long/O summer/O always/O meant/O a/O long/O winter/O ./O 
This/O summer/O had/O lasted/O ten/O years/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O been/O a/O babe/O in/O arms/O when/O it/O began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O ran/O with/O them/O for/O a/O time/O and/O then/O vanished/O among/O the/O trees/O ./O 
Without/O the/O direwolf/O ,/O Jon/PERSON felt/O almost/O naked/O ./O 
He/O found/O himself/O glancing/O at/O every/O shadow/O with/O unease/O ./O 
Unbidden/O ,/O he/O thought/O back/O on/O the/O tales/O that/O Old/O Nan/PERSON used/O to/O tell/O them/O ,/O when/O he/O was/O a/O boy/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
He/O could/O almost/O hear/O her/O voice/O again/O ,/O and/O the/O click-click-click/O of/O her/O needles/O ./O 
In/O that/O darkness/O ,/O the/O Others/O came/O riding/O ,/O she/O used/O to/O say/O ,/O dropping/O her/O voice/O lower/O and/O lower/O ./O 
Cold/O and/O dead/O they/O were/O ,/O and/O they/O hated/O iron/O and/O fire/O and/O the/O touch/O of/O the/O sun/O ,/O and/O every/O living/O creature/O with/O hot/O blood/O in/O its/O veins/O ./O 
Holdfasts/O and/O cities/O and/O kingdoms/O of/O men/O allfell/O before/O them/O ,/O as/O they/O moved/O south/O on/O pale/O dead/O horses/O ,/O leading/O hosts/O of/O the/O slain/O ./O 
They/O fed/O their/O dead/O servants/O on/O the/O flesh/O of/O human/O children/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O he/O caught/O his/O first/O glimpse/O of/O the/O Wall/O looming/O above/O the/O tops/O of/O an/O ancient/O gnarled/O oak/O ,/O Jon/PERSON was/O vastly/O relieved/O ./O 
Mormont/O reined/O up/O suddenly/O and/O turned/O in/O his/O saddle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tarly/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O barked/O ,/O \/O ``/O come/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/O saw/O the/O start/O of/O fright/O on/O Sam/PERSON 's/O face/O as/O he/O lumbered/O up/O on/O his/O mare/O ;/O doubtless/O he/O thought/O he/O was/O in/O trouble/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O fat/O but/O you/O 're/O not/O stupid/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O said/O gruffly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O did/O well/O back/O there/O ./O 
And/O you/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON blushed/O a/O vivid/O crimson/O and/O tripped/O over/O his/O own/O tongue/O as/O he/O tried/O to/O stammer/O out/O a/O courtesy/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O to/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O they/O emerged/O from/O under/O the/O trees/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON spurred/O his/O tough/O little/O garron/O to/O a/O trot/O ./O 
Ghost/O came/O streaking/O out/O from/O the/O woods/O to/O meet/O them/O ,/O licking/O his/O chops/O ,/O his/O muzzle/O red/O from/O prey/O ./O 
High/O above/O ,/O the/O men/O on/O the/O Wall/O saw/O the/O column/O approaching/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON heard/O the/O deep/O ,/O throaty/O call/O of/O the/O watchman/O 's/O great/O horn/O ,/O calling/O out/O across/O the/O miles/O ;/O a/O single/O long/O blast/O that/O shuddered/O through/O the/O trees/O and/O echoed/O off/O the/O ice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O UUUUUUUOOOOOOOOOOOOOOooooooooooooooooooooooo/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sound/O faded/O slowly/O to/O silence/O ./O 
One/O blast/O meant/O rangers/O returning/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON thought/O ,/O I/O was/O a/O rangerfor/O one/O day/O ,/O at/O least/O ./O 
Whatever/O may/O come/O ,/O they/O can/O not/O take/O that/O away/O from/O me/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON was/O waiting/O at/O the/O first/O gate/O as/O they/O led/O their/O garrons/O through/O the/O icy/O tunnel/O ./O 
The/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON was/O red/O -/O faced/O and/O agitated/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O blurted/O at/O Mormont/LOCATION as/O he/O swung/O open/O the/O iron/O bars/O ,/O \/O ``/O there/O 's/O been/O a/O bird/O ,/O you/O must/O come/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ,/O man/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O gruffly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Curiously/O ,/O Marsh/PERSON glanced/O at/O Jon/PERSON before/O he/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON has/O the/O letter/O ./O 
He/O 's/O waiting/O in/O your/O solar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O well/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON ,/O see/O to/O my/O horse/O ,/O and/O tell/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON to/O put/O the/O dead/O men/O in/O a/O storeroom/O until/O the/O maester/O is/O ready/O for/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON strode/O away/O grumbling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O they/O led/O their/O horses/O back/O to/O the/O stable/O ,/O Jon/PERSON was/O uncomfortably/O aware/O that/O people/O were/O watching/O him/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON was/O drilling/O his/O boys/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O but/O he/O broke/O off/O to/O stare/O at/O Jon/PERSON ,/O a/O faint/O half/O smile/O on/O his/O lips/O ./O 
One-armed/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON stood/O in/O the/O door/O of/O the/O armory/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O be/O with/O you/O ,/O Snow/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Something/O 's/O wrong/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O ./O 
Something/O 's/O very/O wrong/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dead/O men/O were/O carried/O to/O one/O of/O the/O storerooms/O along/O the/O base/O of/O the/O Wall/O ,/O a/O dark/O cold/O cell/O chiseled/O from/O the/O ice/O and/O used/O to/O keep/O meat/O and/O grain/O and/O sometimes/O even/O beer/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON saw/O that/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/O 's/O horse/O was/O fed/O and/O watered/O and/O groomed/O before/O he/O took/O care/O of/O his/O own/O ./O 
Afterward/O he/O sought/O out/O his/O friends/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON and/O Toad/ORGANIZATION were/O on/O watch/O ,/O but/O he/O found/O Pyp/PERSON in/O the/O common/O hall/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O 's/O happened/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pyp/O lowered/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O 's/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O stunned/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON had/O looked/O old/O and/O fat/O when/O he/O visited/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O yet/O he/O 'd/O seemed/O hale/O enough/O ,/O and/O there/O 'd/O been/O no/O talk/O of/O illness/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O can/O you/O know/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O guards/O overheard/O Clydas/O reading/O the/O letter/O to/O Maester/O Aemon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON leaned/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O I/O 'm/O sorry/O ./O 
He/O was/O your/O father/O 's/O friend/O ,/O was/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O were/O as/O close/O as/O brothers/O ,/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON wondered/O if/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O keep/O his/O father/O as/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O seem/O likely/O ./O 
That/O might/O mean/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON would/O return/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O and/O his/O sisters/O as/O well/O ./O 
He/O might/O even/O be/O allowed/O to/O visit/O them/O ,/O with/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O permission/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O good/O to/O see/O Arya/PERSON 's/O grin/O again/O and/O to/O talk/O with/O his/O father/O ./O 
I/O will/O ask/O him/O about/O my/O mother/O ,/O he/O resolved/O ./O 
I/O am/O a/O man/O now/O ,/O it/O is/O past/O time/O he/O told/O me/O ./O 
Even/O if/O she/O was/O a/O whore/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O ,/O I/O want/O to/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O heard/O Hake/PERSON say/O the/O dead/O men/O were/O your/O uncle/O 's/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Two/O of/O the/O six/O he/O took/O with/O him/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O been/O dead/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O only/O .../O the/O bodies/O are/O queer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Queer/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON was/O all/O curiosity/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O queer/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sam/PERSON will/O tell/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O want/O to/O talk/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O see/O if/O the/O Old/O Bear/O has/O need/O of/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O walked/O to/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O Tower/O alone/O ,/O with/O a/O curious/O sense/O of/O apprehension/O ./O 
The/O brothers/O on/O guard/O eyed/O him/O solemnly/O as/O he/O approached/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O in/O his/O solar/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O them/O announced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O asking/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
He/O should/O have/O come/O straight/O from/O the/O stable/O ./O 
He/O climbed/O the/O tower/O steps/O briskly/O ./O 
He/O wants/O wine/O or/O a/O fire/O in/O his/O hearth/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O ,/O he/O told/O himself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O entered/O the/O solar/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O raven/O screamed/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O bird/O shrieked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O !/O 
Corn/O !/O 
Corn/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O you/O believe/O it/O ,/O I/O just/O fed/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O growled/O ./O 
He/O was/O seated/O by/O the/O window/O ,/O reading/O a/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O me/O a/O cup/O of/O wine/O ,/O and/O pour/O one/O for/O yourself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O myself/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON lifted/O his/O eyes/O from/O the/O letter/O to/O stare/O at/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
There/O was/O pity/O in/O that/O look/O ;/O he/O could/O taste/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O heard/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON poured/O with/O exaggerated/O care/O ,/O vaguely/O aware/O that/O he/O was/O drawing/O out/O the/O act/O ./O 
When/O the/O cups/O were/O filled/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O face/O whatever/O was/O in/O that/O letter/O ./O 
Yet/O all/O too/O soon/O ,/O they/O were/O filled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sit/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON commanded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Drink/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON remained/O standing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O my/O father/O ,/O is/O n't/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O tapped/O the/O letter/O with/O a/O finger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O father/O and/O the/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O rumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O lie/O to/O you/O ,/O it/O 's/O grievous/O news/O ./O 
I/O never/O thought/O to/O see/O another/O king/O ,/O not/O at/O my/O age/O ,/O with/O Robert/PERSON half/O my/O years/O and/O strong/O as/O a/O bull/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O a/O gulp/O of/O wine/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O say/O the/O king/O loved/O to/O hunt/O ./O 
The/O things/O we/O love/O destroy/O us/O every/O time/O ,/O lad/O ./O 
Remember/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O My/O son/O loved/O that/O young/O wife/O of/O his/O ./O 
Vain/O woman/O ./O 
If/O not/O for/O her/O ,/O he/O would/O never/O have/O thought/O to/O sell/O those/O poachers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON could/O scarcely/O follow/O what/O he/O was/O saying/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O understand/O ./O 
What/O 's/O happened/O to/O my/O father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O told/O you/O to/O sit/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON grumbled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sit/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O raven/O screamed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O have/O a/O drink/O ,/O damn/O you/O ./O 
That/O 's/O a/O command/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON sat/O ,/O and/O took/O a/O sip/O of/O wine/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON has/O been/O imprisoned/O ./O 
He/O is/O charged/O with/O treason/O ./O 
It/O is/O said/O he/O plotted/O with/O Robert/PERSON 's/O brothers/O to/O deny/O the/O throne/O to/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O could/O n't/O be/O ./O 
My/O father/O would/O never/O betray/O the/O king/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Be/O that/O as/O it/O may/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O for/O me/O to/O say/O ./O 
Nor/O for/O you/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O it/O 's/O a/O lie/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
How/O could/O they/O think/O his/O father/O was/O a/O traitor/O ,/O had/O they/O all/O gone/O mad/O ?/O 
Lord/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON would/O never/O dishonor/O himself/O .../O would/O he/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O fathered/O a/O bastard/O ,/O a/O small/O voice/O whispered/O inside/O him/O ./O 
Where/O was/O the/O honor/O in/O that/O ?/O 
And/O your/O mother/O ,/O what/O of/O her/O ?/O 
He/O will/O not/O even/O speak/O her/O name/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O what/O will/O happen/O to/O him/O ?/O 
Will/O they/O kill/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O to/O that/O ,/O I/O can/O not/O say/O ,/O lad/O ./O 
I/O mean/O to/O send/O a/O letter/O ./O 
I/O knew/O some/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O councillors/O in/O my/O youth/O ./O 
Old/O Pycelle/O ,/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O Ser/O Barristan/O .../O Whatever/O your/O father/O has/O done/O ,/O or/O has/O n't/O done/O ,/O he/O is/O a/O great/O lord/O ./O 
He/O must/O be/O allowed/O to/O take/O the/O black/O and/O join/O us/O here/O ./O 
Gods/O knows/O ,/O we/O need/O men/O of/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O ability/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON knew/O that/O other/O men/O accused/O of/O treason/O had/O been/O allowed/O to/O redeem/O their/O honor/O on/O the/O Wall/O in/O days/O past/O ./O 
Why/O not/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON ?/O 
His/O father/O here/O ./O 
That/O was/O a/O strange/O thought/O ,/O and/O strangely/O uncomfortable/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O a/O monstrous/O injustice/O to/O strip/O him/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION and/O force/O him/O to/O take/O the/O black/O ,/O and/O yet/O if/O it/O meant/O his/O life/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O would/O Joffrey/O allow/O it/O ?/O 
He/O remembered/O the/O prince/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O the/O way/O he/O 'd/O mocked/O Robb/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON himself/O he/O had/O scarcely/O even/O noticed/O ;/O bastards/O were/O beneath/O even/O his/O contempt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O will/O the/O king/O listen/O to/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O boy/O king/O .../O I/O imagine/O he/O 'll/O listen/O to/O his/O mother/O ./O 
A/O pity/O the/O dwarf/O is/O n't/O with/O them/O ./O 
He/O 's/O the/O lad/O 's/O uncle/O ,/O and/O he/O saw/O our/O need/O when/O he/O visited/O us/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O bad/O thing/O ,/O your/O lady/O mother/O taking/O him/O captive/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O is/O not/O my/O mother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON reminded/O him/O sharply/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON had/O been/O a/O friend/O to/O him/O ./O 
If/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON was/O killed/O ,/O she/O would/O be/O as/O much/O to/O blame/O as/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O what/O of/O my/O sisters/O ?/O 
Arya/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON ,/O they/O were/O with/O my/O father/O ,/O do/O you/O know/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pycelle/O makes/O no/O mention/O of/O them/O ,/O but/O doubtless/O they/O 'll/O be/O treated/O gently/O ./O 
I/O will/O ask/O about/O them/O when/O I/O write/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O could/O not/O have/O happened/O at/O a/O worse/O time/O ./O 
If/O ever/O the/O realm/O needed/O a/O strong/O king/O .../O there/O are/O dark/O days/O and/O cold/O nights/O ahead/O ,/O I/O feel/O it/O in/O my/O bones/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O gave/O Jon/PERSON a/O long/O shrewd/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hope/O you/O are/O not/O thinking/O of/O doing/O anything/O stupid/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O 's/O my/O father/O ,/O Jon/PERSON wanted/O to/O say/O ,/O but/O he/O knew/O that/O Mormont/PERSON would/O not/O want/O to/O hear/O it/O ./O 
His/O throat/O was/O dry/O ./O 
He/O made/O himself/O take/O another/O sip/O of/O wine/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O duty/O is/O here/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O old/O life/O ended/O when/O you/O took/O the/O black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O bird/O made/O a/O raucous/O echo/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Black/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON took/O no/O notice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Whatever/O they/O do/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O is/O none/O of/O our/O concern/O ./O 
\/O ''/O When/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O answer/O ,/O the/O old/O man/O finished/O his/O wine/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O free/O to/O go/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O have/O no/O further/O need/O of/O you/O today/O ./O 
On/O the/O morrow/O you/O can/O help/O me/O write/O that/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O remember/O standing/O or/O leaving/O the/O solar/O ./O 
The/O next/O he/O knew/O ,/O he/O was/O descending/O the/O tower/O steps/O ,/O thinking/O ,/O This/O is/O my/O father/O ,/O my/O sisters/O ,/O how/O can/O it/O be/O none/O of/O my/O concern/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O guards/O looked/O at/O him/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Be/O strong/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
The/O gods/O are/O cruel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O know/O ,/O Jon/PERSON realized/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O is/O no/O traitor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O hoarsely/O ./O 
Even/O the/O words/O stuck/O in/O his/O throat/O ,/O as/O if/O to/O choke/O him/O ./O 
The/O wind/O was/O rising/O ,/O and/O it/O seemed/O colder/O in/O the/O yard/O than/O it/O had/O when/O he/O 'd/O gone/O in/O ./O 
Spirit/O summer/O was/O drawing/O to/O an/O end/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rest/O of/O the/O afternoon/O passed/O as/O if/O in/O a/O dream/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O not/O have/O said/O where/O he/O walked/O ,/O what/O he/O did/O ,/O who/O he/O spoke/O with/O ./O 
Ghost/O was/O with/O him/O ,/O he/O knew/O that/O much/O ./O 
The/O silent/O presence/O of/O the/O direwolf/O gave/O him/O comfort/O ./O 
The/O girls/O do/O not/O even/O have/O that/O much/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
Their/O wolves/O might/O have/O kept/O them/O safe/O ,/O but/O Lady/O is/O dead/O and/O Nymeria/LOCATION 's/O lost/O ,/O they/O 're/O all/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O north/O wind/O had/O begun/O to/O blow/O by/O the/O time/O the/O sun/O went/O down/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O hear/O it/O skirling/O against/O the/O Wall/O and/O over/O the/O icy/O battlements/O as/O he/O went/O to/O the/O common/O hall/O for/O the/O evening/O meal/O ./O 
Hobb/PERSON had/O cooked/O up/O a/O venison/O stew/O ,/O thick/O with/O barley/O ,/O onions/O ,/O and/O carrots/O ./O 
When/O he/O spooned/O an/O extra/O portion/O onto/O Jon/PERSON 's/O plate/O and/O gave/O him/O the/O crusty/O heel/O of/O the/O bread/O ,/O he/O knew/O what/O it/O meant/O ./O 
He/O knows/O ./O 
He/O looked/O around/O the/O hall/O ,/O saw/O heads/O turn/O quickly/O ,/O eyes/O politely/O averted/O ./O 
They/O all/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O friends/O rallied/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O asked/O the/O septon/O to/O light/O a/O candle/O for/O your/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Matthar/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O a/O lie/O ,/O we/O all/O know/O it/O 's/O a/O lie/O ,/O even/O Grenn/PERSON knows/O it/O 's/O a/O lie/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON chimed/O in/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON nodded/O ,/O and/O Sam/PERSON clasped/O Jon/PERSON 's/O hand/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O my/O brother/O now/O ,/O so/O he/O 's/O my/O father/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O fat/O boy/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O want/O to/O go/O out/O to/O the/O weirwoods/O and/O pray/O to/O the/O old/O gods/O ,/O I/O 'll/O go/O with/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O weirwoods/O were/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ,/O yet/O he/O knew/O Sam/PERSON meant/O what/O he/O said/O ./O 
They/O are/O my/O brothers/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
As/O much/O as/O Robb/PERSON and/O Bran/O and/O Rickon/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O then/O he/O heard/O the/O laughter/O ,/O sharp/O and/O cruel/O as/O a/O whip/O ,/O and/O the/O voice/O of/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O only/O a/O bastard/O ,/O but/O a/O traitor/O 's/O bastard/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O was/O telling/O the/O men/O around/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O ,/O Jon/PERSON had/O vaulted/O onto/O the/O table/O ,/O dagger/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON made/O a/O grab/O for/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O wrenched/O his/O leg/O away/O ,/O and/O then/O he/O was/O sprinting/O down/O the/O table/O and/O kicking/O the/O bowl/O from/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O hand/O ./O 
Stew/O went/O flying/O everywhere/O ,/O spattering/O the/O brothers/O ./O 
Thorne/PERSON recoiled/O ./O 
People/O were/O shouting/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON did/O not/O hear/O them/O ./O 
He/O lunged/O at/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O face/O with/O the/O dagger/O ,/O slashing/O at/O those/O cold/O onyx/O eyes/O ,/O but/O Sam/PERSON threw/O himself/O between/O them/O and/O before/O Jon/PERSON could/O get/O around/O him/O ,/O Pyp/PERSON was/O on/O his/O back/O clinging/O like/O a/O monkey/O ,/O and/O Grenn/PERSON was/O grabbing/O his/O arm/O while/O Toad/PERSON wrenched/O the/O knife/O from/O his/O fingers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Later/O ,/O much/O later/O ,/O after/O they/O had/O marched/O him/O back/O to/O his/O sleeping/O cell/O ,/O Mormont/PERSON came/O down/O to/O see/O him/O ,/O raven/O on/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O told/O you/O not/O to/O do/O anything/O stupid/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Old/O Bear/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O bird/O chorused/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ,/O disgusted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O to/O think/O I/O had/O high/O hopes/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O took/O his/O knife/O and/O his/O sword/O and/O told/O him/O he/O was/O not/O to/O leave/O his/O cell/O until/O the/O high/O officers/O met/O to/O decide/O what/O was/O to/O be/O done/O with/O him/O ./O 
And/O then/O they/O placed/O a/O guard/O outside/O his/O door/O to/O make/O certain/O he/O obeyed/O ./O 
His/O friends/O were/O not/O allowed/O to/O see/O him/O ,/O but/O the/O Old/O Bear/O did/O relent/O and/O permit/O him/O Ghost/O ,/O so/O he/O was/O not/O utterly/O alone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O father/O is/O no/O traitor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O direwolf/O when/O the/O rest/O had/O gone/O ./O 
Ghost/O looked/O at/O him/O in/O silence/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON slumped/O against/O the/O wall/O ,/O hands/O around/O his/O knees/O ,/O and/O stared/O at/O the/O candle/O on/O the/O table/O beside/O his/O narrow/O bed/O ./O 
The/O flame/O flickered/O and/O swayed/O ,/O the/O shadows/O moved/O around/O him/O ,/O the/O room/O seemed/O to/O grow/O darker/O and/O colder/O ./O 
I/O will/O not/O sleep/O tonight/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O he/O must/O have/O dozed/O ./O 
When/O he/O woke/O ,/O his/O legs/O were/O stiff/O and/O cramped/O and/O the/O candle/O had/O long/O since/O burned/O out/O ./O 
Ghost/O stood/O on/O his/O hind/O legs/O ,/O scrabbling/O at/O the/O door/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON was/O startled/O to/O see/O how/O tall/O he/O 'd/O grown/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O ,/O what/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O softly/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O turned/O his/O head/O and/O looked/O down/O at/O him/O ,/O baring/O his/O fangs/O in/O a/O silent/O snarl/O ./O 
Has/O he/O gone/O mad/O ?/O 
Jon/PERSON wondered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O me/O ,/O Ghost/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O ,/O trying/O not/O to/O sound/O afraid/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O was/O trembling/O ,/O violently/O ./O 
When/O had/O it/O gotten/O so/O cold/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O backed/O away/O from/O the/O door/O ./O 
There/O were/O deep/O gouges/O where/O he/O 'd/O raked/O the/O wood/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON watched/O him/O with/O mounting/O disquiet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O someone/O out/O there/O ,/O is/O n't/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
Crouching/O ,/O the/O direwolf/O crept/O backward/O ,/O white/O fur/O rising/O on/O the/O back/O of/O his/O neck/O ./O 
The/O guard/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O they/O left/O a/O man/O to/O guard/O my/O door/O ,/O Ghost/PERSON smells/O him/O through/O the/O door/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O it/O is/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Slowly/O ,/O Jon/PERSON pushed/O himself/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
He/O was/O shivering/O uncontrollably/O ,/O wishing/O he/O still/O had/O a/O sword/O ./O 
Three/O quick/O steps/O brought/O him/O to/O the/O door/O ./O 
He/O grabbed/O the/O handle/O and/O pulled/O it/O inward/O ./O 
The/O creak/O of/O the/O hinges/O almost/O made/O him/O jump/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O guard/O was/O sprawled/O bonelessly/O across/O the/O narrow/O steps/O ,/O looking/O up/O at/O him/O ./O 
Looking/O up/O at/O him/O ,/O even/O though/O he/O was/O lying/O on/O his/O stomach/O ./O 
His/O head/O had/O been/O twisted/O completely/O around/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O ca/O n't/O be/O ,/O Jon/PERSON told/O himself/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O Tower/O ,/O it/O 's/O guarded/O day/O and/O night/O ,/O this/O could/O n't/O happen/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O dream/O ,/O I/O 'm/O having/O a/O nightmare/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O slid/O past/O him/O ,/O out/O the/O door/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O started/O up/O the/O steps/O ,/O stopped/O ,/O looked/O back/O at/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
That/O was/O when/O he/O heard/O it/O ;/O the/O soft/O scrape/O of/O a/O boot/O on/O stone/O ,/O the/O sound/O of/O a/O latch/O turning/O ./O 
The/O sounds/O came/O from/O above/O ./O 
From/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O chambers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O nightmare/O this/O might/O be/O ,/O yet/O it/O was/O no/O dream/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O guard/O 's/O sword/O was/O in/O its/O sheath/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knelt/O and/O worked/O it/O free/O ./O 
The/O heft/O of/O steel/O in/O his/O fist/O made/O him/O bolder/O ./O 
He/O moved/O up/O the/O steps/O ,/O Ghost/O padding/O silently/O before/O him/O ./O 
Shadows/O lurked/O in/O every/O turn/O of/O the/O stair/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON crept/O up/O warily/O ,/O probing/O any/O suspicious/O darkness/O with/O the/O point/O of/O his/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O he/O heard/O the/O shriek/O of/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O raven/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O bird/O was/O screaming/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ghost/O bounded/O ahead/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON came/O scrambling/O after/O ./O 
The/O door/O to/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O solar/O was/O wide/O open/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O plunged/O through/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON stopped/O in/O the/O doorway/O ,/O blade/O in/O hand/O ,/O giving/O his/O eyes/O a/O moment/O to/O adjust/O ./O 
Heavy/O drapes/O had/O been/O pulled/O across/O the/O windows/O ,/O and/O the/O darkness/O was/O black/O as/O ink/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O 's/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O he/O saw/O it/O ,/O a/O shadow/O in/O the/O shadows/O ,/O sliding/O toward/O the/O inner/O door/O that/O led/O to/O Mormont/PERSON 's/O sleeping/O cell/O ,/O a/O man-shape/O all/O in/O black/O ,/O cloaked/O and/O hooded/O .../O but/O beneath/O the/O hood/O ,/O its/O eyes/O shone/O with/O an/O icy/O blue/O radiance/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ghost/O leapt/O ./O 
Man/O and/O wolf/O went/O down/O together/O with/O neither/O scream/O nor/O snarl/O ,/O rolling/O ,/O smashing/O into/O a/O chair/O ,/O knocking/O over/O a/O table/O laden/O with/O papers/O ./O 
Mormont/PERSON 's/O raven/O was/O flapping/O overhead/O ,/O screaming/O ,/O \/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON felt/O as/O blind/O as/O Maester/O Aemon/O ./O 
Keeping/O the/O wall/O to/O his/O back/O ,/O he/O slid/O toward/O the/O window/O and/O ripped/O down/O the/O curtain/O ./O 
Moonlight/O flooded/O the/O solar/O ./O 
He/O glimpsed/O black/O hands/O buried/O in/O white/O fur/O ,/O swollen/O dark/O fingers/O tightening/O around/O his/O direwolf/O s/O throat/O ./O 
Ghost/O was/O twisting/O and/O snapping/O ,/O legs/O flailing/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O but/O he/O could/O not/O break/O free/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON had/O no/O time/O to/O be/O afraid/O ./O 
He/O threw/O himself/O forward/O ,/O shouting/O ,/O bringing/O down/O the/O longsword/O with/O all/O his/O weight/O behind/O it/O ./O 
Steel/O sheared/O through/O sleeve/O and/O skin/O and/O bone/O ,/O yet/O the/O sound/O was/O wrong/O somehow/O ./O 
The/O smell/O that/O engulfed/O him/O was/O so/O queer/O and/O cold/O he/O almost/O gagged/O ./O 
He/O saw/O arm/O and/O hand/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O black/O fingers/O wriggling/O in/O a/O pool/O of/O moonlight/O ./O 
Ghost/O wrenched/O free/O of/O the/O other/O hand/O and/O crept/O away/O ,/O red/O tongue/O lolling/O from/O his/O mouth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O hooded/O man/O lifted/O his/O pale/O moon/O face/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON slashed/O at/O it/O without/O hesitation/O ./O 
The/O sword/O laid/O the/O intruder/O open/O to/O the/O bone/O ,/O taking/O off/O half/O his/O nose/O and/O opening/O a/O gash/O cheek/O to/O cheek/O under/O those/O eyes/O ,/O eyes/O ,/O eyes/O like/O blue/O stars/O burning/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON knew/O that/O face/O ./O 
Othor/O ,/O he/O thought/O ,/O reeling/O back/O ./O 
Gods/O ,/O he/O 's/O dead/O ,/O he/O 's/O dead/O ,/O I/O saw/O him/O dead/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O felt/O something/O scrabble/O at/O his/O ankle/O ./O 
Black/O fingers/O clawed/O at/O his/O calf/O ./O 
The/O arm/O was/O crawling/O up/O his/O leg/O ,/O ripping/O at/O wool/O and/O flesh/O ./O 
Shouting/O with/O revulsion/O ,/O Jon/PERSON pried/O the/O fingers/O off/O his/O leg/O with/O the/O point/O of/O his/O sword/O and/O flipped/O the/O thing/O away/O ./O 
It/O lay/O writhing/O ,/O fingers/O opening/O and/O closing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O corpse/O lurched/O forward/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O blood/O ./O 
One-armed/O ,/O face/O cut/O near/O in/O half/O ,/O it/O seemed/O to/O feel/O nothing/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON held/O the/O longsword/O before/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stay/O away/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O commanded/O ,/O his/O voice/O gone/O shrill/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Corn/O ,/O \/O ''/O screamed/O the/O raven/O ,/O \/O ``/O corn/O ,/O corn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O severed/O arm/O was/O wriggling/O out/O of/O its/O torn/O sleeve/O ,/O a/O pale/O snake/O with/O a/O black/O five-fingered/O head/O ./O 
Ghost/O pounced/O and/O got/O it/O between/O his/O teeth/O ./O 
Finger/O bones/O crunched/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON hacked/O at/O the/O corpse/O 's/O neck/O ,/O felt/O the/O steel/O bite/O deep/O and/O hard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dead/O Othor/O slammed/O into/O him/O ,/O knocking/O him/O off/O his/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON 's/O breath/O went/O out/O of/O him/O as/O the/O fallen/O table/O caught/O him/O between/O his/O shoulder/O blades/O ./O 
The/O sword/O ,/O where/O was/O the/O sword/O ?/O 
He/O 'd/O lost/O the/O damned/O sword/O !/O 
When/O he/O opened/O his/O mouth/O to/O scream/O ,/O the/O wight/O jammed/O its/O black/O corpse/O fingers/O into/O Jon/PERSON 's/O mouth/O ./O 
Gagging/O ,/O he/O tried/O to/O shove/O it/O off/O ,/O but/O the/O dead/O man/O was/O too/O heavy/O ./O 
Its/O hand/O forced/O itself/O farther/O down/O his/O throat/O ,/O icy/O cold/O ,/O choking/O him/O ./O 
Its/O face/O was/O against/O his/O own/O ,/O filling/O the/O world/O ./O 
Frost/PERSON covered/O its/O eyes/O ,/O sparkling/O blue/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON raked/O cold/O flesh/O with/O his/O nails/O and/O kicked/O at/O the/O thing/O 's/O legs/O ./O 
He/O tried/O to/O bite/O ,/O tried/O to/O punch/O ,/O tried/O to/O breathe/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O suddenly/O the/O corpse/O 's/O weight/O was/O gone/O ,/O its/O fingers/O ripped/O from/O his/O throat/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O Jon/PERSON could/O do/O to/O roll/O over/O ,/O retching/O and/O shaking/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ghost/O had/O it/O again/O ./O 
He/O watched/O as/O the/O direwolf/O buried/O his/O teeth/O in/O the/O wight/O 's/O gut/O and/O began/O to/O rip/O and/O tear/O ./O 
He/O watched/O ,/O only/O half/O conscious/O ,/O for/O a/O long/O moment/O before/O he/O finally/O remembered/O to/O look/O for/O his/O sword/O ./O 
./O 
./O 
and/O saw/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON ,/O naked/O and/O groggy/O from/O sleep/O ,/O standing/O in/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O doorway/O with/O an/O oil/O lamp/O in/O hand/O ./O 
Gnawed/O and/O fingerless/O ,/O the/O arm/O thrashed/O on/O the/O floor/O ,/O wriggling/O toward/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON tried/O to/O shout/O ,/O but/O his/O voice/O was/O gone/O ./O 
Staggering/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O he/O kicked/O the/O arm/O away/O and/O snatched/O the/O lamp/O from/O the/O Old/O Bear/O 's/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O flame/O flickered/O and/O almost/O died/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Burn/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O raven/O cawed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Burn/O ,/O Burn/O ,/O Burn/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Spinning/O ,/O Jon/PERSON saw/O the/O drapes/O he/O 'd/O ripped/O from/O the/O window/O ./O 
He/O flung/O the/O lamp/O into/O the/O puddled/O cloth/O with/O both/O hands/O ./O 
Metal/O crunched/O ,/O glass/O shattered/O ,/O oil/O spewed/O ,/O and/O the/O hangings/O went/O up/O in/O a/O great/O whoosh/O of/O flame/O ./O 
The/O heat/O of/O it/O on/O his/O face/O was/O sweeter/O than/O any/O kiss/O Jon/PERSON had/O ever/O known/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ghost/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O direwo/O If/O wrenched/O free/O and/O came/O to/O him/O as/O the/O wight/O struggled/O to/O rise/O ,/O dark/O snakes/O spilling/O from/O the/O great/O wound/O in/O its/O belly/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON plunged/O his/O hand/O into/O the/O flames/O ,/O grabbed/O a/O fistful/O of/O the/O burning/O drapes/O ,/O and/O whipped/O them/O at/O the/O dead/O man/O ./O 
Let/O it/O burn/O ,/O he/O prayed/O as/O the/O cloth/O smothered/O the/O corpse/O ,/O gods/O ,/O please/O ,/O please/O ,/O let/O it/O burn/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
