-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O rode/O to/O the/O Hand/O 's/O tourney/O with/O Septa/ORGANIZATION Mordane/ORGANIZATION and/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON ,/O in/O a/O litter/O with/O curtains/O of/O yellow/O silk/O so/O fine/O she/O could/O see/O right/O through/O them/O ./O 
They/O turned/O the/O whole/O world/O gold/O ./O 
Beyond/O the/O city/O walls/O ,/O a/O hundred/O pavilions/O had/O been/O raised/O beside/O the/O river/O ,/O and/O the/O common/O folk/O came/O out/O in/O the/O thousands/O to/O watch/O the/O games/O ./O 
The/O splendor/O of/O it/O all/O took/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O breath/O away/O ;/O the/O shining/O armor/O ,/O the/O great/O chargers/O caparisoned/O in/O silver/O and/O gold/O ,/O the/O shouts/O of/O the/O crowd/O ,/O the/O banners/O snapping/O in/O the/O wind/O .../O and/O the/O knights/O themselves/O ,/O the/O knights/O most/O of/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O better/O than/O the/O songs/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O when/O they/O found/O the/O places/O that/O her/O father/O had/O promised/O her/O ,/O among/O the/O high/O lords/O and/O ladies/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O dressed/O beautifully/O that/O day/O ,/O in/O a/O green/O gown/O that/O brought/O out/O the/O auburn/O of/O her/O hair/O ,/O and/O she/O knew/O they/O were/O looking/O at/O her/O and/O smiling/O ./O 
They/O watched/O the/O heroes/O of/O a/O hundred/O songs/O ride/O forth/O ,/O each/O more/O fabulous/O than/O the/O last/O ./O 
The/O seven/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/PERSON took/O the/O field/O ,/O all/O but/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON in/O scaled/O armor/O the/O color/O of/O milk/O ,/O their/O cloaks/O as/O white/O as/O freshfallen/O snow/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON wore/O the/O white/O cloak/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O beneath/O it/O he/O was/O shining/O gold/O from/O head/O to/O foot/O ,/O with/O a/O lion/O 's/O head/O helm/O and/O a/O golden/O sword/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON ,/O the/O Mountain/O That/O Rides/O ,/O thundered/O past/O them/O like/O an/O avalanche/O ./O 
Sansa/O remembered/O Lord/O Yohn/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O guested/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION two/O years/O before/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O armor/O is/O bronze/O ,/O thousands/O and/O thousands/O of/O years/O old/O ,/O engraved/O with/O magic/O runes/O that/O ward/O him/O against/O harm/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O to/O Jeyne/PERSON ./O 
Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON pointed/O out/O Lord/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON ,/O in/O indigo/O chased/O with/O silver/O ,/O the/O wings/O of/O an/O eagle/O on/O his/O helm/O ./O 
He/O had/O cut/O down/O three/O of/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O bannermen/O on/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
The/O girls/O giggled/O over/O the/O warrior/O priest/O Thoros/PERSON of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION ,/O with/O his/O flapping/O red/O robes/O and/O shaven/O head/O ,/O until/O the/O septa/O told/O them/O that/O he/O had/O once/O scaled/O the/O walls/O of/O Pyke/PERSON with/O a/O flaming/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Other/O riders/O Sansa/O did/O not/O know/O ;/O hedge/O knights/O from/O the/O Fingers/O and/O Highgarden/LOCATION and/O the/O mountains/O of/O Dome/LOCATION ,/O unsung/O freeriders/O and/O new-made/O squires/O ,/O the/O younger/O sons/O of/O high/O lords/O and/O the/O heirs/O of/O lesser/O houses/O ./O 
Younger/O men/O ,/O most/O had/O done/O no/O great/O deeds/O as/O yet/O ,/O but/O Sansa/PERSON and/O Jeyne/PERSON agreed/O that/O one/O day/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O would/O resound/O to/O the/O sound/O of/O their/O names/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON ./O 
Lord/O Bryce/PERSON Caron/PERSON of/O the/O Marches/O ./O 
Bronze/O Yohn/PERSON 's/O heir/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Andar/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O and/O his/O younger/O brother/O Ser/PERSON Robar/PERSON ,/O their/O silvered/O steel/O plate/O filigreed/O in/O bronze/O with/O the/O same/O ancient/O runes/O that/O warded/O their/O father/O ./O 
The/O twins/O Ser/PERSON Horas/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Hobber/PERSON ,/O whose/O shields/O displayed/O the/O grape/O cluster/O sigil/O of/O the/O Redwynes/O ,/O burgundy/O on/O blue/O ./O 
Patrek/PERSON Mallister/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Jason/PERSON 's/O son/O ./O 
Six/O Freys/O of/O the/O Crossing/O :/O Ser/PERSON Jared/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Hosteen/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Danwell/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Emmon/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Theo/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Perwyn/PERSON ,/O sons/O and/O grandsons/O of/O old/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON ,/O and/O his/O bastard/O son/O Martyn/PERSON Rivers/PERSON as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON confessed/O herself/O frightened/O by/O the/O look/O of/O Jalabhar/PERSON Xho/PERSON ,/O an/O exile/O prince/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION who/O wore/O a/O cape/O of/O green/O and/O scarlet/O feathers/O over/O skin/O as/O dark/O as/O night/O ,/O but/O when/O she/O saw/O young/O Lord/PERSON Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON ,/O with/O his/O hair/O like/O red/O gold/O and/O his/O black/O shield/O slashed/O by/O lightning/O ,/O she/O pronounced/O herself/O willing/O to/O marry/O him/O on/O the/O instant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O entered/O the/O lists/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O so/O too/O the/O king/O 's/O brother/O ,/O handsome/O Lord/O Renly/O of/O Storm/O 's/O End/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON ,/O Alyn/PERSON ,/O and/O Harwin/PERSON rode/O for/O Winterfell/PERSON and/O the/O north/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jory/PERSON looks/O a/O beggar/O ''/O ,/O ``/O among/O these/O others/O ,/O \/O ''/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON sniffed/O when/O he/O appeared/O ./O 
Sansa/O could/O only/O agree/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON 's/O armor/O was/O blue-grey/O plate/O without/O device/O or/O ornament/O ,/O and/O a/O thin/O grey/O cloak/O hung/O from/O his/O shoulders/O like/O a/O soiled/O rag/O ./O 
Yet/O he/O acquitted/O himself/O well/O ,/O unhorsing/O Horas/PERSON Redwyne/PERSON in/O his/O first/O joust/O and/O one/O of/O the/O Freys/ORGANIZATION in/O his/O second/O ./O 
In/O his/O third/O match/O ,/O he/O rode/O three/O passes/O at/O a/O freerider/O named/O Lothor/PERSON Brune/PERSON whose/O armor/O was/O as/O drab/O as/O his/O own/O ./O 
Neither/O man/O lost/O his/O seat/O ,/O but/O Brune/PERSON 's/O lance/O was/O steadier/O and/O his/O blows/O better/O placed/O ,/O and/O the/O king/O gave/O him/O the/O victory/O ./O 
Alyn/PERSON and/O Harwin/PERSON fared/O less/O well/O ;/O Harwin/PERSON was/O unhorsed/O in/O his/O first/O tilt/O by/O Ser/PERSON Meryn/PERSON of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ,/O while/O Alyn/PERSON fell/O to/O Ser/PERSON Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O jousting/O went/O all/O day/O and/O into/O the/O dusk/O ,/O the/O hooves/O of/O the/O great/O warhorses/O pounding/O down/O the/O lists/O until/O the/O field/O was/O a/O ragged/O wasteland/O of/O torn/O earth/O ./O 
A/O dozen/O times/O Jeyne/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON cried/O out/O in/O unison/O as/O riders/O crashed/O together/O ,/O lances/O exploding/O into/O splinters/O while/O the/O commons/O screamed/O for/O their/O favorites/O ./O 
Jeyne/PERSON covered/O her/O eyes/O whenever/O a/O man/O fell/O ,/O like/O a/O frightened/O little/O girl/O ,/O but/O Sansa/PERSON was/O made/O of/O sterner/O stuff/O ./O 
A/O great/O lady/O knew/O how/O to/O behave/O at/O tournaments/O ./O 
Even/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON noted/O her/O composure/O and/O nodded/O in/O approval/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O rode/O brilliantly/O ./O 
He/O overthrew/O Ser/PERSON Andar/PERSON Royce/PERSON and/O the/O Marcher/O Lord/O Bryce/PERSON Caron/PERSON as/O easily/O as/O if/O he/O were/O riding/O at/O rings/O ,/O and/O then/O took/O a/O hard/O -/O fought/O match/O from/O white/O -/O haired/O Barristan/PERSON Selmy/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O won/O his/O first/O two/O tilts/O against/O men/O thirty/O and/O forty/O years/O his/O junior/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON and/O his/O immense/O brother/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON the/PERSON Mountain/PERSON ,/O seemed/O unstoppable/O as/O well/O ,/O riding/O down/O one/O foe/O after/O the/O next/O in/O ferocious/O style/O ./O 
The/O most/O terrifying/O moment/O of/O the/O day/O came/O during/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O second/O joust/O ,/O when/O his/O lance/O rode/O up/O and/O struck/O a/O young/O knight/O from/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION under/O the/O gorget/O with/O such/O force/O that/O it/O drove/O through/O his/O throat/O ,/O killing/O him/O instantly/O ./O 
The/O youth/O fell/O not/O ten/O feet/O from/O where/O Sansa/PERSON was/O seated/O ./O 
The/O point/O of/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O lance/O had/O snapped/O off/O in/O his/O neck/O ,/O and/O his/O life/O 's/O blood/O flowed/O out/O in/O slow/O pulses/O ,/O each/O weaker/O than/O the/O one/O before/O ./O 
His/O armor/O was/O shiny/O new/O ;/O a/O bright/O streak/O of/O fire/O ran/O down/O his/O outstretched/O arm/O ,/O as/O the/O steel/O caught/O the/O light/O ./O 
Then/O the/O sun/O went/O behind/O a/O cloud/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O gone/O ./O 
His/O cloak/O was/O blue/O ,/O the/O color/O of/O the/O sky/O on/O a/O clear/O summer/O 's/O day/O ,/O trimmed/O with/O a/O border/O of/O crescent/O moons/O ,/O but/O as/O his/O blood/O seeped/O into/O it/O ,/O the/O cloth/O darkened/O and/O the/O moons/O turned/O red/O ,/O one/O by/O one/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON wept/O so/O hysterically/O that/O Septa/O Mordane/O finally/O took/O her/O off/O to/O regain/O her/O composure/O ,/O but/O Sansa/PERSON sat/O with/O her/O hands/O folded/O in/O her/O lap/O ,/O watching/O with/O a/O strange/O fascination/O ./O 
She/O had/O never/O seen/O a/O man/O die/O before/O ./O 
She/O ought/O to/O be/O crying/O too/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O but/O the/O tears/O would/O not/O come/O ./O 
Perhaps/O she/O had/O used/O up/O all/O her/O tears/O for/O Lady/O and/O Bran/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O different/O if/O it/O had/O been/O Jory/PERSON or/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON or/O Father/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
The/O young/O knight/O in/O the/O blue/O cloak/O was/O nothing/O to/O her/O ,/O some/O stranger/O from/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION whose/O name/O she/O had/O forgotten/O as/O soon/O as/O she/O heard/O it/O ./O 
And/O now/O the/O world/O would/O forget/O his/O name/O too/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON realized/O ;/O there/O would/O be/O no/O songs/O sung/O for/O him/O ./O 
That/O was/O sad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O After/O they/O carried/O off/O the/O body/O ,/O a/O boy/O with/O a/O spade/O ran/O onto/O the/O field/O and/O shoveled/O dirt/O over/O the/O spot/O where/O he/O had/O fallen/O ,/O to/O cover/O up/O the/O blood/O ./O 
Then/O the/O jousts/O resumed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Balon/PERSON Swann/PERSON also/O fell/O to/O Gregor/PERSON ,/O and/O Lord/O Renly/O to/O the/O Hound/O ./O 
Renly/PERSON was/O unhorsed/O so/O violently/O that/O he/O seemed/O to/O fly/O backward/O off/O his/O charger/O ,/O legs/O in/O the/O air/O ./O 
His/O head/O hit/O the/O ground/O ''/O ,/O ``/O with/O an/O audible/O crack/O that/O made/O the/O crowd/O gasp/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O just/O the/O golden/O antler/O on/O his/O helm/O ./O 
One/O of/O the/O tines/O had/O snapped/O off/O beneath/O him/O ./O 
When/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON climbed/O to/O his/O feet/O ,/O the/O commons/O cheered/O wildly/O ,/O for/O King/O Robert/PERSON 's/O handsome/O young/O brother/O was/O a/O great/O favorite/O ./O 
He/O handed/O the/O broken/O tine/O to/O his/O conqueror/O with/O a/O gracious/O bow/O ./O 
The/O Hound/O snorted/O and/O tossed/O the/O broken/O antler/O into/O the/O crowd/O ,/O where/O the/O commons/O began/O to/O punch/O and/O claw/O over/O the/O little/O bit/O of/O gold/O ,/O until/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON walked/O out/O among/O them/O and/O restored/O the/O peace/O ./O 
By/O then/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON had/O returned/O ,/O alone/O ./O 
Jeyne/PERSON had/O been/O feeling/O ill/O ,/O she/O explained/O ;/O she/O had/O helped/O her/O back/O to/O the/O castle/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O almost/O forgotten/O about/O Jeyne/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Later/O a/O hedge/O knight/O in/O a/O checkered/O cloak/O disgraced/O himself/O by/O killing/O Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON 's/O horse/O ,/O and/O was/O declared/O forfeit/O ./O 
Lord/O Beric/PERSON shifted/O his/O saddle/O to/O a/O new/O mount/O ,/O only/O to/O be/O knocked/O right/O off/O it/O by/O Thoros/PERSON of/O Myr/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON Santagar/PERSON and/O Lothor/PERSON Brune/PERSON tilted/O thrice/O without/O result/O ;/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON fell/O afterward/O to/O Lord/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON ,/O and/O Brune/PERSON to/O Yohn/PERSON Royce/PERSON 's/O younger/O son/O ,/O Robar/PERSON ./O 
In/O the/O end/O it/O came/O down/O to/O four/O ;/O the/O Hound/O and/O his/O monstrous/O brother/O Gregor/PERSON ,/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON the/PERSON Kingslayer/PERSON ,/O and/O Ser/ORGANIZATION Loras/ORGANIZATION Tyre/ORGANIZATION 11/O ,/O the/O youth/O they/O called/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON was/O the/O youngest/O son/O of/O Mace/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON ,/O the/O Lord/O of/O Highgarden/LOCATION and/O Warden/O of/O the/O South/LOCATION ./O 
At/O sixteen/O ,/O he/O was/O the/O youngest/O rider/O on/O the/O field/O ,/O yet/O he/O had/O unhorsed/O three/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O that/O morning/O in/O his/O first/O three/O jousts/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O never/O seen/O anyone/O so/O beautiful/O ./O 
His/O plate/O was/O intricately/O fashioned/O and/O enameled/O as/O a/O bouquet/O of/O a/O thousand/O different/O flowers/O ,/O and/O his/O snow-white/O stallion/O was/O draped/O in/O a/O blanket/O of/O red/O and/O white/O roses/O ./O 
After/O each/O victory/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON would/O remove/O his/O helm/O and/O ride/O slowly/O round/O the/O fence/O ,/O and/O finally/O pluck/O a/O single/O white/O rose/O from/O the/O blanket/O and/O toss/O it/O to/O some/O fair/O maiden/O in/O the/O crowd/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O last/O match/O of/O the/O day/O was/O against/O the/O younger/O Royce/PERSON ./O 
Ser/PERSON Robar/PERSON 's/O ancestral/O runes/O proved/O small/O protection/O as/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON split/O his/O shield/O and/O drove/O him/O from/O his/O saddle/O to/O crash/O with/O an/O awful/O clangor/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
Robar/PERSON lay/O moaning/O as/O the/O victor/O made/O his/O circuit/O of/O the/O field/O ./O 
Finally/O they/O called/O for/O a/O litter/O and/O carried/O him/O off/O to/O his/O tent/O ,/O dazed/O and/O unmoving/O ./O 
Sansa/O never/O saw/O it/O ./O 
Her/O eyes/O were/O only/O for/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ./O 
When/O the/O white/O horse/O stopped/O in/O front/O of/O her/O ,/O she/O thought/O her/O heart/O would/O burst/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O To/O the/O other/O maidens/O he/O had/O given/O white/O roses/O ,/O but/O the/O one/O he/O plucked/O for/O her/O was/O red/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O no/O victory/O is/O half/O so/O beautiful/O as/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON took/O the/O flower/O timidly/O ,/O struck/O dumb/O by/O his/O gallantry/O ./O 
His/O hair/O was/O a/O mass/O of/O lazy/O brown/O curls/O ,/O his/O eyes/O like/O liquid/O gold/O ./O 
She/O inhaled/O the/O sweet/O fragrance/O of/O the/O rose/O and/O sat/O clutching/O it/O long/O after/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON had/O ridden/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O Sansa/PERSON finally/O looked/O up/O ,/O a/O man/O was/O standing/O over/O her/O ,/O staring/O ./O 
He/O was/O short/O ,/O with/O a/O pointed/O beard/O and/O a/O silver/O streak/O in/O his/O hair/O ,/O almost/O as/O old/O as/O her/O father/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O be/O one/O of/O her/O daughters/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O her/O ./O 
He/O had/O grey-green/O eyes/O that/O did/O not/O smile/O when/O his/O mouth/O did/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O the/O Tully/O look/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O Sansa/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O ill/O at/O ease/O ./O 
The/O man/O wore/O a/O heavy/O cloak/O with/O a/O fur/O collar/O ,/O fastened/O with/O a/O silver/O mockingbird/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O the/O effortless/O manner/O of/O a/O high/O lord/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O not/O know/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O had/O the/O honor/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/O quickly/O took/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/O child/O ,/O this/O is/O Lord/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON ,/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O small/O council/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O mother/O was/O my/O queen/O of/O beauty/O once/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O said/O quietly/O ./O 
His/O breath/O smelled/O of/O mint/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O her/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O fingers/O brushed/O against/O her/O cheek/O as/O he/O stroked/O one/O auburn/O lock/O ./O 
Quite/O abruptly/O he/O turned/O and/O walked/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O then/O ,/O the/O moon/O was/O well/O up/O and/O the/O crowd/O was/O tired/O ,/O so/O the/O king/O decreed/O that/O the/O last/O three/O matches/O would/O be/O fought/O the/O next/O morning/O ,/O before/O the/O melee/O ./O 
While/O the/O commons/O began/O their/O walk/O home/O ,/O talking/O of/O the/O day/O 's/O jousts/O and/O the/O matches/O to/O come/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O the/O court/O moved/O to/O the/O riverside/O to/O begin/O the/O feast/O ./O 
Six/O monstrous/O huge/O aurochs/O had/O been/O roasting/O for/O hours/O ,/O turning/O slowly/O on/O wooden/O spits/O while/O kitchen/O boys/O basted/O them/O with/O butter/O and/O herbs/O until/O the/O meat/O crackled/O and/O spit/O ./O 
Tables/O and/O benches/O had/O been/O raised/O outside/O the/O pavilions/O ,/O piled/O high/O with/O sweetgrass/O and/O strawberries/O and/O fresh-baked/O bread/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O and/O Septa/O Mordane/O were/O given/O places/O of/O high/O honor/O ,/O to/O the/O left/O of/O the/O raised/O dais/O where/O the/O king/O himself/O sat/O beside/O his/O queen/O ./O 
When/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON seated/O himself/O to/O her/O right/O ,/O she/O felt/O her/O throat/O tighten/O ./O 
He/O had/O not/O spoken/O a/O word/O to/O her/O since/O the/O awful/O thing/O had/O happened/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O not/O dared/O to/O speak/O to/O him/O ./O 
At/O first/O she/O thought/O she/O hated/O him/O for/O what/O they/O 'd/O done/O to/O Lady/O ,/O but/O after/O Sansa/PERSON had/O wept/O her/O eyes/O dry/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O that/O it/O had/O not/O been/O Joffrey/PERSON '/O s/O doing/O ,/O not/O truly/O ./O 
The/O queen/O had/O done/O it/O ;/O she/O was/O the/O one/O to/O hate/O ,/O her/O and/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
Nothing/O bad/O would/O have/O happened/O except/O for/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O could/O not/O hate/O Joffrey/PERSON tonight/O ./O 
He/O was/O too/O beautiful/O to/O hate/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O deep/O blue/O doublet/O studded/O with/O a/O double/O row/O of/O golden/O lion/O 's/O heads/O ,/O and/O around/O his/O brow/O a/O slim/O coronet/O made/O of/O gold/O and/O sapphires/O ./O 
His/O hair/O was/O as/O bright/O as/O the/O metal/O ./O 
Sansa/O looked/O at/O him/O and/O trembled/O ,/O afraid/O that/O he/O might/O ignore/O her/O or/O ,/O worse/O ,/O turn/O hateful/O again/O and/O send/O her/O weeping/O from/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Instead/O Joffrey/PERSON smiled/O and/O kissed/O her/O hand/O ,/O handsome/O and/O gallant/O as/O any/O prince/O in/O the/O songs/O ,/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON has/O a/O keen/O eye/O for/O beauty/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O too/O kind/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O demurred/O ,/O trying/O to/O remain/O modest/O and/O calm/O ,/O though/O her/O heart/O was/O singing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Loras/O is/O a/O true/O knight/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O he/O will/O win/O tomorrow/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O dog/O will/O do/O for/O him/O ,/O or/O perhaps/O my/O uncle/O Jaime/PERSON ./O 
And/O in/O a/O few/O years/O ,/O when/O I/O am/O old/O enough/O to/O enter/O the/O lists/O ,/O I/O shall/O do/O for/O them/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O raised/O his/O hand/O to/O summon/O a/O servant/O with/O a/O flagon/O of/O iced/O summerwine/O ,/O and/O poured/O her/O a/O cup/O ./O 
She/O looked/O anxiously/O at/O Septa/ORGANIZATION Mordane/ORGANIZATION ,/O until/O Joffrey/PERSON leaned/O over/O and/O filled/O the/O septa/O 's/O cup/O as/O well/O ,/O so/O she/O nodded/O and/O thanked/O him/O graciously/O and/O said/O not/O another/O word/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O servants/O kept/O the/O cups/O filled/O all/O night/O ,/O yet/O afterward/O Sansa/O could/O not/O recall/O ever/O tasting/O the/O wine/O ./O 
She/O needed/O no/O wine/O ./O 
She/O was/O drunk/O on/O the/O magic/O of/O the/O night/O ,/O giddy/O with/O glamour/O ,/O swept/O away/O by/O beauties/O she/O had/O dreamt/O of/O all/O her/O life/O and/O never/O dared/O hope/O to/O know/O ./O 
Singers/O sat/O before/O the/O king/O 's/O pavilion/O ,/O filling/O the/O dusk/O with/O music/O ./O 
A/O juggler/O kept/O a/O cascade/O of/O burning/O clubs/O spinning/O through/O the/O air/O ./O 
The/O king/O 's/O own/O fool/O ,/O the/O pie-faced/O simpleton/O called/O Moon/PERSON Boy/PERSON ,/O danced/O about/O on/O stilts/O ,/O all/O in/O motley/O ,/O making/O mock/O of/O everyone/O with/O such/O deft/O cruelty/O that/O Sansa/PERSON wondered/O if/O he/O was/O simple/O after/O all/O ./O 
Even/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON was/O helpless/O before/O him/O ;/O when/O he/O sang/O his/O little/O song/O about/O the/O High/O Septon/O ,/O she/O laughed/O so/O hard/O she/O spilled/O wine/O on/O herself/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O Joffrey/PERSON was/O the/O soul/O of/O courtesy/O ./O 
He/O talked/O to/O Sansa/O all/O night/O ,/O showering/O her/O with/O compliments/O ,/O making/O her/O laugh/O ,/O sharing/O little/O bits/O of/O court/O gossip/O ,/O explaining/O Moon/PERSON Boy/PERSON 's/O japes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/PERSON was/O so/O captivated/O that/O she/O quite/O forgot/O all/O her/O courtesies/O and/O ignored/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON ,/O seated/O to/O her/O left/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O All/O the/O while/O the/O courses/O came/O and/O went/O ./O 
A/O thick/O soup/O of/O barley/O and/O venison/O ./O 
Salads/O of/O sweetgrass/O and/O spinach/O and/O plums/O ,/O sprinkled/O with/O crushed/O nuts/O ./O 
Snails/O in/O honey/O and/O garlic/O ./O 
Sansa/O had/O never/O eaten/O snails/O before/O ;/O Joffrey/PERSON showed/O her/O how/O to/O get/O the/O snail/O out/O of/O the/O shell/O ,/O and/O fed/O her/O the/O first/O sweet/O morsel/O himself/O ./O 
Then/O came/O trout/O fresh/O from/O the/O river/O ,/O baked/O in/O clay/O ;/O her/O prince/O helped/O her/O crack/O open/O the/O hard/O casing/O to/O expose/O the/O flaky/O white/O flesh/O within/O ./O 
And/O when/O the/O meat/O course/O was/O brought/O out/O ,/O he/O served/O her/O himself/O ,/O slicing/O a/O queen/O 's/O portion/O from/O the/O joint/O ,/O smiling/O as/O he/O laid/O it/O on/O her/O plate/O ./O 
She/O could/O see/O from/O the/O way/O he/O moved/O that/O his/O right/O arm/O was/O still/O troubling/O him/O ,/O yet/O he/O uttered/O not/O a/O word/O of/O complaint/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Later/O came/O sweetbreads/O and/O pigeon/O pie/O and/O baked/O apples/O fragrant/O with/O cinnamon/O and/O lemon/O cakes/O frosted/O in/O sugar/O ,/O but/O by/O then/O Sansa/PERSON was/O so/O stuffed/O that/O she/O could/O not/O manage/O more/O than/O two/O little/O lemon/O cakes/O ,/O as/O much/O as/O she/O loved/O them/O ./O 
She/O was/O wondering/O whether/O she/O might/O attempt/O a/O third/O when/O the/O king/O began/O to/O shout/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O King/O Robert/PERSON had/O grown/O louder/O with/O each/O course/O ./O 
From/O time/O to/O time/O Sansa/O could/O hear/O him/O laughing/O or/O roaring/O a/O command/O over/O the/O music/O and/O the/O clangor/O of/O plates/O and/O cutlery/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O too/O far/O away/O for/O her/O to/O make/O out/O his/O words/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O everybody/O heard/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O thundered/O in/O a/O voice/O that/O drowned/O out/O all/O other/O speech/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O shocked/O to/O see/O the/O king/O on/O his/O feet/O ,/O red/O of/O face/O ,/O reeling/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O goblet/O of/O wine/O in/O one/O hand/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O drunk/O as/O a/O man/O could/O be/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O not/O tell/O me/O what/O to/O do/O ,/O woman/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O screamed/O at/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O king/O here/O ,/O do/O you/O understand/O ?/O 
I/O rule/O here/O ,/O and/O if/O I/O say/O that/O I/O will/O fight/O tomorrow/O ,/O I/O will/O fight/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Everyone/O was/O staring/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON saw/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O king/O 's/O brother/O Renly/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O short/O man/O who/O had/O talked/O to/O her/O so/O oddly/O and/O touched/O her/O hair/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O made/O a/O move/O to/O interfere/O ./O 
The/O queen/O 's/O face/O was/O a/O mask/O ,/O so/O bloodless/O that/O it/O might/O have/O been/O sculpted/O from/O snow/O ./O 
She/O rose/O from/O the/O table/O ,/O gathered/O her/O skirts/O around/O her/O ,/O and/O stormed/O off/O in/O silence/O ,/O servants/O trailing/O behind/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O on/O the/O king/O 's/O shoulder/O ,/O but/O the/O king/O shoved/O him/O away/O hard/O ./O 
Lannister/PERSON stumbled/O and/O fell/O ./O 
The/O king/O guffawed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O great/O knight/O ./O 
I/O can/O still/O knock/O you/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
Remember/O that/O ,/O Kingslayer/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O slapped/O his/O chest/O with/O the/O jeweled/O goblet/O ,/O splashing/O wine/O all/O over/O his/O satin/O tunic/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O me/O my/O hammer/O and/O not/O a/O man/O in/O the/O realm/O can/O stand/O before/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jaime/O Lannister/O rose/O and/O brushed/O himself/O off/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O was/O stiff/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON came/O forward/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O spilled/O your/O wine/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
Let/O me/O bring/O you/O a/O fresh/O goblet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O started/O as/O Joffrey/PERSON laid/O his/O hand/O on/O her/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O grows/O late/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O prince/O said/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O queer/O look/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O were/O not/O seeing/O her/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O need/O an/O escort/O back/O to/O the/O castle/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O began/O ./O 
She/O looked/O for/O Septa/O Mordane/O ,/O and/O was/O startled/O to/O find/O her/O with/O her/O head/O on/O the/O table/O ,/O snoring/O soft/O and/O ladylike/O snores/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O mean/O to/O say/O .../O yes/O ,/O thank/O you/O ,/O that/O would/O be/O most/O kind/O ./O 
I/O am/O tired/O ,/O and/O the/O way/O is/O so/O dark/O ./O 
I/O should/O be/O glad/O for/O some/O protection/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON called/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O Dog/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON seemed/O to/O take/O form/O out/O of/O the/O night/O ,/O so/O quickly/O did/O he/O appear/O ./O 
He/O had/O exchanged/O his/O armor/O for/O a/O red/O woolen/O tunic/O with/O a/O leather/O dog/O 's/O head/O sewn/O on/O the/O front/O ./O 
The/O light/O of/O the/O torches/O made/O his/O burned/O face/O shine/O a/O dull/O red/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Take/O my/O betrothed/O back/O to/O the/O castle/O ,/O and/O see/O that/O no/O harm/O befalls/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O prince/O told/O him/O brusquely/O ./O 
And/O without/O even/O a/O word/O of/O farewell/O ,/O Joffrey/PERSON strode/O off/O ,/O leaving/O her/O there/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O could/O feel/O the/O Hound/O watching/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O you/O think/O Joff/PERSON was/O going/O to/O take/O you/O himself/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O laugh/O like/O the/O snarling/O of/O dogs/O in/O a/O pit/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Small/O chance/O of/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O pulled/O her/O unresisting/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O you/O 're/O not/O the/O only/O one/O needs/O sleep/O ./O 
I/O 've/O drunk/O too/O much/O ,/O and/O I/O may/O need/O to/O kill/O my/O brother/O tomorrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O terrified/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON pushed/O at/O Septa/ORGANIZATION Mordane/ORGANIZATION 's/O shoulder/O ,/O hoping/O to/O wake/O her/O ,/O but/O she/O only/O snored/O the/O louder/O ./O 
King/O Robert/PERSON had/O stumbled/O off/O and/O half/O the/O benches/O were/O suddenly/O empty/O ./O 
The/O feast/O was/O over/O ,/O and/O the/O beautiful/O dream/O had/O ended/O with/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O snatched/O up/O a/O torch/O to/O light/O their/O way/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON followed/O close/O beside/O him/O ./O 
The/O ground/O was/O rocky/O and/O uneven/O ;/O the/O flickering/O light/O made/O it/O seem/O to/O shift/O and/O move/O beneath/O her/O ./O 
She/O kept/O her/O eyes/O lowered/O ,/O watching/O where/O she/O placed/O her/O feet/O ./O 
They/O walked/O among/O the/O pavilions/O ,/O each/O with/O its/O banner/O and/O its/O armor/O hung/O outside/O ,/O the/O silence/O weighing/O heavier/O with/O every/O step/O ./O 
Sansa/O could/O not/O bear/O the/O sight/O of/O him/O ,/O he/O frightened/O her/O so/O ,/O yet/O she/O had/O been/O raised/O in/O all/O the/O ways/O of/O courtesy/O ./O 
A/O true/O lady/O would/O not/O notice/O his/O face/O ,/O she/O told/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O rode/O gallantly/O today/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Sandor/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O made/O herself/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON snarled/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Spare/O me/O your/O empty/O little/O compliments/O ,/O girl/O .../O and/O your/O ser/O 's/O ./O 
I/O am/O no/O knight/O ./O 
I/O spit/O on/O them/O and/O their/O vows/O ./O 
My/O brother/O is/O a/O knight/O ./O 
Did/O you/O see/O him/O ride/O today/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O whispered/O ,/O trembling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gallant/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Hound/O finished/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O mocking/O her/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O could/O withstand/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O managed/O at/O last/O ,/O proud/O of/O herself/O ./O 
It/O was/O no/O lie/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON stopped/O suddenly/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O a/O dark/O and/O empty/O field/O ./O 
She/O had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O stop/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Some/O septa/O trained/O you/O well/O ./O 
You/O 're/O like/O one/O of/O those/O birds/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION ,/O are/O n't/O you/O ?/O 
A/O pretty/O little/O talking/O -/O bird/O ,/O repeating/O all/O the/O pretty/O little/O words/O they/O taught/O you/O to/O recite/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O unkind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON could/O feel/O her/O heart/O fluttering/O in/O her/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O frightening/O me/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O go/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O could/O withstand/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Hound/O rasped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O truth/O enough/O ./O 
No/O one/O could/O ever/O withstand/O Gregor/PERSON ./O 
That/O boy/O today/O ,/O his/O second/O joust/O ,/O oh/O ,/O that/O was/O a/O pretty/O bit/O of/O business/O ./O 
You/O saw/O that/O ,/O did/O you/O ?/O 
Fool/O boy/O ,/O he/O had/O no/O business/O riding/O in/O this/O company/O ./O 
No/O money/O ,/O no/O squire/O ,/O no/O one/O to/O help/O him/O with/O that/O armor/O ./O 
That/O gorget/O was/O n't/O fastened/O proper/O ./O 
You/O think/O Gregor/PERSON did/O n't/O notice/O that/O ?/O 
You/O think/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O lance/O rode/O up/O by/O chance/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
Pretty/O little/O talking/O girl/O ,/O you/O believe/O that/O ,/O you/O 're/O empty-headed/O as/O a/O bird/O for/O true/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON 's/O lance/O goes/O where/O Gregor/PERSON wants/O it/O to/O go/O ./O 
Look/O at/O me/O ./O 
Look/O at/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON put/O a/O huge/O hand/O under/O her/O chin/O and/O forced/O her/O face/O up/O ./O 
He/O squatted/O in/O front/O of/O her/O ,/O and/O moved/O the/O torch/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O a/O pretty/O for/O ''/O ,/O ``/O you/O ./O 
Take/O a/O good/O long/O stare/O ./O 
You/O know/O you/O want/O to/O ./O 
I/O 've/O watched/O you/O turning/O away/O all/O the/O way/O down/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
Piss/O on/O that/O ./O 
Take/O your/O look/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O fingers/O held/O her/O jaw/O as/O hard/O as/O an/O iron/O trap/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O watched/O hers/O ./O 
Drunken/O eyes/O ,/O sullen/O with/O anger/O ./O 
She/O had/O to/O look/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O right/O side/O of/O his/O face/O was/O gaunt/O ,/O with/O sharp/O cheekbones/O and/O a/O grey/O eye/O beneath/O a/O heavy/O brow/O ./O 
His/O nose/O was/O large/O and/O hooked/O ,/O his/O hair/O thin/O ,/O dark/O ./O 
He/O wore/O it/O long/O and/O brushed/O it/O sideways/O ,/O because/O no/O hair/O grew/O on/O the/O other/O side/O of/O that/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O left/O side/O of/O his/O face/O was/O a/O ruin/O ./O 
His/O ear/O had/O been/O burned/O away/O ;/O there/O was/O nothing/O left/O but/O a/O hole/O ./O 
His/O eye/O was/O still/O good/O ,/O but/O all/O around/O it/O was/O a/O twisted/O mass/O of/O scar/O ,/O slick/O black/O flesh/O hard/O as/O leather/O ,/O pocked/O with/O craters/O and/O fissured/O by/O deep/O cracks/O that/O gleamed/O red/O and/O wet/O when/O he/O moved/O ./O 
Down/O by/O his/O jaw/O ,/O you/O could/O see/O a/O hint/O of/O bone/O where/O the/O flesh/O had/O been/O seared/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O began/O to/O cry/O ./O 
He/O let/O go/O of/O her/O then/O ,/O and/O snuffed/O out/O the/O torch/O in/O the/O dirt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O pretty/O words/O for/O that/O ,/O girl/O ?/O 
No/O little/O compliment/O the/O septa/O taught/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O When/O there/O was/O no/O answer/O ,/O he/O continued/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Most/O of/O them/O ,/O they/O think/O it/O was/O some/O battle/O ./O 
A/O siege/O ,/O a/O burning/O tower/O ,/O an/O enemy/O with/O a/O torch/O ./O 
One/O fool/O asked/O if/O it/O was/O dragonsbreath/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O laugh/O was/O softer/O this/O time/O ,/O but/O just/O as/O bitter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O tell/O you/O what/O it/O was/O ,/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O a/O voice/O from/O the/O night/O ,/O a/O shadow/O leaning/O so/O close/O now/O that/O she/O could/O smell/O the/O sour/O stench/O of/O wine/O on/O his/O breath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O younger/O than/O you/O ,/O six/O ,/O maybe/O seven/O ./O 
A/O woodcarver/O set/O up/O shop/O in/O the/O village/O under/O my/O father/O 's/O keep/O ,/O and/O to/O buy/O favor/O he/O sent/O us/O gifts/O ./O 
The/O old/O man/O made/O marvelous/O toys/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O remember/O what/O I/O got/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O Gregor/PERSON 's/O gift/O I/O wanted/O ./O 
A/O wooden/O knight/O ,/O all/O painted/O up/O ,/O every/O joint/O pegged/O separate/O and/O fixed/O with/O strings/O ,/O so/O you/O could/O make/O him/O fight/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON is/O five/O years/O older/O than/O me/O ,/O the/O toy/O was/O nothing/O to/O him/O ,/O he/O was/O already/O a/O squire/O ,/O near/O six/O foot/O tall/O and/O muscled/O like/O an/O ox/O ./O 
So/O I/O took/O his/O knight/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O joy/O to/O it/O ,/O I/O tell/O you/O ./O 
I/O was/O scared/O all/O the/O while/O ,/O and/O true/O enough/O ,/O he/O found/O me/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O brazier/O in/O the/O room/O ./O 
Gregor/PERSON never/O said/O a/O word/O ,/O just/O picked/O me/O up/O under/O his/O arm/O and/O shoved/O the/O side/O of/O my/O face/O down/O in/O the/O burning/O coals/O and/O held/O me/O there/O while/O I/O screamed/O and/O screamed/O ./O 
You/O saw/O how/O strong/O he/O is/O ./O 
Even/O then/O ,/O it/O took/O three/O grown/O men/O to/O drag/O him/O off/O me/O ./O 
The/O septons/O preach/O about/O the/O seven/O hells/O ./O 
What/O do/O they/O know/O ?/O 
Only/O a/O man/O who/O 's/O been/O burned/O knows/O what/O hell/O is/O truly/O like/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O father/O told/O everyone/O my/O bedding/O had/O caught/O fire/O ,/O and/O our/O maester/O gave/O me/O ointments/O ./O 
Ointments/O !/O 
Gregor/PERSON got/O his/O ointments/O too/O ./O 
Four/O years/O later/O ,/O they/O anointed/O him/O with/O the/O seven/O oils/O and/O he/O recited/O his/O knightly/O vows/O and/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON tapped/O him/O on/O the/O shoulder/O and/O said/O ,/O `/O Arise/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON ./O '/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O rasping/O voice/O trailed/O off/O ./O 
He/O squatted/O silently/O before/O her/O ,/O a/O hulking/O black/O shape/O shrouded/O in/O the/O night/O ,/O hidden/O from/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON could/O hear/O his/O ragged/O breathing/O ./O 
She/O was/O sad/O for/O him/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
Somehow/O ,/O the/O fear/O had/O gone/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O silence/O went/O on/O and/O on/O ,/O so/O long/O that/O she/O began/O to/O grow/O afraid/O once/O more/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O afraid/O for/O him/O now/O ,/O not/O for/O herself/O ./O 
She/O found/O his/O massive/O shoulder/O with/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O no/O true/O knight/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O to/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O threw/O back/O his/O head/O and/O roared/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON stumbled/O back/O ,/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O caught/O her/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O growled/O at/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O no/O ,/O little/O bird/O ,/O he/O was/O no/O true/O knight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O into/O the/O city/O ,/O Sandor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON said/O not/O a/O word/O ./O 
He/O led/O her/O to/O where/O the/O carts/O were/O waiting/O ,/O told/O a/O driver/O to/O take/O them/O back/O to/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O and/O climbed/O in/O after/O her/O ./O 
They/O rode/O in/O silence/O through/O the/O King/O 's/O Gate/O and/O up/O torchlit/O city/O streets/O ./O 
He/O opened/O the/O postern/O door/O and/O led/O her/O into/O the/O castle/O ,/O his/O burned/O face/O twitching/O and/O his/O eyes/O brooding/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O one/O step/O behind/O her/O as/O they/O climbed/O the/O tower/O stairs/O ./O 
He/O took/O her/O safe/O all/O the/O way/O to/O the/O corridor/O outside/O her/O bedchamber/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O meekly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Hound/O caught/O her/O by/O the/O arm/O and/O leaned/O close/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O things/O I/O told/O you/O tonight/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O his/O voice/O sounding/O even/O rougher/O than/O usual/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O ever/O tell/O Joffrey/PERSON .../O your/O sister/O ,/O your/O father/O .../O any/O ofthem/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wo/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O promise/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O not/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O ever/O tell/O anyone/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O finished/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O kill/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
