-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O showing/O Dareon/PERSON how/O best/O to/O deliver/O a/O sidestroke/O when/O the/O new/O recruit/O entered/O the/O practice/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O feet/O should/O be/O farther/O apart/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O urged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O lose/O your/O balance/O ./O 
That/O 's/O good/O ./O 
Now/O pivot/O as/O you/O deliver/O the/O stroke/O ,/O get/O all/O your/O weight/O behind/O the/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dareon/PERSON broke/O off/O and/O lifted/O his/O visor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Seven/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O murmured/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Would/O you/O look/O at/O this/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON turned/O ./O 
Through/O the/O eye/O slit/O of/O his/O helm/O ,/O he/O beheld/O the/O fattest/O boy/O he/O had/O ever/O seen/O standing/O in/O the/O door/O of/O the/O armory/O ./O 
By/O the/O look/O of/O him/O ,/O he/O must/O have/O weighed/O twenty/O stone/O ./O 
The/O fur/O collar/O of/O his/O embroidered/O surcoat/O was/O lost/O beneath/O his/O chins/O ./O 
Pale/O eyes/O moved/O nervously/O in/O a/O great/O round/O moon/O of/O a/O face/O ,/O and/O plump/O sweaty/O fingers/O wiped/O themselves/O on/O the/O velvet/O of/O his/O doublet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O .../O they/O told/O me/O I/O was/O to/O come/O here/O for/O .../O for/O training/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O to/O no/O one/O in/O particular/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O lordling/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON observed/O to/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Southron/O ,/O most/O like/O near/O Highgarden/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON had/O traveled/O the/O Seven/O Kingdo/PERSON ms/O with/O a/O mummers/O '/O troupe/O ,/O and/O bragged/O that/O he/O could/O tell/O what/O you/O were/O and/O where/O you/O 'd/O been/O born/O just/O from/O the/O sound/O of/O your/O voice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O striding/O huntsman/O had/O been/O worked/O in/O scarlet/O thread/O upon/O the/O breast/O of/O the/O fat/O boy/O 's/O fur/O -/O trimmed/O surcoat/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON did/O not/O recognize/O the/O sigil/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON looked/O over/O his/O new/O charge/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O they/O have/O run/O short/O of/O poachers/O and/O thieves/O down/O south/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O they/O send/O us/O pigs/O to/O man/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Is/O fur/O and/O velvet/O your/O notion/O of/O armor/O ,/O my/O Lord/O of/O Ham/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O soon/O revealed/O that/O the/O new/O recruit/O had/O brought/O his/O own/O armor/O with/O him/O ;/O padded/O doublet/O ,/O boiled/O leather/O ,/O mail/O and/O plate/O and/O helm/O ,/O even/O a/O great/O wood-and-leather/O shield/O blazoned/O with/O the/O same/O striding/O huntsman/O he/O wore/O on/O his/O surcoat/O ./O 
As/O none/O of/O it/O was/O black/O ,/O however/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON insisted/O that/O he/O reequip/O himself/O from/O the/O armory/O ./O 
That/O took/O half/O the/O morning/O ./O 
His/O girth/O required/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON to/O take/O apart/O a/O mail/O hauberk/O and/O refit/O it/O with/O leather/O panels/O at/O the/O sides/O ./O 
To/O get/O a/O helm/O over/O his/O head/O the/O armorer/O had/O to/O detach/O the/O visor/O ./O 
His/O leathers/O bound/O so/O tightly/O around/O his/O legs/O and/O under/O his/O arms/O that/O he/O could/O scarcely/O move/O ./O 
Dressed/O for/O battle/O ,/O the/O new/O boy/O looked/O like/O an/O overcooked/O sausage/O about/O to/O burst/O its/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O us/O hope/O you/O are/O not/O as/O inept/O as/O you/O look/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Haider/PERSON ,/O see/O what/O Ser/O Piggy/O can/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/O Snow/O winced/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON had/O been/O born/O in/O a/O quarry/O and/O apprenticed/O as/O a/O stonemason/O ./O 
He/O was/O sixteen/O ,/O tall/O and/O muscular/O ,/O and/O his/O blows/O were/O as/O hard/O as/O any/O Jon/PERSON had/O ever/O felt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O will/O be/O uglier/O than/O a/O whore/O 's/O ass/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON muttered/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O fight/O lasted/O less/O than/O a/O minute/O before/O the/O fat/O boy/O was/O on/O the/O ground/O ,/O his/O whole/O body/O shaking/O as/O blood/O leaked/O through/O his/O shattered/O helm/O and/O between/O his/O pudgy/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O yield/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shrilled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O more/O ,/O I/O yield/O ,/O do/O n't/O hit/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Rast/PERSON and/O some/O of/O the/O other/O boys/O were/O laughing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O then/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON would/O not/O call/O an/O end/O ./O 
\/O ``/O On/O your/O feet/O ,/O Ser/O Piggy/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Pick/O up/O your/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O When/O the/O boy/O continued/O to/O cling/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O Thorne/PERSON gestured/O to/O Haider/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Hit/O him/O with/O the/O flat/O of/O your/O blade/O until/O he/O finds/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Haider/PERSON delivered/O a/O tentative/O smack/O to/O his/O foe/O 's/O upraised/O cheeks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O can/O hit/O harder/O than/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Thorne/PERSON taunted/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON took/O hold/O of/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O longsword/O with/O both/O hands/O and/O brought/O it/O down/O so/O hard/O the/O blow/O split/O leather/O ,/O even/O on/O the/O flat/O ./O 
The/O new/O boy/O screeched/O in/O pain/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON took/O a/O step/O forward/O ./O 
Pyp/O laid/O a/O mailed/O hand/O on/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O no/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O small/O boy/O whispered/O with/O an/O anxious/O glance/O at/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O On/O your/O feet/O ,/O \/O ''/O Thorne/PERSON repeated/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O struggled/O to/O rise/O ,/O slipped/O ,/O and/O fell/O heavily/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Piggy/O is/O starting/O to/O grasp/O the/O notion/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON observed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Again/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Haider/PERSON lifted/O the/O sword/O for/O another/O blow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cut/O us/O off/O a/O ham/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Rast/PERSON urged/O ,/O laughing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shook/O off/O Pyp/PERSON 's/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Haider/PERSON ,/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Haider/PERSON looked/O to/O Ser/O Alliser/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Bastard/O speaks/O and/O the/O peasants/O tremble/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O master-at-arms/O said/O in/O that/O sharp/O ,/O cold/O voice/O of/O his/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O remind/O you/O that/O I/O am/O the/O master-at-arms/O here/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Look/O at/O him/O ,/O Haider/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON urged/O ,/O ignoring/O Thorne/PERSON as/O best/O he/O could/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O no/O honor/O in/O beating/O a/O fallen/O foe/O ./O 
He/O yielded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O knelt/O beside/O the/O fat/O boy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Haider/PERSON lowered/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O yielded/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O echoed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Alliser/O 's/O onyx/O eyes/O were/O fixed/O on/O Jon/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O seem/O our/O Bastard/O is/O in/O love/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O Jon/PERSON helped/O the/O fat/O boy/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Show/O me/O your/O steel/O ,/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON drew/O his/O longsword/O ./O 
He/O dared/O defy/O Ser/O Alliser/O only/O to/O a/O point/O ,/O and/O he/O feared/O he/O was/O well/O beyond/O it/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Thorne/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Bastard/O wishes/O to/O defend/O his/O lady/O love/O ,/O so/O we/O shall/O make/O an/O exercise/O of/O it/O ./O 
Rat/O ,/O Pimple/O ,/O help/O our/O Stone/O Head/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Rast/PERSON and/O Albett/PERSON moved/O to/O join/O Haider/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O of/O you/O ought/O to/O be/O sufficient/O to/O make/O Lady/O Piggy/O squeal/O ./O 
All/O you/O need/O do/O is/O get/O past/O the/O Bastard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stay/O behind/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O to/O the/O fat/O boy/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON had/O often/O sent/O two/O foes/O against/O him/O ,/O but/O never/O three/O ./O 
He/O knew/O he/O would/O likely/O go/O to/O sleep/O bruised/O and/O bloody/O tonight/O ./O 
He/O braced/O himself/O for/O the/O assault/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Suddenly/O Pyp/O was/O beside/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O to/O two/O will/O make/O for/O better/O sport/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O small/O boy/O said/O cheerfully/O ./O 
He/O dropped/O his/O visor/O and/O slid/O out/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Before/O Jon/PERSON could/O even/O think/O to/O protest/O ,/O Grenn/PERSON had/O stepped/O up/O to/O make/O a/O third/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O yard/O had/O grown/O deathly/O quiet/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O feel/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O are/O you/O waiting/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O Rast/PERSON and/O the/O others/O in/O a/O voice/O gone/O deceptively/O soft/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O Jon/PERSON who/O moved/O first/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON barely/O got/O his/O sword/O up/O in/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON drove/O him/O backward/O ,/O attacking/O with/O every/O blow/O ,/O keeping/O the/O older/O boy/O on/O the/O heels/O ./O 
Know/O your/O foe/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON had/O taught/O him/O once/O ;/O Jon/PERSON knew/O Haider/PERSON ,/O brutally/O strong/O but/O short/O of/O patience/O ,/O with/O no/O taste/O for/O defense/O ./O 
Frustrate/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O would/O leave/O himself/O open/O ,/O as/O certain/O as/O sunset/O ./O 
The/O clang/O of/O steel/O echoed/O through/O the/O yard/O as/O the/O others/O joined/O battle/O around/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON blocked/O a/O savage/O cut/O at/O his/O head/O ,/O the/O shock/O of/O impact/O running/O up/O his/O arm/O as/O the/O swords/O crashed/O together/O ./O 
He/O slammed/O a/O sidestroke/O into/O Haider/PERSON 's/O ribs/O ,/O and/O was/O rewarded/O with/O a/O muffled/O grunt/O of/O pain/O ./O 
The/O counterstroke/O caught/O Jon/PERSON on/O the/O shoulder/O ./O 
Chainmail/O crunched/O ,/O and/O pain/O flared/O up/O his/O neck/O ,/O but/O for/O an/O instant/O Haider/PERSON was/O unbalanced/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON cut/O his/O left/O leg/O from/O under/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O fell/O with/O a/O curse/O and/O a/O crash/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grenn/PERSON was/O standing/O his/O ground/O as/O Jon/PERSON had/O taught/O him/O ,/O giving/O Albett/PERSON more/O than/O he/O cared/O for/O ,/O but/O Pyp/PERSON was/O hard-pressed/O ./O 
Rast/PERSON had/O two/O years/O and/O forty/O pounds/O on/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON stepped/O up/O behind/O him/O and/O rang/O the/O raper/O 's/O helm/O like/O a/O bell/O ./O 
As/O Rast/PERSON went/O reeling/O ,/O Pyp/PERSON slid/O in/O under/O his/O guard/O ,/O knocked/O him/O down/O ,/O and/O leveled/O a/O blade/O at/O his/O throat/O ./O 
By/O then/O Jon/PERSON had/O moved/O on/O ./O 
Facing/O two/O swords/O ,/O Albett/PERSON backed/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O yield/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON Thorne/PERSON surveyed/O the/O scene/O with/O disgust/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O mummer/O 's/O farce/O has/O gone/O on/O long/O enough/O for/O today/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O away/O ./O 
The/O session/O was/O at/O an/O end/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dareon/PERSON helped/O Haider/PERSON to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
The/O quarryman/O 's/O son/O wrenched/O off/O his/O helm/O and/O threw/O it/O across/O the/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O an/O instant/O ,/O I/O thought/O I/O finally/O had/O you/O ,/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O an/O instant/O ,/O you/O did/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON replied/O ./O 
Under/O his/O mail/O and/O leather/O ,/O his/O shoulder/O was/O throbbing/O ./O 
He/O sheathed/O his/O sword/O and/O tried/O to/O remove/O his/O helm/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O raised/O his/O arm/O ,/O the/O pain/O made/O him/O grit/O his/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O voice/O said/O ./O 
Thick-fingered/O hands/O unfastened/O helm/O from/O gorget/O and/O lifted/O it/O off/O gently/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O he/O hurt/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O been/O bruised/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O touched/O his/O shoulder/O and/O winced/O ./O 
The/O yard/O was/O emptying/O around/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Blood/O matted/O the/O fat/O boy/O 's/O hair/O where/O Haider/PERSON had/O split/O his/O helm/O asunder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O name/O is/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON ,/O of/O Horn/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O stopped/O and/O licked/O his/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O mean/O ,/O I/O was/O of/O Horn/PERSON Hill/PERSON ,/O until/O I./O ./O 
./O 
left/O ./O 
I/O 've/O come/O to/O take/O the/O black/O ./O 
My/O father/O is/O Lord/PERSON Randyll/PERSON ,/O a/O bannerman/O to/O the/O Tyrells/O of/O Highgarden/LOCATION ./O 
I/O used/O to/O be/O his/O heir/O ,/O only/O His/O voice/O trailed/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ,/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O bastard/O ,/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
My/O mother/O calls/O me/O Sam/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O can/O call/O him/O Lord/O Snow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O as/O he/O came/O up/O to/O join/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O know/O what/O his/O mother/O calls/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O These/O two/O are/O Grenn/PERSON and/O Pypar/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Grenn/O 's/O the/O ugly/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grenn/PERSON scowled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O uglier/O than/O me/O ./O 
At/O least/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O ears/O like/O a/O bat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O thanks/O to/O all/O of/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O fat/O boy/O said/O gravely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O did/O n't/O you/O get/O up/O and/O fight/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON demanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wanted/O to/O ,/O truly/O ./O 
I/O just/O .../O I/O could/O n't/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O want/O him/O to/O hit/O me/O anymore/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O at/O the/O ground/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
My/O lord/O father/O always/O said/O so/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Grenn/O looked/O thunderstruck/O ./O 
Even/O Pyp/PERSON had/O no/O words/O to/O say/O to/O that/O ,/O and/O Pyp/PERSON had/O words/O for/O everything/O ./O 
What/O sort/O of/O man/O would/O proclaim/O himself/O a/O coward/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Samwell/O Tarly/O must/O have/O read/O their/O thoughts/O on/O their/O faces/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O met/O Jon/PERSON 's/O and/O darted/O away/O ,/O quick/O as/O frightened/O animals/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O 'm/O sorry/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O mean/O to/O .../O to/O be/O like/O I/O am/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O heavily/O toward/O the/O armory/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON called/O after/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O were/O hurt/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tomorrow/O you/O 'll/O do/O better/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON looked/O mournfully/O back/O over/O one/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O I/O wo/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O blinking/O back/O tears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O do/O better/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O he/O was/O gone/O ,/O Grenn/PERSON frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Nobody/O likes/O cravens/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O uncomfortably/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wish/O we/O had/O n't/O helped/O him/O ./O 
What/O if/O they/O think/O we/O 're/O craven/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O too/O stupid/O to/O be/O craven/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O you/O are/O ./O 
If/O a/O bear/O attacked/O you/O in/O the/O woods/O ,/O you/O 'd/O be/O too/O stupid/O to/O run/O away/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O run/O away/O faster/O than/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stopped/O suddenly/O ,/O scowling/O when/O he/O saw/O Pyp/PERSON 's/O grin/O and/O realized/O what/O he/O 'd/O just/O said/O ./O 
His/O thick/O neck/O flushed/O a/O dark/O red/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON left/O them/O there/O arguing/O as/O he/O returned/O to/O the/O armory/O ,/O hung/O up/O his/O sword/O ,/O and/O stripped/O off/O his/O battered/O armor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Life/O at/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION followed/O certain/O patterns/O ;/O the/O mornings/O were/O for/O swordplay/O ,/O the/O afternoons/O for/O work/O ./O 
The/O black/O brothers/O set/O new/O recruits/O to/O many/O different/O tasks/O ,/O to/O learn/O where/O their/O skills/O lay/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON cherished/O the/O rare/O afternoons/O when/O he/O was/O sent/O out/O with/O Ghost/O ranging/O at/O his/O side/O to/O bring/O back/O game/O for/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O table/O ,/O but/O for/O every/O day/O spent/O hunting/O ,/O he/O gave/O a/O dozen/O to/O Donal/PERSON Noye/PERSON in/O the/O armory/O ,/O spinning/O the/O whetstone/O while/O the/O one-armed/O smith/O sharpened/O axes/O grown/O dull/O from/O use/O ,/O or/O pumping/O the/O bellows/O as/O Noye/PERSON hammered/O out/O a/O new/O sword/O ./O 
Other/O times/O he/O ran/O messages/O ,/O stood/O at/O guard/O ,/O mucked/O out/O stables/O ,/O fletched/O arrows/O ,/O assisted/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON with/O his/O birds/O or/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON with/O his/O counts/O and/O inventories/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O afternoon/O ,/O the/O watch/O commander/O sent/O him/O to/O the/O winch/O cage/O with/O four/O barrels/O of/O fresh/O -/O crushed/O stone/O ,/O to/O scatter/O gravel/O over/O the/O icy/O footpaths/O atop/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
It/O was/O lonely/O and/O boring/O work/O ,/O even/O with/O Ghost/O along/O for/O company/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON found/O he/O did/O not/O mind/O ./O 
On/O a/O clear/O day/O you/O could/O see/O half/O the/O world/O from/O the/O top/O of/O the/O Wall/O ,/O and/O the/O air/O was/O always/O cold/O and/O bracing/O ./O 
He/O could/O think/O here/O ,/O and/O he/O found/O himself/O thinking/O of/O Samwell/O Tarly/O .../O and/O ,/O oddly/O ,/O of/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O what/O Tyrion/PERSON would/O have/O made/O of/O the/O fat/O boy/O ./O 
Most/O men/O would/O rather/O deny/O a/O hard/O truth/O than/O face/O it/O ,/O the/O dwarf/O had/O told/O him/O ,/O grinning/O ./O 
The/O world/O was/O full/O of/O cravens/O who/O pretended/O to/O be/O heroes/O ;/O it/O took/O a/O queer/O sort/O of/O courage/O to/O admit/O to/O cowardice/O as/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON had/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O sore/O shoulder/O made/O the/O work/O go/O slowly/O ./O 
It/O was/O late/O afternoon/O before/O Jon/PERSON finished/O graveling/O the/O paths/O ./O 
He/O lingered/O on/O high/O to/O watch/O the/O sun/O go/O down/O ,/O turning/O the/O western/O sky/O the/O color/O of/O blood/O ./O 
Finally/O ,/O as/O dusk/O was/O settling/O over/O the/O north/O ,/O Jon/PERSON rolled/O the/O empty/O barrels/O back/O into/O the/O cage/O and/O signaled/O the/O winch/O men/O to/O lower/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O evening/O meal/O was/O almost/O done/O by/O the/O time/O he/O and/O Ghost/O reached/O the/O common/O hall/O ./O 
A/O group/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O were/O dicing/O over/O mulled/O wine/O near/O the/O fire/O ./O 
His/O friends/O were/O at/O the/O bench/O nearest/O the/O west/O wall/O ,/O laughing/O ./O 
Pyp/O was/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O a/O story/O ./O 
The/O mummer/O 's/O boy/O with/O the/O big/O ears/O was/O a/O born/O liar/O with/O a/O hundred/O different/O voices/O ,/O and/O he/O did/O not/O tell/O his/O tales/O so/O much/O as/O live/O them/O ,/O playing/O all/O the/O parts/O as/O needed/O ,/O a/O king/O one/O moment/O and/O a/O swineherd/O the/O next/O ./O 
When/O he/O turned/O into/O an/O alehouse/O girl/O or/O a/O virgin/O princess/O ,/O he/O used/O a/O high/O falsetto/O voice/O that/O reduced/O them/O all/O to/O tears/O of/O helpless/O laughter/O ,/O and/O his/O eunuchs/O were/O always/O eerily/O accurate/O caricatures/O of/O Ser/O Alliser/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON took/O as/O much/O pleasure/O from/O Pyp/PERSON 's/O antics/O as/O anyone/O .../O yet/O that/O night/O he/O turned/O away/O and/O went/O instead/O to/O the/O end/O of/O the/O bench/O ,/O where/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON sat/O alone/O ,/O as/O far/O from/O the/O others/O as/O he/O could/O get/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O finishing/O the/O last/O of/O the/O pork/O pie/O the/O cooks/O had/O served/O up/O for/O supper/O when/O Jon/PERSON sat/O down/O across/O from/O him/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O 's/O eyes/O widened/O at/O the/O sight/O of/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O a/O wolf/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O direwolf/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O His/O name/O is/O Ghost/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O is/O the/O sigil/O of/O my/O father/O 's/O House/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ours/O is/O a/O striding/O huntsman/O ,/O \/O ''/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O like/O to/O hunt/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O fat/O boy/O shuddered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O was/O going/O to/O cry/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O 's/O wrong/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON asked/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O are/O you/O always/O so/O frightened/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON stared/O at/O the/O last/O of/O his/O pork/O pie/O and/O gave/O a/O feeble/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ,/O too/O scared/O even/O to/O talk/O ./O 
A/O burst/O of/O laughter/O filled/O the/O hall/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON heard/O Pyp/O squeaking/O in/O a/O high/O voice/O ./O 
He/O stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O 's/O go/O outside/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O round/O fat/O face/O looked/O up/O at/O him/O ,/O suspicious/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
What/O will/O we/O do/O outside/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Talk/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O seen/O the/O Wall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O fat/O ,/O not/O blind/O ,/O \/O ''/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Of/O course/O I/O saw/O it/O ,/O it/O 's/O seven/O hundred/O feet/O high/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Yet/O he/O stood/O up/O all/O the/O same/O ,/O wrapped/O a/O furlined/O cloak/O over/O his/O shoulders/O ,/O and/O followed/O Jon/PERSON from/O the/O common/O hall/O ,/O still/O wary/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O suspected/O some/O cruel/O trick/O was/O waiting/O for/O him/O in/O the/O night/O ./O 
Ghost/O padded/O along/O beside/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O thought/O it/O would/O be/O like/O this/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON said/O as/O they/O walked/O ,/O his/O words/O steaming/O in/O the/O cold/O air/O ./O 
Already/O he/O was/O huffing/O and/O puffing/O as/O he/O tried/O to/O keep/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O the/O buildings/O are/O falling/O down/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O so/O .../O so/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cold/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O A/O hard/O frost/O was/O settling/O over/O the/O castle/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON could/O hear/O the/O soft/O crunch/O of/O grey/O weeds/O beneath/O his/O boots/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON nodded/O miserably/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O the/O cold/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Last/O night/O I/O woke/O up/O in/O the/O dark/O and/O the/O fire/O had/O gone/O out/O and/O I/O was/O certain/O I/O was/O going/O to/O freeze/O to/O death/O by/O morning/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O must/O have/O been/O warmer/O where/O you/O come/O from/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O never/O saw/O snow/O until/O last/O month/O ./O 
We/O were/O crossing/O the/O barrowlands/O ,/O me/O and/O the/O men/O my/O father/O sent/O to/O see/O me/O north/O ,/O and/O this/O white/O stuff/O began/O to/O fall/O ,/O like/O a/O soft/O rain/O ./O 
At/O first/O I/O thought/O it/O was/O so/O beautiful/O ,/O like/O feathers/O drifting/O from/O the/O sky/O ,/O but/O it/O kept/O on/O and/O on/O ,/O until/O I/O was/O frozen/O to/O the/O bone/O ./O 
The/O men/O had/O crusts/O of/O snow/O in/O their/O beards/O and/O more/O on/O their/O shoulders/O ,/O and/O still/O it/O kept/O coming/O ./O 
I/O was/O afraid/O it/O would/O never/O end/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON smiled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Wall/O loomed/O before/O them/O ,/O glimmering/O palely/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O half/O moon/O ./O 
In/O the/O sky/O above/O ,/O the/O stars/O burned/O clear/O and/O sharp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O they/O going/O to/O make/O me/O go/O up/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON asked/O ./O 
His/O face/O curdled/O like/O old/O milk/O as/O he/O looked/O at/O the/O great/O wooden/O stairs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O die/O if/O I/O have/O to/O climb/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O 's/O a/O winch/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ,/O pointing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O can/O draw/O you/O up/O in/O a/O cage/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON sniffled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O like/O high/O places/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O too/O much/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON frowned/O ,/O incredulous/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O afraid/O of/O everything/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O understand/O ./O 
If/O you/O are/O truly/O so/O craven/O ,/O why/O are/O you/O here/O ?/O 
Why/O would/O a/O coward/O want/O to/O join/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Samwell/O Tarly/O looked/O at/O him/O for/O a/O long/O moment/O ,/O and/O his/O round/O face/O seemed/O to/O cave/O in/O on/O itself/O ./O 
He/O sat/O down/O on/O the/O frost-covered/O ground/O and/O began/O to/O cry/O ,/O huge/O choking/O sobs/O that/O made/O his/O ''/O ,/O ``/O whole/O body/O shake/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON could/O only/O stand/O and/O watch/O ./O 
Like/O the/O snowfall/O on/O the/O barrowlands/O ,/O it/O seemed/O the/O tears/O would/O never/O end/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O Ghost/O who/O knew/O what/O to/O do/O ./O 
Silent/O as/O shadow/O ,/O the/O pale/O direwo/O If/O moved/O closer/O and/O began/O to/O lick/O the/O warm/O tears/O off/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O cried/O out/O ,/O startled/O .../O and/O somehow/O ,/O in/O a/O heartbeat/O ,/O his/O sobs/O turned/O to/O laughter/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON laughed/O with/O him/O ./O 
Afterward/O they/O sat/O on/O the/O frozen/O ground/O ,/O huddled/O in/O their/O cloaks/O with/O Ghost/O between/O them/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON told/O the/O story/O of/O how/O he/O and/O Robb/PERSON had/O found/O the/O pups/O newborn/O in/O the/O late/O summer/O snows/O ./O 
It/O seemed/O a/O thousand/O years/O ago/O now/O ./O 
Before/O long/O he/O found/O himself/O talking/O of/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sometimes/O I/O dream/O about/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O walking/O down/O this/O long/O empty/O hall/O ./O 
My/O voice/O echoes/O all/O around/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O answers/O ,/O so/O I/O walk/O faster/O ,/O opening/O doors/O ,/O shouting/O names/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O even/O know/O who/O I/O 'm/O looking/O for/O ./O 
Most/O nights/O it/O 's/O my/O father/O ,/O but/O sometimes/O it/O 's/O Robb/PERSON instead/O ,/O or/O my/O little/O sister/O Arya/PERSON ,/O or/O my/O uncle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O thought/O of/O Benjen/O Stark/O saddened/O him/O ;/O his/O uncle/O was/O still/O missing/O ./O 
The/O Old/O Bear/O had/O sent/O out/O rangers/O in/O search/O of/O him/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON had/O led/O two/O sweeps/O ,/O and/O Quorin/PERSON Halfhand/PERSON had/O gone/O forth/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Tower/O ,/O but/O they/O 'd/O found/O nothing/O aside/O from/O a/O few/O blazes/O in/O the/O trees/O that/O his/O uncle/O had/O left/O to/O mark/O his/O way/O ./O 
In/O the/O stony/O highlands/O to/O the/O northwest/O ,/O the/O marks/O stopped/O abruptly/O and/O all/O trace/O of/O Ben/PERSON Stark/PERSON vanished/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O ever/O find/O anyone/O in/O your/O dream/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O one/O ./O 
The/O castle/O is/O always/O empty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O never/O told/O anyone/O of/O the/O dream/O ,/O and/O he/O did/O not/O understand/O why/O he/O was/O telling/O Sam/PERSON now/O ,/O yet/O somehow/O it/O felt/O good/O to/O talk/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O the/O ravens/O are/O gone/O from/O the/O rookery/O ,/O and/O the/O stables/O are/O full/O of/O bones/O ./O 
That/O always/O scares/O me/O ./O 
I/O start/O to/O run/O then/O ,/O throwing/O open/O doors/O ,/O climbing/O the/O tower/O three/O steps/O at/O a/O time/O ,/O screaming/O for/O someone/O ,/O for/O anyone/O ./O 
And/O then/O I/O find/O myself/O in/O front/O of/O the/O door/O to/O the/O crypts/O ./O 
It/O 's/O black/O inside/O ,/O and/O I/O can/O see/O the/O steps/O spiraling/O down/O ./O 
Somehow/O I/O know/O I/O have/O to/O go/O down/O there/O ,/O but/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O afraid/O of/O what/O might/O be/O waiting/O for/O me/O ./O 
The/O old/O Kings/O of/O Winter/O are/O down/O there/O ,/O sitting/O on/O their/O thrones/O with/O stone/O wolves/O at/O their/O feet/O and/O iron/O swords/O across/O their/O laps/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O not/O them/O I/O 'm/O afraid/O of/O ./O 
I/O scream/O that/O I/O 'm/O not/O a/O Stark/O ,/O that/O this/O is/O n't/O my/O place/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O no/O good/O ,/O I/O have/O to/O go/O anyway/O ,/O so/O I/O start/O down/O ,/O feeling/O the/O walls/O as/O I/O descend/O ,/O with/O no/O torch/O to/O light/O the/O way/O ./O 
It/O gets/O darker/O and/O darker/O ,/O until/O I/O want/O to/O scream/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O stopped/O ,/O frowning/O ,/O embarrassed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O when/O I/O always/O wake/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O skin/O cold/O and/O clammy/O ,/O shivering/O in/O the/O darkness/O of/O his/O cell/O ./O 
Ghost/O would/O leap/O up/O beside/O him/O ,/O his/O warmth/O as/O comforting/O as/O daybreak/O ./O 
He/O would/O go/O back/O to/O sleep/O with/O his/O face/O pressed/O into/O the/O direwolfs/O shaggy/O white/O fur/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O dream/O of/O Horn/PERSON Hill/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON 's/O mouth/O grew/O tight/O and/O hard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hated/O it/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O scratched/O Ghost/O behind/O the/O ear/O ,/O brooding/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON let/O the/O silence/O breathe/O ./O 
After/O a/O long/O while/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON began/O to/O talk/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON listened/O quietly/O ,/O and/O learned/O how/O it/O was/O that/O a/O self-confessed/O coward/O found/O himself/O on/O the/O Wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Tarlys/O were/O a/O family/O old/O in/O honor/O ,/O bannermen/O to/O Mace/ORGANIZATION Tyrell/ORGANIZATION ,/O Lord/O of/O Highgarden/LOCATION and/O Warden/O of/O the/O South/LOCATION ./O 
The/O eldest/O son/O of/O Lord/O Randyll/PERSON Tarly/PERSON ,/O Samwell/PERSON was/O born/O heir/O to/O rich/O lands/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O a/O strong/O keep/O ,/O and/O a/O storied/O two-handed/O greatsword/O named/O Heartsbane/PERSON ,/O forged/O of/O Valyrian/O steel/O and/O passed/O down/O from/O father/O to/O son/O near/O five/O hundred/O years/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Whatever/O pride/O his/O lord/O father/O might/O have/O felt/O at/O SamwelPs/O birth/O vanished/O as/O the/O boy/O grew/O up/O plump/O ,/O soft/O ,/O and/O awkward/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON loved/O to/O listen/O to/O music/O and/O make/O his/O own/O songs/O ,/O to/O wear/O soft/O velvets/O ,/O to/O play/O in/O the/O castle/O kitchen/O beside/O the/O cooks/O ,/O drinking/O in/O the/O rich/O smells/O as/O he/O snitched/O lemon/O cakes/O and/O blueberry/O tarts/O ./O 
His/O passions/O were/O books/O and/O kittens/O and/O dancing/O ,/O clumsy/O as/O he/O was/O ./O 
But/O he/O grew/O ill/O at/O the/O sight/O of/O blood/O ,/O and/O wept/O to/O see/O even/O a/O chicken/O slaughtered/O ./O 
A/O dozen/O masters-at-arms/O came/O and/O went/O at/O Horn/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION ,/O trying/O to/O turn/O Samwell/PERSON into/O the/O knight/O his/O father/O wanted/O ./O 
The/O boy/O was/O cursed/O and/O caned/O ,/O slapped/O and/O starved/O ./O 
One/O man/O had/O him/O sleep/O in/O his/O chainmail/O to/O make/O him/O more/O martial/O ./O 
Another/O dressed/O him/O in/O his/O mother/O 's/O clothing/O and/O paraded/O him/O through/O the/O bailey/O to/O shame/O him/O into/O valor/O ./O 
He/O only/O grew/O fatter/O and/O more/O frightened/O ,/O until/O Lord/O Randyll/PERSON 's/O disappointment/O turned/O to/O anger/O and/O then/O to/O loathing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O One/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON confided/O ,/O his/O voice/O dropping/O from/O a/O whisper/O ,/O \/O ``/O two/O men/O came/O to/O the/O castle/O ,/O warlocks/O from/O Qarth/LOCATION with/O white/O skin/O and/O blue/O lips/O ./O 
They/O slaughtered/O a/O bull/O aurochs/O and/O made/O me/O bathe/O in/O the/O hot/O blood/O ,/O but/O it/O did/O n't/O make/O me/O brave/O as/O they/O 'd/O promised/O ./O 
I/O got/O sick/O and/O retched/O ./O 
Father/O had/O them/O scourged/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Finally/O ,/O after/O three/O girls/O in/O as/O many/O years/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Tarly/PERSON gave/O her/O lord/O husband/O a/O second/O son/O ./O 
From/O that/O day/O ,/O Lord/O Randyll/PERSON ignored/O Sam/PERSON ,/O devoting/O all/O his/O time/O to/O the/O younger/O boy/O ,/O a/O fierce/O ,/O robust/O child/O more/O to/O his/O liking/O ./O 
Samwell/PERSON had/O known/O several/O years/O of/O sweet/O peace/O with/O his/O music/O and/O his/O books/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Until/O The/O dawn/O of/O his/O fifteenth/O name/O day/O ,/O when/O he/O had/O been/O awakened/O to/O find/O his/O horse/O saddled/O and/O ready/O ./O 
Three/O men-at-arms/O had/O escorted/O him/O into/O a/O wood/O near/O Horn/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION ,/O where/O his/O father/O was/O skinning/O a/O deer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O now/O ,/O and/O my/O heir/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Randyll/PERSON Tarly/PERSON had/O told/O his/O eldest/O son/O ,/O his/O long/O knife/O laying/O bare/O the/O carcass/O as/O he/O spoke/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O given/O me/O no/O cause/O to/O disown/O you/O ,/O but/O neither/O will/O I/O allow/O you/O to/O inherit/O the/O land/O and/O title/O that/O should/O be/O Dickon/PERSON 's/O ./O 
Heartsbane/PERSON must/O go/O to/O a/O man/O strong/O enough/O to/O wield/O her/O ,/O and/O you/O are/O not/O worthy/O to/O touch/O her/O hilt/O ./O 
So/O I/O have/O decided/O that/O you/O shall/O this/O day/O announce/O that/O you/O wish/O to/O take/O the/O black/O ./O 
You/O will/O forsake/O all/O claim/O to/O your/O brother/O 's/O inheritance/O and/O start/O north/O before/O evenfall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O do/O not/O ,/O then/O on/O the/O morrow/O we/O shall/O have/O a/O hunt/O ,/O and/O somewhere/O in/O these/O woods/O your/O horse/O will/O stumble/O ,/O and/O you/O will/O be/O thrown/O from/O the/O saddle/O to/O die/O .../O or/O so/O I/O will/O tell/O your/O mother/O ./O 
She/O has/O a/O woman/O 's/O heart/O and/O finds/O it/O in/O her/O to/O cherish/O even/O you/O ,/O and/O I/O have/O no/O wish/O to/O cause/O her/O pain/O ./O 
Please/O do/O not/O imagine/O that/O it/O will/O truly/O be/O that/O easy/O ,/O should/O you/O think/O to/O defy/O me/O ./O 
Nothing/O would/O please/O me/O more/O than/O to/O hunt/O you/O down/O like/O the/O pig/O you/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O arms/O were/O red/O to/O the/O elbow/O as/O he/O laid/O the/O skinning/O knife/O aside/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O ./O 
There/O is/O your/O choice/O ./O 
The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O \/O ''/O -/O he/O reached/O inside/O the/O deer/O ,/O ripped/O out/O its/O heart/O ,/O and/O held/O it/O in/O his/O fist/O ,/O red/O and/O dripping/O -/O \/O ``/O or/O this/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON told/O the/O tale/O in/O a/O calm/O ,/O dead/O voice/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O were/O something/O that/O had/O happened/O to/O someone/O else/O ,/O not/O to/O him/O ./O 
And/O strangely/O ,/O Jon/PERSON thought/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O weep/O ,/O not/O even/O once/O ./O 
When/O he/O was/O done/O ,/O they/O sat/O together/O and/O listened/O to/O the/O wind/O for/O a/O time/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O other/O sound/O in/O all/O the/O world/O ./O 
Finally/O Jon/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O We/O should/O go/O back/O to/O the/O common/O hall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O hot/O cider/O to/O drink/O ,/O or/O mulled/O wine/O if/O you/O prefer/O ./O 
Some/O nights/O Dareon/PERSON sings/O for/O us/O ,/O if/O the/O mood/O is/O on/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O singer/O ,/O before/O .../O well/O ,/O not/O truly/O ,/O but/O almost/O ,/O an/O apprentice/O singer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O did/O he/O come/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Rowan/PERSON of/O Goldengrove/O found/O him/O in/O bed/O with/O his/O daughter/O ./O 
The/O girl/O was/O two/O years/O older/O ,/O and/O Dareon/PERSON swears/O she/O helped/O him/O through/O her/O window/O ,/O but/O under/O her/O father/O 's/O eye/O she/O named/O it/O rape/O ,/O so/O here/O he/O is/O ./O 
When/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON heard/O him/O sing/O ,/O he/O said/O his/O voice/O was/O honey/O poured/O over/O thunder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Toad/O sometimes/O sings/O too/O ,/O if/O you/O call/O it/O singing/O ./O 
Drinking/O songs/O he/O learned/O in/O his/O father/O 's/O winesink/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON says/O his/O voice/O is/O piss/O poured/O over/O a/O fart/O ./O 
\/O ''/O They/O laughed/O at/O that/O together/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O should/O like/O to/O hear/O them/O both/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON admitted/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O they/O would/O not/O want/O me/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O face/O was/O troubled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O going/O to/O make/O me/O fight/O again/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O is/O n't/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON was/O forced/O to/O say/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON got/O awkwardly/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O better/O try/O to/O sleep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O huddled/O down/O in/O his/O cloak/O and/O plodded/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O others/O were/O still/O in/O the/O common/O room/O when/O Jon/PERSON returned/O ,/O alone/O but/O for/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O have/O you/O been/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Talking/O with/O Sam/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O truly/O is/O craven/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Grenn/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O supper/O ,/O there/O were/O still/O places/O on/O the/O bench/O when/O he/O got/O his/O pie/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O too/O scared/O to/O come/O sit/O with/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lord/O of/O Ham/PERSON thinks/O he/O 's/O too/O good/O to/O eat/O with/O the/O likes/O of/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O suggested/O Jeren/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O saw/O him/O eat/O a/O pork/O pie/O ,/O \/O ''/O Toad/PERSON said/O ,/O smirking/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O it/O was/O a/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O began/O to/O make/O oinking/O noises/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O it/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON snapped/O angrily/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O other/O boys/O fell/O silent/O ,/O taken/O aback/O by/O his/O sudden/O fury/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Listen/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O into/O the/O quiet/O ,/O and/O he/O told/O them/O how/O it/O was/O going/O to/O be/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON backed/O him/O ,/O as/O he/O 'd/O known/O he/O would/O ,/O but/O when/O Haider/PERSON spoke/O up/O ,/O it/O was/O a/O pleasant/O surprise/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON was/O anxious/O at/O the/O first/O ,/O but/O Jon/PERSON knew/O the/O words/O to/O move/O him/O ./O 
One/O by/O one/O the/O rest/O fell/O in/O line/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON persuaded/O some/O ,/O cajoled/O some/O ,/O shamed/O the/O others/O ,/O made/O threats/O where/O threats/O were/O required/O ./O 
At/O the/O end/O they/O had/O all/O agreed/O .../O all/O but/O Rast/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O girls/O do/O as/O you/O please/O ,/O \/O ''/O Rast/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O if/O Thorne/PERSON sends/O me/O against/O Lady/PERSON Piggy/PERSON ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O slice/O me/O off/O a/O rasher/O of/O bacon/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O in/O Jon/PERSON 's/O face/O and/O left/O them/O there/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hours/O later/O ,/O as/O the/O castle/O slept/O ,/O three/O of/O them/O paid/O a/O call/O on/O his/O cell/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON held/O his/O arms/O while/O Pyp/PERSON sat/O on/O his/O legs/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O hear/O Rast/PERSON 's/O rapid/O breathing/O as/O Ghost/O leapt/O onto/O his/O chest/O ./O 
The/O direwolf/O s/O eyes/O burned/O red/O as/O embers/O as/O his/O teeth/O nipped/O lightly/O at/O the/O soft/O skin/O of/O the/O boy/O 's/O throat/O ,/O just/O enough/O to/O draw/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O ,/O we/O know/O where/O you/O sleep/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O softly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O next/O morning/O Jon/PERSON heard/O Rast/PERSON tell/O Albett/PERSON and/O Toad/PERSON how/O his/O razor/O had/O slipped/O while/O he/O shaved/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O that/O day/O forth/O ,/O neither/O Rast/PERSON nor/O any/O of/O the/O others/O would/O hurt/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON ./O 
When/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON matched/O them/O against/O him/O ,/O they/O would/O stand/O their/O ground/O and/O swat/O aside/O his/O slow/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O clumsy/O strokes/O ./O 
If/O the/O master-at-arms/O screamed/O for/O an/O attack/O ,/O they/O would/O dance/O in/O and/O tap/O Sam/PERSON lightly/O on/O breastplate/O or/O helm/O or/O leg/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON raged/O and/O threatened/O and/O called/O them/O all/O cravens/O and/O women/O and/O worse/O ,/O yet/O Sam/PERSON remained/O unhurt/O ./O 
A/O few/O nights/O later/O ,/O at/O Jon/PERSON 's/O urging/O ,/O he/O joined/O them/O for/O the/O evening/O meal/O ,/O taking/O a/O place/O on/O the/O bench/O beside/O Haider/PERSON ./O 
It/O was/O another/O fortnight/O before/O he/O found/O the/O nerve/O to/O join/O their/O talk/O ,/O but/O in/O time/O he/O was/O laughing/O at/O Pyp/LOCATION 's/O faces/O and/O teasing/O Grenn/PERSON with/O the/O best/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Fat/O and/O awkward/O and/O frightened/O he/O might/O be/O ,/O but/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON was/O no/O fool/O ./O 
One/O night/O he/O visited/O Jon/PERSON in/O his/O cell/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O you/O did/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O know/O you/O did/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O away/O shyly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O never/O had/O a/O friend/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 're/O not/O friends/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O put/O a/O hand/O on/O Sam/PERSON 's/O broad/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 're/O brothers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O so/O they/O were/O ,/O he/O thought/O to/O himself/O after/O Sam/PERSON had/O taken/O his/O leave/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON and/O Bran/O and/O Rickon/PERSON were/O his/O father/O 's/O sons/O ,/O and/O he/O loved/O them/O still/O ,/O yet/O Jon/PERSON knew/O that/O he/O had/O never/O truly/O been/O one/O of/O them/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O seen/O to/O that/O ./O 
The/O grey/O walls/O of/O Winterfell/O might/O still/O haunt/O his/O dreams/O ,/O but/O Castle/PERSON Black/PERSON was/O his/O life/O now/O ,/O and/O his/O brothers/O were/O Sam/PERSON and/O Grenn/PERSON and/O Haider/PERSON and/O Pyp/O and/O the/O other/O cast-outs/O who/O wore/O the/O black/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O uncle/O spoke/O truly/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O to/O Ghost/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O if/O he/O would/O ever/O see/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON again/O ,/O to/O tell/O him/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
