-LSB-/O ``/O SANSA/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O would/O n't/O send/O Ser/O Loras/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON told/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON that/O night/O as/O they/O shared/O a/O cold/O supper/O by/O lamplight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O it/O was/O because/O of/O his/O leg/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON had/O taken/O his/O supper/O in/O his/O bedchamber/O with/O Alyn/PERSON ,/O Harwin/PERSON ,/O and/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON ,/O the/O better/O to/O rest/O his/O broken/O leg/O ,/O and/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON had/O complained/O of/O sore/O feet/O after/O standing/O in/O the/O gallery/O all/O day/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O supposed/O to/O join/O them/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O late/O coming/O back/O from/O her/O dancing/O lesson/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O leg/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON said/O uncertainly/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O pretty/O ,/O dark-haired/O girl/O of/O Sansa/O 's/O own/O age/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON hurt/O his/O leg/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O his/O leg/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O nibbling/O delicately/O at/O a/O chicken/O leg/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O 's/O leg/O ,/O silly/O ./O 
It/O hurts/O him/O ever/O so/O much/O ,/O it/O makes/O him/O cross/O ./O 
Otherwise/O I/O 'm/O certain/O he/O would/O have/O sent/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O father/O 's/O decision/O still/O bewildered/O her/O ./O 
When/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/PERSON had/O spoken/O up/O ,/O she/O 'd/O been/O sure/O she/O was/O about/O to/O see/O one/O of/O Old/O Nan/PERSON 's/O stories/O come/O to/O life/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON was/O the/O monster/O and/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON the/O true/O hero/O who/O would/O slay/O him/O ./O 
He/O even/O looked/O a/O true/O hero/O ,/O so/O slim/O and/O beautiful/O ,/O with/O golden/O roses/O around/O his/O slender/O waist/O and/O his/O rich/O brown/O hair/O tumbling/O down/O into/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
And/O then/O Father/O had/O refused/O him/O !/O 
It/O had/O upset/O her/O more/O than/O she/O could/O tell/O ./O 
She/O had/O said/O as/O much/O to/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON as/O they/O descended/O the/O stairs/O from/O the/O gallery/O ,/O but/O the/O septa/O had/O only/O told/O her/O it/O was/O not/O her/O place/O to/O question/O her/O lord/O father/O 's/O decisions/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O when/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON had/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O Septa/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Some/O of/O her/O lord/O father/O 's/O decisions/O could/O do/O with/O a/O bit/O of/O questioning/O ./O 
The/O young/O lady/O is/O as/O wise/O as/O she/O is/O lovely/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O made/O a/O sweeping/O bow/O to/O Sansa/LOCATION ,/O so/O deep/O she/O was/O not/O quite/O sure/O if/O she/O was/O being/O complimented/O or/O mocked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON had/O been/O very/O upset/O to/O realize/O that/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON had/O overheard/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O girl/O was/O just/O talking/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O 'd/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Foolish/O chatter/O ./O 
She/O meant/O nothing/O by/O the/O comment/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON stroked/O his/O little/O pointed/O beard/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O ?/O 
Tell/O me/O ,/O child/O ,/O why/O would/O you/O have/O sent/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O explain/O about/O heroes/O and/O monsters/O ./O 
The/O king/O 's/O councillor/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O those/O are/O not/O the/O reasons/O I/O 'd/O have/O given/O ,/O but/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O had/O touched/O her/O cheek/O ,/O his/O thumb/O lightly/O tracing/O the/O line/O of/O a/O cheekbone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Life/O is/O not/O a/O song/O ,/O sweetling/O ./O 
You/O may/O learn/O that/O one/O day/O to/O your/O sorrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O did/O not/O feel/O like/O telling/O all/O that/O to/O Jeyne/LOCATION ,/O however/O ;/O it/O made/O her/O uneasy/O just/O to/O think/O back/O on/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Ilyn/O 's/O the/O King/O 's/O Justice/O ,/O not/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON should/O have/O sent/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O shuddered/O ./O 
Every/O time/O she/O looked/O at/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON ,/O she/O shivered/O ./O 
He/O made/O her/O feel/O as/O though/O something/O dead/O were/O slithering/O over/O her/O naked/O skin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Ilyn/O 's/O almost/O like/O a/O second/O monster/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O glad/O Father/O did/O n't/O pick/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON is/O as/O much/O a/O hero/O as/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ./O 
He/O 's/O ever/O so/O brave/O and/O gallant/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O suppose/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O doubtfully/O ./O 
Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON was/O handsome/O enough/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O awfully/O old/O ,/O almost/O twenty-two/O ;/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O would/O have/O been/O much/O better/O ./O 
Of/O course/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON had/O been/O in/O love/O with/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON ever/O since/O she/O had/O first/O glimpsed/O him/O in/O the/O lists/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON thought/O she/O was/O being/O silly/O ;/O Jeyne/PERSON was/O only/O a/O steward/O 's/O daughter/O ,/O after/O all/O ,/O and/O no/O matter/O how/O much/O she/O mooned/O after/O him/O ,/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON would/O never/O look/O at/O someone/O so/O far/O beneath/O him/O ,/O even/O if/O she/O had/O n't/O been/O half/O his/O age/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O would/O have/O been/O unkind/O to/O say/O so/O ,/O however/O ,/O so/O Sansa/PERSON took/O a/O sip/O of/O milk/O and/O changed/O the/O subject/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O a/O dream/O that/O Joffrey/PERSON would/O be/O the/O one/O to/O take/O the/O white/O hart/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O more/O of/O a/O wish/O ,/O actually/O ,/O but/O it/O sounded/O better/O to/O call/O it/O a/O dream/O ./O 
Everyone/O knew/O that/O dreams/O were/O prophetic/O ./O 
White/O harts/O were/O supposed/O to/O be/O very/O rare/O and/O magical/O ,/O and/O in/O her/O heart/O she/O knew/O her/O gallant/O prince/O was/O worthier/O than/O his/O drunken/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O dream/O ?/O 
Truly/O ?/O 
Did/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON just/O go/O up/O to/O it/O and/O touch/O it/O with/O his/O bare/O hand/O and/O do/O it/O no/O harm/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O shot/O it/O with/O a/O golden/O arrow/O and/O brought/O it/O back/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O In/O the/O songs/O ,/O the/O knights/O never/O killed/O magical/O beasts/O ,/O they/O just/O went/O up/O to/O them/O and/O touched/O them/O and/O did/O them/O no/O harm/O ,/O but/O she/O knew/O Joffrey/PERSON liked/O hunting/O ,/O especially/O the/O killing/O part/O ./O 
Only/O animals/O ,/O though/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O certain/O her/O prince/O had/O no/O part/O in/O murdering/O Jory/PERSON and/O those/O other/O poor/O men/O ;/O that/O had/O been/O his/O wicked/O uncle/O ,/O the/O Kingslayer/O ./O 
She/O knew/O her/O father/O was/O still/O angry/O about/O that/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O n't/O fair/O to/O blame/O Joff/PERSON ./O 
That/O would/O be/O like/O blaming/O her/O for/O something/O that/O Arya/PERSON had/O done/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O saw/O your/O sister/O this/O afternoon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON blurted/O out/O ,/O as/O if/O she/O 'd/O been/O reading/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O thoughts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O was/O walking/O through/O the/O stables/O on/O her/O hands/O ./O 
Why/O would/O she/O do/O a/O thing/O like/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sure/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O why/O Arya/PERSON does/O anything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON hated/O stables/O ,/O smelly/O places/O full/O of/O manure/O and/O flies/O ./O 
Even/O when/O she/O went/O riding/O ,/O she/O liked/O the/O boy/O to/O saddle/O the/O horse/O and/O bring/O it/O to/O her/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O want/O to/O hear/O about/O the/O court/O or/O not/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There-was/O a/O black/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O begging/O men/O for/O the/O Wall/O ,/O only/O he/O was/O kind/O of/O old/O and/O smelly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O n't/O liked/O that/O at/O all/O ./O 
She/O had/O always/O imagined/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O to/O be/O men/O like/O Uncle/O Benjen/PERSON ./O 
In/O the/O songs/O ,/O they/O were/O called/O the/O black/O knights/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
But/O this/O man/O had/O been/O crookbacked/O and/O hideous/O ,/O and/O he/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O might/O have/O lice/O ./O 
If/O this/O was/O what/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O was/O truly/O like/O ,/O she/O felt/O sorry/O for/O her/O bastard/O half/O brother/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O asked/O if/O there/O were/O any/O knights/O in/O the/O hall/O who/O would/O do/O honor/O to/O their/O houses/O by/O taking/O the/O black/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O came/O forward/O ,/O so/O he/O gave/O this/O Yoren/PERSON his/O pick/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O dungeons/O and/O sent/O him/O on/O his/O way/O ./O 
And/O later/O these/O two/O brothers/O came/O before/O him/O ,/O freeriders/O from/O the/O Dornish/O Marches/O ,/O and/O pledged/O their/O swords/O to/O the/O service/O of/O the/O king/O ./O 
Father/O accepted/O their/O oaths/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON yawned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O there/O any/O lemon/O cakes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O did/O not/O like/O being/O interrupted/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O to/O admit/O ,/O lemon/O cakes/O sounded/O more/O interesting/O than/O most/O of/O what/O had/O gone/O on/O in/O the/O throne/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O 's/O see/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O kitchen/O yielded/O no/O lemon/O cakes/O ,/O but/O they/O did/O find/O half/O of/O a/O cold/O strawberry/O pie/O ,/O and/O that/O was/O almost/O as/O good/O ./O 
They/O ate/O it/O on/O the/O tower/O steps/O ,/O giggling/O and/O gossiping/O and/O sharing/O secrets/O ,/O and/O Sansa/PERSON went/O to/O bed/O that/O night/O feeling/O almost/O as/O wicked/O as/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O next/O morning/O she/O woke/O before/O first/O light/O and/O crept/O sleepily/O to/O her/O window/O to/O watch/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON form/O up/O his/O men/O ./O 
They/O rode/O out/O as/O dawn/O was/O breaking/O over/O the/O city/O ,/O with/O three/O banners/O ''/O ,/O ``/O going/O before/O them/O ;/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O the/O king/O flew/O from/O the/O high/O staff/O ,/O the/O direwolf/O of/O Stark/O and/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON 's/O own/O forked/O lightning/O standard/O from/O shorter/O poles/O ./O 
It/O was/O all/O so/O exciting/O ,/O a/O song/O come/O to/O life/O ;/O the/O clatter/O of/O swords/O ,/O the/O flicker/O of/O torchlight/O ,/O banners/O dancing/O in/O the/O wind/O ,/O horses/O snorting/O and/O whinnying/O ,/O the/O golden/O glow/O of/O sunrise/O slanting/O through/O the/O bars/O of/O the/O portcullis/O as/O it/O jerked/O upward/O ./O 
The/O Winterfell/O men/O looked/O especially/O fine/O in/O their/O silvery/O mail/O and/O long/O grey/O cloaks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Alyn/PERSON carried/O the/O Stark/O banner/O ./O 
When/O she/O saw/O him/O rein/O in/O beside/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON to/O exchange/O words/O ,/O it/O made/O Sansa/PERSON feel/O ever/O so/O proud/O ./O 
Alyn/PERSON was/O handsomer/O than/O Jory/PERSON had/O been/O ;/O he/O was/O going/O to/O be/O a/O knight/O one/O day/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O seemed/O so/O empty/O after/O they/O left/O that/O Sansa/O was/O even/O pleased/O to/O see/O Arya/PERSON when/O she/O went/O down/O to/O break/O her/O fast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O is/O everyone/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O her/O sister/O wanted/O to/O know/O as/O she/O ripped/O the/O skin/O from/O a/O blood/O orange/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O Father/O send/O them/O to/O hunt/O down/O Jaime/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O rode/O with/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON ,/O to/O behead/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON Clegane/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O turned/O to/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O eating/O porridge/O with/O a/O wooden/O spoon/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Septa/ORGANIZATION ,/O will/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON spike/O Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON 's/O head/O on/O his/O own/O gate/O or/O bring/O it/O back/O here/O for/O the/O king/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O and/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON had/O been/O arguing/O over/O that/O last/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O septa/O was/O horror-struck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O lady/O does/O not/O discuss/O such/O things/O over/O her/O porridge/O ./O 
Where/O are/O your/O courtesies/O ,/O Sansa/PERSON ?/O 
I/O swear/O ,/O of/O late/O you/O 've/O been/O near/O as/O bad/O as/O your/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O did/O Gregor/PERSON do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O burned/O down/O a/O holdfast/O and/O murdered/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O ,/O women/O and/O children/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON screwed/O up/O her/O face/O in/O a/O scowl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jaime/O Lannister/O murdered/O Jory/PERSON and/O Heward/PERSON and/O Wyl/O ,/O and/O the/O Hound/O murdered/O Mycah/PERSON ./O 
Somebody/O should/O have/O beheaded/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O not/O the/O same/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Hound/O is/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O sworn/O shield/O ./O 
Your/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O attacked/O the/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Liar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
Her/O hand/O clenched/O the/O blood/O orange/O so/O hard/O that/O red/O juice/O oozed/O between/O her/O fingers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O ahead/O ,/O call/O me/O all/O the/O names/O you/O want/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O airily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O wo/O n't/O dare/O when/O I/O 'm/O married/O to/O Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
You/O 'll/O have/O to/O bow/O to/O me/O and/O call/O me/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O shrieked/O as/O Arya/PERSON flung/O the/O orange/O across/O the/O table/O ./O 
It/O caught/O her/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O forehead/O with/O a/O wet/O squish/O and/O plopped/O down/O into/O her/O lap/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O juice/O on/O your/O face/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O running/O down/O her/O nose/O and/O stinging/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON wiped/O it/O away/O with/O a/O napkin/O ./O 
When/O she/O saw/O what/O the/O fruit/O in/O her/O lap/O had/O done/O to/O her/O beautiful/O ivory/O silk/O dress/O ,/O she/O shrieked/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O horrible/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O screamed/O at/O her/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O should/O have/O killed/O you/O instead/O of/O Lady/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/O came/O lurching/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O lord/O father/O will/O hear/O of/O this/O !/O 
Go/O to/O your/O chambers/O ,/O at/O once/O ./O 
At/O once/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Me/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tears/O welled/O in/O Sansa/O 's/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O not/O fair/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O matter/O is/O not/O subject/O to/O discussion/O ./O 
Go/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O stalked/O away/O with/O her/O head/O up/O ./O 
She/O was/O to/O be/O a/O queen/O ,/O and/O queens/O did/O not/O cry/O ./O 
At/O least/O not/O where/O people/O could/O see/O ./O 
When/O she/O reached/O her/O bedchamber/O ,/O she/O barred/O the/O door/O and/O took/O off/O ''/O ,/O ``/O her/O dress/O ./O 
The/O blood/O orange/O had/O left/O a/O blotchy/O red/O stain/O on/O the/O silk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O her/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O screamed/O ./O 
She/O balled/O up/O the/O dress/O and/O flung/O it/O into/O the/O cold/O hearth/O ,/O on/O top/O of/O the/O ashes/O of/O last/O night/O 's/O fire/O ./O 
When/O she/O saw/O that/O the/O stain/O had/O bled/O through/O onto/O her/O underskirt/O ,/O she/O began/O to/O sob/O despite/O herself/O ./O 
She/O ripped/O off/O the/O rest/O of/O her/O clothes/O wildly/O ,/O threw/O herself/O into/O bed/O ,/O and/O cried/O herself/O back/O to/O sleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O midday/O when/O Septa/O Mordane/O knocked/O upon/O her/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O ./O 
Your/O lord/O father/O will/O see/O you/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O sat/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O it/O was/O as/O if/O the/O direwolf/O was/O there/O in/O the/O room/O ,/O looking/O at/O her/O with/O those/O golden/O eyes/O ,/O sad/O and/O knowing/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O dreaming/O ,/O she/O realized/O ./O 
Lady/O was/O with/O her/O ,/O and/O they/O were/O running/O together/O ,/O and/O .../O and/O .../O trying/O to/O remember/O was/O like/O trying/O to/O catch/O the/O rain/O with/O her/O fingers/O ./O 
The/O dream/O faded/O ,/O and/O Lady/O was/O dead/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sansa/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O rap/O came/O again/O ,/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Septa/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Might/O I/O have/O a/O moment/O to/O dress/O ,/O please/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O eyes/O were/O red/O from/O crying/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O her/O best/O to/O make/O herself/O beautiful/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON was/O bent/O over/O a/O huge/O leather-bound/O book/O when/O Septa/O Mordane/O marched/O her/O into/O the/O solar/O ,/O his/O plaster/O -/O wrapped/O leg/O stiff/O beneath/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O here/O ,/O Sansa/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O not/O unkindly/O ,/O when/O the/O septa/O had/O gone/O for/O her/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sit/O beside/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O closed/O the/O book/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON returned/O with/O Arya/PERSON squirming/O in/O her/O grasp/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O put/O on/O a/O lovely/O pale/O green/O damask/O gown/O and/O a/O look/O of/O remorse/O ,/O but/O her/O sister/O was/O still/O wearing/O the/O ratty/O leathers/O and/O roughspun/O she/O 'd/O worn/O at/O breakfast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O is/O the/O other/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O septa/O announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O thanks/O ,/O Septa/O Mordane/O ./O 
I/O would/O talk/O to/O my/O daughters/O alone/O ,/O if/O you/O would/O be/O so/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O septa/O bowed/O and/O left/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Arya/PERSON started/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O quickly/O ,/O anxious/O to/O have/O the/O first/O word/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O called/O me/O a/O liar/O and/O threw/O an/O orange/O at/O me/O and/O spoiled/O my/O dress/O ,/O the/O ivory/O silk/O ,/O the/O one/O Queen/O Cersei/PERSON gave/O me/O when/O I/O was/O betrothed/O to/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
She/O hates/O that/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O marry/O the/O prince/O ./O 
She/O tries/O to/O spoil/O everything/O ,/O Father/O ,/O she/O ca/O n't/O stand/O for/O anything/O to/O be/O beautiful/O or/O nice/O or/O splendid/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Enough/O ,/O Sansa/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON 's/O voice/O was/O sharp/O with/O impatience/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON raised/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sorry/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
I/O was/O wrong/O and/O I/O beg/O my/O sweet/O sister/O 's/O forgiveness/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O was/O so/O startled/O that/O for/O a/O moment/O she/O was/O speechless/O ./O 
Finally/O she/O found/O her/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O about/O my/O dress/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maybe/O .../O I/O could/O wash/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O doubtfully/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Washing/O wo/O n't/O do/O any/O good/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O if/O you/O scrubbed/O all/O day/O and/O all/O night/O ./O 
The/O silk/O is/O ruined/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O I/O 'll/O .../O make/O you/O a/O new/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O threw/O back/O her/O head/O in/O disdain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ?/O 
You/O could/O n't/O sew/O a/O dress/O fit/O to/O clean/O the/O pigsties/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Their/O father/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O not/O call/O you/O here/O to/O talk/O of/O dresses/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sending/O you/O both/O back/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O the/O second/O time/O Sansa/O found/O herself/O too/O stunned/O for/O words/O ./O 
She/O felt/O her/O eyes/O grow/O moist/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON managed/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O do/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O favored/O his/O daughters/O with/O a/O tired/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O last/O we/O 've/O found/O something/O you/O agree/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O do/O anything/O wrong/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O pleaded/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O go/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O loved/O King/PERSON 's/O Landing/O ;/O the/O pagaentry/O of/O the/O court/O ,/O the/O high/O lords/O and/O ladies/O in/O their/O velvets/O and/O silks/O and/O gemstones/O ,/O the/O great/O city/O with/O all/O its/O people/O ./O 
The/O tournament/O had/O been/O the/O most/O magical/O time/O of/O her/O whole/O life/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O so/O much/O she/O had/O not/O seen/O yet/O ,/O harvest/O feasts/O and/O masked/O balls/O and/O mummer/O shows/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O bear/O the/O thought/O of/O losing/O it/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Send/O Arya/PERSON away/O ,/O she/O started/O it/O ,/O Father/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O be/O good/O ,/O you/O 'll/O see/O ,/O just/O let/O me/O stay/O and/O I/O promise/O to/O be/O as/O fine/O and/O noble/O and/O courteous/O as/O the/O queen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Father/O 's/O mouth/O twitched/O strangely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O sending/O you/O away/O for/O fighting/O ,/O though/O the/O gods/O know/O I/O 'm/O sick/O of/O you/O two/O squabbling/O ./O 
I/O want/O you/O back/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION for/O your/O own/O safety/O ./O 
Three/O of/O my/O men/O were/O cut/O down/O like/O dogs/O not/O a/O league/O from/O where/O we/O sit/O ,/O and/O what/O does/O Robert/PERSON do/O ?/O 
He/O goes/O hunting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON was/O chewing/O at/O her/O lip/O in/O that/O disgusting/O way/O she/O had/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O we/O take/O Syrio/O back/O with/O us/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O cares/O about/O your/O stupid/O dancing/O master/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/O flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ,/O I/O only/O just/O now/O remembered/O ,/O I/O ca/O n't/O go/O away/O ,/O I/O 'm/O to/O marry/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O tried/O to/O smile/O bravely/O for/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O love/O him/O ,/O Father/O ,/O I/O truly/O truly/O do/O ,/O I/O love/O him/O as/O much/O as/O Queen/O Naerys/PERSON loved/O Prince/PERSON Aemon/PERSON the/O Dragonknight/O ,/O as/O much/O as/O Jonquil/O loved/O Ser/PERSON Florian/PERSON ./O 
I/O want/O to/O be/O his/O queen/O and/O have/O his/O babies/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sweet/O one/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O father/O said/O gently/O ,/O \/O ``/O listen/O to/O me/O ./O 
When/O you/O 're/O old/O enough/O ,/O I/O will/O make/O you/O a/O match/O with/O a/O high/O lord/O who/O 's/O worthy/O of/O you/O ,/O someone/O brave/O and/O gentle/O and/O strong/O ./O 
This/O match/O with/O Joffrey/PERSON was/O a/O terrible/O mistake/O ./O 
That/O boy/O is/O no/O Prince/O Aemon/PERSON ,/O you/O must/O believe/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O is/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O someone/O brave/O and/O gentle/O ,/O I/O want/O him/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O be/O ever/O so/O happy/O ,/O just/O like/O in/O the/O songs/O ,/O you/O 'll/O see/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O give/O him/O a/O son/O with/O golden/O hair/O ,/O and/O one/O day/O he/O 'll/O be/O the/O king/O of/O all/O the/O realm/O ,/O the/O greatest/O king/O that/O ever/O was/O ,/O as/O brave/O as/O the/O wolf/O and/O as/O proud/O as/O the/O lion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON made/O a/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O if/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O his/O father/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O a/O liar/O and/O a/O craven/O and/O anyhow/O he/O 's/O a/O stag/O ,/O not/O a/O lion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O felt/O tears/O in/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O not/O !/O 
He/O 's/O not/O the/O least/O bit/O like/O that/O old/O drunken/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O screamed/O at/O her/O sister/O ,/O forgetting/O herself/O in/O her/O grief/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Father/O looked/O at/O her/O strangely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O softly/O ,/O \/O ``/O out/O of/O the/O mouth/O of/O babes/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O shouted/O for/O Septa/O Mordane/O ./O 
To/O the/O girls/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O looking/O for/O a/O fast/O trading/O galley/O to/O take/O you/O home/O ./O 
These/O days/O ,/O the/O sea/O is/O safer/O than/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
You/O will/O sail/O as/O soon/O as/O I/O can/O find/O a/O proper/O ship/O ,/O with/O Septa/O Mordane/O and/O a/O complement/O of/O guards/O .../O and/O yes/O ,/O with/O Syrio/PERSON Forel/PERSON ,/O if/O he/O agrees/O to/O enter/O my/O service/O ./O 
But/O say/O nothing/O of/O this/O ./O 
It/O 's/O better/O if/O no/O one/O knows/O of/O our/O plans/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O talk/O again/O tomorrow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O cried/O as/O Septa/O Mordane/O marched/O them/O down/O the/O steps/O ./O 
They/O were/O going/O to/O take/O it/O all/O away/O ;/O the/O tournaments/O and/O the/O court/O and/O her/O prince/O ,/O everything/O ,/O they/O were/O going/O to/O send/O her/O back/O to/O the/O bleak/O grey/O walls/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION and/O lock/O her/O up/O forever/O ./O 
Her/O life/O was/O over/O before/O it/O had/O begun/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stop/O that/O weeping/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON said/O sternly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O certain/O your/O lord/O father/O knows/O what/O is/O best/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O wo/O n't/O be/O so/O bad/O ,/O Sansa/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 're/O going/O to/O sail/O on/O a/O galley/O ./O 
It/O will/O be/O an/O adventure/O ,/O and/O then/O we/O 'll/O be/O with/O Bran/O and/O Robb/PERSON again/O ,/O and/O Old/O Nan/PERSON and/O Hodor/PERSON and/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O touched/O her/O on/O the/O arm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Sansa/O yelled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ought/O to/O marry/O Hodor/PERSON ,/O you/O 're/O just/O like/O him/O ,/O stupid/O and/O hairy/O and/O ugly/O !/O 
\/O ''/O She/O wrenched/O away/O from/O her/O sister/O 's/O hand/O ,/O stormed/O into/O her/O bedchamber/O ,/O and/O barred/O the/O door/O behind/O her/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
