-LSB-/O ``/O ARYA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O scent/O of/O hot/O bread/O drifting/O from/O the/O shops/O along/O the/O Street/O of/O Flour/O was/O sweeter/O than/O any/O perfume/O Arya/PERSON had/O ever/O smelled/O ./O 
She/O took/O a/O deep/O breath/O and/O stepped/O closer/O to/O the/O pigeon/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O plump/O one/O ,/O speckled/O brown/O ,/O busily/O pecking/O at/O a/O crust/O that/O had/O fallen/O between/O two/O cobblestones/O ,/O but/O when/O Arya/PERSON 's/O shadow/O touched/O it/O ,/O it/O took/O to/O the/O air/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O stick/O sword/O whistled/O out/O and/O caught/O it/O two/O feet/O off/O the/O ground/O ,/O and/O it/O went/O down/O in/O a/O flurry/O of/O brown/O feathers/O ./O 
She/O was/O on/O it/O in/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O ,/O grabbing/O a/O wing/O as/O the/O pigeon/O flapped/O and/O fluttered/O ./O 
It/O pecked/O at/O her/O hand/O ./O 
She/O grabbed/O its/O neck/O and/O twisted/O until/O she/O felt/O the/O bone/O snap/O ./O 
Compared/O with/O catching/O cats/O ,/O pigeons/O were/O easy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O passing/O septon/O was/O looking/O at/O her/O askance/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O 's/O the/O best/O place/O to/O find/O pigeon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON told/O him/O as/O she/O brushed/O herself/O off/O and/O picked/O up/O her/O fallen/O stick/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O come/O for/O the/O crumbs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O hurried/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O tied/O the/O pigeon/O to/O her/O belt/O and/O started/O down/O the/O street/O ./O 
A/O man/O was/O pushing/O a/O load/O of/O tarts/O by/O on/O a/O two-wheeled/O cart/O ;/O the/O smells/O sang/O of/O blueberries/O and/O lemons/O and/O apricots/O ./O 
Her/O stomach/O made/O a/O hollow/O rumbly/O noise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Could/O I/O have/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O heard/O herself/O say/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O lemon/O ,/O or/O .../O or/O any/O kind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O pushcart/O man/O looked/O her/O up/O and/O down/O ./O 
Plainly/O he/O did/O not/O like/O what/O he/O saw/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Three/O coppers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON tapped/O her/O wooden/O sword/O against/O the/O side/O of/O her/O boot/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O trade/O you/O a/O fat/O pigeon/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O take/O your/O pigeon/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O pushcart/O man/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O tarts/O were/O still/O warm/O from/O the/O oven/O ./O 
The/O smells/O were/O making/O her/O mouth/O water/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O not/O have/O three/O coppers/O .../O or/O one/O ./O 
She/O gave/O the/O pushcart/O man/O a/O look/O ,/O remembering/O what/O Syrio/PERSON had/O told/O her/O about/O seeing/O ./O 
He/O was/O short/O ,/O with/O a/O little/O round/O belly/O ,/O and/O when/O he/O moved/O he/O seemed/O to/O favor/O his/O left/O leg/O a/O little/O ./O 
She/O was/O just/O thinking/O that/O if/O she/O snatched/O a/O tart/O and/O ran/O he/O would/O never/O be/O able/O to/O catch/O her/O when/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O be/O keepin/O '/O your/O filthy/O hands/O off/O ./O 
The/O gold/O cloaks/O know/O how/O to/O deal/O with/O thieving/O little/O gutter/O rats/O ,/O that/O they/O do/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON glanced/O warily/O behind/O her/O ./O 
Two/O of/O the/O City/O Watch/O were/O standing/O at/O the/O mouth/O of/O an/O alley/O ./O 
Their/O cloaks/O hung/O almost/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O the/O heavy/O wool/O dyed/O a/O rich/O gold/O ;/O their/O mail/O and/O boots/O and/O gloves/O were/O black/O ./O 
One/O wore/O a/O longsword/O at/O his/O hip/O ,/O the/O other/O an/O iron/O cudgel/O ./O 
With/O a/O last/O wistful/O glance/O at/O the/O tarts/O ,/O Arya/PERSON edged/O back/O from/O the/O cart/O and/O hurried/O off/O ./O 
The/O gold/O cloaks/O had/O not/O been/O paying/O her/O any/O special/O attention/O ,/O but/O the/O sight/O of/O them/O tied/O her/O stomach/O in/O knots/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O been/O staying/O as/O far/O from/O the/O castle/O as/O she/O could/O get/O ,/O yet/O even/O from/O a/O distance/O she/O could/O see/O the/O heads/O rotting/O atop/O the/O high/O red/O walls/O ./O 
Flocks/O of/O crows/O squabbled/O noisily/O over/O each/O head/O ,/O thick/O as/O flies/O ./O 
The/O talk/O in/O Flea/O Bottom/O was/O that/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O had/O thrown/O in/O with/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O their/O commander/O raised/O to/O a/O lord/O ,/O with/O lands/O on/O the/O Trident/O and/O a/O seat/O on/O the/O king/O 's/O council/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O also/O heard/O other/O things/O ,/O scary/O things/O ,/O things/O that/O made/O no/O sense/O to/O her/O ./O 
Some/O said/O her/O father/O had/O murdered/O King/O Robert/PERSON and/O been/O slain/O in/O turn/O by/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON ./O 
Others/O insisted/O that/O Renly/PERSON had/O killed/O the/O king/O in/O a/O drunken/O quarrel/O between/O brothers/O ./O 
Why/O else/O should/O he/O have/O fled/O in/O ''/O ,/O ``/O the/O night/O like/O a/O common/O thief/O ?/O 
One/O story/O said/O the/O king/O had/O been/O killed/O by/O a/O boar/O while/O hunting/O ,/O another/O that/O he/O 'd/O died/O eating/O a/O boar/O ,/O stuffing/O himself/O so/O full/O that/O he/O 'd/O ruptured/O at/O the/O table/O ./O 
No/O ,/O the/O king/O had/O died/O at/O table/O ,/O others/O said/O ,/O but/O only/O because/O Varys/O the/O Spider/O poisoned/O him/O ./O 
No/O ,/O it/O had/O been/O the/O queen/O who/O poisoned/O him/O ./O 
No/O ,/O he/O had/O died/O of/O a/O pox/O ./O 
No/O ,/O he/O had/O choked/O on/O a/O fish/O bone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O One/O thing/O all/O the/O stories/O agreed/O on/O :/O King/O Robert/PERSON was/O dead/O ./O 
The/O bells/O in/O the/O seven/O towers/O of/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION had/O tolled/O for/O a/O day/O and/O a/O night/O ,/O the/O thunder/O of/O their/O grief/O rolling/O across/O the/O city/O in/O a/O bronze/O tide/O ./O 
They/O only/O rang/O the/O bells/O like/O that/O for/O the/O death/O of/O a/O king/O ,/O a/O tanner/O 's/O boy/O told/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O All/O she/O wanted/O was/O to/O go/O home/O ,/O but/O leaving/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O was/O not/O so/O easy/O as/O she/O had/O hoped/O ./O 
Talk/O of/O war/O was/O on/O every/O lip/O ,/O and/O gold/O cloaks/O were/O as/O thick/O on/O the/O city/O walls/O as/O fleas/O on/O .../O well/O ,/O her/O ,/O for/O one/O ./O 
She/O had/O been/O sleeping/O in/O Flea/O Bottom/O ,/O on/O rooftops/O and/O in/O stables/O ,/O wherever/O she/O could/O find/O a/O place/O to/O lie/O down/O ,/O and/O it/O had/O n't/O taken/O her/O long/O to/O learn/O that/O the/O district/O was/O well/O named/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Every/O day/O since/O her/O escape/O from/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O Arya/PERSON had/O visited/O each/O of/O the/O seven/O city/O gates/O in/O turn/O ./O 
The/O Dragon/O Gate/O ,/O the/O Lion/O Gate/O ,/O and/O the/O Old/LOCATION Gate/LOCATION were/O closed/O and/O barred/O ./O 
The/O Mud/O Gate/O and/O the/O Gate/O of/O the/O Gods/O were/O open/O ,/O but/O only/O to/O those/O who/O wanted/O to/O enter/O the/O city/O ;/O the/O guards/O let/O no/O one/O out/O ./O 
Those/O who/O were/O allowed/O to/O leave/O left/O by/O the/O King/O 's/O Gate/O or/O the/O Iron/LOCATION Gate/LOCATION ,/O but/O Lannister/O men-at-arms/O in/O crimson/O cloaks/O and/O lion-crested/O helms/O manned/O the/O guard/O posts/O there/O ./O 
Spying/O down/O from/O the/O roof/O of/O an/O inn/O by/O the/O King/O 's/O Gate/O ,/O Arya/PERSON saw/O them/O searching/O wagons/O and/O carriages/O ,/O forcing/O riders/O to/O open/O their/O saddlebags/O ,/O and/O questioning/O everyone/O who/O tried/O to/O pass/O on/O foot/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sometimes/O she/O thought/O about/O swimming/O the/O river/O ,/O but/O the/O Blackwater/PERSON Rush/PERSON was/O wide/O and/O deep/O ,/O and/O everyone/O agreed/O that/O its/O currents/O were/O wicked/O and/O treacherous/O ./O 
She/O had/O no/O coin/O to/O pay/O a/O ferryman/O or/O take/O passage/O on/O a/O ship/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O lord/O father/O had/O taught/O her/O never/O to/O steal/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O growing/O harder/O to/O remember/O why/O ./O 
If/O she/O did/O not/O get/O out/O soon/O ,/O she/O would/O have/O to/O take/O her/O chances/O with/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O ./O 
She/O had/O n't/O gone/O hungry/O much/O since/O she/O learned/O to/O knock/O down/O birds/O with/O her/O stick/O sword/O ,/O but/O she/O feared/O so/O much/O pigeon/O was/O making/O her/O sick/O ./O 
A/O couple/O she/O 'd/O eaten/O raw/O ,/O before/O she/O found/O Flea/O Bottom/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O Bottom/O there/O were/O pot-shops/O along/O the/O alleys/O where/O huge/O tubs/O of/O stew/O had/O been/O simmering/O for/O years/O ,/O and/O you/O could/O trade/O half/O your/O bird/O for/O a/O heel/O of/O yesterday/O 's/O bread/O and/O a/O \/O ``/O bowl/O o/O '/O brown/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O they/O 'd/O even/O stick/O the/O other/O half/O in/O the/O fire/O and/O crisp/O it/O up/O for/O you/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O you/O plucked/O the/O feathers/O yourself/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON would/O have/O given/O anything/O for/O a/O cup/O of/O milk/O and/O a/O lemon/O cake/O ,/O but/O the/O brown/O was/O n't/O so/O bad/O ./O 
It/O usually/O had/O barley/O in/O it/O ,/O and/O chunks/O of/O carrot/O and/O onion/O and/O turnip/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O even/O apple/O ,/O with/O a/O film/O of/O grease/O swimming/O on/O top/O ./O 
Mostly/O she/O tried/O not/O to/O think/O about/O the/O meat/O ./O 
Once/O she/O had/O gotten/O a/O piece/O offish/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O only/O thing/O was/O ,/O the/O pot-shops/O were/O never/O empty/O ,/O and/O even/O as/O she/O bolted/O down/O her/O food/O ,/O Arya/PERSON could/O feel/O them/O watching/O ./O 
Some/O of/O them/O stared/O at/O her/O boots/O or/O her/O cloak/O ,/O and/O she/O knew/O what/O they/O were/O thinking/O ./O 
With/O others/O ,/O she/O could/O almost/O feel/O their/O eyes/O crawling/O under/O her/O leathers/O ;/O she/O did/O n't/O know/O what/O they/O were/O thinking/O ,/O and/O that/O scared/O her/O even/O more/O ./O 
A/O couple/O ''/O ,/O ``/O times/O ,/O she/O was/O followed/O out/O into/O the/O alleys/O and/O chased/O ,/O but/O so/O far/O no/O one/O had/O been/O able/O to/O catch/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O silver/O bracelet/O she/O 'd/O hoped/O to/O sell/O had/O been/O stolen/O her/O first/O night/O out/O of/O the/O castle/O ,/O along/O with/O her/O bundle/O of/O good/O clothes/O ,/O snatched/O while/O she/O slept/O in/O a/O burnt-out/O house/O off/O Pig/LOCATION Alley/LOCATION ./O 
All/O they/O left/O her/O was/O the/O cloak/O she/O had/O been/O huddled/O in/O ,/O the/O leathers/O on/O her/O back/O ,/O her/O wooden/O practice/O sword/O .../O and/O Needle/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O been/O lying/O on/O top/O of/O Needle/LOCATION ,/O or/O else/O it/O would/O have/O been/O gone/O too/O ;/O it/O was/O worth/O more/O than/O all/O the/O rest/O together/O ./O 
Since/O then/O Arya/PERSON had/O taken/O to/O walking/O around/O with/O her/O cloak/O draped/O over/O her/O right/O arm/O ,/O to/O conceal/O the/O blade/O at/O her/O hip/O ./O 
The/O wooden/O sword/O she/O carried/O in/O her/O left/O hand/O ,/O out/O where/O everybody/O could/O see/O it/O ,/O to/O scare/O off/O robbers/O ,/O but/O there/O were/O men/O in/O the/O pot-shops/O who/O would/O n't/O have/O been/O scared/O off/O if/O she/O 'd/O had/O a/O battle-axe/O ./O 
It/O was/O enough/O to/O make/O her/O lose/O her/O taste/O for/O pigeon/O and/O stale/O bread/O ./O 
Often/O as/O not/O ,/O she/O went/O to/O bed/O hungry/O rather/O than/O risk/O the/O stares/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Once/O she/O was/O outside/O the/O city/O ,/O she/O would/O find/O berries/O to/O pick/O ,/O or/O orchards/O she/O might/O raid/O for/O apples/O and/O cherries/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON remembered/O seeing/O some/O from/O the/O kingsroad/O on/O the/O journey/O south/O ./O 
And/O she/O could/O dig/O for/O roots/O in/O the/O forest/O ,/O even/O run/O down/O some/O rabbits/O ./O 
In/O the/O city/O ,/O the/O only/O things/O to/O run/O down/O were/O rats/O and/O cats/O and/O scrawny/O dogs/O ./O 
The/O potshops/O would/O give/O you/O a/O fistful/O of/O coppers/O for/O a/O litter/O of/O pups/O ,/O she/O 'd/O heard/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O n't/O like/O to/O think/O about/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Down/O below/O the/O Street/O of/O Flour/O was/O a/O maze/O of/O twisting/O alleys/O and/O cross/O streets/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON scrambled/O through/O the/O crowds/O ,/O trying/O to/O put/O distance/O between/O her/O and/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O ./O 
She/O had/O learned/O to/O keep/O to/O the/O center/O of/O the/O street/O ./O 
Sometimes/O she/O had/O to/O dodge/O wagons/O and/O horses/O ,/O but/O at/O least/O you/O could/O see/O them/O coming/O ./O 
If/O you/O walked/O near/O the/O buildings/O ,/O people/O grabbed/O you/O ./O 
In/O some/O alleys/O you/O could/O n't/O help/O but/O brush/O against/O the/O walls/O ;/O the/O buildings/O leaned/O in/O so/O close/O they/O almost/O met/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O whooping/O gang/O of/O small/O children/O went/O running/O past/O ,/O chasing/O a/O rolling/O hoop/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON stared/O at/O them/O with/O resentment/O ,/O remembering/O the/O times/O she/O 'd/O played/O at/O hoops/O with/O Bran/O and/O Jon/PERSON and/O their/O baby/O brother/O Rickon/PERSON ./O 
She/O wondered/O how/O big/O Rickon/PERSON had/O grown/O ,/O and/O whether/O Bran/O was/O sad/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O given/O anything/O if/O Jon/PERSON had/O been/O here/O to/O call/O her/O \/O ``/O little/O sister/O \/O ''/O and/O muss/O her/O hair/O ./O 
Not/O that/O it/O needed/O mussing/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O seen/O her/O reflection/O in/O puddles/O ,/O and/O she/O did/O n't/O think/O hair/O got/O any/O more/O mussed/O than/O hers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O tried/O talking/O to/O the/O children/O she/O saw/O in/O the/O street/O ,/O hoping/O to/O make/O a/O friend/O who/O would/O give/O her/O a/O place/O to/O sleep/O ,/O but/O she/O must/O have/O talked/O wrong/O or/O something/O ./O 
The/O little/O ones/O only/O looked/O at/O her/O with/O quick/O ,/O wary/O eyes/O and/O ran/O away/O if/O she/O came/O too/O close/O ./O 
Their/O big/O brothers/O and/O sisters/O asked/O questions/O Arya/PERSON could/O n't/O answer/O ,/O called/O her/O names/O ,/O and/O tried/O to/O steal/O from/O her/O ./O 
Only/O yesterday/O ,/O a/O scrawny/O barefoot/O girl/O twice/O her/O age/O had/O knocked/O her/O down/O and/O tried/O to/O pull/O the/O boots/O off/O her/O feet/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O crack/O on/O her/O ear/O with/O her/O stick/O sword/O that/O sent/O her/O off/O sobbing/O and/O bleeding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O gull/O wheeled/O overhead/O as/O she/O made/O her/O way/O down/O the/O hill/O toward/O Flea/O Bottom/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON glanced/O at/O it/O thoughtfully/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O well/O beyond/O the/O reach/O of/O her/O stick/O ./O 
It/O made/O her/O think/O of/O the/O sea/O ./O 
Maybe/O that/O was/O the/O way/O out/O ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON used/O to/O tell/O stories/O of/O boys/O who/O stowed/O away/O on/O trading/O galleys/O and/O sailed/O off/O into/O all/O kinds/O of/O adventures/O ./O 
Maybe/O Arya/PERSON could/O do/O that/O too/O ./O 
She/O decided/O to/O ''/O ,/O ``/O visit/O the/O riverfront/O ./O 
It/O was/O on/O the/O way/O to/O the/O Mud/LOCATION Gate/LOCATION anyway/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O n't/O checked/O that/O one/O today/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O wharfs/O were/O oddly/O quiet/O when/O Arya/PERSON got/O there/O ./O 
She/O spied/O another/O pair/O of/O gold/O cloaks/O ,/O walking/O side/O by/O side/O through/O the/O fish/O market/O ,/O but/O they/O never/O so/O much/O as/O looked/O at/O her/O ./O 
Half/O the/O stalls/O were/O empty/O ,/O and/O it/O seemed/O to/O her/O that/O there/O were/O fewer/O ships/O at/O dock/O than/O she/O remembered/O ./O 
Out/O on/O the/O Blackwater/ORGANIZATION ,/O three/O of/O the/O king/O 's/O war/O galleys/O moved/O in/O formation/O ,/O gold-painted/O hulls/O splitting/O the/O water/O as/O their/O oars/O rose/O and/O fell/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON watched/O them/O for/O a/O bit/O ,/O then/O began/O to/O make/O her/O way/O along/O the/O river/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O she/O saw/O the/O guardsmen/O on/O the/O third/O pier/O ,/O in/O grey/O woolen/O cloaks/O trimmed/O with/O white/O satin/O ,/O her/O heart/O almost/O stopped/O in/O her/O chest/O ./O 
The/O sight/O of/O Winterfell/PERSON 's/O colors/O brought/O tears/O to/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Behind/O them/O ,/O a/O sleek/O three-banked/O trading/O galley/O rocked/O at/O her/O moorings/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON could/O not/O read/O the/O name/O painted/O on/O the/O hull/O ;/O the/O words/O were/O strange/O ,/O Myrish/O ,/O Braavosi/PERSON ,/O perhaps/O even/O High/O Valyrian/O ./O 
She/O grabbed/O a/O passing/O longshoreman/O by/O the/O sleeve/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Please/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O what/O ship/O is/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O the/O Wind/O Witch/O ,/O out/O of/O Myr/ORGANIZATION ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O still/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON blurted/O ./O 
The/O longshoreman/O gave/O her/O a/O queer/O look/O ,/O shrugged/O ,/O and/O walked/O away/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON ran/O toward/O the/O pier/O ./O 
The/O Wind/O Witch/O was/O the/O ship/O Father/O had/O hired/O to/O take/O her/O home/O .../O still/O waiting/O !/O 
She/O 'd/O imagined/O it/O had/O sailed/O ages/O ago/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Two/O of/O the/O guardsmen/O were/O dicing/O together/O while/O the/O third/O walked/O rounds/O ,/O his/O hand/O on/O the/O pommel/O of/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Ashamed/O to/O let/O them/O see/O her/O crying/O like/O a/O baby/O ,/O she/O stopped/O to/O rub/O at/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
Her/O eyes/O her/O eyes/O her/O eyes/O ,/O why/O did/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Look/O with/O your/O eyes/O ,/O she/O heard/O Syrio/O whisper/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON looked/O ./O 
She/O knew/O all/O of/O her/O father/O 's/O men/O ./O 
The/O three/O in/O the/O grey/O cloaks/O were/O strangers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O one/O walking/O rounds/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O want/O here/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O other/O two/O looked/O up/O from/O their/O dice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O all/O Arya/PERSON could/O do/O not/O to/O bolt/O and/O run/O ,/O but/O she/O knew/O that/O if/O she/O did/O ,/O they/O would/O be/O after/O her/O at/O once/O ./O 
She/O made/O herself/O walk/O closer/O ./O 
They/O were/O looking/O for/O a/O girl/O ,/O but/O he/O thought/O she/O was/O a/O boy/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O be/O a/O boy/O ,/O then/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Want/O to/O buy/O a/O pigeon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O She/O showed/O him/O the/O dead/O bird/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Get/O out/O of/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O guardsman/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON did/O as/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
She/O did/O not/O have/O to/O pretend/O to/O be/O frightened/O ./O 
Behind/O her/O ,/O the/O men/O went/O back/O to/O their/O dice/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O could/O not/O have/O said/O how/O she/O got/O back/O to/O Flea/PERSON Bottom/PERSON ,/O but/O she/O was/O breathing/O hard/O by/O the/O time/O she/O reached/O the/O narrow/O crooked/O unpaved/O streets/O between/O the/O hills/O ./O 
The/O Bottom/O had/O a/O stench/O to/O it/O ,/O a/O stink/O of/O pigsties/O and/O stables/O and/O tanner/O 's/O sheds/O ,/O mixed/O in/O with/O the/O sour/O smell/O of/O winesinks/O and/O cheap/O whorehouses/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON wound/O her/O way/O through/O the/O maze/O dully/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O until/O she/O caught/O a/O whiff/O of/O bubbling/O brown/O coming/O through/O a/O pot-shop/O door/O that/O she/O realized/O her/O pigeon/O was/O gone/O ./O 
It/O must/O have/O slipped/O from/O her/O belt/O as/O she/O ran/O ,/O or/O someone/O had/O stolen/O it/O and/O she/O 'd/O never/O noticed/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O she/O wanted/O to/O cry/O again/O ./O 
She/O 'd/O have/O to/O walk/O all/O the/O way/O back/O to/O the/O Street/O of/O Flour/O to/O find/O another/O one/O that/O plump/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Far/O across/O the/O city/O ,/O bells/O began/O to/O ring/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON glanced/O up/O ,/O listening/O ,/O wondering/O what/O the/O ringing/O meant/O this/O time/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O 's/O this/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O a/O fat/O man/O called/O from/O the/O pot-shop/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O bells/O again/O ,/O gods/O ha/O `/O mercy/O ,/O \/O ''/O wailed/O an/O old/O woman/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O red-haired/O whore/O in/O a/O wisp/O of/O painted/O silk/O pushed/O open/O a/O secondstory/O window/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O the/O boy/O king/O that/O 's/O died/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O shouted/O down/O ,/O leaning/O out/O over/O the/O street/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O that/O 's/O a/O boy/O for/O you/O ,/O they/O never/O last/O long/O ./O 
\/O ''/O As/O she/O laughed/O ,/O a/O naked/O man/O slid/O his/O arms/O around/O her/O from/O behind/O ,/O biting/O her/O neck/O and/O rubbing/O the/O heavy/O white/O breasts/O that/O hung/O loose/O beneath/O her/O shift/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stupid/O slut/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O fat/O man/O shouted/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O king/O 's/O not/O dead/O ,/O that/O 's/O only/O summoning/O bells/O ./O 
One/O tower/O tolling/O ./O 
When/O the/O king/O dies/O ,/O they/O ring/O every/O bell/O in/O the/O city/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O quit/O your/O biting/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O ring/O your/O bells/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O woman/O in/O the/O window/O said/O to/O the/O man/O behind/O her/O ,/O pushing/O him/O off/O with/O an/O elbow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O who/O is/O it/O died/O ,/O if/O not/O the/O king/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O 's/O a/O summoning/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O fat/O man/O repeated/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Two/O boys/O close/O to/O Arya/PERSON 's/O age/O scampered/O past/O ,/O splashing/O through/O a/O puddle/O ./O 
The/O old/O woman/O cursed/O them/O ,/O but/O they/O kept/O right/O on/O going/O ./O 
Other/O people/O were/O moving/O too/O ,/O heading/O up/O the/O hill/O to/O see/O what/O the/O noise/O was/O about/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON ran/O after/O the/O slower/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O you/O going/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O shouted/O when/O she/O was/O right/O behind/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O 's/O happening/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O glanced/O back/O without/O slowing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gold/O cloaks/O is/O carryin/O '/O him/O to/O the/O sept./O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O yelled/O ,/O running/O hard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Hand/O !/O 
They/O 'll/O be/O taking/O his/O head/O off/O ,/O Buu/PERSON says/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O passing/O wagon/O had/O left/O a/O deep/O rut/O in/O the/O street/O ./O 
The/O boy/O leapt/O over/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON never/O saw/O it/O ./O 
She/O tripped/O and/O fell/O ,/O face/O first/O ,/O scraping/O her/O knee/O open/O on/O a/O stone/O and/O smashing/O her/O fingers/O when/O her/O hands/O hit/O the/O hard-packed/O earth/O ./O 
Needle/O tangled/O between/O her/O legs/O ./O 
She/O sobbed/O as/O she/O struggled/O to/O her/O knees/O ./O 
The/O thumb/O of/O her/O left/O hand/O was/O covered/O with/O blood/O ./O 
When/O she/O sucked/O on/O it/O ,/O she/O saw/O that/O half/O the/O thumbnail/O was/O gone/O ,/O ripped/O off/O in/O her/O fall/O ./O 
Her/O hands/O throbbed/O ,/O and/O her/O knee/O was/O all/O bloody/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Make/O way/O !/O 
\/O ''/O someone/O shouted/O from/O the/O cross/O street/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Make/O wayfor/O my/O lords/O of/O Redwyne/O !/O 
\/O ''/O It/O was/O all/O Arya/PERSON could/O do/O to/O get/O out/O of/O the/O road/O before/O they/O ran/O her/O down/O ,/O four/O guardsmen/O on/O huge/O horses/O ,/O pounding/O past/O at/O a/O gallop/O ./O 
They/O wore/O checked/O cloaks/O ,/O blue-and-burgundy/O ./O 
Behind/O them/O ,/O two/O young/O lordlings/O rode/O side/O by/O side/O on/O a/O pair/O of/O chestnut/O mares/O alike/O as/O peas/O in/O a/O pod/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O seen/O them/O in/O the/O bailey/O a/O hundred/O times/O ;/O the/O Redwyne/O twins/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Horas/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Hobber/PERSON ,/O homely/O youths/O with/O orange/O hair/O and/O square/O ,/O freckled/O faces/O ./O 
Sansa/O and/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON used/O to/O call/O them/O Ser/O Horror/O and/O Ser/PERSON Slobber/PERSON ,/O and/O giggle/O whenever/O they/O caught/O sight/O of/O them/O ./O 
They/O did/O not/O look/O funny/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Everyone/O was/O moving/O in/O the/O same/O direction/O ,/O all/O in/O a/O hurry/O to/O see/O what/O the/O ringing/O was/O all/O about/O ./O 
The/O bells/O seemed/O louder/O now/O ,/O clanging/O ,/O calling/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON joined/O the/O stream/O of/O people/O ./O 
Her/O thumb/O hurt/O so/O bad/O where/O the/O nail/O had/O broken/O that/O it/O was/O all/O she/O could/O do/O not/O to/O cry/O ./O 
She/O bit/O her/O lip/O as/O she/O limped/O along/O ,/O listening/O to/O the/O excited/O voices/O around/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
They/O 're/O carrying/O him/O up/O to/O Baelor/PERSON 's/O Sept./O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O heard/O he/O was/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Soon/O enough/O ,/O soon/O enough/O ./O 
Here/O ,/O I/O got/O me/O a/O silver/O stag/O says/O they/O lop/O his/O head/O off/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Past/O time/O ,/O the/O traitor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O spat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON struggled/O to/O find/O a/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O never/O -/O \/O ''/O she/O started/O ,/O but/O she/O was/O only/O a/O child/O and/O they/O talked/O right/O over/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fool/O !/O 
They/O ai/O n't/O neither/O going/O to/O lop/O him/O ./O 
Since/O when/O do/O they/O knick/O traitors/O on/O the/O steps/O of/O the/O Great/O Sept/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O they/O do/O n't/O mean/O to/O anoint/O him/O no/O knight/O ./O 
I/O heard/O it/O was/O Stark/O killed/O old/O King/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
Slit/O his/O throat/O in/O the/O woods/O ,/O and/O when/O they/O found/O him/O ,/O he/O stood/O there/O cool/O as/O you/O please/O and/O said/O it/O was/O some/O old/O boar/O did/O for/O His/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ah/O ,/O that/O 's/O not/O true/O ,/O it/O was/O his/O own/O brother/O did/O him/O ,/O that/O Renly/PERSON ,/O him/O with/O his/O gold/O antlers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O shut/O your/O lying/O mouth/O ,/O woman/O ./O 
You/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O you/O 're/O saying/O ,/O his/O lordship/O 's/O a/O fine/O true/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O By/O the/O time/O they/O reached/O the/O Street/O of/O the/O Sisters/O ,/O they/O were/O packed/O in/O shoulder/O to/O shoulder/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON let/O the/O human/O current/O carry/O her/O along/O ,/O up/O to/O the/O top/O of/O Visenya/PERSON 's/O Hill/PERSON ./O 
The/O white/O marble/O plaza/O was/O a/O solid/O mass/O of/O people/O ,/O all/O yammering/O excitedly/O at/O each/O other/O and/O straining/O to/O get/O closer/O to/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION ./O 
The/O bells/O were/O very/O loud/O here/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON squirmed/O through/O the/O press/O ,/O ducking/O between/O the/O legs/O of/O horses/O and/O clutching/O tight/O to/O her/O sword/O stick/O ./O 
From/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O crowd/O ,/O all/O she/O could/O see/O were/O arms/O and/O legs/O and/O stomachs/O ,/O and/O the/O seven/O slender/O towers/O of/O the/O sept/O looming/O overhead/O ./O 
She/O spotted/O a/O wood/O wagon/O and/O thought/O to/O climb/O up/O on/O the/O back/O where/O she/O might/O be/O able/O to/O see/O ,/O but/O others/O had/O the/O same/O idea/O ./O 
The/O teamster/O cursed/O at/O them/O and/O drove/O them/O off/O with/O a/O crack/O of/O his/O whip/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON grew/O frantic/O ./O 
Forcing/O her/O way/O to/O the/O front/O of/O the/O crowd/O ,/O she/O was/O shoved/O up/O against/O the/O stone/O of/O a/O plinth/O ./O 
She/O looked/O up/O at/O Baelor/LOCATION the/O Blessed/O ,/O the/O septon/O king/O ./O 
Sliding/O her/O stick/O sword/O through/O her/O belt/O ,/O Arya/PERSON began/O to/O climb/O ./O 
Her/O broken/O thumbnail/O left/O smears/O of/O blood/O on/O the/O painted/O marble/O ,/O but/O she/O made/O it/O up/O ,/O and/O wedged/O herself/O in/O between/O the/O king/O 's/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O when/O she/O saw/O her/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON stood/O on/O the/O High/O Septon/O 's/O pulpit/O outside/O the/O doors/O of/O the/O sept/O ,/O supported/O between/O two/O of/O the/O gold/O cloaks/O ./O 
He/O was/O dressed/O in/O a/O rich/O grey/O velvet/O doublet/O with/O a/O white/O wolf/O sewn/O on/O the/O front/O in/O beads/O ,/O and/O a/O grey/O wool/O cloak/O trimmed/O with/O fur/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O thinner/O than/O Arya/PERSON had/O ever/O seen/O him/O ,/O his/O long/O face/O drawn/O with/O pain/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O standing/O so/O much/O as/O being/O held/O up/O ;/O the/O cast/O over/O his/O broken/O leg/O was/O grey/O and/O rotten/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O High/O Septon/O himself/O stood/O behind/O him/O ,/O a/O squat/O man/O ,/O grey/O with/O age/O and/O ponderously/O fat/O ,/O wearing/O long/O white/O robes/O and/O an/O immense/O crown/O of/O spun/O gold/O and/O crystal/O that/O wreathed/O his/O head/O with/O rainbows/O whenever/O he/O moved/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Clustered/O around/O the/O doors/O of/O the/O sept/O ,/O in/O front/O of/O the/O raised/O marble/O pulpit/O ,/O were/O a/O knot/O of/O knights/O and/O high/O lords/O ./O 
Joffrey/PERSON was/O prominent/O among/O them/O ,/O his/O raiment/O all/O crimson/O ,/O silk/O and/O satin/O patterned/O with/O prancing/O stags/O and/O roaring/O lions/O ,/O a/O gold/O crown/O on/O his/O head/O ./O 
His/O queen/O mother/O stood/O beside/O him/O in/O a/O black/O mourning/O gown/O slashed/O with/O crimson/O ,/O a/O veil/O of/O black/O diamonds/O in/O her/O hair/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON recognized/O the/O Hound/O ,/O wearing/O a/O snowy/O white/O cloak/O over/O his/O dark/O grey/O armor/O ,/O with/O four/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O around/O him/O ./O 
She/O saw/O Varys/PERSON the/O eunuch/O gliding/O among/O ''/O ,/O ``/O the/O lords/O in/O soft/O slippers/O and/O a/O patterned/O damask/O robe/O ,/O and/O she/O thought/O the/O short/O man/O with/O the/O silvery/O cape/O and/O pointed/O beard/O might/O be/O the/O one/O who/O had/O once/O fought/O a/O duel/O for/O Mother/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O there/O in/O their/O midst/O was/O Sansa/O ,/O dressed/O in/O sky-blue/O silk/O ,/O with/O her/O long/O auburn/O hair/O washed/O and/O curled/O and/O silver/O bracelets/O on/O her/O wrists/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON scowled/O ,/O wondering/O what/O her/O sister/O was/O doing/O here/O ,/O why/O she/O looked/O so/O happy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O long/O line/O of/O gold-cloaked/O spearmen/O held/O back/O the/O crowd/O ,/O commanded/O by/O a/O stout/O man/O in/O elaborate/O armor/O ,/O all/O black/O lacquer/O and/O gold/O filigree/O ./O 
His/O cloak/O had/O the/O metallic/O shimmer/O of/O true/O cloth-of-gold/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O bell/O ceased/O to/O toll/O ,/O a/O quiet/O slowly/O settled/O across/O the/O great/O plaza/O ,/O and/O her/O father/O lifted/O his/O head/O and/O began/O to/O speak/O ,/O his/O voice/O so/O thin/O and/O weak/O she/O could/O scarcely/O make/O him/O out/O ./O 
People/O behind/O her/O began/O to/O shout/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O What/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O and/O \/O ``/O Louder/O !/O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O in/O the/O black-and-gold/O armor/O stepped/O up/O behind/O Father/O and/O prodded/O him/O sharply/O ./O 
You/O leave/O him/O alone/O !/O 
Arya/PERSON wanted/O to/O shout/O ,/O but/O she/O knew/O no/O one/O would/O listen/O ./O 
She/O chewed/O her/O lip/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O father/O raised/O his/O voice/O and/O began/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O Eddard/O Stark/O ,/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION and/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O more/O loudly/O ,/O his/O voice/O carrying/O across/O the/O plaza/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O I/O come/O before/O you/O to/O confess/O my/O treason/O in/O the/O sight/O of/O gods/O and/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON whimpered/O ./O 
Below/O her/O ,/O the/O crowd/O began/O to/O scream/O and/O shout/O ./O 
Taunts/O and/O obscenities/O filled/O the/O air/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O hidden/O her/O face/O in/O her/O hands/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O father/O raised/O his/O voice/O still/O higher/O ,/O straining/O to/O be/O heard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O betrayed/O the/O faith/O of/O my/O king/O and/O the/O trust/O of/O my/O friend/O ,/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O swore/O to/O defend/O and/O protect/O his/O children/O ,/O yet/O before/O his/O blood/O was/O cold/O ,/O I/O plotted/O to/O depose/O and/O murder/O his/O son/O and/O seize/O the/O throne/O for/O myself/O ./O 
Let/O the/O High/O Septon/O and/O Baelor/O the/O Beloved/O and/O the/O Seven/O bear/O witness/O to/O the/O truth/O of/O what/O I/O say/O :/O Joffrey/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON is/O the/O one/O true/O heir/O to/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O and/O by/O the/O grace/O of/O all/O the/O gods/O ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O and/O Protector/O of/O the/O Realm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O stone/O came/O sailing/O out/O of/O the/O crowd/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON cried/O out/O as/O she/O saw/O her/O father/O hit/O ./O 
The/O gold/O cloaks/O kept/O him/O from/O falling/O ./O 
Blood/O ran/O down/O his/O face/O from/O a/O deep/O gash/O across/O his/O forehead/O ./O 
More/O stones/O followed/O ./O 
One/O struck/O the/O guard/O to/O Father/O 's/O left/O ./O 
Another/O went/O clanging/O off/O the/O breastplate/O of/O the/O knight/O in/O the/O black-and-gold/O armor/O ./O 
Two/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/PERSON stepped/O in/O front/O of/O Joffrey/LOCATION and/O the/O queen/O ,/O protecting/O them/O with/O their/O shields/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Her/O hand/O slid/O beneath/O her/O cloak/O and/O found/O Needle/O in/O its/O sheath/O ./O 
She/O tightened/O her/O fingers/O around/O the/O grip/O ,/O squeezing/O as/O hard/O as/O she/O had/O ever/O squeezed/O anything/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O gods/O ,/O keep/O him/O safe/O ,/O she/O prayed/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O let/O them/O hurt/O my/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O High/O Septon/O knelt/O before/O Joffrey/PERSON and/O his/O mother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O we/O sin/O ,/O so/O do/O we/O suffer/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O intoned/O ,/O in/O a/O deep/O swelling/O voice/O much/O louder/O than/O Father/O 's/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O man/O has/O confessed/O his/O crimes/O in/O the/O sight/O of/O gods/O and/O men/O ,/O here/O in/O this/O holy/O place/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Rainbows/O danced/O around/O his/O head/O as/O he/O lifted/O his/O hands/O in/O entreaty/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O are/O just/O ,/O yet/O Blessed/PERSON Baelor/PERSON taught/O us/O that/O they/O are/O also/O merciful/O ./O 
What/O shall/O be/O done/O with/O this/O traitor/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O thousand/O voices/O were/O screaming/O ,/O but/O Arya/PERSON never/O heard/O them/O ./O 
Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON .../O no/O ,/O King/ORGANIZATION Joffrey/ORGANIZATION .../O stepped/O out/O from/O behind/O the/O shields/O of/O his/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O mother/O bids/O me/O let/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON take/O the/O black/O ,/O and/O Lady/PERSON Sansa/PERSON has/O begged/O mercy/O for/O her/O father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O straight/O at/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O then/O ,/O and/O smiled/O ,/O and/O for/O a/O moment/O Arya/PERSON thought/O that/O the/O gods/O had/O heard/O her/O prayer/O ,/O until/O Joffrey/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O the/O crowd/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O But/O they/O have/O the/O soft/O hearts/O of/O women/O ./O 
So/O long/O as/O I/O am/O your/O king/O ,/O treason/O shall/O never/O go/O unpunished/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON ,/O bring/O me/O his/O head/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O crowd/O roared/O ,/O and/O Arya/PERSON felt/O the/O statue/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION rock/O as/O they/O surged/O against/O it/O ./O 
The/O High/O Septon/O clutched/O at/O the/O king/O 's/O cape/O ,/O and/O Varys/PERSON came/O rushing/O over/O waving/O his/O arms/O ,/O and/O even/O the/O queen/O was/O saying/O something/O to/O him/O ,/O but/O Joffrey/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
Lords/O and/O knights/O moved/O aside/O as/O he/O stepped/O through/O ,/O tall/O and/O fleshless/O ,/O a/O skeleton/O in/O iron/O mail/O ,/O the/O King/O 's/O Justice/O ./O 
Dimly/O ,/O as/O if/O from/O far/O off/O ,/O Arya/PERSON heard/O her/O sister/O scream/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O fallen/O to/O her/O knees/O ,/O sobbing/O hysterically/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON climbed/O the/O steps/O of/O the/O pulpit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON wriggled/O between/O Baelor/PERSON 's/O feet/O and/O threw/O herself/O into/O the/O crowd/O ,/O drawing/O Needle/O ./O 
She/O landed/O on/O a/O man/O in/O a/O butcher/O 's/O apron/O ,/O knocking/O him/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Immediately/O someone/O slammed/O into/O her/O back/O and/O she/O almost/O went/O down/O herself/O ./O 
Bodies/O closed/O in/O around/O her/O ,/O stumbling/O and/O pushing/O ,/O trampling/O on/O the/O poor/O butcher/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON slashed/O at/O them/O with/O Needle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O High/O atop/O the/O pulpit/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON gestured/O and/O the/O knight/O in/O black-and-gold/O gave/O a/O command/O ./O 
The/O gold/O cloaks/O flung/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON to/O the/O marble/O ,/O with/O his/O head/O and/O chest/O out/O over/O the/O edge/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Here/O ,/O you/O !/O 
\/O ''/O an/O angry/O voice/O shouted/O at/O Arya/PERSON ,/O but/O she/O bowled/O past/O ,/O shoving/O people/O aside/O ,/O squirming/O between/O them/O ,/O slamming/O into/O anyone/O in/O her/O way/O ./O 
A/O hand/O fumbled/O at/O her/O leg/O and/O she/O hacked/O at/O it/O ,/O kicked/O at/O shins/O ./O 
A/O woman/O stumbled/O and/O Arya/PERSON ran/O up/O her/O back/O ,/O cutting/O to/O both/O sides/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O no/O good/O ,/O no/O good/O ,/O there/O were/O too/O many/O people/O ,/O no/O sooner/O did/O she/O make/O a/O hole/O than/O it/O closed/O again/O ./O 
Someone/O buffeted/O her/O aside/O ./O 
She/O could/O still/O hear/O Sansa/O screaming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Ilyn/O drew/O a/O two-handed/O greatsword/O from/O the/O scabbard/O on/O his/O back/O ./O 
As/O he/O lifted/O the/O blade/O above/O his/O head/O ,/O sunlight/O seemed/O to/O ripple/O and/O dance/O down/O the/O dark/O metal/O ,/O glinting/O off/O an/O edge/O sharper/O than/O any/O razor/O ./O 
Ice/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O he/O has/O Ice/O !/O 
Her/O tears/O streamed/O down/O her/O face/O ,/O blinding/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O then/O a/O hand/O shot/O out/O of/O the/O press/O and/O closed/O round/O her/O arm/O like/O a/O wolf/O trap/O ,/O so/O hard/O that/O Needle/PERSON went/O flying/O from/O her/O hand/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON was/O wrenched/O off/O her/O feet/O ./O 
She/O would/O have/O fallen/O if/O he/O had/O n't/O held/O her/O up/O ,/O as/O easy/O as/O if/O she/O were/O a/O doll/O ./O 
A/O face/O pressed/O close/O to/O hers/O ,/O long/O black/O hair/O and/O tangled/O beard/O and/O rotten/O teeth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O look/O !/O 
\/O ''/O a/O thick/O voice/O snarled/O at/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O ./O 
I./O ./O 
./O 
Arya/PERSON sobbed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O shook/O her/O so/O hard/O her/O teeth/O rattled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shut/O your/O mouth/O and/O close/O your/O eyes/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dimly/O ,/O as/O if/O from/O far/O away/O ,/O she/O heard/O a./O ./O 
./O 
a/O noise/O .../O a/O soft/O sighing/O sound/O ,/O as/O if/O a/O million/O people/O had/O let/O out/O their/O breath/O at/O once/O ./O 
The/O old/O man/O 's/O fingers/O dug/O into/O her/O arm/O ,/O stiff/O as/O iron/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O at/O me/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O way/O of/O it/O ,/O at/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sour/O wine/O perfumed/O his/O breath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Remember/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O smell/O that/O did/O it/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON saw/O the/O matted/O greasy/O hair/O ,/O the/O patched/O ,/O dusty/O black/O cloak/O that/O covered/O his/O twisted/O shoulders/O ,/O the/O hard/O black/O eyes/O squinting/O at/O her/O ./O 
And/O she/O remembered/O the/O black/O brother/O who/O had/O come/O to/O visit/O her/O father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Know/O me/O now/O ,/O do/O you/O ?/O 
There/O 's/O a/O bright/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O spat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O done/O here/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O be/O coming/O with/O me/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O be/O keeping/O your/O mouth/O shut/O ./O 
\/O ''/O When/O she/O started/O to/O reply/O ,/O he/O shook/O her/O again/O ,/O even/O harder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shut/O ,/O I/O said/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O plaza/O was/O beginning/O to/O empty/O ./O 
The/O press/O dissolved/O around/O them/O as/O people/O drifted/O back/O to/O their/O lives/O ./O 
But/O Arya/PERSON 's/O life/O was/O gone/O ./O 
Numb/O ,/O she/O trailed/O along/O beside/O .../O Yoren/PERSON ,/O yes/O ,/O his/O name/O is/O Yoren/PERSON ./O 
She/O did/O not/O recall/O him/O finding/O Needle/O ,/O until/O he/O handed/O the/O sword/O back/O to/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hope/O you/O can/O use/O that/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O -/O \/O ''/O she/O started/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O shoved/O her/O into/O a/O doorway/O ,/O thrust/O dirty/O fingers/O through/O her/O hair/O ,/O and/O gave/O it/O a/O twist/O ,/O yanking/O her/O head/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O -/O not/O a/O smart/O boy/O ,/O that/O what/O you/O mean/O to/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O had/O a/O knife/O in/O his/O other/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O As/O the/O blade/O flashed/O toward/O her/O face/O ,/O Arya/PERSON threw/O herself/O backward/O ,/O kicking/O wildly/O ,/O wrenching/O her/O head/O from/O side/O to/O side/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O her/O by/O the/O hair/O ,/O so/O strong/O ,/O she/O could/O feel/O her/O scalp/O tearing/O ,/O and/O on/O her/O lips/O the/O salt/O taste/O of/O tears/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
