-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O never/O liked/O this/O godswood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O been/O born/O a/O Tully/O ,/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION far/O to/O the/O south/O ,/O on/O the/O Red/O Fork/O of/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
The/O godswood/O there/O was/O a/O garden/O ,/O bright/O and/O airy/O ,/O where/O tall/O redwoods/O spread/O dappled/O shadows/O across/O tinkling/O streams/O ,/O birds/O sang/O from/O hidden/O nests/O ,/O and/O the/O air/O was/O spicy/O with/O the/O scent/O of/O flowers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O gods/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION kept/O a/O different/O sort/O of/O wood/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O dark/O ,/O primal/O place/O ,/O three/O acres/O of/O old/O forest/O untouched/O for/O ten/O thousand/O years/O as/O the/O gloomy/O castle/O rose/O around/O it/O ./O 
It/O smelled/O of/O moist/O earth/O and/O decay/O ./O 
No/O redwoods/O grew/O here/O ./O 
This/O was/O a/O wood/O of/O stubborn/O sentinel/O trees/O armored/O in/O grey-green/O needles/O ,/O of/O mighty/O oaks/O ,/O of/O ironwoods/O as/O old/O as/O the/O realm/O itself/O ./O 
Here/O thick/O black/O trunks/O crowded/O close/O together/O while/O twisted/O branches/O wove/O a/O dense/O canopy/O overhead/O and/O misshappen/O roots/O wrestled/O beneath/O the/O soil/O ./O 
This/O was/O a/O place/O of/O deep/O silence/O and/O brooding/O shadows/O ,/O and/O the/O gods/O who/O lived/O here/O had/O no/O names/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O she/O knew/O she/O would/O find/O her/O husband/O here/O tonight/O ./O 
Whenever/O he/O took/O a/O man/O 's/O life/O ,/O afterward/O he/O would/O seek/O the/O quiet/O of/O the/O godswood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O been/O anointed/O with/O the/O seven/O oils/O and/O named/O in/O the/O rainbow/O of/O light/O that/O filled/O the/O sept/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
She/O was/O of/O the/O Faith/O ,/O like/O her/O father/O and/O grandfather/O and/O his/O father/O before/O him/O ./O 
Her/O gods/O had/O names/O ,/O and/O their/O faces/O were/O as/O familiar/O as/O the/O faces/O of/O her/O parents/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Worship/O was/O a/O septon/O with/O a/O censer/O ,/O the/O smell/O of/O incense/O ,/O a/O seven-sided/O crystal/O alive/O with/O light/O ,/O voices/O raised/O in/O song/O ./O 
The/O Tullys/PERSON kept/O a/O godswood/O ,/O as/O all/O the/O great/O houses/O did/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O only/O a/O place/O to/O walk/O or/O read/O or/O lie/O in/O the/O sun/O ./O 
Worship/O was/O for/O the/O sept./O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O her/O sake/O ,/O Ned/PERSON had/O built/O a/O small/O sept/O where/O she/O might/O sing/O to/O the/O seven/O faces/O of/O god/O ,/O but/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O still/O flowed/O in/O the/O veins/O of/O the/O Starks/PERSON ,/O and/O his/O own/O gods/O were/O the/O old/O ones/O ,/O the/O nameless/O ,/O faceless/O gods/O of/O the/O greenwood/O they/O shared/O with/O the/O vanished/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O the/O center/O of/O the/O grove/O an/O ancient/O weirwood/O brooded/O over/O a/O small/O pool/O where/O the/O waters/O were/O black/O and/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O heart/O tree/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON called/O it/O ./O 
The/O weirwood/O 's/O bark/O was/O white/O as/O bone/O ,/O its/O leaves/O dark/O red/O ,/O like/O a/O thousand/O bloodstained/O hands/O ./O 
A/O face/O had/O been/O carved/O in/O the/O trunk/O of/O the/O great/O tree/O ,/O its/O features/O long/O and/O melancholy/O ,/O the/O deep-cut/O eyes/O red/O with/O dried/O sap/O and/O strangely/O watchful/O ./O 
They/O were/O old/O ,/O those/O eyes/O ;/O older/O than/O Winterfell/O itself/O ./O 
They/O had/O seen/O Brandon/PERSON the/PERSON Builder/PERSON set/O the/O first/O stone/O ,/O if/O the/O tales/O were/O true/O ;/O they/O had/O watched/O the/O castle/O 's/O granite/O walls/O rise/O around/O them/O ./O 
It/O was/O said/O that/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O had/O carved/O the/O faces/O in/O the/O trees/O during/O the/O dawn/O centuries/O before/O the/O coming/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O the/O south/O the/O last/O weirwoods/O had/O been/O cut/O down/O or/O burned/O out/O a/O thousand/O years/O ago/O ,/O except/O on/O the/O Isle/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Faces/ORGANIZATION where/O the/O green/O men/O kept/O their/O silent/O watch/O ./O 
Up/O here/O it/O was/O different/O ./O 
Here/O every/O castle/O had/O its/O godswood/O ,/O and/O every/O godswood/O had/O its/O heart/O tree/O ,/O and/O every/O heart/O tree/O its/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O found/O her/O husband/O beneath/O the/O weirwood/O ,/O seated/O on/O a/O moss-covered/O stone/O ./O 
The/O greatsword/O Ice/O was/O across/O his/O lap/O ,/O and/O he/O was/O cleaning/O the/O blade/O in/O those/O waters/O black/O as/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O thousand/O years/O of/O humus/O lay/O thick/O upon/O the/O godswood/O floor/O ,/O swallowing/O the/O sound/O of/O her/O feet/O ,/O but/O the/O red/O eyes/O of/O the/O weirwood/O seemed/O to/O follow/O her/O as/O she/O came/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ned/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O softly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O lifted/O his/O head/O to/O look/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Catelyn/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
His/O voice/O was/O distant/O and/O formal/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O the/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O would/O always/O ask/O her/O that/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O the/O kitchen/O ,/O arguing/O about/O names/O for/O the/O wolf/O pups/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O spread/O her/O cloak/O on/O the/O forest/O floor/O and/O sat/O beside/O the/O pool/O ,/O her/O back/O to/O the/O weirwood/O ./O 
She/O could/O feel/O the/O eyes/O watching/O her/O ,/O but/O she/O did/O her/O best/O to/O ignore/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON is/O already/O in/O love/O ,/O and/O Sansa/O is/O charmed/O and/O gracious/O ,/O but/O Rickon/PERSON is/O not/O quite/O sure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O he/O afraid/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O little/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O only/O three/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O frowned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O must/O learn/O to/O face/O his/O fears/O ./O 
He/O will/O not/O be/O three/O forever/O ./O 
And/O winter/O is/O coming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
The/O words/O gave/O her/O a/O chill/O ,/O as/O they/O always/O did/O ./O 
The/O Stark/O words/O ./O 
Every/O noble/O house/O had/O its/O words/O ./O 
Family/O mottoes/O ,/O touchstones/O ,/O prayers/O of/O sorts/O ,/O they/O boasted/O of/O honor/O and/O glory/O ,/O promised/O loyalty/O and/O truth/O ,/O swore/O faith/O and/O courage/O ./O 
All/O but/O the/O Starks/PERSON ./O 
Winter/O is/O coming/O ,/O said/O the/O Stark/O words/O ./O 
Not/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ,/O she/O reflected/O on/O what/O a/O strange/O people/O these/O northerners/O ;/O were/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O man/O died/O well/O ,/O I/O 'll/O give/O him/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O swatch/O of/O oiled/O leather/O in/O one/O hand/O ./O 
He/O ran/O it/O lightly/O up/O the/O greatsword/O as/O he/O spoke/O ,/O polishing/O the/O metal/O to/O a/O dark/O glow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O glad/O for/O Bran/O 's/O sake/O ./O 
You/O would/O have/O been/O proud/O of/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O always/O proud/O of/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ,/O watching/O the/O sword/O as/O he/O stroked/O it/O ./O 
She/O could/O see/O the/O rippling/O deep/O within/O the/O steel/O ,/O where/O the/O metal/O had/O been/O folded/O back/O on/O itself/O a/O hundred/O times/O in/O the/O forging/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O no/O love/O for/O swords/O ,/O but/O she/O could/O not/O deny/O that/O Ice/O had/O its/O own/O beauty/O ./O 
It/O had/O been/O forged/O in/O Valyria/LOCATION ,/O before/O the/O Doom/O had/O come/O to/O the/O old/O Freehold/LOCATION ,/O when/O the/O ironsmiths/O had/O worked/O their/O metal/O with/O spells/O as/O well/O as/O hammers/O ./O 
Four/O hundred/O years/O old/O it/O was/O ,/O and/O as/O sharp/O as/O the/O day/O it/O was/O forged/O ./O 
The/O name/O it/O bore/O was/O older/O still/O ,/O a/O legacy/O from/O the/O age/O of/O heroes/O ,/O when/O the/O Starks/PERSON were/O Kings/O in/O the/O North/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O was/O the/O fourth/O this/O year/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O grimly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O poor/O man/O was/O half-mad/O ./O 
Something/O had/O put/O a/O fear/O in/O him/O so/O deep/O that/O my/O words/O could/O not/O reach/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ben/PERSON writes/O that/O the/O strength/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O down/O below/O a/O thousand/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O only/O desertions/O ./O 
They/O are/O losing/O men/O on/O rangings/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O it/O the/O wildlings/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O else/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON lifted/O Ice/O ,/O looked/O down/O the/O cool/O steel/O length/O of/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O it/O will/O only/O grow/O worse/O ./O 
The/O day/O may/O come/O when/O I/O will/O have/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O call/O the/O banners/O and/O ride/O north/O to/O deal/O with/O this/O Kingbeyond-the-Wall/PERSON for/O good/O and/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O Wall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O thought/O made/O Catelyn/O shudder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O saw/O the/O dread/O on/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON is/O nothing/O for/O us/O to/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O darker/O things/O beyond/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O glanced/O behind/O her/O at/O the/O heart/O tree/O ,/O the/O pale/O bark/O and/O red/O eyes/O ,/O watching/O ,/O listening/O ,/O thinking/O its/O long/O slow/O thoughts/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O smile/O was/O gentle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O listen/O to/O too/O many/O of/O Old/O Nan/PERSON 's/O stories/O ./O 
The/O Others/O are/O as/O dead/O as/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ,/O gone/O eight/O thousand/O years/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON will/O tell/O you/O they/O never/O lived/O at/O all/O ./O 
No/O living/O man/O has/O ever/O seen/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Until/O this/O morning/O ,/O no/O living/O man/O had/O ever/O seen/O a/O direwolf/O either/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O ought/O to/O know/O better/O than/O to/O argue/O with/O a/O Tully/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O with/O a/O rueful/O smile/O ./O 
He/O slid/O Ice/O back/O into/O its/O sheath/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O did/O not/O come/O here/O to/O tell/O me/O crib/O tales/O ./O 
I/O know/O how/O little/O you/O like/O this/O place/O ./O 
What/O is/O it/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O her/O husband/O 's/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O was/O grievous/O news/O today/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
I/O did/O not/O wish/O to/O trouble/O you/O until/O you/O had/O cleansed/O yourself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O was/O no/O way/O to/O soften/O the/O blow/O ,/O so/O she/O told/O him/O straight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O so/O sorry/O ,/O my/O love/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON is/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O found/O hers/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O see/O how/O hard/O it/O took/O him/O ,/O as/O she/O had/O known/O it/O would/O ./O 
In/O his/O youth/O ,/O Ned/PERSON had/O fostered/O at/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O and/O the/O childless/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON had/O become/O a/O second/O father/O to/O him/O and/O his/O fellow/O ward/O ,/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ./O 
When/O the/O Mad/O King/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON had/O demanded/O their/O heads/O ,/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON had/O raised/O his/O moon-and-falcon/O banners/O in/O revolt/O rather/O than/O give/O up/O those/O he/O had/O pledged/O to/O protect/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O one/O day/O fifteen/O years/O ago/O ,/O this/O second/O father/O had/O become/O a/O brother/O as/O well/O ,/O as/O he/O and/O Ned/PERSON stood/O together/O in/O the/O sept/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION to/O wed/O two/O sisters/O ,/O the/O daughters/O of/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/O .../O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O news/O certain/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O king/O 's/O seal/O ,/O and/O the/O letter/O is/O in/O Robert/PERSON 's/O own/O hand/O ./O 
I/O saved/O it/O for/O you/O ./O 
He/O said/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON was/O taken/O quickly/O ./O 
Even/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON was/O helpless/O ,/O but/O he/O brought/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O so/O Jon/PERSON did/O not/O linger/O long/O in/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O is/O some/O small/O mercy/O ,/O I/O suppose/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
She/O could/O see/O the/O grief/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O but/O even/O then/O he/O thought/O first/O of/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O sister/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Jon/PERSON 's/O boy/O ./O 
What/O word/O of/O them/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O message/O said/O only/O that/O they/O were/O well/O ,/O and/O had/O returned/O to/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wish/O they/O had/O gone/O to/O Riverrun/O instead/O ./O 
The/O Eyrie/O is/O high/O and/O lonely/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O ever/O her/O husband/O 's/O place/O ,/O not/O hers/O ./O 
Lord/O Jon/PERSON 's/O memory/O will/O haunt/O each/O stone/O ./O 
I/O know/O my/O sister/O ./O 
She/O needs/O the/O comfort/O of/O family/O and/O friends/O around/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O uncle/O waits/O in/O the/O Vale/O ,/O does/O he/O not/O ?/O 
Jon/PERSON named/O him/O Knight/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON Gate/PERSON ,/O I/O 'd/O heard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Brynden/PERSON will/O do/O what/O he/O can/O for/O her/O ,/O and/O for/O the/O boy/O ./O 
That/O is/O some/O comfort/O ,/O but/O still/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O to/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON urged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O the/O children/O ./O 
Fill/O her/O halls/O with/O noise/O and/O shouts/O and/O laughter/O ./O 
That/O boy/O of/O hers/O needs/O other/O children/O about/O him/O ,/O and/O Lysa/PERSON should/O not/O be/O alone/O in/O her/O grief/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O that/O I/O could/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O letter/O had/O other/O tidings/O ./O 
The/O king/O is/O riding/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION to/O seek/O you/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O took/O Ned/PERSON a/O moment/O to/O comprehend/O her/O words/O ,/O but/O when/O the/O understanding/O came/O ,/O the/O darkness/O left/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON is/O coming/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O When/O she/O nodded/O ,/O a/O smile/O broke/O across/O his/O face/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON wished/O she/O could/O share/O his/O joy/O ./O 
But/O she/O had/O heard/O the/O talk/O in/O the/O yards/O ;/O a/O direwolf/O dead/O in/O the/O snow/O ,/O a/O broken/O antler/O in/O its/O throat/O ./O 
Dread/O coiled/O within/O her/O like/O a/O snake/O ,/O but/O she/O forced/O herself/O to/O smile/O at/O this/O man/O she/O loved/O ,/O this/O man/O who/O put/O no/O faith/O in/O signs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O knew/O that/O would/O please/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O should/O send/O word/O to/O your/O brother/O on/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ben/PERSON will/O want/O to/O be/O here/O ./O 
I/O shall/O tell/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON to/O send/O his/O swiftest/O bird/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON rose/O and/O pulled/O her/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Damnation/O ,/O how/O many/O years/O has/O it/O been/O ?/O 
And/O he/O gives/O us/O no/O more/O notice/O than/O this/O ?/O 
How/O many/O in/O his/O party/O ,/O did/O the/O message/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O should/O think/O a/O hundred/O knights/O ,/O at/O the/O least/O ,/O with/O all/O their/O retainers/O ,/O and/O half/O again/O as/O many/O freeriders/O ./O 
Cersei/PERSON and/O the/O children/O travel/O with/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON will/O keep/O an/O easy/O pace/O for/O their/O sakes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O just/O as/O well/O ./O 
That/O will/O give/O us/O more/O time/O to/O prepare/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O queen/O 's/O brothers/O are/O also/O in/O the/O party/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON grimaced/O at/O that/O ./O 
There/O was/O small/O love/O between/O him/O and/O the/O queen/O 's/O family/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION had/O come/O late/O to/O Robert/PERSON 's/O cause/O ,/O when/O victory/O was/O all/O but/O certain/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O never/O forgiven/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O if/O the/O price/O for/O Robert/PERSON 's/O company/O is/O an/O infestation/O of/O Lannisters/O ,/O so/O be/O it/O ./O 
It/O sounds/O as/O though/O Robert/PERSON is/O bringing/O half/O his/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Where/O the/O king/O goes/O ,/O the/O realm/O follows/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O good/O to/O see/O the/O children/O ./O 
The/O youngest/O was/O still/O sucking/O at/O the/O Lannister/O woman/O 's/O teat/O the/O last/O time/O I/O saw/O him/O ./O 
He/O must/O be/O ,/O what/O ,/O five/O by/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Prince/O Tornmen/PERSON is/O seven/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O same/O age/O as/O Bran/O ./O 
Please/O ,/O Ned/PERSON ,/O guard/O your/O tongue/O ./O 
The/O Lannister/O woman/O is/O our/O queen/O ,/O and/O her/O pride/O is/O said/O to/O grow/O with/O every/O passing/O year/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON squeezed/O her/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O must/O be/O a/O feast/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O with/O singers/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON will/O want/O to/O hunt/O ./O 
I/O shall/O send/O Jory/PERSON south/O with/O an/O honor/O guard/O to/O meet/O them/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O escort/O them/O back/O ./O 
Gods/O ,/O how/O are/O we/O going/O to/O feed/O them/O all/O ?/O 
On/O his/O way/O already/O ,/O you/O said/O ?/O 
Damn/O the/O man/O ./O 
Damn/O his/O royal/O hide/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
