-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O you/O ought/O cover/O your/O head/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON told/O her/O as/O their/O horses/O plodded/O north/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O take/O a/O chill/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O only/O water/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ./O 
Her/O hair/O hung/O wet/O and/O heavy/O ,/O a/O loose/O strand/O stuck/O to/O her/O forehead/O ,/O and/O she/O could/O imagine/O how/O ragged/O and/O wild/O she/O must/O look/O ,/O but/O for/O once/O she/O did/O not/O care/O ./O 
The/O southern/O rain/O was/O soft/O and/O warm/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON liked/O the/O feel/O of/O it/O on/O her/O face/O ,/O gentle/O as/O a/O mother/O 's/O kisses/O ./O 
It/O took/O her/O back/O to/O her/O childhood/O ,/O to/O long/O grey/O days/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
She/O remembered/O the/O godswood/O ,/O drooping/O branches/O heavy/O with/O moisture/O ,/O and/O the/O sound/O of/O her/O brother/O 's/O laughter/O as/O he/O chased/O her/O through/O piles/O of/O damp/O leaves/O ./O 
She/O remembered/O making/O mud/O pies/O with/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O the/O weight/O of/O them/O ,/O the/O mud/O slick/O and/O brown/O between/O her/O fingers/O ./O 
They/O had/O served/O them/O to/O Little/O finger/O ,/O giggling/O ,/O and/O he/O 'd/O eaten/O so/O much/O mud/O he/O was/O sick/O for/O a/O week/O ./O 
How/O young/O they/O all/O had/O been/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O almost/O forgotten/O ./O 
In/O the/O north/O ,/O the/O rain/O fell/O cold/O and/O hard/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O at/O night/O it/O turned/O to/O ice/O ./O 
It/O was/O as/O likely/O to/O kill/O a/O crop/O as/O nurture/O it/O ,/O and/O it/O sent/O grown/O men/O running/O for/O the/O nearest/O shelter/O ./O 
That/O was/O no/O rain/O for/O little/O girls/O to/O play/O in/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O soaked/O through/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON complained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O my/O bones/O are/O wet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O woods/O pressed/O close/O around/O them/O ,/O and/O the/O steady/O pattering/O of/O rain/O on/O leaves/O was/O accompanied/O by/O the/O small/O sucking/O sounds/O their/O horses/O made/O as/O their/O hooves/O pulled/O free/O of/O the/O mud/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O will/O want/O a/O fire/O tonight/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O and/O a/O hot/O meal/O would/O serve/O us/O both/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O an/O inn/O at/O the/O crossroads/O up/O ahead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
She/O had/O slept/O many/O a/O night/O there/O in/O her/O youth/O ,/O traveling/O with/O her/O father/O ./O 
Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON had/O been/O a/O restless/O man/O in/O his/O prime/O ,/O always/O riding/O somewhere/O ./O 
She/O still/O remembered/O the/O innkeep/O ,/O a/O fat/O woman/O named/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON who/O chewed/O sourleaf/O night/O and/O day/O and/O seemed/O to/O have/O an/O endless/O supply/O of/O smiles/O and/O sweet/O cakes/O for/O the/O children/O ./O 
The/O sweet/O cakes/O had/O been/O soaked/O with/O honey/O ,/O rich/O and/O heavy/O on/O the/O tongue/O ,/O but/O how/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O dreaded/O those/O smiles/O ./O 
The/O sourleaf/O had/O stained/O Masha/PERSON 's/O teeth/O a/O dark/O red/O ,/O and/O made/O her/O smile/O a/O bloody/O horror/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O An/O inn/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON repeated/O wistfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O only/O .../O but/O we/O dare/O not/O risk/O it/O ./O 
If/O we/O wish/O to/O remain/O unknown/O ,/O I/O think/O it/O best/O we/O seek/O out/O some/O small/O holdfast/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O broke/O off/O as/O they/O heard/O sounds/O up/O the/O road/O ;/O splashing/O water/O ,/O the/O clink/O of/O mail/O ,/O a/O horse/O 's/O whinny/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Riders/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O warned/O ,/O his/O hand/O dropping/O to/O the/O hilt/O of/O his/O sword/O ./O 
Even/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ,/O it/O never/O hurt/O to/O be/O wary/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O followed/O the/O sounds/O around/O a/O lazy/O bend/O of/O the/O road/O and/O saw/O them/O ;/O a/O column/O of/O armed/O men/O noisily/O fording/O a/O swollen/O stream/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON reined/O up/O to/O let/O them/O pass/O ./O 
The/O banner/O in/O the/O hand/O of/O the/O foremost/O rider/O hung/O sodden/O and/O limp/O ,/O but/O the/O guardsmen/O wore/O indigo/O cloaks/O and/O on/O their/O shoulders/O flew/O the/O silver/O eagle/O of/O Seagard/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Mallisters/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON whispered/O to/O her/O ,/O as/O if/O she/O had/O not/O known/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O best/O pull/O up/O your/O hood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON made/O no/O move/O ./O 
Lord/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON himself/O rode/O with/O them/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O his/O knights/O ,/O his/O son/O Patrek/PERSON by/O his/O side/O and/O their/O squires/O close/O behind/O ./O 
They/O were/O riding/O for/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O the/O Hand/O 's/O tourney/O ,/O she/O knew/O ./O 
For/O the/O past/O week/O ,/O the/O travelers/O had/O been/O thick/O as/O flies/O upon/O the/O kingsroad/O ;/O knights/O and/O freeriders/O ,/O singers/O with/O their/O harps/O and/O drums/O ,/O heavy/O ''/O ,/O ``/O wagons/O laden/O with/O hops/O or/O corn/O or/O casks/O of/O honey/O ,/O traders/O and/O craftsmen/O and/O whores/O ,/O and/O all/O of/O them/O moving/O south/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O studied/O Lord/O Jason/PERSON boldly/O ./O 
The/O last/O time/O she/O had/O seen/O him/O he/O had/O been/O jesting/O with/O her/O uncle/O at/O her/O wedding/O feast/O ;/O the/O Mallisters/O stood/O bannermen/O to/O the/O Tullys/O ,/O and/O his/O gifts/O had/O been/O lavish/O ./O 
His/O brown/O hair/O was/O salted/O with/O white/O now/O ,/O his/O face/O chiseled/O gaunt/O by/O time/O ,/O yet/O the/O years/O had/O not/O touched/O his/O pride/O ./O 
He/O rode/O like/O a/O man/O who/O feared/O nothing/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON envied/O him/O that/O ;/O she/O had/O come/O to/O fear/O so/O much/O ./O 
As/O the/O riders/O passed/O ,/O Lord/O Jason/PERSON nodded/O a/O curt/O greeting/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O only/O a/O high/O lord/O 's/O courtesy/O to/O strangers/O chance/O met/O on/O the/O road/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O recognition/O in/O those/O fierce/O eyes/O ,/O and/O his/O son/O did/O not/O even/O waste/O a/O look/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O did/O not/O know/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O after/O ,/O wondering/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O saw/O a/O pair/O of/O mud-spattered/O travelers/O by/O the/O side/O of/O the/O road/O ,/O wet/O and/O tired/O ./O 
It/O would/O never/O occur/O to/O him/O to/O suspect/O that/O one/O of/O them/O was/O the/O daughter/O of/O his/O liege/O lord/O ./O 
I/O think/O we/O shall/O be/O safe/O enough/O at/O the/O inn/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O near/O dark/O when/O they/O reached/O it/O ,/O at/O the/O crossroads/O north/O of/O the/O great/O confluence/O of/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON was/O fatter/O and/O greyer/O than/O Catelyn/O remembered/O ,/O still/O chewing/O her/O sourleaf/O ,/O but/O she/O gave/O them/O only/O the/O most/O cursory/O of/O looks/O ,/O with/O nary/O a/O hint/O of/O her/O ghastly/O red/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Two/O rooms/O at/O the/O top/O of/O the/O stair/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O there/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O chewing/O all/O the/O while/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O under/O the/O bell/O tower/O ,/O you/O wo/O n't/O be/O missing/O meals/O ,/O though/O there/O 's/O some/O thinks/O it/O too/O noisy/O ./O 
Ca/O n't/O be/O helped/O ./O 
We/O 're/O full/O up/O ,/O or/O near/O as/O makes/O no/O matter/O ./O 
It/O 's/O those/O rooms/O or/O the/O road/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O those/O rooms/O ,/O low/O ,/O dusty/O garrets/O at/O the/O top/O of/O a/O cramped/O narrow/O staircase/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Leave/O your/O boots/O down/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Masha/PERSON told/O them/O after/O she/O 'd/O taken/O their/O coin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O will/O clean/O them/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O have/O you/O tracking/O mud/O up/O my/O stairs/O ./O 
Mind/O the/O bell/O ./O 
Those/O who/O come/O late/O to/O meals/O do/O n't/O eat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O were/O no/O smiles/O ,/O and/O no/O mention/O of/O sweet/O cakes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O supper/O bell/O rang/O ,/O the/O sound/O was/O deafening/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON had/O changed/O into/O dry/O clothes/O ./O 
She/O sat/O by/O the/O window/O ,/O watching/O rain/O run/O down/O the/O pane/O ./O 
The/O glass/O was/O milky/O and/O full/O of/O bubbles/O ,/O and/O a/O wet/O dusk/O was/O falling/O outside/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON could/O just/O make/O out/O the/O muddy/O crossing/O where/O the/O two/O great/O roads/O met/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O crossroads/O gave/O her/O pause/O ./O 
If/O they/O turned/O west/O from/O here/O ,/O it/O was/O an/O easy/O ride/O down/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
Her/O father/O had/O always/O given/O her/O wise/O counsel/O when/O she/O needed/O it/O most/O ,/O and/O she/O yearned/O to/O talk/O to/O him/O ,/O to/O warn/O him/O of/O the/O gathering/O storm/O ./O 
If/O Winterfell/PERSON needed/O to/O brace/O for/O war/O ,/O how/O much/O more/O so/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O so/O much/O closer/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O with/O the/O power/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION looming/O to/O the/O west/O like/O a/O shadow/O ./O 
If/O only/O her/O father/O had/O been/O stronger/O ,/O she/O might/O have/O chanced/O it/O ,/O but/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON had/O been/O bedridden/O these/O past/O two/O years/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O loath/O to/O tax/O him/O now/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O eastern/O road/O was/O wilder/O and/O more/O dangerous/O ,/O climbing/O through/O rocky/O foothills/O and/O thick/O forests/O into/O the/O Mountains/LOCATION of/LOCATION the/LOCATION Moon/LOCATION ,/O past/O high/O passes/O and/O deep/O chasms/O to/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O stony/O Fingers/O beyond/O ./O 
Above/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O Eyrie/O stood/O high/O and/O impregnable/O ,/O its/O towers/O reaching/O for/O the/O sky/O ./O 
There/O she/O would/O find/O her/O sister/O .../O and/O ,/O perhaps/O ,/O some/O of/O the/O answers/O Ned/PERSON sought/O ./O 
Surely/O Lysa/PERSON knew/O more/O than/O she/O had/O dared/O to/O put/O in/O her/O letter/O ./O 
She/O might/O have/O the/O very/O ''/O ,/O ``/O proof/O that/O Ned/PERSON needed/O to/O bring/O the/O Lannisters/O to/O ruin/O ,/O and/O if/O it/O came/O to/O war/O ,/O they/O would/O need/O the/O Arryns/O and/O the/O eastern/O lords/O who/O owed/O them/O service/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O the/O mountain/O road/O was/O perilous/O ./O 
Shadowcats/O prowled/O those/O passes/O ,/O rock/O slides/O were/O common/O ,/O and/O the/O mountain/O clans/O were/O lawless/O brigands/O ,/O descending/O from/O the/O heights/O to/O rob/O and/O kill/O and/O melting/O away/O like/O snow/O whenever/O the/O knights/O rode/O out/O from/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION in/O search/O of/O them/O ./O 
Even/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O as/O great/O a/O lord/O as/O any/O the/O Eyrie/O had/O ever/O known/O ,/O had/O always/O traveled/O in/O strength/O when/O he/O crossed/O the/O mountains/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON 's/O only/O strength/O was/O one/O elderly/O knight/O ,/O armored/O in/O loyalty/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O Riverrun/PERSON and/O the/O Eyrie/O would/O have/O to/O wait/O ./O 
Her/O path/O ran/O north/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O where/O her/O sons/O and/O her/O duty/O were/O waiting/O for/O her/O ./O 
As/O soon/O as/O they/O were/O safely/O past/O the/O Neck/O ,/O she/O could/O declare/O herself/O to/O one/O of/O Ned/PERSON 's/O bannermen/O ,/O and/O send/O riders/O racing/O ahead/O with/O orders/O to/O mount/O a/O watch/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O rain/O obscured/O the/O fields/O beyond/O the/O crossroads/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O the/O land/O clear/O enough/O in/O her/O memory/O ./O 
The/O marketplace/O was/O just/O across/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O the/O village/O a/O mile/O farther/O on/O ,/O half/O a/O hundred/O white/O cottages/O surrounding/O a/O small/O stone/O sept./O ./O 
There/O would/O be/O more/O now/O ;/O the/O summer/O had/O been/O long/O and/O peaceful/O ./O 
North/O of/O here/O the/O kingsroad/O ran/O along/O the/O Green/O Fork/O of/O the/O Trident/O ,/O through/O fertile/O valleys/O and/O green/O woodlands/O ,/O past/O thriving/O towns/O and/O stout/O holdfasts/O and/O the/O castles/O of/O the/O river/O lords/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O them/O all/O :/O the/O Blackwoods/O and/O the/O Brackens/PERSON ,/O ever/O enemies/O ,/O whose/O quarrels/O her/O father/O was/O obliged/O to/O settle/O ;/O Lady/PERSON Whent/PERSON ,/O last/O of/O her/O line/O ,/O who/O dwelt/O with/O her/O ghosts/O in/O the/O cavernous/O vaults/O of/O Harrenhal/LOCATION ;/O irascible/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O outlived/O seven/O wives/O and/O filled/O his/O twin/O castles/O with/O children/O ,/O grandchildren/O ,/O and/O great-grandchildren/O ,/O and/O bastards/O and/O grandbastards/O as/O well/O ./O 
All/O of/O them/O were/O bannermen/O to/O the/O Tullys/O ,/O their/O swords/O sworn/O to/O the/O service/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON wondered/O if/O that/O would/O be/O enough/O ,/O if/O it/O came/O to/O war/O ./O 
Her/O father/O was/O the/O staunchest/O man/O who/O 'd/O ever/O lived/O ,/O and/O she/O had/O no/O doubt/O that/O he/O would/O call/O his/O banners/O .../O but/O would/O the/O banners/O come/O ?/O 
The/O Darrys/O and/O Rygers/O and/O Mootons/PERSON had/O sworn/O oaths/O to/O Riverrun/PERSON as/O well/O ,/O yet/O they/O had/O fought/O with/O Rhaegar/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON on/O the/O Trident/O ,/O while/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON had/O arrived/O with/O his/O levies/O well/O after/O the/O battle/O was/O over/O ,/O leaving/O some/O doubt/O as/O to/O which/O army/O he/O had/O planned/O to/O join/O -LRB-/O theirs/O ,/O he/O had/O assured/O the/O victors/O solemnly/O in/O the/O aftermath/O ,/O but/O ever/O after/O her/O father/O had/O called/O him/O the/O Late/O Lord/O Frey/PERSON -RRB-/O ./O 
It/O must/O not/O come/O to/O war/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O fervently/O ./O 
They/O must/O not/O let/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON came/O for/O her/O just/O as/O the/O bell/O ceased/O its/O clangor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O had/O best/O make/O haste/O if/O we/O hope/O to/O eat/O tonight/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O might/O be/O safer/O if/O we/O were/O not/O knight/O and/O lady/O until/O we/O pass/O the/O Neck/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Common/O travelers/O attract/O less/O notice/O ./O 
A/O father/O and/O daughter/O taken/O to/O the/O road/O on/O some/O family/O business/O ,/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
It/O was/O only/O when/O she/O laughed/O that/O he/O realized/O what/O he/O 'd/O done/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O old/O courtesies/O die/O hard/O ,/O my-my/O daughter/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O tried/O to/O tug/O on/O his/O missing/O whiskers/O ,/O and/O sighed/O with/O exasperation/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON took/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O find/O that/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON sets/O a/O good/O table/O ,/O I/O think/O ,/O but/O try/O not/O to/O praise/O her/O ./O 
You/O truly/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O see/O her/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O common/O room/O was/O long/O and/O drafty/O ,/O with/O a/O row/O of/O huge/O wooden/O kegs/O at/O one/O end/O and/O a/O fireplace/O at/O the/O other/O ./O 
A/O serving/O boy/O ran/O back/O and/O forth/O with/O skewers/O of/O meat/O while/O Masha/PERSON drew/O beer/O from/O the/O kegs/O ,/O chewing/O her/O sour/O leaf/O all/O the/O while/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O benches/O were/O crowded/O ,/O townsfolk/O and/O farmers/O mingling/O freely/O with/O all/O manner/O of/O travelers/O ./O 
The/O crossroads/O made/O for/O odd/O companions/O ;/O dyers/O with/O black/O and/O purple/O hands/O shared/O a/O bench/O with/O rivermen/O reeking/O offish/O ,/O an/O ironsmith/O thick/O with/O muscle/O squeezed/O in/O beside/O a/O wizened/O old/O septon/O ,/O hard-bitten/O sellswords/O and/O soft/O plump/O merchants/O swapped/O news/O like/O boon/O companions/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O company/O included/O more/O swords/O than/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O have/O liked/O ./O 
Three/O by/O the/O fire/O wore/O the/O red/O stallion/O badge/O of/O the/O Brackens/PERSON ,/O and/O there/O was/O a/O large/O party/O in/O blue/O steel/O ringmail/O and/O capes/O of/O a/O silvery/O grey/O ./O 
On/O their/O shoulder/O was/O another/O familiar/O sigil/O ,/O the/O twin/O towers/O of/O House/O Frey/PERSON ./O 
She/O studied/O their/O faces/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O all/O too/O young/O to/O have/O known/O her/O ./O 
The/O senior/O among/O them/O would/O have/O been/O no/O older/O than/O Bran/O when/O she/O went/O north/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON found/O them/O an/O empty/O place/O on/O the/O bench/O near/O the/O kitchen/O ./O 
Across/O the/O table/O a/O handsome/O youth/O was/O fingering/O a/O woodharp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Seven/O blessings/O to/O you/O ,/O goodfolk/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O they/O sat/O ./O 
An/O empty/O wine/O cup/O stood/O on/O the/O table/O before/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O to/O you/O ,/O singer/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON returned/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON called/O for/O bread/O and/O meat/O and/O beer/O in/O a/O tone/O that/O meant/O now/O ./O 
The/O singer/O ,/O a/O youth/O of/O some/O eighteen/O years/O ,/O eyed/O them/O boldly/O and/O asked/O where/O they/O were/O going/O ,/O and/O from/O whence/O they/O had/O come/O ,/O and/O what/O news/O they/O had/O ,/O letting/O the/O questions/O fly/O as/O quick/O as/O arrows/O and/O never/O pausing/O for/O an/O answer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O left/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O a/O fortnight/O ago/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ,/O answering/O the/O safest/O of/O his/O questions/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O where/O I/O 'm/O bound/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O youth/O said/O ./O 
As/O she/O had/O suspected/O ,/O he/O was/O more/O interested/O in/O telling/O his/O own/O story/O than/O in/O hearing/O theirs/O ./O 
Singers/O loved/O nothing/O half/O so/O well/O as/O the/O sound/O of/O their/O own/O voices/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Hand/O 's/O tourney/O means/O rich/O lords/O with/O fat/O purses/O ./O 
The/O last/O time/O I/O came/O away/O with/O more/O silver/O than/O I/O could/O carry/O .../O or/O would/O have/O ,/O if/O I/O had/O n't/O lost/O it/O all/O betting/O on/O the/O Kingslayer/O to/O win/O the/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O gods/O frown/O on/O the/O gambler/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O sternly/O ./O 
He/O was/O of/O the/O north/O ,/O and/O shared/O the/O Stark/O views/O on/O tournaments/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O frowned/O on/O me/O ,/O for/O certain/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O singer/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O cruel/O gods/O and/O the/O Knight/O of/O Flowers/O altogether/O did/O me/O in/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O doubt/O that/O was/O a/O lesson/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O ./O 
This/O time/O my/O coin/O will/O champion/O Ser/PERSON Loras/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tried/O to/O tug/O at/O whiskers/O that/O were/O not/O there/O ,/O but/O before/O he/O could/O frame/O a/O rebuke/O the/O serving/O boy/O came/O scurrying/O up/O ./O 
He/O laid/O trenchers/O of/O bread/O before/O them/O and/O filled/O them/O with/O chunks/O of/O browned/O meat/O off/O a/O skewer/O ,/O dripping/O with/O hot/O juice/O ./O 
Another/O skewer/O held/O tiny/O onions/O ,/O fire/O peppers/O ,/O and/O fat/O mushrooms/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON set/O to/O lustily/O as/O the/O lad/O ran/O back/O to/O fetch/O them/O beer/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O name/O is/O Marillion/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O singer/O said/O ,/O plucking/O a/O string/O on/O his/O woodharp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Doubtless/O you/O 've/O heard/O me/O play/O somewhere/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O manner/O made/O Catelyn/O smile/O ./O 
Few/O wandering/O singers/O ever/O ventured/O as/O far/O north/O as/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O but/O she/O knew/O his/O like/O from/O her/O girlhood/O in/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O not/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O drew/O a/O plaintive/O chord/O from/O the/O woodharp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O is/O your/O loss/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O was/O the/O finest/O singer/O you/O 've/O ever/O heard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Alia/PERSON of/O Braavos/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON answered/O at/O once/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O 'm/O much/O better/O than/O that/O old/O stick/O ,/O \/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O you/O have/O the/O silver/O for/O a/O song/O ,/O I/O 'll/O gladly/O show/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O might/O have/O a/O copper/O or/O two/O ,/O but/O I/O 'd/O sooner/O toss/O it/O down/O a/O well/O than/O pay/O for/O your/O howling/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON groused/O ./O 
His/O opinion/O of/O singers/O was/O well/O known/O ;/O music/O was/O a/O lovely/O thing/O for/O girls/O ,/O but/O he/O could/O not/O comprehend/O why/O any/O healthy/O boy/O would/O fill/O his/O hand/O with/O a/O harp/O when/O he/O might/O have/O had/O a/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O grandfather/O has/O a/O sour/O nature/O ,/O \/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON said/O to/O Catelyn/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O meant/O to/O do/O you/O honor/O ./O 
An/O homage/O to/O your/O beauty/O ./O 
In/O truth/O ,/O I/O was/O made/O to/O sing/O for/O kings/O and/O high/O lords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O I/O can/O see/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Tully/PERSON is/O fond/O of/O song/O ,/O I/O hear/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O you/O 've/O been/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O hundred/O times/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O singer/O said/O airily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O keep/O a/O chamber/O for/O me/O ,/O and/O the/O young/O lord/O is/O like/O a/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON smiled/O ,/O wondering/O what/O Edmure/PERSON would/O think/O of/O that/O ./O 
Another/O singer/O had/O once/O bedded/O a/O girl/O her/O brother/O fancied/O ;/O he/O had/O hated/O the/O breed/O ever/O since/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O Winterfell/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Have/O you/O traveled/O north/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O I/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Marillion/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O all/O blizzards/O and/O bearskins/O up/O there/O ,/O and/O the/O Starks/PERSON know/O no/O music/O but/O the/O howling/O of/O wolves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Distantly/O ,/O she/O was/O aware/O of/O the/O door/O banging/O open/O at/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Innkeep/O ,/O \/O ''/O a/O servant/O 's/O voice/O called/O out/O behind/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O have/O horses/O that/O want/O stabling/O ,/O and/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O requires/O a/O room/O and/O a/O hot/O bath/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O gods/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O before/O Catelyn/PERSON reached/O out/O to/O silence/O him/O ,/O her/O fingers/O tightening/O hard/O around/O his/O forearm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON was/O bowing/O and/O smiling/O her/O hideous/O red/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O sorry/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O truly/O ,/O we/O 're/O full/O up/O ,/O every/O room/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O were/O four/O of/O them/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O ./O 
An/O old/O man/O in/O the/O black/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O two/O servants/O .../O and/O him/O ,/O standing/O there/O small/O and/O bold/O as/O life/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O men/O will/O steep/O in/O your/O stable/O ,/O and/O as/O for/O myself/O ,/O well/O ,/O I/O do/O not/O require/O a/O large/O room/O ,/O as/O you/O can/O plainly/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O flashed/O a/O mocking/O grin/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O long/O as/O the/O fire/O 's/O warm/O and/O the/O straw/O reasonably/O free/O of/O fleas/O ,/O I/O am/O a/O happy/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON was/O beside/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O M'lord/O ,/O there/O 's/O nothing/O ,/O it/O 's/O the/O tourney/O ,/O there/O 's/O no/O help/O for/O it/O ,/O oh/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O pulled/O a/O coin/O from/O his/O purse/O and/O flicked/O it/O up/O over/O his/O head/O ,/O caught/O it/O ,/O tossed/O it/O again/O ./O 
Even/O across/O the/O room/O ,/O where/O Catelyn/PERSON sat/O ,/O the/O wink/O of/O gold/O was/O unmistakable/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O freerider/O in/O a/O faded/O blue/O cloak/O lurched/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O welcome/O to/O my/O room/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O there/O 's/O a/O clever/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON said/O as/O he/O sent/O the/O coin/O spinning/O across/O the/O room/O ./O 
The/O freerider/O snatched/O it/O from/O the/O air/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O a/O nimble/O one/O to/O boot/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O dwarf/O turned/O back/O to/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O will/O be/O able/O to/O manage/O food/O ,/O I/O trust/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Anything/O you/O like/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O anything/O at/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O innkeep/O promised/O ./O 
And/O may/O he/O choke/O on/O it/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON thought/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O Bran/O she/O saw/O choking/O ,/O drowning/O on/O his/O own/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lannister/O glanced/O at/O the/O nearest/O tables/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O men/O will/O have/O whatever/O you/O 're/O serving/O these/O people/O ./O 
Double/O portions/O ,/O we/O 've/O had/O a/O long/O hard/O ride/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O take/O a/O roast/O fowl-chicken/O ,/O duck/O ,/O pigeon/O ,/O it/O makes/O no/O matter/O ./O 
And/O send/O up/O a/O flagon/O of/O your/O best/O wine/O ./O 
Yoren/PERSON ,/O will/O you/O sup/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Aye/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O I/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O black/O brother/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O had/O not/O so/O much/O as/O glanced/O toward/O the/O far/O end/O of/O the/O room/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O thinking/O how/O grateful/O she/O was/O for/O the/O crowded/O benches/O between/O them/O when/O suddenly/O Marillion/PERSON bounded/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O would/O be/O pleased/O to/O entertain/O you/O while/O you/O eat/O ./O 
Let/O me/O sing/O you/O the/O lay/O of/O your/O father/O 's/O great/O victory/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O would/O be/O more/O likely/O to/O ruin/O my/O supper/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O said/O dryly/O ./O 
His/O mismatched/O eyes/O considered/O the/O singer/O briefly/O ,/O started/O to/O move/O away/O .../O and/O found/O Catelyn/PERSON ./O 
He/O looked/O at/O her/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O puzzled/O ./O 
She/O turned/O her/O face/O away/O ,/O but/O too/O late/O ./O 
The/O dwarf/O was/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O what/O an/O unexpected/O pleasure/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O sorry/O to/O miss/O you/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Marillion/O gaped/O at/O her/O ,/O confusion/O giving/O way/O to/O chagrin/O as/O Catelyn/PERSON rose/O slowly/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
She/O heard/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON curse/O ./O 
If/O only/O the/O man/O had/O lingered/O at/O the/O Wall/O ,/O she/O thought/O ,/O if/O only/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O .../O Stark/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Masha/PERSON Heddle/PERSON said/O thickly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O was/O still/O Catelyn/O Tully/O the/O last/O time/O I/O bedded/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O the/O innkeep/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O the/O muttering/O ,/O feel/O the/O eyes/O upon/O her/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON glanced/O around/O the/O room/O ,/O at/O the/O faces/O of/O the/O knights/O and/O sworn/O swords/O ,/O and/O took/O a/O deep/O breath/O to/O slow/O the/O frantic/O beating/O of/O her/O heart/O ./O 
Did/O she/O dare/O take/O the/O risk/O ?/O 
There/O was/O no/O time/O to/O think/O it/O through/O ,/O only/O the/O moment/O and/O the/O sound/O of/O her/O own/O voice/O ringing/O in/O her/O ears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O in/O the/O corner/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O to/O an/O older/O man/O she/O had/O not/O noticed/O until/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O that/O the/O black/O bat/O of/O Harrenhal/O I/O see/O embroidered/O on/O your/O surcoat/O ,/O ser/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O man/O got/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O is/O Lady/O Whent/O a/O true/O and/O honest/O friend/O to/O my/O father/O ,/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON of/O Riverrun/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O replied/O stoutly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Rodrik/PERSON rose/O quietly/O and/O loosened/O his/O sword/O in/O its/O scabbard/O ./O 
The/O dwarf/O was/O blinking/O at/O them/O ,/O blank/O -/O faced/O ,/O with/O puzzlement/O in/O his/O mismatched/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O red/O stallion/O was/O ever/O a/O welcome/O sight/O in/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O to/O the/O trio/O by/O the/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O counts/O Jonos/PERSON Bracken/PERSON among/O his/O oldest/O and/O most/O loyal/O bannermen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O three/O men-at-arms/O exchanged/O uncertain/O looks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Our/O lord/O is/O honored/O by/O his/O trust/O ,/O \/O ''/O one/O of/O them/O said/O hesitantly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O envy/O your/O father/O all/O these/O fine/O friends/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON quipped/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O do/O not/O quite/O see/O the/O purpose/O of/O this/O ,/O Lady/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O ignored/O him/O ,/O turning/O to/O the/O large/O party/O in/O blue/O and/O grey/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O heart/O of/O the/O matter/O ;/O there/O were/O more/O than/O twenty/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O your/O sigil/O as/O well/O :/O the/O twin/O towers/O of/O Frey/PERSON ./O 
How/O fares/O your/O good/O lord/O ,/O sers/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Their/O captain/O rose/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Walder/PERSON is/O well/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
He/O plans/O to/O take/O a/O new/O wife/O on/O his/O ninetieth/O name/O day/O ,/O and/O has/O asked/O your/O lord/O father/O to/O honor/O the/O wedding/O with/O his/O presence/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O sniggered/O ./O 
That/O was/O when/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O he/O was/O hers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O man/O came/O a/O guest/O into/O my/O house/O ,/O and/O there/O conspired/O to/O murder/O my/O son/O ,/O a/O boy/O of/O seven/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O proclaimed/O to/O the/O room/O at/O large/O ,/O pointing/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON moved/O to/O her/O side/O ,/O his/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O the/O name/O of/O King/O Robert/PERSON and/O the/O good/O lords/O you/O serve/O ,/O I/O call/O upon/O you/O to/O seize/O him/O and/O help/O me/O return/O him/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON to/O await/O the/O king/O 's/O justice/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O did/O not/O know/O what/O was/O more/O satisfying/O :/O the/O sound/O of/O a/O dozen/O swords/O drawn/O as/O one/O or/O the/O look/O on/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
