-LSB-/O ``/O BRAN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O In/O the/O yard/O below/O ,/O Rickon/PERSON ran/O with/O the/O wolves/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O watched/O from/O his/O window/O seat/O ./O 
Wherever/O the/O boy/O went/O ,/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON was/O there/O first/O ,/O loping/O ahead/O to/O cut/O him/O off/O ,/O until/O Rickon/PERSON saw/O him/O ,/O screamed/O in/O delight/O ,/O and/O went/O pelting/O off/O in/O another/O direction/O ./O 
Shaggydog/PERSON ran/O at/O his/O heels/O ,/O spinning/O and/O snapping/O if/O the/O other/O wolves/O came/O too/O close/O ./O 
His/O fur/O had/O darkened/O until/O he/O was/O all/O black/O ,/O and/O his/O eyes/O were/O green/O fire/O ./O 
Bran/O 's/O Summer/O came/O last/O ./O 
He/O was/O silver/O and/O smoke/O ,/O with/O eyes/O of/O yellow/O gold/O that/O saw/O all/O there/O was/O to/O see/O ./O 
Smaller/O than/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON ,/O and/O more/O wary/O ./O 
Bran/O thought/O he/O was/O the/O smartest/O of/O the/O litter/O ./O 
He/O could/O hear/O his/O brother/O 's/O breathless/O laughter/O as/O Rickon/PERSON dashed/O across/O the/O hardpacked/O earth/O on/O little/O baby/O legs/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O His/O eyes/O stung/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O be/O down/O there/O ,/O laughing/O and/O running/O ./O 
Angry/O at/O the/O thought/O ,/O Bran/O knuckled/O away/O the/O tears/O before/O they/O could/O fall/O ./O 
His/O eighth/O name/O day/O had/O come/O and/O gone/O ./O 
He/O was/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O now/O ,/O too/O old/O to/O cry/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O was/O just/O a/O lie/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O bitterly/O ,/O remembering/O the/O crow/O from/O his/O dream/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O fly/O ./O 
I/O ca/O n't/O even/O run/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Crows/O are/O all/O liars/O ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON agreed/O ,/O from/O the/O chair/O where/O she/O sat/O doing/O her/O needlework/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O a/O story/O about/O a/O crow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O any/O more/O stories/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O snapped/O ,/O his/O voice/O petulant/O ./O 
He/O had/O liked/O Old/O Nan/PERSON and/O her/O stories/O once/O ./O 
Before/O ./O 
But/O it/O was/O different/O now/O ./O 
They/O left/O her/O with/O him/O all/O day/O now/O ,/O to/O watch/O over/O him/O and/O clean/O him/O and/O keep/O him/O from/O being/O lonely/O ,/O but/O she/O just/O made/O it/O worse/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O your/O stupid/O stories/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O old/O woman/O smiled/O at/O him/O toothlessly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O stories/O ?/O 
No/O ,/O my/O little/O lord/O ,/O not/O mine/O ./O 
The/O stories/O are/O ,/O before/O me/O and/O after/O me/O ,/O before/O you/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O was/O a/O very/O ugly/O old/O woman/O ,/O Bran/O thought/O spitefully/O ;/O shrunken/O and/O wrinkled/O ,/O almost/O blind/O ,/O too/O weak/O to/O climb/O stairs/O ,/O with/O only/O a/O few/O wisps/O of/O white/O hair/O left/O to/O cover/O a/O mottled/O pink/O scalp/O ./O 
No/O one/O really/O knew/O how/O old/O she/O was/O ,/O but/O his/O father/O said/O she/O 'd/O been/O called/O Old/O Nan/PERSON even/O when/O he/O was/O a/O boy/O ./O 
She/O was/O the/O oldest/O person/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION for/O certain/O ,/O maybe/O the/O oldest/O person/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
Nan/PERSON had/O come/O to/O the/O castle/O as/O a/O wet/O nurse/O for/O a/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON whose/O mother/O had/O died/O birthing/O him/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O an/O older/O brother/O of/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON ,/O Bran/O 's/O grandfather/O ,/O or/O perhaps/O a/O younger/O brother/O ,/O or/O a/O brother/O to/O Lord/O Rickard/PERSON 's/O father/O ./O 
Sometimes/O Old/O Nan/PERSON told/O it/O one/O way/O and/O sometimes/O another/O ./O 
In/O all/O the/O stories/O the/O little/O boy/O died/O at/O three/O of/O a/O summer/O chill/O ,/O but/O Old/O Nan/PERSON stayed/O on/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O her/O own/O children/O ./O 
She/O had/O lost/O both/O her/O sons/O to/O the/O war/O when/O King/O Robert/PERSON won/O the/O throne/O ,/O and/O her/O grandson/O was/O killed/O on/O the/O walls/O of/O Pyke/PERSON during/O Balon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON 's/O rebellion/O ./O 
Her/O daughters/O had/O long/O ago/O married/O and/O moved/O away/O and/O died/O ./O 
All/O that/O was/O left/O of/O her/O own/O blood/O was/O Hodor/PERSON ,/O the/O simpleminded/O giant/O who/O worked/O in/O the/O stables/O ,/O but/O Old/O Nan/PERSON just/O lived/O on/O and/O on/O ,/O doing/O her/O needlework/O and/O telling/O her/O stories/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O care/O whose/O stories/O they/O are/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O told/O her/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O hate/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O did/O n't/O want/O stories/O and/O he/O did/O n't/O want/O Old/O Nan/PERSON ./O 
He/O wanted/O his/O mother/O and/O father/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O go/O running/O with/O Summer/O loping/O beside/O him/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O climb/O the/O broken/O tower/O and/O feed/O corn/O to/O the/O crows/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O ride/O his/O pony/O again/O with/O his/O brothers/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O it/O to/O be/O the/O way/O it/O had/O been/O before/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O a/O story/O about/O a/O boy/O who/O hated/O stories/O ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O with/O her/O stupid/O little/O smile/O ,/O her/O needles/O moving/O all/O the/O while/O ,/O click/O click/O click/O ,/O until/O Bran/O was/O ready/O to/O scream/O at/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O would/O never/O be/O the/O way/O it/O had/O been/O ,/O he/O knew/O ./O 
The/O crow/O had/O tricked/O him/O into/O flying/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O woke/O up/O he/O was/O broken/O and/O the/O world/O was/O changed/O ./O 
They/O had/O all/O left/O him/O ,/O his/O father/O and/O his/O mother/O and/O his/O sisters/O and/O even/O his/O bastard/O brother/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
His/O father/O had/O promised/O he/O would/O ride/O a/O real/O horse/O to/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O but/O they/O 'd/O gone/O without/O him/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON had/O sent/O a/O bird/O after/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON with/O a/O message/O ,/O and/O another/O to/O Mother/O and/O a/O third/O to/O Jon/PERSON on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O but/O there/O had/O been/O no/O answers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ofttimes/O the/O birds/O are/O lost/O ,/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O had/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O many/O a/O mile/O and/O many/O a/O hawk/O between/O here/O and/O King/LOCATION 's/LOCATION Landing/LOCATION ,/O the/O message/O may/O not/O have/O reached/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Yet/O to/O Bran/O it/O felt/O as/O if/O they/O had/O all/O died/O while/O he/O had/O slept/O .../O or/O perhaps/O Bran/O had/O died/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O forgotten/O him/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON and/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON had/O gone/O too/O ,/O and/O Hullen/PERSON and/O Harwin/PERSON and/O Fat/O Tom/PERSON and/O a/O quarter/O of/O the/O guard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Only/O Robb/PERSON and/O baby/O Rickon/O were/O still/O here/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON was/O changed/O ./O 
He/O was/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O now/O ,/O or/O trying/O to/O be/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O real/O sword/O and/O never/O smiled/O ./O 
His/O days/O were/O spent/O drilling/O the/O guard/O and/O practicing/O his/O swordplay/O ,/O making/O the/O yard/O ring/O with/O the/O sound/O of/O steel/O as/O Bran/O watched/O forlornly/O from/O his/O window/O ./O 
At/O night/O he/O closeted/O himself/O with/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O talking/O or/O going/O over/O account/O books/O ./O 
Sometimes/O he/O would/O ride/O out/O with/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON and/O be/O gone/O for/O days/O at/O a/O time/O ,/O visiting/O distant/O holdfasts/O ./O 
Whenever/O he/O was/O away/O more/O than/O a/O day/O ,/O Rickon/PERSON would/O cry/O and/O ask/O Bran/O if/O Robb/PERSON was/O ever/O coming/O back/O ./O 
Even/O when/O he/O was/O home/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O seemed/O to/O have/O more/O time/O for/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON and/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON than/O he/O ever/O did/O for/O his/O brothers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O could/O tell/O you/O the/O story/O about/O Brandon/PERSON the/PERSON Builder/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O was/O always/O your/O favorite/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Thousands/O and/O thousands/O of/O years/O ago/O ,/O Brandon/PERSON the/PERSON Builder/PERSON had/O raised/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O and/O some/O said/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Bran/O knew/O the/O story/O ,/O but/O it/O had/O never/O been/O his/O favorite/O ./O 
Maybe/O one/O of/O the/O other/O Brandons/PERSON had/O liked/O that/O story/O ./O 
Sometimes/O Nan/PERSON would/O talk/O to/O him/O as/O if/O he/O were/O her/O Brandon/PERSON ,/O the/O baby/O she/O had/O nursed/O all/O those/O years/O ago/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O she/O confused/O him/O with/O his/O uncle/O Brandon/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O killed/O by/O the/O Mad/O King/O before/O Bran/O was/O even/O born/O ./O 
She/O had/O lived/O so/O long/O ,/O Mother/PERSON had/O told/O him/O once/O ,/O that/O all/O the/O Brandon/PERSON Starks/PERSON had/O become/O one/O person/O in/O her/O head/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O not/O my/O favorite/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O favorites/O were/O the/O scary/O ones/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O heard/O some/O sort/O of/O commotion/O outside/O and/O turned/O back/O to/O the/O window/O ./O 
Rickon/PERSON was/O running/O across/O the/O yard/O toward/O the/O gatehouse/O ,/O the/O wolves/O following/O him/O ,/O but/O the/O tower/O faced/O the/O wrong/O way/O for/O Bran/O to/O see/O what/O was/O happening/O ./O 
He/O smashed/O a/O fist/O on/O his/O thigh/O in/O frustration/O and/O felt/O nothing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O my/O sweet/O summer/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O quietly/O ,/O \/O ``/O what/O do/O you/O know/O of/O fear/O ?/O 
Fear/O is/O for/O the/O winter/O ,/O my/O little/O lord/O ,/O when/O the/O snows/O fall/O a/O hundred/O feet/O deep/O and/O the/O ice/O wind/O comes/O howling/O out/O of/O the/O north/O ./O 
Fear/O is/O for/O the/O long/O night/O ,/O when/O the/O sun/O hides/O its/O face/O for/O years/O at/O a/O time/O ,/O and/O little/O children/O are/O born/O and/O live/O and/O die/O all/O in/O darkness/O while/O the/O direwolves/O grow/O gaunt/O and/O hungry/O ,/O and/O the/O white/O walkers/O move/O through/O the/O woods/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O mean/O the/O Others/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O querulously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Others/O ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Thousands/O and/O thousands/O of/O years/O ago/O ,/O a/O winter/O fell/O that/O was/O cold/O and/O hard/O and/O endless/O beyond/O all/O memory/O of/O man/O ./O 
There/O came/O a/O night/O that/O lasted/O a/O generation/O ,/O and/O kings/O shivered/O and/O died/O in/O their/O castles/O even/O as/O the/O swineherds/O in/O their/O hovels/O ./O 
Women/O smothered/O their/O children/O rather/O than/O see/O them/O starve/O ,/O and/O cried/O ,/O and/O felt/O their/O tears/O freeze/O on/O their/O cheeks/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O voice/O and/O her/O needles/O fell/O silent/O ,/O and/O she/O glanced/O up/O at/O Bran/O with/O pale/O ,/O filmy/O eyes/O and/O asked/O ,/O \/O ``/O So/O ,/O child/O ./O 
This/O is/O the/O sort/O of/O story/O you/O like/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O reluctantly/O ,/O \/O ``/O yes/O ,/O only/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O Old/O Nan/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O In/O that/O darkness/O ,/O the/O Others/O came/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O as/O her/O needles/O went/O click/O click/O click/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O were/O cold/O things/O ,/O dead/O things/O ,/O that/O hated/O iron/O and/O fire/O and/O the/O touch/O of/O the/O sun/O ,/O and/O every/O creature/O with/O hot/O blood/O in/O its/O veins/O ./O 
They/O swept/O over/O holdfasts/O and/O cities/O and/O kingdoms/O ,/O felled/O heroes/O and/O armies/O by/O the/O score/O ,/O riding/O their/O pale/O dead/O horses/O and/O leading/O hosts/O of/O the/O slain/O ./O 
All/O the/O swords/O of/O men/O could/O not/O stay/O their/O advance/O ,/O and/O even/O maidens/O and/O suckling/O babes/O found/O no/O pity/O in/O them/O ./O 
They/O hunted/O the/O maids/O through/O frozen/O forests/O ,/O and/O fed/O their/O dead/O servants/O on/O the/O flesh/O of/O human/O children/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O voice/O had/O dropped/O very/O low/O ,/O almost/O to/O a/O whisper/O ,/O and/O Bran/O found/O himself/O leaning/O forward/O to/O listen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O these/O were/O the/O days/O before/O the/O Andals/O came/O ,/O and/O long/O before/O the/O women/O fled/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O from/O the/O cities/O of/O the/O Rhoyne/O ,/O and/O the/O hundred/O kingdoms/O of/O those/O times/O were/O the/O kingdoms/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O ,/O who/O had/O taken/O these/O lands/O from/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O ./O 
Yet/O here/O and/O there/O in/O the/O fastness/O of/O the/O woods/O the/O children/O still/O lived/O in/O their/O wooden/O cities/O and/O hollow/O hills/O ,/O and/O the/O faces/O in/O the/O trees/O kept/O watch/O ./O 
So/O as/O cold/O and/O death/O filled/O the/O earth/O ,/O the/O last/O hero/O determined/O to/O seek/O out/O the/O children/O ,/O in/O the/O hopes/O that/O their/O ancient/O magics/O could/O win/O back/O what/O the/O armies/O of/O men/O had/O lost/O ./O 
He/O set/O out/O into/O the/O dead/O lands/O with/O a/O sword/O ,/O a/O horse/O ,/O a/O dog/O ,/O and/O a/O dozen/O companions/O ./O 
For/O years/O he/O searched/O ,/O until/O he/O despaired/O of/O ever/O finding/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O in/O their/O secret/O cities/O ./O 
One/O by/O one/O his/O friends/O died/O ,/O and/O his/O horse/O ,/O and/O finally/O even/O his/O dog/O ,/O and/O his/O sword/O froze/O so/O hard/O the/O blade/O snapped/O when/O he/O tried/O to/O use/O it/O ./O 
And/O the/O Others/O smelled/O the/O hot/O blood/O in/O him/O ,/O and/O came/O silent/O on/O his/O trail/O ,/O stalking/O him/O with/O packs/O of/O pale/O white/O spiders/O big/O as/O hounds/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O door/O opened/O with/O a/O bang/O ,/O and/O Bran/O 's/O heart/O leapt/O up/O into/O his/O mouth/O in/O sudden/O fear/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O only/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O with/O Hodor/PERSON looming/O in/O the/O stairway/O behind/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O stableboy/O announced/O ,/O as/O was/O his/O custom/O ,/O smiling/O hugely/O at/O them/O all/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON was/O not/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O visitors/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O your/O presence/O is/O required/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O listening/O to/O a/O story/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O complained/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stories/O wait/O ,/O my/O little/O lord/O ,/O and/O when/O you/O come/O back/O to/O them/O ,/O why/O ,/O there/O they/O are/O ,/O \/O ''/O Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Visitors/O are/O not/O so/O patient/O ,/O and/O ofttimes/O they/O bring/O stories/O of/O their/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O asked/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ,/O and/O some/O men/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O with/O word/O from/O your/O brother/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
Robb/PERSON is/O meeting/O with/O them/O now/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON ,/O will/O you/O help/O Bran/O down/O to/O the/O hall/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Hodor/PERSON agreed/O happily/O ./O 
He/O ducked/O to/O get/O his/O great/O shaggy/O head/O under/O the/O door/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON was/O nearly/O seven/O feet/O tall/O ./O 
It/O was/O hard/O to/O believe/O that/O he/O was/O the/O same/O blood/O as/O Old/O Nan/PERSON ./O 
Bran/O wondered/O if/O he/O would/O shrivel/O up/O as/O small/O as/O his/O great-grandmother/O when/O he/O was/O old/O ./O 
It/O did/O not/O seem/O likely/O ,/O even/O if/O Hodor/PERSON lived/O to/O be/O a/O thousand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hodor/PERSON lifted/O Bran/O as/O easy/O as/O if/O he/O were/O a/O bale/O of/O hay/O ,/O and/O cradled/O him/O against/O his/O massive/O chest/O ./O 
He/O always/O smelled/O faintly/O of/O horses/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O not/O a/O bad/O smell/O ./O 
His/O arms/O were/O thick/O with/O muscle/O and/O matted/O with/O brown/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O again/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON had/O once/O commented/O that/O Hodor/PERSON did/O not/O know/O much/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O could/O doubt/O that/O he/O knew/O his/O name/O ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON had/O cackled/O like/O a/O hen/O when/O Bran/PERSON told/O her/O that/O ,/O and/O confessed/O that/O Hodor/PERSON 's/O real/O name/O was/O Walder/PERSON ./O 
No/O one/O knew/O where/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O \/O ''/O had/O come/O from/O ,/O she/O said/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O started/O saying/O it/O ,/O they/O started/O calling/O him/O by/O it/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O only/O word/O he/O had/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O left/O Old/O Nan/PERSON in/O the/O tower/O room/O with/O her/O needles/O and/O her/O memories/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON hummed/O tunelessly/O as/O he/O carried/O Bran/O down/O the/O steps/O and/O through/O the/O gallery/O ,/O with/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON following/O behind/O ,/O hurrying/O to/O keep/O up/O with/O the/O stableboy/O 's/O long/O strides/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON was/O seated/O in/O Father/O 's/O high/O seat/O ,/O wearing/O ringmail/O and/O boiled/O leather/O and/O the/O stern/O face/O of/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON and/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON stood/O behind/O him/O ./O 
A/O dozen/O guardsmen/O lined/O the/O grey/O stone/O walls/O beneath/O tall/O narrow/O windows/O ./O 
In/O the/O center/O of/O the/O room/O the/O dwarf/O stood/O with/O his/O servants/O ,/O and/O four/O strangers/O in/O the/O black/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O sense/O the/O anger/O in/O the/O hall/O the/O moment/O that/O Hodor/PERSON carried/O him/O through/O the/O doors/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Any/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O welcome/O here/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION for/O as/O long/O as/O he/O wishes/O to/O stay/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON was/O saying/O with/O the/O voice/O of/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ./O 
His/O sword/O was/O across/O his/O knees/O ,/O the/O steel/O bare/O for/O all/O the/O world/O to/O see/O ./O 
Even/O Bran/O knew/O what/O it/O meant/O to/O greet/O a/O guest/O with/O an/O unsheathed/O sword/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Any/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O repeated/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O not/O me/O ,/O do/O I/O take/O your/O meaning/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON stood/O and/O pointed/O at/O the/O little/O man/O with/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O lord/O here/O while/O my/O mother/O and/O father/O are/O away/O ,/O Lannister/PERSON ./O 
I/O am/O not/O your/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O are/O a/O lord/O ,/O you/O might/O learn/O a/O lord/O 's/O courtesy/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O little/O man/O replied/O ,/O ignoring/O the/O sword/O point/O in/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O bastard/O brother/O has/O all/O your/O father/O 's/O graces/O ,/O it/O would/O seem/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O gasped/O out/O from/O Hodor/LOCATION 's/O arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O turned/O to/O look/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O it/O is/O true/O ,/O the/O boy/O lives/O ./O 
I/O could/O scarce/O believe/O it/O ./O 
You/O Starks/PERSON are/O hard/O to/O kill/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O Lannisters/O had/O best/O remember/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ,/O lowering/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O bring/O my/O brother/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Hodor/PERSON said/O ,/O and/O he/O trotted/O forward/O smiling/O and/O set/O Bran/O in/O the/O high/O seat/O of/O the/O Starks/PERSON ,/O where/O the/O Lords/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION had/O sat/O since/O the/O days/O when/O they/O called/O themselves/O the/O Kings/ORGANIZATION in/O the/O North/O ./O 
The/O seat/O was/O cold/O stone/O ,/O polished/O smooth/O by/O countless/O bottoms/O ;/O the/O carved/O heads/O of/O direwolves/O snarled/O on/O the/O ends/O of/O its/O massive/O arms/O ./O 
Bran/O clasped/O them/O as/O he/O sat/O ,/O his/O useless/O legs/O dangling/O ./O 
The/O great/O seat/O made/O him/O feel/O half/O a/O baby/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON put/O a/O hand/O on/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O said/O you/O had/O business/O with/O Bran/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O here/O he/O is/O ,/O Lannister/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O was/O uncomfortably/O aware/O of/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O eyes/O ./O 
One/O was/O black/O and/O one/O was/O green/O ,/O and/O both/O were/O looking/O at/O him/O ,/O studying/O him/O ,/O weighing/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O told/O you/O were/O quite/O the/O climber/O ,/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O little/O man/O said/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O how/O is/O it/O you/O happened/O to/O fall/O that/O day/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O never/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O insisted/O ./O 
He/O never/O fell/O ,/O never/O never/O never/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O child/O does/O not/O remember/O anything/O of/O the/O fall/O ,/O or/O the/O climb/O that/O came/O before/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON gently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Curious/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O brother/O is/O not/O here/O to/O answer/O questions/O ,/O Lannister/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O curtly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O your/O business/O and/O be/O on/O your/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O a/O gift/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O said/O to/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O like/O to/O ride/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/O Luwin/O came/O forward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O the/O child/O has/O lost/O the/O use/O of/O his/O legs/O ./O 
He/O can/O not/O sit/O a/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nonsense/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Lannister/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O the/O right/O horse/O and/O the/O right/O saddle/O ,/O even/O a/O cripple/O can/O ride/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O word/O was/O a/O knife/O through/O Bran/O 's/O heart/O ./O 
He/O felt/O tears/O come/O unbidden/O to/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O a/O cripple/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O I/O am/O not/O a/O dwarf/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O said/O with/O a/O twist/O of/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O will/O rejoice/O to/O hear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Greyjoy/PERSON laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O sort/O of/O horse/O and/O saddle/O are/O you/O suggesting/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O smart/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O can/O not/O use/O his/O legs/O to/O command/O the/O animal/O ,/O so/O you/O must/O shape/O the/O horse/O to/O the/O rider/O ,/O teach/O it/O to/O respond/O to/O the/O reins/O ,/O to/O the/O voice/O ./O 
I/O would/O begin/O with/O an/O unbroken/O yearling/O ,/O with/O no/O old/O training/O to/O be/O unlearned/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O a/O rolled/O paper/O from/O his/O belt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O this/O to/O your/O saddler/O ./O 
He/O will/O provide/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON took/O the/O paper/O from/O the/O dwarfs/O hand/O ,/O curious/O as/O a/O small/O grey/O squirrel/O ./O 
He/O unrolled/O it/O ,/O studied/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O ./O 
You/O draw/O nicely/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O this/O ought/O to/O work/O ./O 
I/O should/O have/O thought/O of/O this/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O came/O easier/O to/O me/O ,/O Maester/O ./O 
It/O is/O not/O terribly/O unlike/O my/O own/O saddles/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O I/O truly/O be/O able/O to/O ride/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O asked/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O believe/O them/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O afraid/O ./O 
Perhaps/O it/O was/O just/O another/O lie/O ./O 
The/O crow/O had/O promised/O him/O that/O he/O could/O fly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O dwarf/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O I/O swear/O to/O you/O ,/O boy/O ,/O on/O horseback/O you/O will/O be/O as/O tall/O as/O any/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON seemed/O puzzled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O this/O some/O trap/O ,/O Lannister/O ?/O 
What/O 's/O Bran/O to/O you/O ?/O 
Why/O should/O you/O want/O to/O help/O him/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O Jon/PERSON asked/O it/O of/O me/O ./O 
And/O I/O have/O a/O tender/O spot/O in/O my/O heart/O for/O cripples/O and/O bastards/O and/O broken/O things/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON placed/O a/O hand/O over/O his/O heart/O and/O grinned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O door/O to/O the/O yard/O flew/O open/O ./O 
Sunlight/O came/O streaming/O across/O the/O hall/O as/O Rickon/PERSON burst/O in/O ,/O breathless/O ./O 
The/O direwolves/O were/O with/O him/O ./O 
The/O boy/O stopped/O by/O the/O door/O ,/O wide-eyed/O ,/O but/O the/O wolves/O came/O on/O ./O 
Their/O eyes/O found/O Lannister/PERSON ,/O or/O perhaps/O they/O caught/O his/O scent/O ./O 
Summer/O began/O to/O ''/O ,/O ``/O growl/O first/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON picked/O it/O up/O ./O 
They/O padded/O toward/O the/O little/O man/O ,/O one/O from/O the/O right/O and/O one/O from/O the/O left/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O wolves/O do/O not/O like/O your/O smell/O ,/O Lannister/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON Greyioy/PERSON commented/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O it/O 's/O time/O I/O took/O my/O leave/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O took/O a/O step/O backward/O .../O and/O Shaggydog/PERSON came/O out/O of/O the/O shadows/O behind/O him/O ,/O snarling/O ./O 
Lannister/O recoiled/O ,/O and/O Summer/O lunged/O at/O him/O from/O the/O other/O side/O ./O 
He/O reeled/O away/O ,/O unsteady/O on/O his/O feet/O ,/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON snapped/O at/O his/O arm/O ,/O teeth/O ripping/O at/O his/O sleeve/O and/O tearing/O loose/O a/O scrap/O of/O cloth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O shouted/O from/O the/O high/O seat/O as/O Lannister/PERSON 's/O men/O reached/O for/O their/O steel/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Summer/O ,/O here/O ./O 
Summer/O ,/O to/O me/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O direwo/O If/O heard/O the/O voice/O ,/O glanced/O at/O Bran/O ,/O and/O again/O at/O Lannister/LOCATION ./O 
He/O crept/O backward/O ,/O away/O from/O the/O little/O man/O ,/O and/O settled/O down/O below/O Bran/O 's/O dangling/O feet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON had/O been/O holding/O his/O breath/O ./O 
He/O let/O it/O out/O with/O a/O sigh/O and/O called/O ,/O \/O ``/O Grey/O Wind/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O direwo/O If/O moved/O to/O him/O ,/O swift/O and/O silent/O ./O 
Now/O there/O was/O only/O Shaggydog/LOCATION ,/O rumbling/O at/O the/O small/O man/O ,/O his/O eyes/O burning/O like/O green/O fire/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rickon/PERSON ,/O call/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON shouted/O to/O his/O baby/O brother/O ,/O and/O Rickon/PERSON remembered/O himself/O and/O screamed/O ,/O \/O ``/O Home/O ,/O Shaggy/O ,/O home/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O black/O wolf/O gave/O Lannister/O one/O final/O snarl/O and/O bounded/O off/O to/O Rickon/PERSON ,/O who/O hugged/O him/O tightly/O around/O the/O neck/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O undid/O his/O scarf/O ,/O mopped/O at/O his/O brow/O ,/O and/O said/O in/O a/O flat/O voice/O ,/O \/O ``/O How/O interesting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O you/O well/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O one/O of/O his/O men/O ,/O his/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O 
He/O glanced/O nervously/O at/O the/O direwolves/O as/O he/O spoke/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O sleeve/O is/O torn/O and/O my/O breeches/O are/O unaccountably/O damp/O ,/O but/O nothing/O was/O harmed/O save/O my/O dignity/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Even/O Robb/PERSON looked/O shaken/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wolves/O .../O I/O do/O n't/O know/O why/O they/O did/O that/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O doubt/O they/O mistook/O me/O for/O dinner/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lannister/PERSON bowed/O stiffly/O to/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O for/O calling/O them/O off/O ,/O young/O ser/O ./O 
I/O promise/O you/O ,/O they/O would/O have/O found/O me/O quite/O indigestible/O ./O 
And/O now/O I/O will/O be/O leaving/O ,/O truly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O moment/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O moved/O to/O Robb/PERSON and/O they/O huddled/O close/O together/O ,/O whispering/O ./O 
Bran/O tried/O to/O hear/O what/O they/O were/O saying/O ,/O but/O their/O voices/O were/O too/O low/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON finally/O sheathed/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I./O ./O 
./O 
I/O may/O have/O been/O hasty/O with/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O done/O Bran/O a/O kindness/O ,/O and/O ,/O well/O .../O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON composed/O himself/O with/O an/O effort/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O hospitality/O of/O Winterfell/O is/O yours/O if/O you/O wish/O it/O ,/O Lannister/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Spare/O me/O your/O false/O courtesies/O ,/O boy/O ./O 
You/O do/O not/O love/O me/O and/O you/O do/O not/O want/O me/O here/O ./O 
I/O saw/O an/O inn/O outside/O your/O walls/O ,/O in/O the/O winter/O town/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O find/O a/O bed/O there/O ,/O and/O both/O of/O us/O will/O sleep/O easier/O ./O 
For/O a/O few/O coppers/O I/O may/O even/O find/O a/O comely/O wench/O to/O warm/O the/O sheets/O for/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O spoke/O to/O one/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O ,/O an/O old/O man/O with/O a/O twisted/O back/O and/O a/O tangled/O beard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yoren/O ,/O we/O go/O south/O at/O daybreak/O ./O 
You/O will/O find/O me/O on/O the/O road/O ,/O no/O doubt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O With/O that/O he/O made/O his/O exit/O ,/O struggling/O across/O the/O hall/O on/O his/O short/O legs/O ,/O past/O Rickon/PERSON and/O out/O the/O door/O ./O 
His/O men/O followed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O four/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O remained/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON turned/O to/O them/O uncertainly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O had/O rooms/O prepared/O ,/O and/O you/O 'll/O find/O no/O lack/O of/O hot/O water/O to/O wash/O off/O the/O dust/O of/O the/O road/O ./O 
I/O hope/O you/O will/O ''/O ,/O ``/O honor/O us/O at/O table/O tonight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O spoke/O the/O words/O so/O awkwardly/O that/O even/O Bran/PERSON took/O note/O ;/O it/O was/O a/O speech/O he/O had/O learned/O ,/O not/O words/O from/O the/O heart/O ,/O but/O the/O black/O brothers/O thanked/O him/O all/O the/O same/O ./O 
Summer/O followed/O them/O up/O the/O tower/O steps/O as/O Hodor/PERSON carried/O Bran/O back/O to/O his/O bed/O ./O 
Old/O Nan/PERSON was/O asleep/O in/O her/O chair/O ./O 
Hodor/PERSON said/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O gathered/O up/O his/O great-grandmother/O ,/O and/O carried/O her/O off/O ,/O snoring/O softly/O ,/O while/O Bran/O lay/O thinking/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON had/O promised/O that/O he/O could/O feast/O with/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Summer/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O bounded/O up/O on/O the/O bed/O ./O 
Bran/O hugged/O him/O so/O hard/O he/O could/O feel/O the/O hot/O breath/O on/O his/O cheek/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O ride/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O to/O his/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O can/O go/O hunting/O in/O the/O woods/O soon/O ,/O wait/O and/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O After/O a/O time/O he/O slept/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O his/O dream/O he/O was/O climbing/O again/O ,/O pulling/O himself/O up/O an/O ancient/O windowless/O tower/O ,/O his/O fingers/O forcing/O themselves/O between/O blackened/O stones/O ,/O his/O feet/O scrabbling/O for/O purchase/O ./O 
Higher/O and/O higher/O he/O climbed/O ,/O through/O the/O clouds/O and/O into/O the/O night/O sky/O ,/O and/O still/O the/O tower/O rose/O before/O him/O ./O 
When/O he/O paused/O to/O look/O down/O ,/O his/O head/O swam/O dizzily/O and/O he/O felt/O his/O fingers/O slipping/O ./O 
Bran/O cried/O out/O and/O clung/O for/O dear/O life/O ./O 
The/O earth/O was/O a/O thousand/O miles/O beneath/O him/O and/O he/O could/O not/O fly/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O fly/O ./O 
He/O waited/O until/O his/O heart/O had/O stopped/O pounding/O ,/O until/O he/O could/O breathe/O ,/O and/O he/O began/O to/O climb/O again/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O way/O to/O go/O but/O up/O ./O 
Far/O above/O him/O ,/O outlined/O against/O a/O vast/O pale/O moon/O ,/O he/O thought/O he/O could/O see/O the/O shapes/O of/O gargoyles/O ./O 
His/O arms/O were/O sore/O and/O aching/O ,/O but/O he/O dared/O not/O rest/O ./O 
He/O forced/O himself/O to/O climb/O faster/O ./O 
The/O gargoyles/O watched/O him/O ascend/O ./O 
Their/O eyes/O glowed/O red/O as/O hot/O coals/O in/O a/O brazier/O ./O 
Perhaps/O once/O they/O had/O been/O lions/O ,/O but/O now/O they/O were/O twisted/O and/O grotesque/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O hear/O them/O whispering/O to/O each/O other/O in/O soft/O stone/O voices/O terrible/O to/O hear/O ./O 
He/O must/O not/O listen/O ,/O he/O told/O himself/O ,/O he/O must/O not/O hear/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O he/O did/O not/O hear/O them/O he/O was/O safe/O ./O 
But/O when/O the/O gargoyles/O pulled/O themselves/O loose/O from/O the/O stone/O and/O padded/O down/O the/O side/O of/O the/O tower/O to/O where/O Bran/O clung/O ,/O he/O knew/O he/O was/O not/O safe/O after/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O hear/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O wept/O as/O they/O came/O closer/O and/O closer/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O ,/O I/O did/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O woke/O gasping/O ,/O lost/O in/O darkness/O ,/O and/O saw/O a/O vast/O shadow/O looming/O over/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O hear/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ,/O trembling/O in/O fear/O ,/O but/O then/O the/O shadow/O said/O \/O ``/O Hodor/O ,/O \/O ''/O and/O lit/O the/O candle/O by/O the/O bedside/O ,/O and/O Bran/O sighed/O with/O relief/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Hodor/PERSON washed/O the/O sweat/O from/O him/O with/O a/O warm/O ,/O damp/O cloth/O and/O dressed/O him/O with/O deft/O and/O gentle/O hands/O ./O 
When/O it/O was/O time/O ,/O he/O carried/O him/O down/O to/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O where/O a/O long/O trestle/O table/O had/O been/O set/O up/O near/O the/O fire/O ./O 
The/O lord/O 's/O seat/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O table/O had/O been/O left/O empty/O ,/O but/O Robb/PERSON sat/O to/O the/O right/O of/O it/O ,/O with/O Bran/O across/O from/O him/O ./O 
They/O ate/O suckling/O pig/O that/O night/O ,/O and/O pigeon/O pie/O ,/O and/O turnips/O soaking/O in/O butter/O ,/O and/O afterward/O the/O cook/O had/O promised/O honeycombs/O ./O 
Summer/O snatched/O table/O scraps/O from/O Bran/O 's/O hand/O ,/O while/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON and/O Shaggydog/PERSON fought/O over/O a/O bone/O in/O the/O corner/O ./O 
Winterfell/PERSON 's/O dogs/O would/O not/O come/O near/O the/O hall/O now/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O found/O that/O strange/O at/O first/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O growing/O used/O to/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yoren/PERSON was/O senior/O among/O the/O black/O brothers/O ,/O so/O the/O steward/O had/O seated/O him/O between/O Robb/PERSON and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O 
The/O old/O man/O had/O a/O sour/O smell/O ,/O as/O if/O he/O had/O not/O washed/O in/O a/O long/O time/O ./O 
He/O ripped/O at/O the/O meat/O with/O his/O teeth/O ,/O cracked/O the/O ribs/O to/O suck/O out/O the/O marrow/O from/O the/O bones/O ,/O and/O shrugged/O at/O the/O mention/O of/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Alliser/O 's/O bane/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O grunted/O ,/O and/O two/O of/O his/O companions/O shared/O a/O laugh/O that/O Bran/O did/O not/O understand/O ./O 
But/O when/O Robb/PERSON asked/O for/O news/O of/O their/O uncle/O Benjen/PERSON ,/O the/O black/O brothers/O grew/O ominously/O quiet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yoren/PERSON wiped/O his/O fingers/O on/O his/O vest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O hard/O news/O ,/O m/O `/O lords/O ,/O and/O a/O cruel/O way/O to/O pay/O you/O for/O your/O meat/O and/O mead/O ,/O but/O the/O man/O as/O asks/O the/O question/O must/O bear/O the/O answer/O ./O 
Stark/O 's/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O One/O of/O the/O other/O men/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O sent/O him/O out/O to/O look/O for/O Waymar/PERSON Royce/PERSON ,/O and/O he/O 's/O late/O returning/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Too/O long/O ,/O \/O ''/O Yoren/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Most/O like/O he/O 's/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O uncle/O is/O not/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON said/O loudly/O ,/O anger/O in/O his/O tones/O ./O 
He/O rose/O from/O the/O bench/O and/O laid/O his/O hand/O on/O the/O hilt/O of/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
My/O uncle/O is/O not/O dead/O !/O 
\/O ''/O His/O voice/O rang/O against/O the/O stone/O walls/O ,/O and/O Bran/O was/O suddenly/O afraid/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Old/O sour-smelling/O Yoren/PERSON looked/O up/O at/O Robb/LOCATION ,/O unimpressed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Whatever/O you/O say/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O sucked/O at/O a/O piece/O of/O meat/O between/O his/O teeth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O youngest/O of/O the/O black/O brothers/O shifted/O uncomfortably/O in/O his/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O not/O a/O man/O on/O the/O Wall/O knows/O the/O haunted/O forest/O better/O than/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
He/O 'll/O find/O his/O way/O back/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Yoren/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O maybe/O he/O will/O and/O maybe/O he/O wo/O n't/O ./O 
Good/O men/O have/O gone/O into/O those/O woods/O before/O ,/O and/O never/O come/O out/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O All/O Bran/O could/O think/O of/O was/O Old/O Nan/PERSON 's/O story/O of/O the/O Others/O and/O the/O last/O hero/O ,/O hounded/O through/O the/O white/O woods/O by/O dead/O men/O and/O spiders/O big/O as/O hounds/O ./O 
He/O was/O afraid/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O until/O he/O remembered/O how/O that/O story/O ended/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O children/O will/O help/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O blurted/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON sniggered/O ,/O and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O the/O children/O of/O the/O forest/O have/O been/O dead/O and/O gone/O for/O thousands/O of/O years/O ./O 
All/O that/O is/O left/O of/O them/O are/O the/O faces/O in/O the/O trees/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Down/O here/O ,/O might/O be/O that/O 's/O true/O ,/O Maester/O ,/O \/O ''/O Yoren/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O up/O past/O the/O Wall/O ,/O who/O 's/O to/O say/O ?/O 
Up/O there/O ,/O a/O man/O ca/O n't/O always/O tell/O what/O 's/O alive/O and/O what/O 's/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O night/O ,/O after/O the/O plates/O had/O been/O cleared/O ,/O Robb/PERSON carried/O Bran/O up/O to/O bed/O himself/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON led/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O Summer/O came/O close/O behind/O ./O 
His/O brother/O was/O strong/O for/O his/O age/O ,/O and/O Bran/O was/O as/O light/O as/O a/O bundle/O of/O rags/O ,/O but/O the/O stairs/O were/O steep/O and/O dark/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON was/O breathing/O hard/O by/O the/O time/O they/O reached/O the/O top/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O put/O Bran/O into/O bed/O ,/O covered/O him/O with/O blankets/O ,/O and/O blew/O out/O the/O candle/O ./O 
For/O a/O time/O Robb/PERSON sat/O beside/O him/O in/O the/O dark/O ./O 
Bran/O wanted/O to/O talk/O to/O him/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O know/O what/O to/O say/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 'll/O find/O a/O horse/O for/O you/O ,/O I/O promise/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON whispered/O at/O last/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O they/O ever/O coming/O back/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O with/O such/O hope/O in/O his/O voice/O that/O Bran/O knew/O he/O was/O hearing/O his/O brother/O and/O not/O just/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O will/O be/O home/O soon/O ./O 
Maybe/O we/O can/O ride/O out/O to/O meet/O her/O when/O she/O comes/O ./O 
Would/O n't/O that/O surprise/O her/O ,/O to/O see/O you/O ahorse/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Even/O in/O the/O dark/O room/O ,/O Bran/PERSON could/O feel/O his/O brother/O 's/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O afterward/O ,/O we/O 'll/O ride/O north/O to/O see/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
We/O wo/O n't/O even/O tell/O Jon/PERSON we/O 're/O coming/O ,/O we/O 'll/O just/O be/O there/O one/O day/O ,/O you/O and/O me/O ./O 
It/O will/O be/O an/O adventure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O An/O adventure/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O repeated/O wistfully/O ./O 
He/O heard/O his/O brother/O sob/O ./O 
The/O room/O was/O so/O dark/O he/O could/O not/O see/O the/O tears/O on/O Robb/PERSON 's/O face/O ,/O so/O he/O reached/O out/O and/O found/O his/O hand/O ./O 
Their/O fingers/O twined/O together/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
