-LSB-/O ``/O TYRION/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Chella/PERSON daughter/O of/O Cheyk/O of/O the/O Black/ORGANIZATION Ears/ORGANIZATION had/O gone/O ahead/O to/O scout/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O she/O who/O brought/O back/O word/O of/O the/O army/O at/O the/O crossroads/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O their/O fires/O I/O call/O them/O twenty/O thousand/O strong/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Their/O banners/O are/O red/O ,/O with/O a/O golden/O lion/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Bronn/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Or/O my/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O shall/O know/O soon/O enough/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O surveyed/O his/O ragged/O band/O of/O brigands/O :/O near/O three/O hundred/O Stone/O Crows/O ,/O Moon/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION ,/O Black/O Ears/O ,/O and/O Burned/O Men/O ,/O and/O those/O just/O the/O seed/O of/O the/O army/O he/O hoped/O to/O grow/O ./O 
Gunthor/O son/O of/O Gurn/PERSON was/O raising/O the/O other/O clans/O even/O now/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O what/O his/O lord/O father/O would/O make/O of/O them/O in/O their/O skins/O and/O bits/O of/O stolen/O steel/O ./O 
If/O truth/O be/O told/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O know/O what/O to/O make/O of/O them/O himself/O ./O 
Was/O he/O their/O commander/O or/O their/O captive/O ?/O 
Most/O of/O the/O time/O ,/O it/O seemed/O to/O be/O a/O little/O of/O both/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O might/O be/O best/O if/O I/O rode/O down/O alone/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O suggested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Best/O for/O Tyrion/O son/O of/O Tywin/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Ulf/PERSON ,/O who/O spoke/O for/O the/O Moon/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Shagga/PERSON glowered/O ,/O a/O fearsome/O sight/O to/O see/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shagga/O son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON likes/O this/O not/O ./O 
Shagga/PERSON will/O go/O with/O the/O boyman/O ,/O and/O if/O the/O boyman/O lies/O ,/O Shagga/PERSON will/O chop/O off/O his/O manhood/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O and/O feed/O it/O to/O the/O goats/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O wearily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Shagga/O ,/O I/O give/O you/O my/O word/O as/O a/O Lannister/O ,/O I/O will/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O should/O we/O trust/O your/O word/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Chella/PERSON was/O a/O small/O hard/O woman/O ,/O flat/O as/O a/O boy/O ,/O and/O no/O fool/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lowland/O lords/O have/O lied/O to/O the/O clans/O before/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O wound/O me/O ,/O Chella/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O I/O thought/O we/O had/O become/O such/O friends/O ./O 
But/O as/O you/O will/O ./O 
You/O shall/O ride/O with/O me/O ,/O and/O Shagga/PERSON and/O Conn/LOCATION for/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O ,/O Ulf/PERSON for/O the/O Moon/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O Timett/O son/O of/O Timett/PERSON for/O the/O Burned/O Men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O clansmen/O exchanged/O wary/O looks/O as/O he/O named/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O rest/O shall/O wait/O here/O until/O I/O send/O for/O you/O ./O 
Try/O not/O to/O kill/O and/O maim/O each/O other/O while/O I/O 'm/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O put/O his/O heels/O to/O his/O horse/O and/O trotted/O off/O ,/O giving/O them/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O follow/O or/O be/O left/O behind/O ./O 
Either/O was/O fine/O with/O him/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O they/O did/O not/O sit/O down/O to/O talk/O for/O a/O day/O and/O a/O night/O ./O 
That/O was/O the/O trouble/O with/O the/O clans/O ;/O they/O had/O an/O absurd/O notion/O that/O every/O man/O 's/O voice/O should/O be/O heard/O in/O council/O ,/O so/O they/O argued/O about/O everything/O ,/O endlessly/O ./O 
Even/O their/O women/O were/O allowed/O to/O speak/O ./O 
Small/O wonder/O that/O it/O had/O been/O hundreds/O of/O years/O since/O they/O last/O threatened/O the/O Vale/O with/O anything/O beyond/O an/O occasional/O raid/O ./O 
Tyrion/O meant/O to/O change/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON rode/O with/O him/O ./O 
Behind/O them-after/O a/O quick/O bit/O of/O grumbling-the/O five/O clansmen/O followed/O on/O their/O undersize/O garrons/O ,/O scrawny/O things/O that/O looked/O like/O ponies/O and/O scrambled/O up/O rock/O walls/O like/O goats/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Stone/O Crows/O rode/O together/O ,/O and/O Chella/PERSON and/O Ulf/PERSON stayed/O close/O as/O well/O ,/O as/O the/O Moon/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION Ears/ORGANIZATION had/O strong/O bonds/O between/O them/O ./O 
Timett/O son/O of/O Timett/PERSON rode/O alone/O ./O 
Every/O clan/O in/O the/O Mountains/O of/O the/O Moon/O feared/O the/O Burned/O Men/O ,/O who/O mortified/O their/O flesh/O with/O fire/O to/O prove/O their/O courage/O and/O -LRB-/O the/O others/O said/O -RRB-/O roasted/O babies/O at/O their/O feasts/O ./O 
And/O even/O the/O other/O Burned/O Men/O feared/O Timett/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O put/O out/O his/O own/O left/O eye/O with/O a/O white-hot/O knife/O when/O he/O reached/O the/O age/O of/O manhood/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON gathered/O that/O it/O was/O more/O customary/O for/O a/O boy/O to/O burn/O off/O a/O nipple/O ,/O a/O finger/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O or/O -LRB-/O if/O he/O was/O truly/O brave/O ,/O or/O truly/O mad/O -RRB-/O an/O ear/O ./O 
Timett/PERSON 's/O fellow/O Burned/O Men/O were/O so/O awed/O by/O his/O choice/O of/O an/O eye/O that/O they/O promptly/O named/O him/O a/O red/O hand/O ,/O which/O seemed/O to/O be/O some/O sort/O of/O a/O war/O chief/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O wonder/O what/O their/O king/O burned/O off/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O to/O Bronn/LOCATION when/O he/O heard/O the/O tale/O ./O 
Grinning/O ,/O the/O sellsword/O had/O tugged/O at/O his/O crotch/O .../O but/O even/O Bronn/PERSON kept/O a/O respectful/O tongue/O around/O Timett/LOCATION ./O 
If/O a/O man/O was/O mad/O enough/O to/O put/O out/O his/O own/O eye/O ,/O he/O was/O unlikely/O to/O be/O gentle/O to/O his/O enemies/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Distant/O watchers/O peered/O down/O from/O towers/O of/O unmortared/O stone/O as/O the/O party/O descended/O through/O the/O foothills/O ,/O and/O once/O Tyrion/PERSON saw/O a/O raven/O take/O wing/O ./O 
Where/O the/O high/O road/O twisted/O between/O two/O rocky/O outcrops/O ,/O they/O came/O to/O the/O first/O strong/O point/O ./O 
A/O low/O earthen/O wall/O four/O feet/O high/O closed/O off/O the/O road/O ,/O and/O a/O dozen/O crossbowmen/O manned/O the/O heights/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON halted/O his/O followers/O out/O of/O range/O and/O rode/O to/O the/O wall/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Who/O commands/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O shouted/O up/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O captain/O was/O quick/O to/O appear/O ,/O and/O even/O quicker/O to/O give/O them/O an/O escort/O when/O he/O recognized/O his/O lord/O 's/O son/O ./O 
They/O trotted/O past/O blackened/O fields/O and/O burned/O holdfasts/O ,/O down/O to/O the/O riverlands/O and/O the/O Green/O Fork/O of/O the/O Trident/O ./O 
Tyrion/O saw/O no/O bodies/O ,/O but/O the/O air/O was/O full/O of/O ravens/O and/O carrion/O crows/O ;/O there/O had/O been/O fighting/O here/O ,/O and/O recently/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Haifa/LOCATION league/O from/O the/O crossroads/O ,/O a/O barricade/O of/O sharpened/O stakes/O had/O been/O erected/O ,/O manned/O by/O pikemen/O and/O archers/O ./O 
Behind/O the/O line/O ,/O the/O camp/O spread/O out/O to/O the/O far/O distance/O ./O 
Thin/O fingers/O of/O smoke/O rose/O from/O hundreds/O of/O cookfires/O ,/O mailed/O men/O sat/O under/O trees/O and/O honed/O their/O blades/O ,/O and/O familiar/O banners/O fluttered/O from/O staffs/O thrust/O into/O the/O muddy/O ground/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O party/O of/O mounted/O horsemen/O rode/O forward/O to/O challenge/O them/O as/O they/O approached/O the/O stakes/O ./O 
The/O knight/O who/O led/O them/O wore/O silver/O armor/O inlaid/O with/O amethysts/O and/O a/O striped/O purple-and-silver/O cloak/O ./O 
His/O shield/O bore/O a/O unicorn/O sigil/O ,/O and/O a/O spiral/O horn/O two/O feet/O long/O jutted/O up/O from/O the/O brow/O of/O his/O horsehead/O helm/O ./O 
Tyrion/O reined/O up/O to/O greet/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Flement/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Flement/O Brax/O lifted/O his/O visor/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O astonishment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O we/O all/O feared/O you/O dead/O ,/O or/O .../O \/O ''/O He/O looked/O at/O the/O clansmen/O uncertainly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O .../O companions/O of/O yours/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bosom/O friends/O and/O loyal/O retainers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O will/O I/O find/O my/O lord/O father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O has/O taken/O the/O inn/O at/O the/O crossroads/O for/O his/O quarters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O laughed/O ./O 
The/O inn/O at/O the/O crossroads/O !/O 
Perhaps/O the/O gods/O were/O just/O after/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O see/O him/O at/O once/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Flement/PERSON wheeled/O his/O horse/O about/O and/O shouted/O commands/O ./O 
Three/O rows/O of/O stakes/O were/O pulled/O from/O the/O ground/O to/O make/O a/O hole/O in/O the/O line/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON led/O his/O party/O through/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O camp/O spread/O over/O leagues/O ./O 
Chella/PERSON 's/O estimate/O of/O twenty/O thousand/O men/O could/O not/O be/O far/O wrong/O ./O 
The/O common/O men/O camped/O out/O in/O the/O open/O ,/O but/O the/O knights/O had/O thrown/O up/O tents/O ,/O and/O some/O of/O the/O high/O lords/O had/O erected/O pavilions/O as/O large/O as/O houses/O ./O 
Tyrion/O spied/O the/O red/O ox/O of/O the/O Presters/O ,/O Lord/O Crakehall/PERSON 's/O brindled/O boar/O ,/O the/O burning/O tree/O of/O Marbrand/LOCATION ,/O the/O badger/O of/O Lydden/LOCATION ./O 
Knights/O called/O out/O to/O him/O as/O he/O cantered/O past/O ,/O and/O men-at-arms/O gaped/O at/O the/O clansmen/O in/O open/O astonishment/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Shagga/PERSON was/O gaping/O back/O ;/O beyond/O a/O certainty/O ,/O he/O had/O never/O seen/O so/O many/O men/O ,/O horses/O ,/O and/O weapons/O in/O all/O his/O days/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O the/O mountain/O brigands/O did/O a/O better/O job/O of/O guarding/O their/O faces/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O no/O doubts/O that/O they/O were/O full/O as/O much/O in/O awe/O ./O 
Better/O and/O better/O ./O 
The/O more/O impressed/O they/O were/O with/O the/O power/O of/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O the/O easier/O they/O would/O be/O to/O command/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O inn/O and/O its/O stables/O were/O much/O as/O he/O remembered/O ,/O though/O little/O more/O than/O tumbled/O stones/O and/O blackened/O foundations/O remained/O where/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O village/O had/O stood/O ./O 
A/O gibbet/O had/O been/O erected/O in/O the/O yard/O ,/O and/O the/O body/O that/O swung/O there/O was/O covered/O with/O ravens/O ./O 
At/O Tyrion/LOCATION 's/O approach/O they/O took/O to/O the/O air/O ,/O squawking/O and/O flapping/O their/O black/O wings/O ./O 
He/O dismounted/O and/O glanced/O up/O at/O what/O remained/O of/O the/O corpse/O ./O 
The/O birds/O had/O eaten/O her/O lips/O and/O eyes/O and/O most/O of/O her/O cheeks/O ,/O baring/O her/O stained/O red/O teeth/O in/O a/O hideous/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O room/O ,/O a/O meal/O ,/O and/O a/O flagon/O of/O wine/O ,/O that/O was/O all/O I/O asked/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O reminded/O her/O with/O a/O sigh/O of/O reproach/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Boys/O emerged/O hesitantly/O from/O the/O stables/O to/O see/O to/O their/O horses/O ./O 
Shagga/PERSON did/O not/O want/O to/O give/O his/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O lad/O wo/O n't/O steal/O your/O mare/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/O assured/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O only/O wants/O to/O give/O her/O some/O oats/O and/O water/O and/O brush/O out/O her/O coat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Shagga/PERSON '/O s/O coat/O could/O have/O used/O a/O good/O brushing/O too/O ,/O but/O it/O would/O have/O been/O less/O than/O tactful/O to/O mention/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O my/O word/O ,/O the/O horse/O will/O not/O be/O harmed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Glaring/O ,/O Shagga/PERSON let/O go/O his/O grip/O on/O the/O reins/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O horse/O of/O Shagga/LOCATION son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O roared/O at/O the/O stableboy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O he/O does/O n't/O give/O her/O back/O ,/O chop/O off/O his/O manhood/O and/O feed/O it/O to/O the/O goats/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Provided/O you/O can/O find/O some/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O pair/O of/O house/O guards/O in/O crimson/O cloaks/O and/O lion-crested/O helms/O stood/O under/O the/O inn/O 's/O sign/O ,/O on/O either/O side/O of/O the/O door/O ./O 
Tyrion/PERSON recognized/O their/O captain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O In/O the/O common/O room/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O men/O will/O want/O meat/O and/O mead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O that/O they/O get/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O entered/O the/O inn/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O Father/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tywin/O Lannister/O ,/O Lord/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION and/O Warden/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O was/O in/O his/O middle/O fifties/O ,/O yet/O hard/O as/O a/O man/O of/O twenty/O ./O 
Even/O seated/O ,/O he/O was/O tall/O ,/O with/O long/O legs/O ,/O broad/O shoulders/O ,/O a/O flat/O stomach/O ./O 
His/O thin/O arms/O were/O corded/O with/O muscle/O ./O 
When/O his/O once-thick/O golden/O hair/O had/O begun/O to/O recede/O ,/O he/O had/O commanded/O his/O barber/O to/O shave/O his/O head/O ;/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON did/O not/O believe/O in/O half/O measures/O ./O 
He/O razored/O his/O lip/O and/O chin/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O kept/O his/O side-whiskers/O ,/O two/O great/O thickets/O of/O wiry/O golden/O hair/O that/O covered/O most/O of/O his/O cheeks/O from/O ear/O to/O jaw/O ./O 
His/O eyes/O were/O a/O pale/O green/O ,/O flecked/O with/O gold/O ./O 
A/O fool/O more/O foolish/O than/O most/O had/O once/O jested/O that/O even/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON 's/O shit/O was/O flecked/O with/O gold/O ./O 
Some/O said/O the/O man/O was/O still/O alive/O ,/O deep/O in/O the/O bowels/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O his/O father/O 's/O only/O surviving/O brother/O ,/O was/O sharing/O a/O flagon/O of/O ale/O with/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON when/O Tyrion/PERSON entered/O the/O common/O room/O ./O 
His/O uncle/O was/O portly/O and/O balding/O ,/O with/O a/O close/O -/O cropped/O yellow/O beard/O that/O followed/O the/O line/O of/O his/O massive/O jaw/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON saw/O him/O first/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O surprise/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Uncle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O bowing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O my/O lord/O father/O ./O 
What/O a/O pleasure/O to/O find/O you/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON did/O not/O stir/O from/O his/O chair/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O give/O his/O dwarf/O son/O a/O long/O ,/O searching/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O that/O the/O rumors/O of/O your/O demise/O were/O unfounded/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Sorry/O to/O disappoint/O you/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O need/O to/O leap/O up/O and/O embrace/O me/O ,/O I/O would/O n't/O want/O you/O to/O strain/O yourself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O crossed/O the/O room/O to/O their/O table/O ,/O acutely/O conscious/O of/O the/O way/O his/O stunted/O legs/O made/O him/O waddle/O with/O every/O step/O ./O 
Whenever/O his/O father/O 's/O eyes/O were/O on/O him/O ,/O he/O became/O uncomfortably/O aware/O of/O all/O his/O deformities/O and/O shortcomings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Kind/O of/O you/O to/O go/O to/O war/O for/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O climbed/O into/O a/O chair/O and/O helped/O himself/O to/O a/O cup/O of/O his/O father/O 's/O ale/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O By/O my/O lights/O ,/O it/O was/O you/O who/O started/O this/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O Jaime/PERSON would/O never/O have/O meekly/O submitted/O to/O capture/O at/O the/O hands/O of/O a/O woman/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O That/O 's/O one/O way/O we/O differ/O ,/O Jaime/PERSON and/O I./O He/O 's/O taller/O as/O well/O ,/O you/O may/O have/O noticed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O father/O ignored/O the/O sally/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O honor/O of/O our/O House/ORGANIZATION was/O at/O stake/O ./O 
I/O had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O ride/O ./O 
No/O man/O sheds/O Lannister/O blood/O with/O impunity/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hear/O Me/O Roar/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O grinning/O ./O 
The/O Lannister/O words/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Truth/O be/O told/O ,/O none/O of/O my/O blood/O was/O actually/O shed/O ,/O although/O it/O was/O a/O close/O thing/O once/O or/O twice/O ./O 
Morrec/PERSON and/O Jyck/PERSON were/O killed/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O suppose/O you/O will/O be/O wanting/O some/O new/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O trouble/O yourself/O ,/O Father/O ,/O I/O 've/O acquired/O a/O few/O of/O my/O own/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O tried/O a/O swallow/O of/O the/O ale/O ./O 
It/O was/O brown/O and/O yeasty/O ,/O so/O thick/O you/O could/O almost/O chew/O it/O ./O 
Very/O fine/O ,/O in/O truth/O ./O 
A/O pity/O his/O father/O had/O hanged/O the/O innkeep/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O is/O your/O war/O going/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O uncle/O answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O enough/O ,/O for/O the/O nonce/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Edmure/PERSON had/O scattered/O small/O troops/O of/O men/O along/O his/O borders/O to/O stop/O our/O raiding/O ,/O and/O your/O lord/O father/O and/O I/O were/O able/O to/O destroy/O most/O of/O them/O piecemeal/O before/O they/O could/O regroup/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O has/O been/O covering/O himself/O with/O glory/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O smashed/O the/O Lords/O Vance/PERSON and/O Piper/ORGANIZATION at/O the/O Golden/LOCATION Tooth/LOCATION ,/O and/O met/O the/O massed/O power/O of/O the/O Tullys/O under/O the/O walls/O of/O Riverrun/O ./O 
The/O lords/O of/O the/O Trident/O have/O been/O put/O to/O rout/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Edmure/PERSON Tully/PERSON was/O taken/O captive/O ,/O with/O many/O of/O his/O knights/O and/O bannermen/O ./O 
Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON led/O a/O few/O survivors/O back/O to/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O where/O Jaime/PERSON has/O them/O under/O siege/O ./O 
The/O rest/O fled/O to/O their/O own/O strongholds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O father/O and/O I/O have/O been/O marching/O on/O each/O in/O turn/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O Lord/O Blackwood/PERSON gone/O ,/O Raventree/PERSON fell/O at/O once/O ,/O and/O Lady/PERSON Whent/PERSON yielded/O Harrenhal/O for/O want/O of/O men/O to/O defend/O it/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Gregor/PERSON burnt/O out/O the/O Pipers/O and/O the/O Brackens/PERSON .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Leaving/O you/O unopposed/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O wholly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Mallisters/O still/O hold/O Seagard/LOCATION and/O Walder/PERSON Frey/PERSON is/O marshaling/O his/O levies/O at/O the/O Twins/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O matter/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Frey/PERSON only/O takes/O the/O field/O when/O the/O scent/O of/O victory/O is/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O and/O all/O he/O smells/O now/O is/O ruin/O ./O 
And/O Jason/PERSON Mallister/PERSON lacks/O the/O strength/O to/O fight/O alone/O ./O 
Once/O Jaime/PERSON takes/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O they/O will/O both/O be/O quick/O enough/O to/O bend/O the/O knee/O ./O 
Unless/O the/O Starks/PERSON and/O the/O Arryns/O come/O forth/O to/O oppose/O us/O ,/O this/O war/O is/O good/O as/O won/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O not/O fret/O overmuch/O about/O the/O Arryns/O if/O I/O were/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Starks/PERSON are/O another/O matter/O ./O 
Lord/O Eddard/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ''/O -/O is/O our/O hostage/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O will/O lead/O no/O armies/O while/O he/O rots/O in/O a/O dungeon/O under/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON agreed/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O his/O son/O has/O called/O the/O banners/O and/O sits/O at/O Moat/LOCATION Cailin/LOCATION with/O a/O strong/O host/O around/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O sword/O is/O strong/O until/O it/O 's/O been/O tempered/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON declared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Stark/O boy/O is/O a/O child/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O he/O likes/O the/O sound/O of/O warhorns/O well/O enough/O ,/O and/O the/O sight/O of/O his/O banners/O fluttering/O in/O the/O wind/O ,/O but/O in/O the/O end/O it/O comes/O down/O to/O butcher/O 's/O work/O ./O 
I/O doubt/O he/O has/O the/O stomach/O for/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Things/O had/O gotten/O interesting/O while/O he/O 'd/O been/O away/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON reflected/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O is/O our/O fearless/O monarch/O doing/O whilst/O all/O this/O `/O butcher/O 's/O work/O '/O is/O being/O done/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O wondered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O has/O my/O lovely/O and/O persuasive/O sister/O gotten/O Robert/PERSON to/O agree/O to/O the/O imprisonment/O of/O his/O dear/O friend/O Ned/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON is/O dead/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O nephew/O reigns/O in/O King/O 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O did/O take/O Tyrion/O aback/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sister/O ,/O you/O mean/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O another/O gulp/O of/O ale/O ./O 
The/O realm/O would/O be/O a/O much/O different/O place/O with/O Cersei/PERSON ruling/O in/O place/O of/O her/O husband/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O you/O have/O a/O mind/O to/O make/O yourself/O of/O use/O ,/O I/O will/O give/O you/O a/O command/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O father/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Marq/PERSON Piper/PERSON and/O Karyl/PERSON Vance/PERSON are/O loose/O in/O our/O rear/O ,/O raiding/O our/O lands/O across/O the/O Red/O Fork/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O made/O a/O tsking/O sound/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gall/O of/O them/O ,/O fighting/O back/O ./O 
Ordinarily/O I/O 'd/O be/O glad/O to/O punish/O such/O rudeness/O ,/O Father/O ,/O but/O the/O truth/O is/O ,/O I/O have/O pressing/O business/O elsewhere/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON did/O not/O seem/O awed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O also/O have/O a/O pair/O of/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O afterthoughts/O making/O a/O nuisance/O of/O themselves/O by/O harassing/O my/O foraging/O parties/O ./O 
Beric/PERSON Dondarrion/PERSON ,/O some/O young/O lordling/O with/O delusions/O of/O valor/O ./O 
He/O has/O that/O fat/O jape/O of/O a/O priest/O with/O him/O ,/O the/O one/O who/O likes/O to/O set/O his/O sword/O on/O fire/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O you/O might/O be/O able/O to/O deal/O with/O them/O as/O you/O scamper/O off/O ?/O 
Without/O making/O too/O much/O a/O botch/O of/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O wiped/O his/O mouth/O with/O the/O back/O of/O his/O hand/O and/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Father/O ,/O it/O warms/O my/O heart/O to/O think/O that/O you/O might/O entrust/O me/O with/O .../O what/O ,/O twenty/O men/O ?/O 
Fifty/O ?/O 
Are/O you/O sure/O you/O can/O spare/O so/O many/O ?/O 
Well/O ,/O no/O matter/O ./O 
If/O I/O should/O come/O across/O Thoros/O and/O Lord/O Beric/PERSON ,/O I/O shall/O spank/O them/O both/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O climbed/O down/O from/O his/O chair/O and/O waddled/O to/O the/O sideboard/O ,/O where/O a/O wheel/O of/O veined/O white/O cheese/O sat/O surrounded/O by/O fruit/O ./O 
\/O ``/O First/O ,/O though/O ,/O I/O have/O some/O promises/O of/O my/O own/O to/O keep/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O sliced/O off/O a/O wedge/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O require/O three/O thousand/O helms/O and/O as/O many/O hauberks/O ,/O plus/O swords/O ,/O pikes/O ,/O steel/O spearheads/O ,/O maces/O ,/O battleaxes/O ,/O gauntlets/O ,/O gorgets/O ,/O greaves/O ,/O breastplates/O ,/O wagons/O to/O carry/O all/O this/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O door/O behind/O him/O opened/O with/O a/O crash/O ,/O so/O violently/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON almost/O dropped/O his/O cheese/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON leapt/O up/O swearing/O as/O the/O captain/O of/O the/O guard/O went/O flying/O across/O the/O room/O to/O smash/O against/O the/O hearth/O ./O 
As/O he/O tumbled/O down/O into/O the/O cold/O ashes/O ,/O his/O lion/O helm/O askew/O ,/O Shagga/PERSON snapped/O the/O man/O 's/O sword/O in/O two/O over/O a/O knee/O thick/O as/O a/O tree/O trunk/O ,/O threw/O down/O the/O pieces/O ,/O and/O lumbered/O into/O the/O common/O room/O ./O 
He/O was/O preceded/O by/O his/O stench/O ,/O riper/O than/O the/O cheese/O and/O overpowering/O in/O the/O closed/O space/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Little/O redcape/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O snarled/O ,/O \/O ``/O when/O next/O you/O bare/O steel/O on/O Shagga/O son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON ,/O I/O will/O chop/O off/O your/O manhood/O and/O roast/O it/O in/O the/O fire/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O ,/O no/O goats/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O ,/O taking/O a/O bite/O of/O cheese/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O other/O clansmen/O followed/O Shagga/O into/O the/O common/O room/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON with/O them/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O gave/O Tyrion/PERSON a/O rueful/O shrug/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O might/O you/O be/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON asked/O ,/O cool/O as/O snow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O followed/O me/O home/O ,/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON explained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O I/O keep/O them/O ?/O 
They/O do/O n't/O eat/O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O No/O one/O was/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O what/O right/O do/O you/O savages/O intrude/O on/O our/O councils/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O demanded/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Savages/O ,/O lowlander/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Conn/PERSON might/O have/O been/O handsome/O if/O you/O washed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O free/O men/O ,/O and/O free/O men/O by/O rights/O sit/O on/O all/O war/O councils/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Which/O one/O is/O the/O lion/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Chella/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O are/O both/O old/O men/O ,/O \/O ''/O announced/O Timett/PERSON son/PERSON of/PERSON Timett/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O yet/O to/O see/O his/O twentieth/O year/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON '/O s/O hand/O went/O to/O his/O sword/O hilt/O ,/O but/O his/O brother/O placed/O two/O fingers/O on/O his/O wrist/O and/O held/O him/O fast/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON seemed/O unperturbed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O ,/O have/O you/O forgotten/O your/O courtesies/O ?/O 
Kindly/O acquaint/O us/O with/O our/O .../O honored/O guests/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON licked/O his/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O With/O pleasure/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O fair/O maid/O is/O Chella/PERSON daughter/O of/O Cheyk/PERSON of/O the/O Black/O Ears/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O no/O maid/O ,/O \/O ''/O Chella/PERSON protested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sons/O have/O taken/O fifty/O ears/O among/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O May/O they/O take/O fifty/O more/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON waddled/O away/O from/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O Conn/PERSON son/O of/O Coratt/O ./O 
Shagga/O son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON is/O the/O one/O who/O looks/O like/O Casterly/O Rock/O with/O hair/O ./O 
They/O are/O Stone/O Crows/O ./O 
Here/O is/O Ulf/PERSON son/PERSON of/PERSON Umar/PERSON of/PERSON the/PERSON Moon/PERSON Brothers/PERSON ,/O and/O here/O Timett/O son/O of/O Timett/PERSON ,/O a/O red/O hand/O of/O the/O Burned/O Men/O ./O 
And/O this/O is/O Bronn/PERSON ,/O a/O sellsword/O of/O no/O particular/O allegiance/O ./O 
He/O has/O already/O changed/O sides/O twice/O in/O the/O short/O time/O I/O 've/O known/O him/O ,/O you/O and/O he/O ought/O to/O get/O on/O famously/O ,/O Father/O ./O 
\/O ''/O To/O Bronn/LOCATION and/O the/O clansmen/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O May/O I/O present/O my/O lord/O father/O ,/O Tywin/PERSON son/O of/O Tytos/O of/O House/O Lannister/O ,/O Lord/O of/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O Warden/O of/O the/O West/LOCATION ,/O Shield/O of/O Lannisport/LOCATION ,/O and/O once/O and/O future/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON rose/O ,/O dignified/O and/O correct/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O in/O the/O west/O ,/O we/O know/O the/O prowess/O of/O the/O warrior/O clans/O of/O the/O Mountains/O of/O the/O Moon/O ./O 
What/O brings/O you/O down/O from/O your/O strongholds/O ,/O my/O lords/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Horses/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Shagga/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O promise/O of/O silk/O and/O steel/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Timett/PERSON son/O of/O Timett/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O about/O to/O tell/O his/O lord/O father/O how/O he/O proposed/O to/O reduce/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION to/O a/O smoking/O wasteland/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O never/O given/O the/O chance/O ./O 
The/O door/O banged/O open/O again/O ./O 
The/O messenger/O gave/O Tyrion/PERSON '/O s/O clansmen/O a/O quick/O ,/O queer/O look/O as/O he/O dropped/O to/O one/O knee/O before/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Addam/O bid/O me/O tell/O you/O that/O the/O Stark/O host/O is/O moving/O down/O the/O causeway/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON did/O not/O smile/O ./O 
Lord/O Tywin/PERSON never/O smiled/O ,/O but/O Tyrion/PERSON had/O learned/O to/O read/O his/O father/O 's/O pleasure/O all/O the/O same/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O there/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O the/O wolfling/O is/O leaving/O his/O den/O to/O play/O among/O the/O lions/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O voice/O of/O quiet/O satisfaction/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Splendid/O ./O 
Return/O to/O Ser/PERSON Addam/PERSON and/O tell/O him/O to/O fall/O back/O ./O 
He/O is/O not/O to/O engage/O the/O northerners/O until/O we/O arrive/O ,/O but/O I/O want/O him/O to/O harass/O their/O flanks/O and/O draw/O them/O farther/O south/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O as/O you/O command/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O rider/O took/O his/O leave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O are/O well/O situated/O here/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Close/O to/O the/O ford/O and/O ringed/O by/O pits/O and/O spikes/O ./O 
If/O they/O are/O coming/O south/O ,/O I/O say/O let/O them/O come/O ,/O and/O break/O themselves/O against/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O boy/O may/O hang/O back/O or/O lose/O his/O courage/O when/O he/O sees/O our/O numbers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sooner/O the/O Starks/O are/O broken/O ,/O the/O sooner/O I/O shall/O be/O free/O to/O deal/O with/O Stannis/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON ./O 
Tell/O the/O drummers/O to/O beat/O assembly/O ,/O and/O send/O word/O to/O Jaime/PERSON that/O I/O am/O marching/O against/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Kevan/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Tyrion/PERSON watched/O with/O a/O grim/O fascination/O as/O his/O lord/O father/O turned/O next/O to/O the/O half-wild/O clansmen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O said/O that/O the/O men/O of/O the/O mountain/O clans/O are/O warriors/O without/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O said/O truly/O ,/O \/O ''/O Conn/O of/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O answered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O the/O women/O ,/O \/O ''/O Chella/PERSON added/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ride/O with/O me/O against/O my/O enemies/O ,/O and/O you/O shall/O have/O all/O my/O son/O promised/O you/O ,/O and/O more/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON told/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O you/O pay/O us/O with/O our/O own/O coin/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ulf/PERSON son/PERSON of/PERSON Umar/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O should/O we/O need/O the/O father/O 's/O promise/O ,/O when/O we/O have/O the/O son/O 's/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O said/O nothing/O of/O need/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O words/O were/O courtesy/O ,/O nothing/O more/O ./O 
You/O need/O not/O join/O us/O ./O 
The/O men/O of/O the/O winterlands/O are/O made/O of/O iron/O and/O ice/O ,/O and/O even/O my/O boldest/O knights/O fear/O to/O face/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O deftly/O done/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON thought/O ,/O smiling/O crookedly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Burned/O Men/O fear/O nothing/O ./O 
Timett/O son/O of/O Timett/PERSON will/O ride/O with/O the/O lions/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wherever/O the/O Burned/O Men/O go/O ,/O the/O Stone/O Crows/O have/O been/O there/O first/O ,/O \/O ''/O Conn/PERSON declared/O hotly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O ride/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shagga/O son/O of/O Dolf/PERSON will/O chop/O off/O their/O manhoods/O and/O feed/O them/O to/O the/O crows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O will/O ride/O with/O you/O ,/O lion/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Chella/PERSON daughter/O of/O Cheyk/LOCATION agreed/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O only/O if/O your/O halfman/O son/O goes/O with/O us/O ./O 
He/O has/O bought/O his/O breath/O with/O promises/O ./O 
Until/O we/O hold/O the/O steel/O he/O has/O pledged/O us/O ,/O his/O life/O is/O ours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON turned/O his/O go/O Id/O -/O flecked/O eyes/O on/O his/O son/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Joy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON said/O with/O a/O resigned/O smile/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
