-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O will/O make/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O within/O the/O hour/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON turned/O away/O from/O the/O rail/O and/O forced/O herself/O to/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O oarmen/O have/O done/O well/O by/O us/O ,/O Captain/O ./O 
Each/O one/O of/O them/O shall/O have/O a/O silver/O stag/O ,/O as/O a/O token/O of/O my/O gratitude/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Captain/O Moreo/PERSON Turnitis/PERSON favored/O her/O with/O a/O half/O bow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O far/O too/O generous/O ,/O Lady/O Stark/O ./O 
The/O honor/O of/O carrying/O a/O great/O lady/O like/O yourself/O is/O all/O the/O reward/O they/O need/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O they/O 'll/O take/O the/O silver/O anyway/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Moreo/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O spoke/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O fluently/O ,/O with/O only/O the/O slightest/O hint/O of/O a/O Tyroshi/O accent/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O been/O plying/O the/O narrow/O sea/O for/O thirty/O years/O ,/O he/O 'd/O told/O her/O ,/O as/O oarman/O ,/O quartermaster/O ,/O and/O finally/O captain/O of/O his/O own/O trading/O galleys/O ./O 
The/O Storm/O Dancer/O was/O his/O fourth/O ship/O ,/O and/O his/O fastest/O ,/O a/O two-masted/O galley/O of/O sixty/O oars/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O certainly/O been/O the/O fastest/O of/O the/O ships/O available/O in/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION when/O Catelyn/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON had/O arrived/O after/O their/O headlong/O gallop/O downriver/O ./O 
The/O Tyroshi/O were/O notorious/O for/O their/O avarice/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON had/O argued/O for/O hiring/O a/O fishing/O sloop/O out/O of/O the/O Three/O Sisters/O ,/O but/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O insisted/O on/O the/O galley/O ./O 
It/O was/O good/O that/O she/O had/O ./O 
The/O winds/O had/O been/O against/O them/O much/O of/O the/O voyage/O ,/O and/O without/O the/O galley/O 's/O oars/O they/O 'd/O still/O be/O beating/O their/O way/O past/O the/O Fingers/O ,/O instead/O of/O skimming/O toward/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O and/O journey/O 's/O end/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O So/O close/O ,/O she/O thought/O ./O 
Beneath/O the/O linen/O bandages/O ,/O her/O fingers/O still/O throbbed/O where/O the/O dagger/O had/O bitten/O ./O 
The/O pain/O was/O her/O scourge/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON felt/O ,/O lest/O she/O forget/O ./O 
She/O could/O not/O bend/O the/O last/O two/O fingers/O on/O her/O left/O hand/O ,/O and/O the/O others/O would/O never/O again/O be/O dexterous/O ./O 
Yet/O that/O was/O a/O small/O enough/O price/O to/O pay/O for/O Bran/O 's/O life/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON chose/O that/O moment/O to/O appear/O on/O deck/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O good/O friend/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Moreo/PERSON through/O his/O forked/O green/O beard/O ./O 
The/O Tyroshi/O loved/O bright/O colors/O ,/O even/O in/O their/O facial/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O is/O so/O fine/O to/O see/O you/O looking/O better/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON agreed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O n't/O wanted/O to/O die/O for/O almost/O two/O days/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O bowed/O to/O Catelyn/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O was/O looking/O better/O ./O 
A/O shade/O thinner/O than/O he/O had/O been/O when/O they/O set/O out/O from/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ,/O but/O almost/O himself/O again/O ./O 
The/O strong/O winds/O in/O the/O Bite/O and/O the/O roughness/O of/O the/O narrow/O sea/O had/O not/O agreed/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O he/O 'd/O almost/O gone/O over/O the/O side/O when/O the/O storm/O seized/O them/O unexpectedly/O off/O Dragonstone/PERSON ,/O yet/O somehow/O he/O had/O clung/O to/O a/O rope/O until/O three/O of/O Moreo/PERSON 's/O men/O could/O rescue/O him/O and/O carry/O him/O safely/O below/O decks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O captain/O was/O just/O telling/O me/O that/O our/O voyage/O is/O almost/O at/O an/O end/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON managed/O a/O wry/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O soon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O odd/O without/O his/O great/O white/O side/O whiskers/O ;/O smaller/O somehow/O ,/O less/O fierce/O ,/O and/O ten/O years/O older/O ./O 
Yet/O back/O on/O the/O Bite/O it/O had/O seemed/O prudent/O to/O submit/O to/O a/O crewman/O 's/O razor/O ,/O after/O his/O whiskers/O had/O become/O hopelessly/O befouled/O for/O the/O third/O time/O while/O he/O leaned/O over/O the/O rail/O and/O retched/O into/O the/O swirling/O winds/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O leave/O you/O to/O discuss/O your/O business/O ,/O \/O ''/O Captain/O Moreo/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O bowed/O and/O took/O his/O leave/O of/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O galley/O skimmed/O the/O water/O like/O a/O dragonfly/O ,/O her/O oars/O rising/O and/O falling/O in/O perfect/O time/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON held/O the/O rail/O and/O looked/O out/O over/O the/O passing/O shore/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O not/O been/O the/O most/O valiant/O of/O protectors/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON touched/O his/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O here/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O and/O safely/O ./O 
That/O is/O all/O that/O truly/O matters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Her/O hand/O groped/O beneath/O her/O cloak/O ,/O her/O fingers/O stiff/O and/O fumbling/O ./O 
The/O dagger/O was/O still/O at/O her/O side/O ./O 
She/O found/O she/O had/O to/O touch/O it/O now/O and/O then/O ,/O to/O reassure/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Now/O we/O must/O reach/O the/O king/O 's/O master-at-arms/O ,/O and/O pray/O that/O he/O can/O be/O trusted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Aron/PERSON Santagar/PERSON is/O a/O vain/O man/O ,/O but/O an/O honest/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON 's/O hand/O went/O to/O his/O face/O to/O stroke/O his/O whiskers/O and/O discovered/O once/O again/O that/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O 
He/O looked/O nonplussed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O may/O know/O the/O blade/O ,/O yes/O .../O but/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O the/O moment/O we/O go/O ashore/O we/O are/O at/O risk/O ./O 
And/O there/O are/O those/O at/O court/O who/O will/O know/O you/O on/O sight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O 's/O mouth/O grew/O tight/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Littlefinger/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O murmured/O ./O 
His/O face/O swam/O up/O before/O her/O ;/O a/O boy/O 's/O face/O ,/O though/O he/O was/O a/O boy/O no/O longer/O ./O 
His/O father/O had/O died/O several/O years/O before/O ,/O so/O he/O was/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON now/O ,/O yet/O still/O they/O called/O him/O Littlefinger/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O Edmure/PERSON had/O given/O him/O that/O name/O ,/O long/O ago/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
His/O family/O 's/O modest/O holdings/O were/O on/O the/O smallest/O of/O the/O Fingers/O ,/O and/O Petyr/PERSON had/O been/O slight/O and/O short/O for/O his/O age/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON cleared/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON once/O ,/O ah/O His/O thought/O trailed/O off/O uncertainly/O in/O search/O of/O the/O polite/O word/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O past/O delicacy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O my/O father/O 's/O ward/O ./O 
We/O grew/O up/O together/O in/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
I/O thought/O of/O him/O as/O a/O brother/O ,/O but/O his/O feelings/O for/O me/O were/O .../O more/O than/O brotherly/O ./O 
When/O it/O was/O announced/O that/O I/O was/O to/O wed/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O Petyr/PERSON challenged/O for/O the/O right/O to/O my/O hand/O ./O 
It/O was/O madness/O ./O 
Brandon/PERSON was/O twenty/O ,/O Petyr/PERSON scarcely/O fifteen/O ./O 
I/O had/O to/O beg/O Brandon/PERSON to/O spare/O Petyr/PERSON '/O s/O life/O ./O 
He/O let/O him/O off/O with/O a/O scar/O ./O 
Afterward/O my/O father/O sent/O him/O away/O ./O 
I/O have/O not/O seen/O him/O since/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O lifted/O her/O face/O to/O the/O spray/O ,/O as/O if/O the/O brisk/O wind/O could/O blow/O the/O memories/O away/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O wrote/O to/O me/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION after/O Brandon/PERSON was/O killed/O ,/O but/O I/O burned/O the/O letter/O unread/O ./O 
By/O then/O I/O knew/O that/O Ned/PERSON would/O marry/O me/O in/O his/O brother/O 's/O place/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON 's/O fingers/O fumbled/O once/O again/O for/O nonexistent/O whiskers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON sits/O on/O the/O small/O council/O now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O knew/O he/O would/O rise/O high/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O always/O clever/O ,/O even/O as/O a/O boy/O ,/O but/O it/O is/O one/O thing/O to/O be/O clever/O and/O another/O to/O be/O wise/O ./O 
I/O wonder/O what/O the/O years/O have/O done/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O High/O overhead/O ,/O the/O far-eyes/O sang/O out/O from/O the/O rigging/O ./O 
Captain/O Moreo/PERSON came/O scrambling/O across/O the/O deck/O ,/O giving/O orders/O ,/O and/O all/O around/O them/O the/O Storm/O Dancer/O burst/O into/O frenetic/O activity/O as/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O slid/O into/O view/O atop/O its/O three/O high/O hills/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Three/O hundred/O years/O ago/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON knew/O ,/O those/O heights/O had/O been/O covered/O with/O forest/O ,/O and/O only/O a/O handful/O of/O fisherfolk/O had/O lived/O on/O the/O north/O shore/O of/O the/O Blackwater/O Rush/O where/O that/O deep/O ,/O swift/O river/O flowed/O into/O the/O sea/O ./O 
Then/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O had/O sailed/O from/O Dragonstone/LOCATION ./O 
It/O was/O here/O that/O his/O army/O had/O put/O ashore/O ,/O and/O there/O on/O the/O highest/O hill/O that/O he/O built/O his/O first/O crude/O redoubt/O of/O wood/O and/O earth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Now/O the/O city/O covered/O the/O shore/O as/O far/O as/O Catelyn/PERSON could/O see/O ;/O manses/O and/O arbors/O and/O granaries/O ,/O brick/O storehouses/O and/O timbered/O inns/O and/O merchant/O 's/O stalls/O ,/O taverns/O and/O graveyards/O and/O brothels/O ,/O ''/O ,/O ``/O all/O piled/O one/O on/O another/O ./O 
She/O could/O hear/O the/O clamor/O of/O the/O fish/O market/O even/O at/O this/O distance/O ./O 
Between/O the/O buildings/O were/O broad/O roads/O lined/O with/O trees/O ,/O wandering/O crookback/O streets/O ,/O and/O alleys/O so/O narrow/O that/O two/O men/O could/O not/O walk/O abreast/O ./O 
Visenya/PERSON 's/O hill/O was/O crowned/O by/O the/O Great/O Sept/O of/O Baelor/LOCATION with/O its/O seven/O crystal/O towers/O ./O 
Across/O the/O city/O on/O the/O hill/O of/O Rhaenys/LOCATION stood/O the/O blackened/O walls/O of/O the/O Dragonpit/O ,/O its/O huge/O dome/O collapsing/O into/O ruin/O ,/O its/O bronze/O doors/O closed/O now/O for/O a/O century/O ./O 
The/O Street/O of/O the/O Sisters/O ran/O between/O them/O ,/O straight/O as/O an/O arrow/O ./O 
The/O city/O walls/O rose/O in/O the/O distance/O ,/O high/O and/O strong/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O hundred/O quays/O lined/O the/O waterfront/O ,/O and/O the/O harbor/O was/O crowded/O with/O ships/O ./O 
Deepwater/O fishing/O boats/O and/O river/O runners/O came/O and/O went/O ,/O ferrymen/O poled/O back/O and/O forth/O across/O the/O Blackwater/O Rush/O ,/O trading/O galleys/O unloaded/O goods/O from/O Braavos/LOCATION and/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION and/O Lys/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON spied/O the/O queen/O 's/O ornate/O barge/O ,/O tied/O up/O beside/O a/O fat-bellied/O whaler/O from/O the/O Port/LOCATION of/LOCATION Ibben/LOCATION ,/O its/O hull/O black/O with/O tar/O ,/O while/O upriver/O a/O dozen/O lean/O golden/O warships/O rested/O in/O their/O cribs/O ,/O sails/O furled/O and/O cruel/O iron/O rams/O lapping/O at/O the/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O above/O it/O all/O ,/O frowning/O down/O from/O Aegon/ORGANIZATION 's/O high/O hill/O ,/O was/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ;/O seven/O huge/O drum/O -/O towers/O crowned/O with/O iron/O ramparts/O ,/O an/O immense/O grim/O barbican/O ,/O vaulted/O halls/O and/O covered/O bridges/O ,/O barracks/O and/O dungeons/O and/O granaries/O ,/O massive/O curtain/O walls/O studded/O with/O archers/O '/O nests/O ,/O all/O fashioned/O of/O pale/O red/O stone/O ./O 
Aegon/ORGANIZATION the/O Conqueror/O had/O commanded/O it/O built/O ./O 
His/O son/O Maegor/PERSON the/PERSON Cruel/PERSON had/O seen/O it/O completed/O ./O 
Afterward/O he/O had/O taken/O the/O heads/O of/O every/O stonemason/O ,/O woodworker/O ,/O and/O builder/O who/O had/O labored/O on/O it/O ./O 
Only/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O would/O ever/O know/O the/O secrets/O of/O the/O fortress/O the/O Dragonlords/O had/O built/O ,/O he/O vowed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O now/O the/O banners/O that/O flew/O from/O its/O battlements/O were/O golden/O ,/O not/O black/O ,/O and/O where/O the/O three/O -/O headed/O dragon/O had/O once/O breathed/O fire/O ,/O now/O pranced/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Baratheon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O high-masted/O swan/O ship/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION was/O beating/O out/O from/O port/O ,/O its/O white/O sails/O huge/O with/O wind/O ./O 
The/O Storm/O Dancer/O moved/O past/O it/O ,/O pulling/O steadily/O for/O shore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O have/O thought/O on/O how/O best/O to/O proceed/O while/O I/O lay/O abed/O ./O 
You/O must/O not/O enter/O the/O castle/O ./O 
I/O will/O go/O in/O your/O stead/O and/O bring/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON to/O you/O in/O some/O safe/O place/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O studied/O the/O old/O knight/O as/O the/O galley/O drew/O near/O to/O a/O pier/O ./O 
Moreo/PERSON was/O shouting/O in/O the/O vulgar/O Valyrian/O of/O the/O Free/O Cities/O ./O 
`/O You/O would/O be/O as/O much/O at/O risk/O as/O I/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O think/O not/O ./O 
I/O looked/O at/O my/O reflection/O in/O the/O water/O earlier/O and/O scarcely/O recognized/O myself/O ./O 
My/O mother/O was/O the/O last/O person/O to/O see/O me/O without/O whiskers/O ,/O and/O she/O is/O forty/O years/O dead/O ./O 
I/O believe/O I/O am/O safe/O enough/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Moreo/PERSON bellowed/O a/O command/O ./O 
As/O one/O ,/O sixty/O oars/O lifted/O from/O the/O river/O ,/O then/O reversed/O and/O backed/O water/O ./O 
The/O galley/O slowed/O ./O 
Another/O shout/O ./O 
The/O oars/O slid/O back/O inside/O the/O hull/O ./O 
As/O they/O thumped/O against/O the/O dock/O ,/O Tyroshi/PERSON seamen/O leapt/O down/O to/O tie/O up/O ./O 
Moreo/PERSON came/O bustling/O up/O ,/O all/O smiles/O ./O 
\/O ``/O King/O 's/O Landing/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O as/O you/O did/O command/O ,/O and/O never/O has/O a/O ship/O made/O a/O swifter/O or/O surer/O passage/O ./O 
Will/O you/O be/O needing/O assistance/O to/O carry/O your/O things/O to/O the/O castle/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O shall/O not/O be/O going/O to/O the/O castle/O ./O 
Perhaps/O you/O can/O suggest/O an/O inn/O ,/O someplace/O clean/O and/O comfortable/O and/O not/O too/O far/O from/O the/O river/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Tyroshi/PERSON fingered/O his/O forked/O green/O beard/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O so/O ./O 
I/O know/O of/O several/O establishments/O that/O might/O suit/O your/O needs/O ./O 
Yet/O first/O ,/O if/O I/O may/O be/O so/O bold/O ,/O there/O is/O the/O matter/O of/O the/O second/O half/O of/O the/O ''/O ,/O ``/O payment/O we/O agreed/O upon/O ./O 
And/O of/O course/O the/O extra/O silver/O you/O were/O so/O kind/O as/O to/O promise/O ./O 
Sixty/O stags/O ,/O I/O believe/O it/O was/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O For/O the/O oarmen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O of/O a/O certainty/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Moreo/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Though/O perhaps/O I/O should/O hold/O it/O for/O them/O until/O we/O return/O to/O Tyrosh/O ./O 
For/O the/O sake/O of/O their/O wives/O and/O children/O ./O 
If/O you/O give/O them/O the/O silver/O here/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O they/O will/O dice/O it/O away/O or/O spend/O it/O all/O for/O a/O night/O 's/O pleasure/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O are/O worse/O things/O to/O spend/O money/O on/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON put/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Winter/O is/O coming/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O man/O must/O make/O his/O own/O choices/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O earned/O the/O silver/O ./O 
How/O they/O spend/O it/O is/O no/O concern/O of/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Moreo/PERSON replied/O ,/O bowing/O and/O smiling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Just/O to/O be/O sure/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON paid/O the/O oarmen/O herself/O ,/O a/O stag/O to/O each/O man/O ,/O and/O a/O copper/O to/O the/O two/O men/O who/O carried/O their/O chests/O halfway/O up/O Visenya/PERSON 's/O hill/O to/O the/O inn/O that/O Moreo/PERSON had/O suggested/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O rambling/O old/O place/O on/O Eel/LOCATION Alley/LOCATION ./O 
The/O woman/O who/O owned/O it/O was/O a/O sour/O crone/O with/O a/O wandering/O eye/O who/O looked/O them/O over/O suspiciously/O and/O bit/O the/O coin/O that/O Catelyn/PERSON offered/O her/O to/O make/O sure/O it/O was/O real/O ./O 
Her/O rooms/O were/O large/O and/O airy/O ,/O though/O ,/O and/O Moreo/PERSON swore/O that/O her/O fish/O stew/O was/O the/O most/O savory/O in/O all/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
Best/O of/O all/O ,/O she/O had/O no/O interest/O in/O their/O names/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O think/O it/O best/O if/O you/O stay/O away/O from/O the/O common/O room/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ,/O after/O they/O had/O settled/O in/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Even/O in/O a/O place/O like/O this/O ,/O one/O never/O knows/O who/O may/O be/O watching/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O wore/O ringmail/O ,/O dagger/O ,/O and/O longsword/O under/O a/O dark/O cloak/O with/O a/O hood/O he/O could/O pull/O up/O over/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O be/O back/O before/O nightfall/O ,/O with/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O promised/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rest/O now/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O tired/O ./O 
The/O voyage/O had/O been/O long/O and/O fatiguing/O ,/O and/O she/O was/O no/O longer/O as/O young/O as/O she/O had/O been/O ./O 
Her/O windows/O opened/O on/O the/O alley/O and/O rooftops/O ,/O with/O a/O view/O of/O the/O Blackwater/ORGANIZATION beyond/O ./O 
She/O watched/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON set/O off/O ,/O striding/O briskly/O through/O the/O busy/O streets/O until/O he/O was/O lost/O in/O the/O crowds/O ,/O then/O decided/O to/O take/O his/O advice/O ./O 
The/O bedding/O was/O stuffed/O with/O straw/O instead/O of/O feathers/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O no/O trouble/O falling/O asleep/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O woke/O to/O a/O pounding/O on/O her/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON sat/O up/O sharply/O ./O 
Outside/O the/O window/O ,/O the/O rooftops/O of/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O were/O red/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O setting/O sun/O ./O 
She/O had/O slept/O longer/O than/O she/O intended/O ./O 
A/O fist/O hammered/O at/O her/O door/O again/O ,/O and/O a/O voice/O called/O out/O ,/O \/O ``/O Open/O ,/O in/O the/O name/O of/O the/O king/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O moment/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O out/O ./O 
She/O wrapped/O herself/O in/O her/O cloak/O ./O 
The/O dagger/O was/O on/O the/O bedside/O table/O ./O 
She/O snatched/O it/O up/O before/O she/O unlatched/O the/O heavy/O wooden/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O men/O who/O pushed/O into/O the/O room/O wore/O the/O black/O ringmail/O and/O golden/O cloaks/O of/O the/O City/O Watch/O ./O 
Their/O leader/O smiled/O at/O the/O dagger/O in/O her/O hand/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O No/O need/O for/O that/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ./O 
We/O 're/O to/O escort/O you/O to/O the/O castle/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O By/O whose/O authority/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O showed/O her/O a/O ribbon/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON felt/O her/O breath/O catch/O in/O her/O throat/O ./O 
The/O seal/O was/O a/O mockingbird/O ,/O in/O grey/O wax/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Petyr/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
So/O soon/O ./O 
Something/O must/O have/O happened/O to/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
She/O looked/O at/O the/O head/O guardsman/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O you/O know/O who/O I/O am/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O m/O `/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O M'lord/O Little/O finger/O said/O only/O to/O bring/O you/O to/O him/O ,/O and/O see/O that/O you/O were/O not/O mistreated/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O may/O wait/O outside/O while/O I/O dress/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O bathed/O her/O hands/O in/O the/O basin/O and/O wrapped/O them/O in/O clean/O linen/O ./O 
Her/O fingers/O were/O thick/O and/O awkward/O as/O she/O struggled/O to/O lace/O up/O her/O bodice/O and/O knot/O a/O drab/O brown/O cloak/O about/O her/O neck/O ./O 
How/O could/O Littlefinger/PERSON have/O known/O she/O was/O here/O ?/O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON would/O never/O have/O told/O him/O ./O 
Old/O he/O might/O be/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O stubborn/O ,/O and/O loyal/O to/O a/O fault/O ./O 
Were/O they/O too/O late/O ,/O had/O the/O Lannisters/O reached/O King/O 's/O Landing/O before/O her/O ?/O 
No/O ,/O if/O that/O were/O true/O ,/O Ned/PERSON would/O be/O here/O too/O ,/O and/O surely/O he/O would/O have/O come/O to/O her/O ./O 
How/O .../O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Then/O she/O thought/O ,/O Moreo/PERSON ./O 
The/O Tyroshi/PERSON knew/O who/O they/O were/O and/O where/O they/O were/O ,/O damn/O him/O ./O 
She/O hoped/O he/O 'd/O gotten/O a/O good/O price/O for/O the/O information/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O had/O brought/O a/O horse/O for/O her/O ./O 
The/O lamps/O were/O being/O lit/O along/O the/O streets/O as/O they/O set/O out/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON felt/O the/O eyes/O of/O the/O city/O on/O her/O as/O she/O rode/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O the/O guard/O in/O their/O golden/O cloaks/O ./O 
When/O they/O reached/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O the/O portcullis/O was/O down/O and/O the/O great/O gates/O sealed/O for/O the/O night/O ,/O but/O the/O castle/O windows/O were/O alive/O with/O flickering/O lights/O ./O 
The/O guardsmen/O left/O their/O mounts/O outside/O the/O walls/O and/O escorted/O her/O through/O a/O narrow/O postern/O door/O ,/O then/O up/O endless/O steps/O to/O a/O tower/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O was/O alone/O in/O the/O room/O ,/O seated/O at/O a/O heavy/O wooden/O table/O ,/O an/O oil/O lamp/O beside/O him/O as/O he/O wrote/O ./O 
When/O they/O ushered/O her/O inside/O ,/O he/O set/O down/O his/O pen/O and/O looked/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cat/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O quietly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O have/O I/O been/O brought/O here/O in/O this/O fashion/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O rose/O and/O gestured/O brusquely/O to/O the/O guards/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Leave/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O men/O departed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O were/O not/O mistreated/O ,/O I/O trust/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O after/O they/O had/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O gave/O firm/O instructions/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O noticed/O her/O bandages/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O hands/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON ignored/O the/O implied/O question/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O not/O accustomed/O to/O being/O summoned/O like/O a/O serving/O wench/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O icily/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O a/O boy/O ,/O you/O still/O knew/O the/O meaning/O of/O courtesy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 've/O angered/O you/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
That/O was/O never/O my/O intent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O contrite/O ./O 
The/O look/O brought/O back/O vivid/O memories/O for/O Catelyn/O ./O 
He/O had/O been/O a/O sly/O child/O ,/O but/O after/O his/O mischiefs/O he/O always/O looked/O contrite/O ;/O it/O was/O a/O gift/O he/O had/O ./O 
The/O years/O had/O not/O changed/O him/O much/O ./O 
Petyr/PERSON had/O been/O a/O small/O boy/O ,/O and/O he/O had/O grown/O into/O a/O small/O man/O ,/O an/O inch/O or/O two/O shorter/O than/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O slender/O and/O quick/O ,/O with/O the/O sharp/O features/O she/O remembered/O and/O the/O same/O laughing/O grey-green/O eyes/O ./O 
He/O had/O a/O little/O pointed/O chin/O beard/O now/O ,/O and/O threads/O of/O silver/O in/O his/O dark/O hair/O ,/O though/O he/O was/O still/O shy/O of/O thirty/O ./O 
They/O went/O well/O with/O the/O silver/O mockingbird/O that/O fastened/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
Even/O as/O a/O child/O ,/O he/O had/O always/O loved/O his/O silver/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O did/O you/O know/O I/O was/O in/O the/O city/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON knows/O all/O ,/O \/O ''/O Petyr/PERSON said/O with/O a/O sly/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O will/O be/O joining/O us/O shortly/O ,/O but/O I/O wanted/O to/O see/O you/O alone/O first/O ./O 
It/O has/O been/O too/O long/O ,/O Cat/O ./O 
How/O many/O years/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON ignored/O his/O familiarity/O ./O 
There/O were/O more/O important/O questions/O ./O 
\/O ``/O So/O it/O was/O the/O King/O 's/O Spider/O who/O found/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON winced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O call/O him/O that/O ./O 
He/O 's/O very/O sensitive/O ./O 
Comes/O of/O being/O an/O eunuch/O ,/O I/O imagine/O ./O 
Nothing/O happens/O in/O this/O city/O without/O Varys/O knowing/O ./O 
Oftimes/O he/O knows/O about/O ''/O ,/O ``/O it/O before/O it/O happens/O ./O 
He/O has/O informants/O everywhere/O ./O 
His/O little/O birds/O ,/O he/O calls/O them/O ./O 
One/O of/O his/O little/O birds/O heard/O about/O your/O visit/O ./O 
Thankfully/O ,/O Varys/PERSON came/O to/O me/O first/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O not/O me/O ?/O 
I/O am/O master/O of/O coin/O ,/O the/O king/O 's/O own/O councillor/O ./O 
Selmy/PERSON and/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON rode/O north/O to/O meet/O Robert/PERSON ,/O and/O Lord/LOCATION Stannis/LOCATION is/O gone/O to/O Dragonstone/LOCATION ,/O leaving/O only/O Maester/O Pycelle/O and/O me/O ./O 
I/O was/O the/O obvious/O choice/O ./O 
I/O was/O ever/O a/O friend/O to/O your/O sister/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O Varys/PERSON knows/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Does/O Varys/O know/O about/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON knows/O everything/O .../O except/O why/O you/O are/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O lifted/O an/O eyebrow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O are/O you/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wife/O is/O allowed/O to/O yearn/O for/O her/O husband/O ,/O and/O if/O a/O mother/O needs/O her/O daughters/O close/O ,/O who/O can/O tell/O her/O no/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O very/O good/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O but/O please/O do/O n't/O expect/O me/O to/O believe/O that/O ./O 
I/O know/O you/O too/O well/O ./O 
What/O were/O the/O Tully/O words/O again/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Her/O throat/O was/O dry/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Family/O ,/O Duty/O ,/O Honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O recited/O stiffly/O ./O 
He/O did/O know/O her/O too/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Family/O ,/O Duty/O ,/O Honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O echoed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O of/O which/O required/O you/O to/O remain/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O where/O our/O Hand/O left/O you/O ./O 
No/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O something/O has/O happened/O ./O 
This/O sudden/O trip/O of/O yours/O bespeaks/O a/O certain/O urgency/O ./O 
I/O beg/O of/O you/O ,/O let/O me/O help/O ./O 
Old/O sweet/O friends/O should/O never/O hesitate/O to/O rely/O upon/O each/O other/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O was/O a/O soft/O knock/O on/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Enter/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O man/O who/O stepped/O through/O the/O door/O was/O plump/O ,/O perfumed/O ,/O powdered/O ,/O and/O as/O hairless/O as/O an/O egg/O ./O 
He/O wore/O a/O vest/O of/O woven/O gold/O thread/O over/O a/O loose/O gown/O of/O purple/O silk/O ,/O and/O on/O his/O feet/O were/O pointed/O slippers/O of/O soft/O velvet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lady/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O taking/O her/O hand/O in/O both/O of/O his/O ,/O \/O ``/O to/O see/O you/O again/O after/O so/O many/O years/O is/O such/O a/O joy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O flesh/O was/O soft/O and/O moist/O ,/O and/O his/O breath/O smelled/O of/O lilacs/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O your/O poor/O hands/O ./O 
Have/O you/O burned/O yourself/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ?/O 
The/O fingers/O are/O so/O delicate/O .../O Our/O good/O Maester/O Pycelle/O makes/O a/O marvelous/O salve/O ,/O shall/O I/O send/O for/O ajar/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON slid/O her/O fingers/O from/O his/O grasp/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O thank/O you/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O but/O my/O own/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON has/O already/O seen/O to/O my/O hurts/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O bobbed/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O grievous/O sad/O to/O hear/O about/O your/O son/O ./O 
And/O him/O so/O young/O ./O 
The/O gods/O are/O cruel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O On/O that/O we/O agree/O ,/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
The/O title/O was/O but/O a/O courtesy/O due/O him/O as/O a/O council/O member/O ;/O Varys/PERSON was/O lord/O of/O nothing/O but/O the/O spiderweb/O ,/O the/O master/O of/O none/O but/O his/O whisperers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O eunuch/O spread/O his/O soft/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ``/O On/O more/O than/O that/O ,/O I/O hope/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
I/O have/O great/O esteem/O for/O your/O husband/O ,/O our/O new/O Hand/O ,/O and/O I/O know/O we/O do/O both/O love/O King/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O was/O forced/O to/O say/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O a/O certainty/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Never/O has/O a/O king/O been/O so/O beloved/O as/O our/O Robert/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O quipped/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
He/O smiled/O slyly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O At/O least/O in/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON 's/O hearing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O with/O great/O solicitude/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O are/O men/O in/O the/O Free/O Cities/O with/O wondrous/O healing/O powers/O ./O 
Say/O only/O the/O word/O ,/O and/O I/O will/O send/O for/O one/O for/O your/O dear/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON is/O doing/O all/O that/O can/O be/O done/O for/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ./O 
She/O would/O not/O speak/O of/O Bran/O ,/O not/O here/O ,/O not/O with/O these/O men/O ./O 
She/O trusted/O Littlefinger/PERSON only/O a/O little/O ,/O and/O Varys/O not/O at/O all/O ./O 
She/O ''/O ,/O ``/O would/O not/O let/O them/O see/O her/O grief/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON tells/O me/O that/O I/O have/O you/O to/O thank/O for/O bringing/O me/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O giggled/O like/O a/O little/O girl/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
I/O suppose/O I/O am/O guilty/O ./O 
I/O hope/O you/O forgive/O me/O ,/O kind/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O eased/O himself/O down/O into/O a/O seat/O and/O put/O his/O hands/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O if/O we/O might/O trouble/O you/O to/O show/O us/O the/O dagger/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O Stark/O stared/O at/O the/O eunuch/O in/O stunned/O disbelief/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O spider/O ,/O she/O thought/O wildly/O ,/O an/O enchanter/O or/O worse/O ./O 
He/O knew/O things/O no/O one/O could/O possibly/O know/O ,/O unless/O \/O ``/O What/O have/O you/O done/O to/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O demanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON was/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O feel/O rather/O like/O the/O knight/O who/O arrives/O at/O the/O battle/O without/O his/O lance/O ./O 
What/O dagger/O are/O we/O talking/O about/O ?/O 
Who/O is/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON is/O master-at-arms/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/O informed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O assure/O you/O ,/O Lady/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O nothing/O at/O all/O has/O been/O done/O to/O the/O good/O knight/O ./O 
He/O did/O call/O here/O early/O this/O afternoon/O ./O 
He/O visited/O with/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON Santagar/PERSON in/O the/O armory/O ,/O and/O they/O talked/O of/O a/O certain/O dagger/O ./O 
About/O sunset/O ,/O they/O left/O the/O castle/O together/O and/O walked/O to/O that/O dreadful/O hovel/O where/O you/O were/O staying/O ./O 
They/O are/O still/O there/O ,/O drinking/O in/O the/O common/O room/O ,/O waiting/O for/O your/O return/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON was/O very/O distressed/O to/O find/O you/O gone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O could/O you/O know/O all/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O whisperings/O of/O little/O birds/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O know/O things/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
That/O is/O the/O nature/O of/O my/O service/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O do/O have/O the/O dagger/O with/O you/O ,/O yes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON pulled/O it/O out/O from/O beneath/O her/O cloak/O and/O threw/O it/O down/O on/O the/O table/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ./O 
Perhaps/O your/O little/O birds/O will/O whisper/O the/O name/O of/O the/O man/O it/O belongs/O to/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Varys/O lifted/O the/O knife/O with/O exaggerated/O delicacy/O and/O ran/O a/O thumb/O along/O its/O edge/O ./O 
Blood/O welled/O ,/O and/O he/O let/O out/O a/O squeal/O and/O dropped/O the/O dagger/O back/O on/O the/O table/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Careful/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O it/O 's/O sharp/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O holds/O an/O edge/O like/O Valyrian/O steel/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O as/O Varys/PERSON sucked/O at/O his/O bleeding/O thumb/O and/O looked/O at/O Catelyn/LOCATION with/O sullen/O admonition/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON hefted/O the/O knife/O lightly/O in/O his/O hand/O ,/O testing/O the/O grip/O ./O 
He/O flipped/O it/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O caught/O it/O again/O with/O his/O other/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Such/O sweet/O balance/O ./O 
You/O want/O to/O find/O the/O owner/O ,/O is/O that/O the/O reason/O for/O this/O visit/O ?/O 
You/O have/O no/O need/O of/O Ser/PERSON Aron/PERSON for/O that/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
You/O should/O have/O come/O to/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O if/O I/O had/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O what/O would/O you/O have/O told/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O have/O told/O you/O that/O there/O was/O only/O one/O knife/O like/O this/O at/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O grasped/O the/O blade/O between/O thumb/O and/O forefinger/O ,/O drew/O it/O back/O over/O his/O shoulder/O ,/O and/O threw/O it/O across/O the/O room/O with/O a/O practiced/O flick/O of/O his/O wrist/O ./O 
It/O struck/O the/O door/O and/O buried/O itself/O deep/O in/O the/O oak/O ,/O quivering/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O mine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yours/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O It/O made/O no/O sense/O ./O 
Petyr/PERSON had/O not/O been/O at/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Until/O the/O tourney/O on/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON 's/O name/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O crossing/O the/O room/O to/O wrench/O the/O dagger/O from/O the/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O backed/O Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON in/O the/O jousting/O ,/O along/O with/O half/O the/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Petyr/PERSON 's/O sheepish/O grin/O made/O him/O look/O half/O a/O boy/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O Loras/PERSON Tyrell/PERSON unhorsed/O him/O ,/O many/O of/O us/O became/O a/O trifle/O poorer/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jaime/PERSON lost/O a/O hundred/O golden/O dragons/O ,/O the/O queen/O lost/O an/O emerald/O pendant/O ,/O and/O I/O lost/O my/O knife/O ./O 
Her/O Grace/O got/O the/O emerald/O back/O ,/O but/O the/O winner/O kept/O the/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Who/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON demanded/O ,/O her/O mouth/O dry/O with/O fear/O ./O 
Her/O fingers/O ached/O with/O remembered/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Imp/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Little/O finger/O as/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON watched/O her/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
