-LSB-/O ``/O DAENERYS/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Horse/O Gate/O of/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON was/O made/O of/O two/O gigantic/O bronze/O stallions/O ,/O rearing/O ,/O their/O hooves/O meeting/O a/O hundred/O feet/O above/O the/O roadway/O to/O form/O a/O pointed/O arch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON could/O not/O have/O said/O why/O the/O city/O needed/O a/O gate/O when/O it/O had/O no/O walls/O .../O and/O no/O buildings/O that/O she/O could/O see/O ./O 
Yet/O there/O it/O stood/O ,/O immense/O and/O beautiful/O ,/O the/O great/O horses/O framing/O the/O distant/O purple/O mountain/O beyond/O ./O 
The/O bronze/O stallions/O threw/O long/O shadows/O across/O the/O waving/O grasses/O as/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON led/O the/O khalasar/O under/O their/O hooves/O and/O down/O the/O godsway/O ,/O his/O bloodriders/O beside/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON followed/O on/O her/O silver/O ,/O escorted/O by/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON and/O her/O brother/O Viserys/PERSON ,/O mounted/O once/O more/O ./O 
After/O the/O day/O in/O the/O grass/O when/O she/O had/O left/O him/O to/O walk/O back/O to/O the/O khalasar/O ,/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON had/O laughingly/O called/O him/O Khal/O Rhae/O Mhar/O ,/O the/O Sorefoot/O King/O ./O 
Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON had/O offered/O him/O a/O place/O in/O a/O cart/O the/O next/O day/O ,/O and/O Viserys/PERSON had/O accepted/O ./O 
In/O his/O stubborn/O ignorance/O ,/O he/O had/O not/O even/O known/O he/O was/O being/O mocked/O ;/O the/O carts/O were/O for/O eunuchs/O ,/O cripples/O ,/O women/O giving/O birth/O ,/O the/O very/O young/O and/O the/O very/O old/O ./O 
That/O won/O him/O yet/O another/O name/O :/O Khal/PERSON Rhaggat/PERSON ,/O the/O Cart/O King/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O had/O thought/O it/O was/O the/O khal/O 's/O way/O of/O apologizing/O for/O the/O wrong/O Dany/PERSON had/O done/O him/O ./O 
She/O had/O begged/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON not/O to/O tell/O him/O the/O truth/O ,/O lest/O he/O be/O shamed/O ./O 
The/O knight/O had/O replied/O that/O the/O king/O could/O well/O do/O with/O a/O bit/O of/O shame/O .../O yet/O he/O had/O done/O as/O she/O bid/O ./O 
It/O had/O taken/O much/O pleading/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O pillow/O tricks/O Doreah/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O ,/O before/O Dany/PERSON had/O been/O able/O to/O make/O Drogo/PERSON relent/O and/O allow/O Viserys/PERSON to/O rejoin/O them/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O column/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Where/O is/O the/O city/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O as/O they/O passed/O beneath/O the/O bronze/O arch/O ./O 
There/O were/O no/O buildings/O to/O be/O seen/O ,/O no/O people/O ,/O only/O the/O grass/O and/O the/O road/O ,/O lined/O with/O ancient/O monuments/O from/O all/O the/O lands/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON had/O sacked/O over/O the/O centuries/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ahead/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON answered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Under/O the/O mountain/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O horse/O gate/O ,/O plundered/O gods/O and/O stolen/O heroes/O loomed/O to/O either/O side/O of/O them/O ./O 
The/O forgotten/O deities/O of/O dead/O cities/O brandished/O their/O broken/O thunderbolts/O at/O the/O sky/O as/O Dany/PERSON rode/O her/O silver/O past/O their/O feet/O ./O 
Stone/O kings/O looked/O down/O on/O her/O from/O their/O thrones/O ,/O their/O faces/O chipped/O and/O stained/O ,/O even/O their/O names/O lost/O in/O the/O mists/O of/O time/O ./O 
Lithe/O young/O maidens/O danced/O on/O marble/O plinths/O ,/O draped/O only/O in/O flowers/O ,/O or/O poured/O air/O from/O shattered/O jars/O ./O 
Monsters/O stood/O in/O the/O grass/O beside/O the/O road/O ;/O black/O iron/O dragons/O with/O jewels/O for/O eyes/O ,/O roaring/O griffins/O ,/O manticores/O with/O their/O barbed/O tails/O poised/O to/O strike/O ,/O and/O other/O beasts/O she/O could/O not/O name/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O statues/O were/O so/O lovely/O they/O took/O her/O breath/O away/O ,/O others/O so/O misshapen/O and/O terrible/O that/O Dany/PERSON could/O scarcely/O bear/O to/O look/O at/O them/O ./O 
Those/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O ,/O had/O likely/O come/O from/O the/O Shadow/O Lands/O beyond/O Asshai/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O many/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O as/O her/O silver/O stepped/O slowly/O onward/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O from/O so/O many/O lands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O was/O less/O impressed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O trash/O of/O dead/O cities/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O sneered/O ./O 
He/O was/O careful/O to/O speak/O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ,/O which/O few/O Dothraki/PERSON could/O understand/O ,/O yet/O even/O so/O Dany/PERSON found/O herself/O glancing/O back/O at/O the/O men/O of/O her/O khas/O ,/O to/O make/O certain/O he/O had/O not/O been/O overheard/O ./O 
He/O went/O on/O blithely/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O these/O savages/O know/O how/O to/O do/O is/O steal/O the/O things/O better/O men/O have/O built/O .../O and/O kill/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O do/O know/O how/O to/O kill/O ./O 
Otherwise/O I/O 'd/O have/O no/O use/O for/O them/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O are/O my/O people/O now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O should/O not/O call/O them/O savages/O ,/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O dragon/O speaks/O as/O he/O likes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON said/O .../O in/O the/O Common/O Tongue/O ./O 
He/O glanced/O over/O his/O shoulder/O at/O Aggo/LOCATION and/O Rakharo/PERSON ,/O riding/O behind/O them/O ,/O and/O favored/O them/O with/O a/O mocking/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O See/O ,/O the/O savages/O lack/O the/O wit/O to/O understand/O the/O speech/O of/O civilized/O men/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O mosseaten/O stone/O monolith/O loomed/O over/O the/O road/O ,/O fifty/O feet/O tall/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON gazed/O at/O it/O with/O boredom/O in/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O long/O must/O we/O linger/O amidst/O these/O ruins/O before/O Drogo/PERSON gives/O me/O my/O army/O ?/O 
I/O grow/O tired/O of/O waiting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O princess/O must/O be/O presented/O to/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O crones/O ,/O yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O brother/O interrupted/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O there/O 's/O to/O be/O some/O mummer/O 's/O show/O of/O a/O prophecy/O for/O the/O whelp/O in/O her/O belly/O ,/O you/O told/O me/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O What/O is/O that/O to/O me/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O tired/O of/O eating/O horsemeat/O and/O I/O 'm/O sick/O of/O the/O stink/O of/O these/O savages/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sniffed/O at/O the/O wide/O ,/O floppy/O sleeve/O of/O his/O tunic/O ,/O where/O it/O was/O his/O custom/O to/O keep/O a/O sachet/O ./O 
It/O could/O not/O have/O helped/O much/O ./O 
The/O tunic/O was/O filthy/O ./O 
All/O the/O silk/O and/O heavy/O wools/O that/O Viserys/PERSON had/O worn/O out/O of/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION were/O stained/O by/O hard/O travel/O and/O rotted/O from/O sweat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON Mormont/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O The/O Western/O Market/O will/O have/O food/O more/O to/O your/O taste/O ,/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
The/O traders/O from/O the/O Free/O Cities/O come/O there/O to/O sell/O their/O wares/O ./O 
The/O khal/O will/O honor/O his/O promise/O in/O his/O own/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O had/O better/O ,/O \/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON said/O grimly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O promised/O a/O crown/O ,/O and/O I/O mean/O to/O have/O it/O ./O 
The/O dragon/O is/O not/O mocked/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Spying/O an/O obscene/O likeness/O of/O a/O woman/O with/O six/O breasts/O and/O a/O ferret/O 's/O head/O ,/O he/O rode/O off/O to/O inspect/O it/O more/O closely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON was/O relieved/O ,/O yet/O no/O less/O anxious/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O pray/O that/O my/O sun-and-stars/O will/O not/O keep/O him/O waiting/O too/O long/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON when/O her/O brother/O was/O out/O of/O earshot/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O knight/O looked/O after/O Viserys/O doubtfully/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O should/O have/O bided/O his/O time/O in/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ./O 
There/O is/O no/O place/O for/O him/O in/O a/O khalasar/O ./O 
Illyrio/PERSON tried/O to/O warn/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O will/O go/O as/O soon/O as/O he/O has/O his/O ten/O thousand/O ./O 
My/O lord/O husband/O promised/O a/O golden/O crown/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O grunted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ,/O but/O .../O the/O Dothraki/LOCATION look/O on/O these/O things/O differently/O than/O we/O do/O in/O the/O west/O ./O 
I/O have/O told/O him/O as/O much/O ,/O as/O Illyrio/PERSON told/O him/O ,/O but/O your/O brother/O does/O not/O listen/O ./O 
The/O horselords/O are/O no/O traders/O ./O 
Viserys/PERSON thinks/O he/O sold/O you/O ,/O and/O now/O he/O wants/O his/O price/O ./O 
Yet/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON would/O say/O he/O had/O you/O as/O a/O gift/O ./O 
He/O will/O give/O Viserys/PERSON a/O gift/O in/O return/O ,/O yes/O .../O in/O his/O own/O time/O ./O 
You/O do/O not/O demand/O a/O gift/O ,/O not/O of/O a/O khal/O You/O do/O not/O demand/O anything/O of/O a/O khal/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O not/O right/O to/O make/O him/O wait/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON did/O not/O know/O why/O she/O was/O defending/O her/O brother/O ,/O yet/O she/O was/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON says/O he/O could/O sweep/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O with/O ten/O thousand/O Dothraki/O screamers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON snorted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Viserys/O could/O not/O sweep/O a/O stable/O with/O ten/O thousand/O brooms/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dany/PERSON could/O not/O pretend/O to/O surprise/O at/O the/O disdain/O in/O his/O tone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O .../O what/O if/O it/O were/O not/O Viserys/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O she/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O it/O were/O someone/O else/O who/O led/O them/O ?/O 
Someone/O stronger/O ?/O 
Could/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON truly/O conquer/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/O Jorah/O 's/O face/O grew/O thoughtful/O as/O their/O horses/O trod/O together/O down/O the/O godsway/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O first/O went/O into/O exile/O ,/O I/O looked/O at/O the/O Dothraki/LOCATION and/O saw/O half-naked/O barbarians/O ,/O as/O wild/O as/O their/O horses/O ./O 
If/O you/O had/O asked/O me/O then/O ,/O Princess/O ,/O I/O should/O have/O told/O you/O that/O a/O thousand/O good/O knights/O would/O have/O no/O trouble/O putting/O to/O flight/O a/O hundred/O times/O as/O many/O Dothraki/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O But/O if/O I/O asked/O you/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O knight/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O less/O certain/O ./O 
They/O are/O better/O riders/O than/O any/O knight/O ,/O utterly/O fearless/O ,/O and/O their/O bows/O outrange/O ours/O ./O 
In/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O most/O archers/O fight/O on/O foot/O ,/O from/O behind/O a/O shieldwall/O or/O a/O barricade/O of/O sharpened/O stakes/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/O fire/O from/O horseback/O ,/O charging/O or/O retreating/O ,/O it/O makes/O no/O matter/O ,/O they/O are/O full/O as/O deadly/O .../O and/O there/O are/O so/O many/O of/O them/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
Your/O lord/O husband/O alone/O counts/O forty/O thousand/O mounted/O warriors/O in/O his/O khalasar/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O that/O truly/O so/O many/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O Rhaegar/PERSON brought/O as/O many/O men/O to/O the/O Trident/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON admitted/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O of/O that/O number/O ,/O no/O more/O than/O a/O tenth/O were/O knights/O ./O 
The/O rest/O were/O archers/O ,/O freeriders/O ,/O and/O foot/O soldiers/O armed/O with/O spears/O and/O pikes/O ./O 
When/O Rhaegar/PERSON fell/O ,/O many/O threw/O down/O their/O weapons/O and/O fled/O the/O field/O ./O 
How/O long/O do/O you/O imagine/O such/O a/O rabble/O would/O stand/O against/O the/O charge/O of/O forty/O thousand/O screamers/O howling/O for/O blood/O ?/O 
How/O well/O would/O boiled/O leather/O jerkins/O and/O mailed/O shirts/O protect/O them/O when/O the/O arrows/O fall/O like/O rain/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O long/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O not/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mind/O you/O ,/O Princess/O ,/O if/O the/O lords/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O have/O the/O wit/O the/O gods/O gave/O a/O goose/O ,/O it/O will/O never/O come/O to/O that/O ./O 
The/O riders/O have/O no/O taste/O for/O siegecraft/O ./O 
I/O doubt/O they/O could/O take/O even/O the/O weakest/O castle/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O but/O if/O Robert/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON were/O fool/O enough/O to/O give/O them/O battle/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O he/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O fool/O ,/O I/O mean/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON considered/O that/O for/O a/O moment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Robert/PERSON should/O have/O been/O born/O Dothraki/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O at/O last/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O khal/O would/O tell/O you/O that/O only/O a/O coward/O hides/O behind/O stone/O walls/O instead/O of/O facing/O his/O enemy/O with/O a/O blade/O in/O hand/O ./O 
The/O Usurper/O would/O agree/O ./O 
He/O is/O a/O strong/O man/O ,/O brave/O .../O and/O rash/O enough/O to/O meet/O a/O Dothraki/O horde/O in/O the/O open/O field/O ./O 
But/O the/O men/O around/O him/O ,/O well/O ,/O their/O pipers/O play/O a/O different/O tune/O ./O 
His/O brother/O Stannis/PERSON ,/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON Lannister/PERSON ,/O Eddard/O Stark/O He/O spat/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O hate/O this/O Lord/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O took/O from/O me/O all/O I/O loved/O ,/O for/O the/O sake/O of/O a/O few/O lice-ridden/O poachers/O and/O his/O precious/O honor/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON said/O bitterly/O ./O 
From/O his/O tone/O ,/O she/O could/O tell/O the/O loss/O still/O pained/O him/O ./O 
He/O changed/O the/O subject/O quickly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O ,/O pointing/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON ./O 
The/O city/O of/O the/O horselords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON and/O his/O bloodriders/O led/O them/O through/O the/O great/O bazaar/O of/O the/O Western/O Market/O ,/O down/O the/O broad/O ways/O beyond/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON followed/O close/O on/O her/O silver/O ,/O staring/O at/O the/O strangeness/O about/O her/O ./O 
Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON was/O at/O once/O the/O largest/O city/O and/O the/O smallest/O that/O she/O had/O ever/O known/O ./O 
She/O thought/O it/O must/O be/O ten/O times/O as/O large/O as/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O vastness/O without/O walls/O or/O limits/O ,/O its/O broad/O windswept/O streets/O paved/O in/O grass/O and/O mud/O and/O carpeted/O with/O wildflowers/O ./O 
In/O the/O Free/O Cities/O of/O the/O west/O ,/O towers/O and/O manses/O and/O hovels/O and/O bridges/O and/O shops/O and/O halls/O all/O crowded/O in/O on/O one/O another/O ,/O but/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON sprawled/O languorously/O ,/O baking/O in/O the/O warm/O sun/O ,/O ancient/O ,/O arrogant/O ,/O and/O empty/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Even/O the/O buildings/O were/O so/O queer/O to/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O saw/O carved/O stone/O pavilions/O ,/O manses/O of/O woven/O grass/O as/O large/O as/O castles/O ,/O rickety/O wooden/O towers/O ,/O stepped/O pyramids/O faced/O with/O marble/O ,/O log/O halls/O ''/O ,/O ``/O open/O to/O the/O sky/O ./O 
In/O place/O of/O walls/O ,/O some/O palaces/O were/O surrounded/O by/O thorny/O hedges/O ./O 
\/O ``/O None/O of/O them/O are/O alike/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O brother/O had/O part/O of/O the/O truth/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jo/PERSON rah/O admitted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Dothraki/O do/O not/O build/O ./O 
A/O thousand/O years/O ago/O ,/O to/O make/O a/O house/O ,/O they/O would/O dig/O a/O hole/O in/O the/O earth/O and/O cover/O it/O with/O a/O woven/O grass/O roof/O ./O 
The/O buildings/O you/O see/O were/O made/O by/O slaves/O brought/O here/O from/O lands/O they/O 've/O plundered/O ,/O and/O they/O built/O each/O after/O the/O fashion/O of/O their/O own/O peoples/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Most/O of/O the/O halls/O ,/O even/O the/O largest/O ,/O seemed/O deserted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O are/O the/O people/O who/O live/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON asked/O ./O 
The/O bazaar/O had/O been/O full/O of/O running/O children/O and/O men/O shouting/O ,/O but/O elsewhere/O she/O had/O seen/O only/O a/O few/O eunuchs/O going/O about/O their/O business/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O dwell/O permanently/O in/O the/O sacred/O city/O ,/O them/O and/O their/O slaves/O and/O servants/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON is/O large/O enough/O to/O house/O every/O man/O of/O every/O khalasar/O ,/O should/O all/O the/O khals/O return/O to/O the/O Mother/O at/O once/O ./O 
The/O crones/O have/O prophesied/O that/O one/O day/O that/O will/O come/O to/O pass/O ,/O and/O so/O Vaes/PERSON Dothrak/PERSON must/O be/O ready/O to/O embrace/O all/O its/O children/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON finally/O called/O a/O halt/O near/O the/O Eastern/LOCATION Market/LOCATION where/O the/O caravans/O from/O Yi/PERSON Ti/PERSON and/O Asshai/PERSON and/O the/O Shadow/O Lands/O came/O to/O trade/O ,/O with/O the/O Mother/LOCATION of/LOCATION Mountains/LOCATION looming/O overhead/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON smiled/O as/O she/O recalled/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON 's/O slave/O girl/O and/O her/O talk/O of/O a/O palace/O with/O two/O hundred/O rooms/O and/O doors/O of/O solid/O silver/O ./O 
The/O \/O ``/O palace/O \/O ''/O was/O a/O cavernous/O wooden/O feasting/O hall/O ,/O its/O rough-hewn/O timbered/O walls/O rising/O forty/O feet/O ,/O its/O roof/O sewn/O silk/O ,/O a/O vast/O billowing/O tent/O that/O could/O be/O raised/O to/O keep/O out/O the/O rare/O rains/O ,/O or/O lowered/O to/O admit/O the/O endless/O sky/O ./O 
Around/O the/O hall/O were/O broad/O grassy/O horse/O yards/O fenced/O with/O high/O hedges/O ,/O firepits/O ,/O and/O hundreds/O of/O round/O earthen/O houses/O that/O bulged/O from/O the/O ground/O like/O miniature/O hills/O ,/O covered/O with/O grass/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O small/O army/O of/O slaves/O had/O gone/O ahead/O to/O prepare/O for/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON 's/O arrival/O ./O 
As/O each/O rider/O swung/O down/O from/O his/O saddle/O ,/O he/O unbelted/O his/O arakh/O and/O handed/O it/O to/O a/O waiting/O slave/O ,/O and/O any/O other/O weapons/O he/O carried/O as/O well/O ./O 
Even/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON himself/O was/O not/O exempt/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON had/O explained/O that/O it/O was/O forbidden/O to/O carry/O a/O blade/O in/O Vaes/O Dothrak/O ,/O or/O to/O shed/O a/O free/O man/O 's/O blood/O ./O 
Even/O warring/O khalasars/O put/O aside/O their/O feuds/O and/O shared/O meat/O and/O mead/O together/O when/O they/O were/O in/O sight/O of/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION ./O 
In/O this/O place/O ,/O the/O crones/O of/O the/O dosh/O khaleen/O had/O decreed/O ,/O all/O Dothraki/PERSON were/O one/O blood/O ,/O one/O khalasar/O ,/O one/O herd/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Cohollo/O came/O to/O Dany/PERSON as/O Irri/PERSON and/O Jhiqui/PERSON were/O helping/O her/O down/O off/O her/O silver/O ./O 
He/O was/O the/O oldest/O of/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O three/O bloodriders/O ,/O a/O squat/O bald/O man/O with/O a/O crooked/O nose/O and/O a/O mouth/O full/O of/O broken/O teeth/O ,/O shattered/O by/O a/O mace/O twenty/O years/O before/O when/O he/O saved/O the/O young/O khalakka/O from/O sellswords/O who/O hoped/O to/O sell/O him/O to/O his/O father/O 's/O enemies/O ./O 
His/O life/O had/O been/O bound/O to/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O the/O day/O her/O lord/O husband/O was/O born/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Every/O khal/O had/O his/O bloodriders/O ./O 
At/O first/O Dany/PERSON had/O thought/O of/O them/O as/O a/O kind/O of/O Dothraki/PERSON Kingsguard/PERSON ,/O sworn/O to/O protect/O their/O lord/O ,/O but/O it/O went/O further/O than/O that/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON had/O taught/O her/O that/O a/O bloodrider/O was/O more/O than/O a/O guard/O ;/O they/O were/O the/O khal/O 's/O brothers/O ,/O his/O shadows/O ,/O his/O fiercest/O friends/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O \/O ''/O Drogo/PERSON called/O them/O ,/O and/O so/O it/O was/O ;/O they/O shared/O a/O single/O life/O ./O 
The/O ancient/O traditions/O of/O the/O horselords/O demanded/O that/O when/O the/O khal/O died/O ,/O his/O bloodriders/O died/O with/O him/O ,/O to/O ride/O at/O his/O side/O in/O the/O night/O lands/O ./O 
If/O the/O khal/O died/O at/O the/O hands/O of/O some/O enemy/O ,/O they/O lived/O only/O long/O enough/O to/O avenge/O him/O ,/O and/O then/O followed/O him/O joyfully/O into/O the/O grave/O ./O 
In/O some/O ''/O ,/O ``/O khalasars/O ,/O Jhiqui/PERSON said/O ,/O the/O bloodriders/O shared/O the/O khal/O 's/O wine/O ,/O his/O tent/O ,/O and/O even/O his/O wives/O ,/O though/O never/O his/O horses/O ./O 
A/O man/O 's/O mount/O was/O his/O own/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Daenerys/PERSON was/O glad/O that/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON did/O not/O hold/O to/O those/O ancient/O ways/O ./O 
She/O should/O not/O have/O liked/O being/O shared/O ./O 
And/O while/O old/O Cohollo/PERSON treated/O her/O kindly/O enough/O ,/O the/O others/O frightened/O her/O ;/O Haggo/PERSON ,/O huge/O and/O silent/O ,/O often/O glowered/O as/O if/O he/O had/O forgotten/O who/O she/O was/O ,/O and/O Qotho/PERSON had/O cruel/O eyes/O and/O quick/O hands/O that/O liked/O to/O hurt/O ./O 
He/O left/O bruises/O on/O Doreah/PERSON 's/O soft/O white/O skin/O whenever/O he/O touched/O her/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O made/O Irri/ORGANIZATION sob/O in/O the/O night/O ./O 
Even/O his/O horses/O seemed/O to/O fear/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Yet/O they/O were/O bound/O to/O Drogo/PERSON for/O life/O and/O death/O ,/O so/O Daenerys/PERSON had/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O accept/O them/O ./O 
And/O sometimes/O she/O found/O herself/O wishing/O her/O father/O had/O been/O protected/O by/O such/O men/O ./O 
In/O the/O songs/O ,/O the/O white/O knights/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O were/O ever/O noble/O ,/O valiant/O ,/O and/O true/O ,/O and/O yet/O King/O Aerys/PERSON had/O been/O murdered/O by/O one/O of/O them/O ,/O the/O handsome/O boy/O they/O now/O called/O the/O Kingslayer/O ,/O and/O a/O second/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON the/PERSON Bold/PERSON ,/O had/O gone/O over/O to/O the/O Usurper/O ./O 
She/O wondered/O if/O all/O men/O were/O as/O false/O in/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ./O 
When/O her/O son/O sat/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O ,/O she/O would/O see/O that/O he/O had/O bloodriders/O of/O his/O own/O to/O protect/O him/O against/O treachery/O in/O his/O Kingsguard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O \/O ''/O Cohollo/PERSON said/O to/O her/O ,/O in/O Dothraki/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Drogo/PERSON ,/O who/O is/O blood/O of/O my/O blood/O ,/O commands/O me/O to/O tell/O you/O that/O he/O must/O ascend/O the/O Mother/O of/O Mountains/LOCATION this/O night/O ,/O to/O sacrifice/O to/O the/O gods/O for/O his/O safe/O return/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Only/O men/O were/O allowed/O to/O set/O foot/O on/O the/O Mother/O ,/O Dany/PERSON knew/O ./O 
The/O khal/O 's/O bloodriders/O would/O go/O with/O him/O ,/O and/O return/O at/O dawn/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O my/O sun-and-stars/O that/O I/O dream/O of/O him/O ,/O and/O wait/O anxious/O for/O his/O return/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O replied/O ,/O thankful/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON tired/O more/O easily/O as/O the/O child/O grew/O within/O her/O ;/O in/O truth/O ,/O a/O night/O of/O rest/O would/O be/O most/O welcome/O ./O 
Her/O pregnancy/O only/O seemed/O to/O have/O inflamed/O Drogo/PERSON 's/O desire/O for/O her/O ,/O and/O of/O late/O his/O embraces/O left/O her/O exhausted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Doreah/PERSON led/O her/O to/O the/O hollow/O hill/O that/O had/O been/O prepared/O for/O her/O and/O her/O khal/O ./O 
It/O was/O cool/O and/O dim/O within/O ,/O like/O a/O tent/O made/O of/O earth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jhiqui/O ,/O a/O bath/O ,/O please/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O commanded/O ,/O to/O wash/O the/O dust/O of/O travel/O from/O her/O skin/O and/O soak/O her/O weary/O bones/O ./O 
It/O was/O pleasant/O to/O know/O that/O they/O would/O linger/O here/O for/O a/O while/O ,/O that/O she/O would/O not/O need/O to/O climb/O back/O on/O her/O silver/O on/O the/O morrow/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O water/O was/O scalding/O hot/O ,/O as/O she/O liked/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O give/O my/O brother/O his/O gifts/O tonight/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O decided/O as/O Jhiqui/PERSON was/O washing/O her/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O should/O look/O a/O king/O in/O the/O sacred/O city/O ./O 
Doreah/PERSON ,/O run/O and/O find/O him/O and/O invite/O him/O to/O sup/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Viserys/PERSON was/O nicer/O to/O the/O Lysene/O girl/O than/O to/O her/O Dothraki/O handmaids/O ,/O perhaps/O because/O Magister/PERSON Illyrio/PERSON had/O let/O him/O bed/O her/O back/O in/O Pentos/ORGANIZATION ./O 
\/O ``/O Irri/O ,/O go/O to/O the/O bazaar/O and/O buy/O fruit/O and/O meat/O ./O 
Anything/O but/O horseflesh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Horse/O is/O best/O ,/O \/O ''/O Irri/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Horse/O makes/O a/O man/O strong/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Viserys/O hates/O horsemeat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Khaleesi/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O brought/O back/O a/O haunch/O of/O goat/O and/O a/O basket/O of/O fruits/O and/O vegetables/O ./O 
Jhiqui/PERSON roasted/O the/O meat/O with/O sweetgrass/O and/O firepods/O ,/O basting/O it/O with/O honey/O as/O it/O cooked/O ,/O and/O there/O were/O melons/O and/O pomegranates/O and/O plums/O and/O some/O queer/O eastern/O fruit/O Dany/PERSON did/O not/O know/O ./O 
While/O her/O handmaids/O prepared/O the/O meal/O ,/O Dany/PERSON laid/O out/O the/O clothing/O she/O 'd/O had/O made/O to/O her/O brother/O 's/O measure/O :/O a/O tunic/O and/O leggings/O of/O crisp/O white/O linen/O ,/O leather/O sandals/O that/O laced/O up/O to/O the/O knee/O ,/O a/O bronze/O medallion/O belt/O ,/O a/O leather/O vest/O painted/O with/O fire-breathing/O dragons/O ./O 
The/O Dothraki/PERSON would/O respect/O him/O more/O if/O ''/O ,/O ``/O he/O looked/O less/O a/O beggar/O ,/O she/O hoped/O ,/O and/O perhaps/O he/O would/O forgive/O her/O for/O shaming/O him/O that/O day/O in/O the/O grass/O ./O 
He/O was/O still/O her/O king/O ,/O after/O all/O ,/O and/O her/O brother/O ./O 
They/O were/O both/O blood/O of/O the/O dragon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O was/O arranging/O the/O last/O of/O his/O gifts-a/O sandsilk/O cloak/O ,/O green/O as/O grass/O ,/O with/O a/O pale/O grey/O border/O that/O would/O bring/O out/O the/O silver/O in/O his/O hair/O -/O when/O Viserys/PERSON arrived/O ,/O dragging/O Doreah/PERSON by/O the/O arm/O ./O 
Her/O eye/O was/O red/O where/O he/O 'd/O hit/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O dare/O you/O send/O this/O whore/O to/O give/O me/O commands/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O shoved/O the/O handmaid/O roughly/O to/O the/O carpet/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O anger/O took/O Dany/PERSON utterly/O by/O surprise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O only/O wanted/O .../O Doreah/O ,/O what/O did/O you/O say/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Khaleesi/O ,/O pardons/O ,/O forgive/O me/O ./O 
I/O went/O to/O him/O ,/O as/O you/O bid/O ,/O and/O told/O him/O you/O commanded/O him/O to/O join/O you/O for/O supper/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O one/O commands/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Viserys/O snarled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O your/O king/O !/O 
I/O should/O have/O sent/O you/O back/O her/O head/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Lysene/O girl/O quailed/O ,/O but/O Dany/PERSON calmed/O her/O with/O a/O touch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O afraid/O ,/O he/O wo/O n't/O hurt/O you/O ./O 
Sweet/O brother/O ,/O please/O ,/O forgive/O her/O ,/O the/O girl/O misspoke/O herself/O ,/O I/O told/O her/O to/O ask/O you/O to/O sup/O with/O me/O ,/O if/O it/O pleases/O Your/O Grace/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O took/O him/O by/O the/O hand/O and/O drew/O him/O across/O the/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Look/O ./O 
These/O are/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/O frowned/O suspiciously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O is/O all/O this/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O New/O raiment/O ./O 
I/O had/O it/O made/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Dany/PERSON smiled/O shyly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O looked/O at/O her/O and/O sneered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Dothraki/O rags/O ./O 
Do/O you/O presume/O to/O dress/O me/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Please/O .../O you/O 'll/O be/O cooler/O and/O more/O comfortable/O ,/O and/O I/O thought/O .../O maybe/O if/O you/O dressed/O like/O them/O ,/O the/O Dothraki/PERSON Dany/PERSON did/O not/O know/O how/O to/O say/O it/O without/O waking/O his/O dragon/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Next/O you/O 'll/O want/O to/O braid/O my/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O never/O .../O \/O ''/O Why/O was/O he/O always/O so/O cruel/O ?/O 
She/O had/O only/O wanted/O to/O help/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O no/O right/O to/O a/O braid/O ,/O you/O have/O won/O no/O victories/O yet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O wrong/O thing/O to/O say/O ./O 
Fury/O shone/O from/O his/O lilac/O eyes/O ,/O yet/O he/O dared/O not/O strike/O her/O ,/O not/O with/O her/O handmaids/O watching/O and/O the/O warriors/O of/O her/O khas/O outside/O ./O 
Viserys/O picked/O up/O the/O cloak/O and/O sniffed/O at/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O stinks/O of/O manure/O ./O 
Perhaps/O I/O shall/O use/O it/O as/O a/O horse/O blanket/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O had/O Doreah/O sew/O it/O specially/O for/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O him/O ,/O wounded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O These/O are/O garments/O fit/O for/O a/O khal/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Seven/O Kingdoms/O ,/O not/O some/O grass-stained/O savage/O with/O bells/O in/O his/O hair/O ,/O \/O ''/O Viserys/O spat/O back/O at/O her/O ./O 
He/O grabbed/O her/O arm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O forget/O yourself/O ,/O slut/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O that/O big/O belly/O will/O protect/O you/O if/O you/O wake/O the/O dragon/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O His/O fingers/O dug/O into/O her/O arm/O painfully/O and/O for/O an/O instant/O Dany/PERSON felt/O like/O a/O child/O again/O ,/O quailing/O in/O the/O face/O of/O his/O rage/O ./O 
She/O reached/O out/O with/O her/O other/O hand/O and/O grabbed/O the/O first/O thing/O she/O touched/O ,/O the/O belt/O she/O 'd/O hoped/O to/O give/O him/O ,/O a/O heavy/O chain/O of/O ornate/O bronze/O medallions/O ./O 
She/O swung/O it/O with/O all/O her/O strength/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O caught/O him/O full/O in/O the/O face/O ./O 
Viserys/O let/O go/O of/O her/O ./O 
Blood/O ran/O down/O his/O cheek/O where/O the/O edge/O of/O one/O of/O the/O medallions/O had/O sliced/O it/O open/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O one/O who/O forgets/O himself/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O n't/O you/O learn/O anything/O that/O day/O in/O the/O grass/O ?/O 
Leave/O me/O now/O ,/O before/O I/O summon/O my/O khas/O to/O drag/O you/O out/O ./O 
And/O pray/O that/O Khal/PERSON Drogo/PERSON does/O not/O hear/O of/O this/O ,/O or/O he/O will/O cut/O open/O your/O belly/O and/O feed/O you/O your/O own/O entrails/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Viserys/PERSON scrambled/O back/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O come/O into/O my/O kingdom/O ,/O you/O will/O rue/O this/O day/O ,/O slut/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O off/O ,/O holding/O his/O torn/O face/O ,/O leaving/O her/O gifts/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Drops/O of/O his/O blood/O had/O spattered/O the/O beautiful/O sandsilk/O cloak/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON clutched/O the/O soft/O cloth/O to/O her/O cheek/O and/O sat/O cross-legged/O on/O her/O sleeping/O mats/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O supper/O is/O ready/O ,/O Khaleesi/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Jhiqui/PERSON announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O hungry/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON said/O sadly/O ./O 
She/O was/O suddenly/O very/O tired/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Share/O the/O food/O among/O yourselves/O ,/O and/O send/O some/O to/O Ser/PERSON Jorah/PERSON ,/O if/O you/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O After/O a/O moment/O she/O added/O ,/O \/O ``/O Please/O ,/O bring/O me/O one/O of/O the/O dragon/O 's/O eggs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Irri/ORGANIZATION fetched/O the/O egg/O with/O the/O deep/O green/O shell/O ,/O bronze/O flecks/O shining/O amid/O its/O scales/O as/O she/O turned/O it/O in/O her/O small/O hands/O ./O 
Dany/PERSON curled/O up/O on/O her/O side/O ,/O pulling/O the/O sandsilk/O cloak/O across/O her/O and/O cradling/O the/O egg/O in/O the/O hollow/O between/O her/O swollen/O belly/O and/O small/O ,/O tender/O breasts/O ./O 
She/O liked/O to/O hold/O them/O ./O 
They/O were/O so/O beautiful/O ,/O and/O sometimes/O just/O being/O close/O to/O them/O made/O her/O feel/O stronger/O ,/O braver/O ,/O as/O if/O somehow/O she/O were/O drawing/O strength/O from/O the/O stone/O dragons/O locked/O inside/O ./O 
She/O was/O lying/O there/O ,/O holding/O the/O egg/O ,/O when/O she/O felt/O the/O child/O move/O within/O her/O .../O as/O if/O he/O were/O reaching/O out/O ,/O brother/O to/O brother/O ,/O blood/O to/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O dragon/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dany/PERSON whispered/O to/O him/O ,/O \/O ``/O the/O true/O dragon/O ./O 
I/O know/O it/O ./O 
I/O know/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O she/O smiled/O ,/O and/O went/O to/O sleep/O dreaming/O of/O home/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
