-LSB-/O ``/O EDDARD/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Eddard/O Stark/O rode/O through/O the/O towering/O bronze/O doors/O of/O the/O Red/O Keep/O sore/O ,/O tired/O ,/O hungry/O ,/O and/O irritable/O ./O 
He/O was/O still/O a/O horse/O ,/O dreaming/O of/O a/O long/O hot/O soak/O ,/O a/O roast/O fowl/O ,/O and/O a/O featherbed/O ,/O when/O the/O king/O 's/O steward/O told/O him/O that/O Grand/O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON had/O convened/O an/O urgent/O meeting/O of/O the/O small/O council/O ./O 
The/O honor/O of/O the/O Hand/O 's/O presence/O was/O requested/O as/O soon/O as/O it/O was/O convenient/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O convenient/O on/O the/O morrow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON snapped/O as/O he/O dismounted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O steward/O bowed/O very/O low/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O shall/O give/O the/O councillors/O your/O regrets/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O damn/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O do/O to/O offend/O the/O council/O before/O he/O had/O even/O begun/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O see/O them/O ./O 
Pray/O give/O me/O a/O few/O moments/O to/O change/O into/O something/O more/O presentable/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O steward/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O given/O you/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON 's/O former/O chambers/O in/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O ,/O if/O it/O please/O you/O ./O 
I/O shall/O have/O your/O things/O taken/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O thanks/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O as/O he/O ripped/O off/O his/O riding/O gloves/O and/O tucked/O them/O into/O his/O belt/O ./O 
The/O rest/O of/O his/O household/O was/O coming/O through/O the/O gate/O behind/O him/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON saw/O Vayon/PERSON Poole/PERSON ,/O his/O own/O steward/O ,/O and/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O seems/O the/O council/O has/O urgent/O need/O of/O me/O ./O 
See/O that/O my/O daughters/O find/O their/O bedchambers/O ,/O and/O tell/O Jory/PERSON to/O keep/O them/O there/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON is/O not/O to/O go/O exploring/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Poole/PERSON bowed/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O the/O royal/O steward/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O wagons/O are/O still/O straggling/O through/O the/O city/O ./O 
I/O shall/O need/O appropriate/O garments/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O be/O my/O great/O pleasure/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O steward/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O so/O Ned/PERSON had/O come/O striding/O into/O the/O council/O chambers/O ,/O bonetired/O and/O dressed/O in/O borrowed/O clothing/O ,/O to/O find/O four/O members/O of/O the/O small/O council/O waiting/O for/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O chamber/O was/O richly/O furnished/O ./O 
Myrish/O carpets/O covered/O the/O floor/O instead/O of/O rushes/O ,/O and/O in/O one/O corner/O a/O hundred/O fabulous/O beasts/O cavorted/O in/O bright/O paints/O on/O a/O carved/O screen/O from/O the/O Summer/LOCATION Isles/LOCATION ./O 
The/O walls/O were/O hung/O with/O tapestries/O from/O Norvos/LOCATION and/O Qohor/O and/O Lys/PERSON ,/O and/O a/O pair/O of/O Valyrian/O sphinxes/O flanked/O the/O door/O ,/O eyes/O of/O polished/O garnet/O smoldering/O in/O black/O marble/O faces/O ./O 
The/O councillor/O Ned/PERSON liked/O least/O ,/O the/O eunuch/O Varys/PERSON ,/O accosted/O him/O the/O moment/O he/O entered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ,/O I/O was/O grievous/O sad/O to/O hear/O about/O your/O troubles/O on/O the/O kingsroad/O ./O 
We/O have/O all/O been/O visiting/O the/O sept/O to/O light/O candles/O for/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ./O 
I/O pray/O for/O his/O recovery/O ./O 
\/O ''/O His/O hand/O left/O powder/O stains/O on/O Ned/PERSON 's/O sleeve/O ,/O and/O he/O smelled/O as/O foul/O and/O sweet/O as/O flowers/O on/O a/O grave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O gods/O have/O heard/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O ,/O cool/O yet/O polite/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O prince/O grows/O stronger/O every/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O disentangled/O himself/O from/O the/O eunuch/O 's/O grip/O and/O crossed/O the/O room/O to/O where/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON stood/O by/O the/O screen/O ,/O talking/O quietly/O with/O a/O short/O man/O who/O could/O only/O be/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
Renly/PERSON had/O been/O a/O boy/O of/O eight/O when/O Robert/PERSON won/O the/O throne/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O grown/O into/O a/O man/O so/O like/O his/O brother/O that/O Ned/PERSON found/O it/O disconcerting/O ./O 
Whenever/O he/O saw/O him/O ,/O it/O was/O as/O if/O the/O years/O had/O slipped/O away/O and/O Robert/PERSON stood/O before/O him/O ,/O fresh/O from/O his/O victory/O on/O the/O Trident/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O see/O you/O have/O arrived/O safely/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Renly/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O you/O as/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O must/O forgive/O me/O ,/O but/O sometimes/O you/O look/O the/O very/O image/O of/O your/O brother/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O poor/O copy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Renly/PERSON said/O with/O a/O shrug/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Though/O much/O better/O dressed/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON quipped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON spends/O more/O on/O clothing/O than/O half/O the/O ladies/O of/O the/O court/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O true/O enough/O ./O 
Lord/O Renly/PERSON was/O in/O dark/O green/O velvet/O ,/O with/O a/O dozen/O golden/O stags/O embroidered/O on/O his/O doublet/O ./O 
A/O cloth-of-gold/O half/O cape/O was/O draped/O casually/O across/O one/O shoulder/O ,/O fastened/O with/O an/O emerald/O brooch/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O are/O worse/O crimes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Renly/PERSON said/O with/O a/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O way/O you/O dress/O ,/O for/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON ignored/O the/O jibe/O ./O 
He/O eyed/O Ned/PERSON with/O a/O smile/O on/O his/O lips/O that/O bordered/O on/O insolence/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O hoped/O to/O meet/O you/O for/O some/O years/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON has/O mentioned/O me/O to/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O has/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O chill/O in/O his/O voice/O ./O 
The/O sly/O arrogance/O of/O the/O comment/O rankled/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O understand/O you/O knew/O my/O brother/O Brandon/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Renly/O Baratheon/O laughed/O ./O 
Varys/PERSON shuffled/O over/O to/O listen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rather/O too/O well/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O still/O carry/O a/O token/O of/O his/O esteem/O ./O 
Did/O Brandon/PERSON speak/O of/O me/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Often/O ,/O and/O with/O some/O heat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ,/O hoping/O that/O would/O end/O it/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O patience/O with/O this/O game/O they/O played/O ,/O this/O dueling/O with/O words/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O should/O have/O thought/O that/O heat/O ill/O suits/O you/O Starks/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O in/O the/O south/O ,/O they/O say/O you/O are/O all/O made/O of/O ice/O ,/O and/O melt/O when/O you/O ride/O below/O the/O Neck/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O plan/O on/O melting/O soon/O ,/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ./O 
You/O may/O count/O on/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON moved/O to/O the/O council/O table/O and/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Maester/O Pycelle/O ,/O I/O trust/O you/O are/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O Grand/O Maester/O smiled/O gently/O from/O his/O tall/O chair/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O enough/O for/O a/O man/O of/O my/O years/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O yet/O I/O do/O tire/O easily/O ,/O I/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Wispy/O strands/O of/O white/O hair/O fringed/O the/O broad/O bald/O dome/O of/O his/O forehead/O above/O a/O kindly/O face/O ./O 
His/O maester/O 's/O collar/O was/O no/O simple/O metal/O choker/O such/O as/O Luwin/PERSON wore/O ,/O but/O two/O dozen/O heavy/O chains/O wound/O together/O into/O a/O ponderous/O metal/O necklace/O that/O covered/O him/O from/O throat/O to/O breast/O ./O 
The/O links/O were/O forged/O of/O every/O metal/O known/O to/O man/O :/O black/O iron/O and/O red/O gold/O ,/O bright/O copper/O and/O dull/O lead/O ,/O steel/O and/O tin/O and/O pale/O silver/O ,/O brass/O and/O bronze/O and/O platinum/O ./O 
Garnets/O and/O amethysts/O and/O black/O pearls/O adorned/O the/O metalwork/O ,/O and/O here/O and/O there/O an/O emerald/O or/O ruby/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O we/O might/O begin/O soon/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION said/O ,/O hands/O knitting/O together/O atop/O his/O broad/O stomach/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O I/O shall/O fall/O asleep/O if/O we/O wait/O much/O longer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O king/O 's/O seat/O sat/O empty/O at/O the/O head/O of/O the/O table/O ,/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O Baratheon/LOCATION embroidered/O in/O gold/O thread/O on/O its/O pillows/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON took/O the/O chair/O beside/O it/O ,/O as/O the/O right/O hand/O of/O his/O king/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O formally/O ,/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O sorry/O to/O have/O kept/O you/O waiting/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O serve/O at/O your/O pleasure/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O the/O others/O took/O their/O accustomed/O seats/O ,/O it/O struck/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON forcefully/O that/O he/O did/O not/O belong/O here/O ,/O in/O this/O room/O ,/O with/O these/O men/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O what/O Robert/PERSON had/O told/O him/O in/O the/O crypts/O below/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
I/O am/O surrounded/O by/O flatterers/O and/O fools/O ,/O the/O king/O had/O insisted/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON looked/O down/O the/O council/O table/O and/O wondered/O which/O were/O the/O flatterers/O and/O which/O the/O fools/O ./O 
He/O thought/O he/O knew/O already/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O are/O but/O five/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O pointed/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lord/O Stannis/PERSON took/O himself/O to/O Dragonstone/O not/O long/O after/O the/O king/O went/O north/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O our/O gallant/O Ser/O Barristan/O no/O doubt/O rides/O beside/O the/O king/O as/O he/O makes/O his/O way/O through/O the/O city/O ,/O as/O befits/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Kingsguard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Perhaps/O we/O had/O best/O wait/O for/O Ser/PERSON Barristan/PERSON and/O the/O king/O to/O join/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON suggested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Renly/O Baratheon/O laughed/O aloud/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O we/O wait/O for/O my/O brother/O to/O grace/O us/O with/O his/O royal/O presence/O ,/O it/O could/O be/O a/O long/O sit/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Our/O good/O King/O Robert/PERSON has/O many/O cares/O ,/O \/O ''/O Varys/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O entrusts/O some/O small/O matters/O to/O us/O ,/O to/O lighten/O his/O load/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O Lord/O Varys/PERSON means/O is/O that/O all/O this/O business/O of/O coin/O and/O crops/O and/O justice/O bores/O my/O royal/O brother/O to/O tears/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O so/O it/O falls/O to/O us/O to/O govern/O the/O realm/O ./O 
He/O does/O send/O us/O a/O command/O from/O time/O to/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O drew/O a/O tightly/O rolled/O paper/O from/O his/O sleeve/O and/O laid/O it/O on/O the/O table/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O morning/O he/O commanded/O me/O to/O ride/O ahead/O with/O all/O haste/O and/O ask/O Grand/LOCATION Maester/LOCATION Pycelle/LOCATION to/O convene/O this/O council/O at/O once/O ./O 
He/O has/O an/O urgent/O task/O for/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON smiled/O and/O handed/O the/O paper/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
It/O bore/O the/O royal/O seal/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON broke/O the/O wax/O with/O his/O thumb/O and/O flattened/O the/O letter/O to/O consider/O the/O king/O 's/O urgent/O command/O ,/O reading/O the/O words/O with/O mounting/O disbelief/O ./O 
Was/O there/O no/O end/O to/O Robert/PERSON 's/O folly/O ?/O 
And/O to/O do/O this/O in/O his/O name/O ,/O that/O was/O salt/O in/O the/O wound/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O be/O good/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O swore/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON means/O to/O say/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON announced/O ,/O \/O ``/O is/O that/O His/O Grace/O instructs/O us/O to/O stage/O a/O great/O tournament/O in/O honor/O of/O his/O appointment/O as/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O How/O much/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O mildly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O read/O the/O answer/O off/O the/O letter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Forty/O thousand/O golden/O dragons/O to/O the/O champion/O ./O 
Twenty/O thousand/O to/O the/O man/O who/O comes/O second/O ,/O another/O twenty/O to/O the/O winner/O of/O the/O melee/O ,/O and/O ten/O thousand/O to/O the/O victor/O of/O the/O archery/O competition/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ninety/O thousand/O gold/O pieces/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O we/O must/O not/O neglect/O the/O other/O costs/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON will/O want/O a/O prodigious/O feast/O ./O 
That/O means/O cooks/O ,/O carpenters/O ,/O serving/O girls/O ,/O singers/O ,/O jugglers/O ,/O fools/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fools/O we/O have/O in/O plenty/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O looked/O to/O Littlefinger/PERSON and/O asked/O ,/O \/O ``/O Will/O the/O treasury/O bear/O the/O expense/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O treasury/O is/O that/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON replied/O with/O a/O twist/O of/O his/O mouth/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Spare/O me/O the/O foolishness/O ,/O Maester/O ./O 
You/O know/O as/O well/O as/O I/O that/O the/O treasury/O has/O been/O empty/O for/O years/O ./O 
I/O shall/O have/O to/O borrow/O the/O money/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O the/O Lannisters/O will/O be/O accommodating/O ./O 
We/O owe/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON some/O three/O million/O dragons/O at/O present/O ,/O what/O matter/O another/O hundred/O thousand/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O was/O stunned/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O claiming/O that/O the/O Crown/O is/O three/O million/O gold/O pieces/O in/O debt/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Crown/O is/O more/O than/O six/O million/O gold/O pieces/O in/O debt/O ,/O Lord/O Stark/O ./O 
The/O Lannisters/O are/O the/O biggest/O part/O of/O it/O ,/O but/O we/O have/O also/O borrowed/O from/O Lord/O Tyrell/PERSON ,/O the/O Iron/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Braavos/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O several/O Tyroshi/O trading/O cartels/O ./O 
Of/O late/O I/O 've/O had/O to/O turn/O to/O the/O Faith/O ./O 
The/O High/O Septon/O haggles/O worse/O than/O a/O Dornish/O fishmonger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O was/O aghast/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON left/O a/O treasury/O flowing/O with/O gold/O ./O 
How/O could/O you/O let/O this/O happen/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Little/O finger/O gave/O a/O shrug/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O master/O of/O coin/O finds/O the/O money/O ./O 
The/O king/O and/O the/O Hand/O spend/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O believe/O that/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON allowed/O Robert/PERSON to/O beggar/O the/O realm/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O hotly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Grand/O Maester/O Pycelle/O shook/O his/O great/O bald/O head/O ,/O his/O chains/O clinking/O softly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON was/O a/O prudent/O man/O ,/O but/O I/O fear/O that/O His/O Grace/O does/O not/O always/O listen/O to/O wise/O counsel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O royal/O brother/O loves/O tournaments/O and/O feasts/O ,/O \/O ''/O Renly/PERSON Baratheon/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O and/O he/O loathes/O what/O he/O calls/O `/O counting/O coppers/O ./O '/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O will/O speak/O with/O His/O Grace/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O tourney/O is/O an/O extravagance/O the/O realm/O can/O not/O afford/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Speak/O to/O him/O as/O you/O will/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Renly/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O we/O had/O still/O best/O make/O our/O plans/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Another/O day/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
Perhaps/O too/O sharply/O ,/O from/O the/O looks/O they/O gave/O him/O ./O 
He/O would/O have/O to/O remember/O that/O he/O was/O no/O longer/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O where/O only/O the/O king/O stood/O higher/O ;/O here/O ,/O he/O was/O but/O first/O among/O equals/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Forgive/O me/O ,/O my/O lords/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O softer/O tone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O tired/O ./O 
Let/O us/O call/O a/O halt/O for/O today/O and/O resume/O when/O we/O are/O fresher/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O did/O not/O ask/O for/O their/O consent/O ,/O but/O stood/O abruptly/O ,/O nodded/O at/O them/O all/O ,/O and/O made/O for/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Outside/O ,/O wagons/O and/O riders/O were/O still/O pouring/O through/O the/O castle/O gates/O ,/O and/O the/O yard/O was/O a/O chaos/O of/O mud/O and/O horseflesh/O and/O shouting/O men/O ./O 
The/O king/O had/O not/O yet/O arrived/O ,/O he/O was/O told/O ./O 
Since/O the/O ugliness/O on/O the/O Trident/O ,/O the/O Starks/PERSON and/O their/O household/O had/O ridden/O well/O ahead/O of/O the/O main/O column/O ,/O the/O better/O to/O separate/O themselves/O from/O the/O Lannisters/O and/O the/O growing/O tension/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON had/O hardly/O been/O seen/O ;/O the/O talk/O was/O he/O was/O traveling/O in/O the/O huge/O wheelhouse/O ,/O drunk/O as/O often/O as/O not/O ./O 
If/O so/O ,/O he/O might/O be/O hours/O behind/O ,/O but/O he/O would/O still/O be/O here/O too/O soon/O for/O Ned/PERSON 's/O liking/O ./O 
He/O had/O only/O to/O look/O at/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O face/O to/O feel/O the/O rage/O twisting/O inside/O him/O once/O again/O ./O 
The/O last/O fortnight/O of/O their/O journey/O had/O been/O a/O misery/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON blamed/O Arya/PERSON and/O told/O her/O that/O it/O should/O have/O been/O Nymeria/PERSON who/O died/O ./O 
And/O Arya/PERSON was/O lost/O after/O she/O heard/O what/O had/O happened/O to/O her/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON cried/O herself/O to/O sleep/O ,/O Arya/PERSON brooded/O silently/O all/O day/O long/O ,/O and/O Eddard/O Stark/O dreamed/O of/O a/O frozen/O hell/O reserved/O for/O the/O Starks/PERSON of/O Winterfell/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O crossed/O the/O outer/O yard/O ,/O passed/O under/O a/O portcullis/O into/O the/O inner/O bailey/O ,/O and/O was/O walking/O toward/O what/O he/O thought/O was/O the/O Tower/O of/O the/O Hand/O when/O Little/O finger/O appeared/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O going/O the/O wrong/O way/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
Come/O with/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Hesitantly/O ,/O Ned/PERSON followed/O ./O 
Littlefinger/PERSON led/O him/O into/O a/O tower/O ,/O down/O a/O stair/O ,/O across/O a/O small/O sunken/O courtyard/O ,/O and/O along/O a/O deserted/O corridor/O where/O empty/O suits/O of/O armor/O stood/O sentinel/O along/O the/O walls/O ./O 
They/O were/O relics/O of/O the/O Targaryens/O ,/O black/O steel/O with/O dragon/O scales/O cresting/O their/O helms/O ,/O now/O dusty/O and/O forgotten/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O not/O the/O way/O to/O my/O chambers/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Did/O I/O say/O it/O was/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O leading/O you/O to/O the/O dungeons/O to/O slit/O your/O throat/O and/O seal/O your/O corpse/O up/O behind/O a/O wall/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON replied/O ,/O his/O voice/O dripping/O with/O sarcasm/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O no/O time/O for/O this/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
Your/O wife/O awaits/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O game/O are/O you/O playing/O ,/O Littlefinger/PERSON ?/O 
Catelyn/O is/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O hundreds/O of/O leagues/O from/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON 's/O grey-green/O eyes/O glittered/O with/O amusement/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O it/O appears/O someone/O has/O managed/O an/O astonishing/O impersonation/O ./O 
For/O the/O last/O time/O ,/O come/O ./O 
Or/O do/O n't/O come/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O keep/O her/O for/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O hurried/O down/O the/O steps/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON followed/O him/O warily/O ,/O wondering/O if/O this/O day/O would/O ever/O end/O ./O 
He/O had/O no/O taste/O for/O these/O intrigues/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O beginning/O to/O realize/O that/O they/O were/O meat/O and/O mead/O to/O a/O man/O like/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O At/O the/O foot/O of/O the/O steps/O was/O a/O heavy/O door/O of/O oak/O and/O iron/O ./O 
Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON lifted/O the/O crossbar/O and/O gestured/O Ned/PERSON through/O ./O 
They/O stepped/O out/O into/O the/O ruddy/O glow/O of/O dusk/O ,/O on/O a/O rocky/O bluff/O high/O above/O the/O river/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O 're/O outside/O the/O castle/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O a/O hard/O man/O to/O fool/O ,/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O with/O a/O smirk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Was/O it/O the/O sun/O that/O gave/O it/O away/O ,/O or/O the/O sky/O ?/O 
Follow/O me/O ./O 
There/O are/O niches/O cut/O in/O the/O rock/O ./O 
Try/O not/O to/O fall/O to/O your/O death/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON would/O never/O understand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O With/O that/O ,/O he/O was/O over/O the/O side/O of/O the/O cliff/O ,/O descending/O as/O quick/O as/O a/O monkey/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON studied/O the/O rocky/O face/O of/O the/O bluff/O for/O a/O moment/O ,/O then/O followed/O more/O slowly/O ./O 
The/O niches/O were/O there/O ,/O as/O Littlefinger/PERSON had/O promised/O ,/O shallow/O cuts/O that/O would/O be/O invisible/O from/O below/O ,/O unless/O you/O knew/O just/O where/O to/O look/O for/O them/O ./O 
The/O river/O was/O a/O long/O ,/O dizzying/O distance/O below/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON kept/O his/O face/O pressed/O to/O the/O rock/O and/O tried/O not/O to/O look/O down/O any/O more/O often/O than/O he/O had/O to/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O at/O last/O he/O reached/O the/O bottom/O ,/O a/O narrow/O ,/O muddy/O trail/O along/O the/O water/O 's/O edge/O ,/O Littlefinger/PERSON was/O lazing/O against/O a/O rock/O and/O eating/O an/O apple/O ./O 
He/O was/O almost/O down/O to/O the/O core/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O growing/O old/O and/O slow/O ,/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O flipping/O the/O apple/O casually/O into/O the/O rushing/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O matter/O ,/O we/O ride/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O had/O two/O horses/O waiting/O ./O 
Ned/PERSON mounted/O up/O and/O trotted/O behind/O him/O ,/O down/O the/O trail/O and/O into/O the/O city/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Finally/O Baelish/PERSON drew/O rein/O in/O front/O of/O a/O ramshackle/O building/O ,/O three/O stories/O ,/O timbered/O ,/O its/O windows/O bright/O with/O lamplight/O in/O the/O gathering/O dusk/O ./O 
The/O sounds/O of/O music/O and/O raucous/O laughter/O drifted/O out/O and/O floated/O over/O the/O water/O ./O 
Beside/O the/O door/O swung/O an/O ornate/O oil/O lamp/O on/O a/O heavy/O chain/O ,/O with/O a/O globe/O of/O leaded/O red/O glass/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON Stark/PERSON dismounted/O in/O a/O fury/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O brothel/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O seized/O Littlefinger/PERSON by/O the/O shoulder/O and/O spun/O him/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O brought/O me/O all/O this/O way/O to/O take/O me/O to/O a/O brothel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O wife/O is/O inside/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O the/O final/O insult/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Brandon/PERSON was/O too/O kind/O to/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O as/O he/O slammed/O the/O small/O man/O back/O against/O a/O wall/O and/O shoved/O his/O dagger/O up/O under/O the/O little/O pointed/O chin/O beard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ,/O no/O ,/O \/O ''/O an/O urgent/O voice/O called/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O speaks/O the/O truth/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O were/O footsteps/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O spun/O ,/O knife/O in/O hand/O ,/O as/O an/O old/O white-haired/O man/O hurried/O toward/O them/O ./O 
He/O was/O dressed/O in/O brown/O roughspun/O ,/O and/O the/O soft/O flesh/O under/O his/O chin/O wobbled/O as/O he/O ran/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O no/O business/O of/O yours/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON began/O ;/O then/O ,/O suddenly/O ,/O the/O recognition/O came/O ./O 
He/O lowered/O the/O dagger/O ,/O astonished/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O lady/O awaits/O you/O upstairs/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O was/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Catelyn/O is/O truly/O here/O ?/O 
This/O is/O not/O some/O strange/O jape/O of/O Littlefinger/PERSON 's/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O sheathed/O his/O blade/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Would/O that/O it/O were/O ,/O Stark/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Follow/O me/O ,/O and/O try/O to/O look/O a/O shade/O more/O lecherous/O and/O a/O shade/O less/O like/O the/O King/O 's/O Hand/O ./O 
It/O would/O not/O do/O to/O have/O you/O recognized/O ./O 
Perhaps/O you/O could/O fondle/O a/O breast/O or/O two/O ,/O just/O in/O passing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O They/O went/O inside/O ,/O through/O a/O crowded/O common/O room/O where/O a/O fat/O woman/O was/O singing/O bawdy/O songs/O while/O pretty/O young/O girls/O in/O linen/O shifts/O and/O wisps/O of/O colored/O silk/O pressed/O themselves/O against/O their/O lovers/O and/O dandled/O on/O their/O laps/O ./O 
No/O one/O paid/O Ned/PERSON the/O least/O bit/O of/O attention/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON waited/O below/O while/O Littlefinger/PERSON led/O him/O up/O to/O the/O third/O floor/O ,/O along/O a/O corridor/O ,/O and/O through/O a/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O waiting/O ./O 
She/O cried/O out/O when/O she/O saw/O him/O ,/O ran/O to/O him/O ,/O and/O embraced/O him/O fiercely/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON whispered/O in/O wonderment/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O very/O good/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Littlefinger/PERSON ,/O closing/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O recognized/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O feared/O you/O 'd/O never/O come/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O against/O his/O chest/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Petyr/O has/O been/O bringing/O me/O reports/O ./O 
He/O told/O me/O of/O your/O troubles/O with/O Arya/PERSON and/O the/O young/O prince/O ./O 
How/O are/O my/O girls/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Both/O in/O mourning/O ,/O and/O full/O of/O anger/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Cat/O ,/O I/O do/O not/O understand/O ./O 
What/O are/O you/O doing/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ?/O 
What/O 's/O happened/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O his/O wife/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O Bran/O ?/O 
Is/O he/O .../O \/O ''/O Dead/O was/O the/O word/O that/O came/O to/O his/O lips/O ,/O but/O he/O could/O not/O say/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O is/O Bran/O ,/O but/O not/O as/O you/O think/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ned/O was/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O how/O ?/O 
Why/O are/O you/O here/O ,/O my/O love/O ?/O 
What/O is/O this/O place/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Just/O what/O it/O appears/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ,/O easing/O himself/O onto/O a/O window/O seat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O brothel/O ./O 
Can/O you/O think/O of/O a/O less/O likely/O place/O to/O find/O a/O Catelyn/PERSON Tully/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O it/O chances/O ,/O I/O own/O this/O particular/O establishment/O ,/O so/O arrangements/O were/O easily/O made/O ./O 
I/O am/O most/O anxious/O to/O keep/O the/O Lannisters/O from/O learning/O that/O Cat/O is/O here/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ned/PERSON asked/O ./O 
He/O saw/O her/O hands/O then/O ,/O the/O awkward/O way/O she/O held/O them/O ,/O the/O raw/O red/O scars/O ,/O the/O stiffness/O of/O the/O last/O two/O fingers/O on/O her/O left/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 've/O been/O hurt/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O took/O her/O hands/O in/O his/O own/O ,/O turned/O them/O over/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gods/O ./O 
Those/O are/O deep/O cuts/O .../O a/O gash/O from/O a/O sword/O or/O .../O how/O did/O this/O happen/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O slid/O a/O dagger/O out/O from/O under/O her/O cloak/O and/O placed/O it/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O blade/O was/O sent/O to/O open/O Bran/O 's/O throat/O and/O spill/O his/O life/O 's/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON 's/O head/O jerked/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O But/O .../O who/O .../O why/O would/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O put/O a/O finger/O to/O his/O lips/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O tell/O it/O all/O ,/O my/O love/O ./O 
It/O will/O go/O faster/O that/O way/O ./O 
Listen/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O So/O he/O listened/O ,/O and/O she/O told/O it/O all/O ,/O from/O the/O fire/O in/O the/O library/O tower/O to/O Varys/LOCATION and/O the/O guardsmen/O and/O Littlefinger/PERSON ./O 
And/O when/O she/O was/O done/O ,/O Eddard/PERSON Stark/PERSON sat/O dazed/O beside/O the/O table/O ,/O the/O dagger/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
Bran/O 's/O wolf/O had/O saved/O the/O boy/O 's/O life/O ,/O he/O thought/O dully/O ./O 
What/O was/O it/O that/O Jon/PERSON had/O said/O when/O they/O found/O the/O pups/O in/O the/O snow/O ?/O 
Your/O children/O were/O meant/O to/O have/O these/O pups/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
And/O he/O had/O killed/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O ,/O and/O for/O what/O ?/O 
Was/O it/O guilt/O he/O was/O feeling/O ?/O 
Or/O fear/O ?/O 
If/O the/O gods/O had/O sent/O these/O wolves/O ,/O what/O folly/O had/O he/O done/O ?/O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Painfully/O ,/O Ned/PERSON forced/O his/O thoughts/O back/O to/O the/O dagger/O and/O what/O it/O meant/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Imp/O 's/O dagger/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O repeated/O ./O 
It/O made/O no/O sense/O ./O 
His/O hand/O curled/O around/O the/O smooth/O dragonbone/O hilt/O ,/O and/O he/O ''/O ,/O ``/O slammed/O the/O blade/O into/O the/O table/O ,/O felt/O it/O bite/O into/O the/O wood/O ./O 
It/O stood/O mocking/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O should/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O want/O Bran/O dead/O ?/O 
The/O boy/O has/O never/O done/O him/O harm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O Starks/PERSON have/O nought/O but/O snow/O between/O your/O ears/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Imp/O would/O never/O have/O acted/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O rose/O and/O paced/O the/O length/O of/O the/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O the/O queen/O had/O a/O role/O in/O this/O or/O ,/O gods/O forbid/O ,/O the/O king/O himself/O .../O no/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O believe/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Yet/O even/O as/O he/O said/O the/O words/O ,/O he/O remembered/O that/O chill/O morning/O on/O the/O barrowlands/O ,/O and/O Robert/PERSON 's/O talk/O of/O sending/O hired/O knives/O after/O the/O Targaryen/O princess/O ./O 
He/O remembered/O Rhaegar/PERSON 's/O infant/O son/O ,/O the/O red/O ruin/O of/O his/O skull/O ,/O and/O the/O way/O the/O king/O had/O turned/O away/O ,/O as/O he/O had/O turned/O away/O in/O Dairy/O 's/O audience/O hall/O not/O so/O long/O ago/O ./O 
He/O could/O still/O hear/O Sansa/O pleading/O ,/O as/O Lyanna/PERSON had/O pleaded/O once/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Most/O likely/O the/O king/O did/O not/O know/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O would/O not/O be/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
Our/O good/O Robert/PERSON is/O practiced/O at/O closing/O his/O eyes/O to/O things/O he/O would/O rather/O not/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O had/O no/O reply/O for/O that/O ./O 
The/O face/O of/O the/O butcher/O 's/O boy/O swam/O up/O before/O his/O eyes/O ,/O cloven/O almost/O in/O two/O ,/O and/O afterward/O the/O king/O had/O said/O not/O a/O word/O ./O 
His/O head/O was/O pounding/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Littlefinger/PERSON sauntered/O over/O to/O the/O table/O ,/O wrenched/O the/O knife/O from/O the/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O accusation/O is/O treason/O either/O way/O ./O 
Accuse/O the/O king/O and/O you/O will/O dance/O with/O Ilyn/PERSON Payne/PERSON before/O the/O words/O are/O out/O of/O your/O mouth/O ./O 
The/O queen/O .../O if/O you/O can/O find/O proof/O ,/O and/O if/O you/O can/O make/O Robert/PERSON listen/O ,/O then/O perhaps/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O have/O proof/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O the/O dagger/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON flipped/O the/O knife/O casually/O end/O over/O end/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O sweet/O piece/O of/O steel/O ,/O but/O it/O cuts/O two/O ways/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
The/O Imp/O will/O no/O doubt/O swear/O the/O blade/O was/O lost/O or/O stolen/O while/O he/O was/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O with/O his/O hireling/O dead/O ,/O who/O is/O there/O to/O give/O him/O the/O lie/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O tossed/O the/O knife/O lightly/O to/O Ned/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O counsel/O is/O to/O drop/O that/O in/O the/O river/O and/O forget/O that/O it/O was/O ever/O forged/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/O regarded/O him/O coldly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ,/O I/O am/O a/O Stark/O of/O Winterfell/O ./O 
My/O son/O lies/O crippled/O ,/O perhaps/O dying/O ./O 
He/O would/O be/O dead/O ,/O and/O Catelyn/PERSON with/O him/O ,/O but/O for/O a/O wolf/O pup/O we/O found/O in/O the/O snow/O ./O 
If/O you/O truly/O believe/O I/O could/O forget/O that/O ,/O you/O are/O as/O big/O a/O fool/O now/O as/O when/O you/O took/O up/O sword/O against/O my/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O fool/O I/O may/O be/O ,/O Stark/O .../O yet/O I/O 'm/O still/O here/O ,/O while/O your/O brother/O has/O been/O moldering/O in/O his/O frozen/O grave/O for/O some/O fourteen/O years/O now/O ./O 
If/O you/O are/O so/O eager/O to/O molder/O beside/O him/O ,/O far/O be/O it/O from/O me/O to/O dissuade/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O would/O rather/O not/O be/O included/O in/O the/O party/O ,/O thank/O you/O very/O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O would/O be/O the/O last/O man/O I/O would/O willingly/O include/O in/O any/O party/O ,/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O wound/O me/O deeply/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON placed/O a/O hand/O over/O his/O heart/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O my/O part/O ,/O I/O always/O found/O you/O Starks/PERSON a/O tiresome/O lot/O ,/O but/O Cat/O seems/O to/O have/O become/O attached/O to/O you/O ,/O for/O reasons/O I/O can/O not/O comprehend/O ./O 
I/O shall/O try/O to/O keep/O you/O alive/O for/O her/O sake/O ./O 
A/O fool/O 's/O task/O ,/O admittedly/O ,/O but/O I/O could/O never/O refuse/O your/O wife/O anything/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Littlefinger/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O warn/O you/O ,/O Stark/O ,/O we/O usually/O charge/O for/O that/O sort/O of/O thing/O around/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O moment/O alone/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O I/O ask/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Very/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON strolled/O to/O the/O door/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O too/O long/O ./O 
It/O is/O past/O time/O the/O Hand/O and/O I/O returned/O to/O the/O castle/O ,/O before/O our/O absence/O is/O noted/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O went/O to/O him/O and/O took/O his/O hands/O in/O her/O own/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O will/O not/O forget/O the/O help/O you/O gave/O me/O ,/O Petyr/PERSON ./O 
When/O your/O men/O came/O for/O me/O ,/O I/O did/O not/O know/O whether/O they/O were/O taking/O me/O to/O a/O friend/O or/O an/O enemy/O ./O 
I/O have/O found/O you/O more/O than/O a/O friend/O ./O 
I/O have/O found/O a/O brother/O I/O 'd/O thought/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O desperately/O sentimental/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
Best/O not/O tell/O anyone/O ./O 
I/O have/O spent/O years/O convincing/O the/O court/O that/O I/O am/O wicked/O and/O cruel/O ,/O and/O I/O should/O hate/O to/O see/O all/O that/O hard/O work/O go/O for/O naught/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Ned/PERSON believed/O not/O a/O word/O of/O that/O ,/O but/O he/O kept/O his/O voice/O polite/O as/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O my/O thanks/O as/O well/O ,/O Lord/O Baelish/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O now/O there/O 's/O a/O treasure/O ,/O \/O ''/O Littlefinger/PERSON said/O ,/O exiting/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O door/O had/O closed/O behind/O him/O ,/O Ned/PERSON turned/O back/O to/O his/O wife/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Once/O you/O are/O home/O ,/O send/O word/O to/O Helman/PERSON Tallhart/PERSON and/O Galbart/PERSON Glover/PERSON under/O my/O seal/O ./O 
They/O are/O to/O raise/O a/O hundred/O bowmen/O each/O and/O fortify/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ./O 
Two/O hundred/O determined/O archers/O can/O hold/O the/O Neck/O against/O an/O army/O ./O 
Instruct/O Lord/O Manderly/O that/O he/O is/O to/O strengthen/O and/O repair/O all/O his/O defenses/O at/O White/LOCATION Harbor/LOCATION ,/O and/O see/O that/O they/O are/O well/O manned/O ./O 
And/O from/O this/O day/O on/O ,/O I/O want/O a/O careful/O watch/O kept/O over/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ./O 
If/O there/O is/O war/O ,/O we/O shall/O have/O sore/O need/O of/O his/O father/O 's/O fleet/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O War/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O The/O fear/O was/O plain/O on/O Catelyn/PERSON '/O s/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O It/O will/O not/O come/O to/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ned/PERSON promised/O her/O ,/O praying/O it/O was/O true/O ./O 
He/O took/O her/O in/O his/O arms/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O are/O merciless/O in/O the/O face/O of/O weakness/O ,/O as/O Aerys/PERSON Targaryen/PERSON learned/O to/O his/O sorrow/O ,/O but/O they/O would/O not/O dare/O attack/O the/O north/O without/O all/O the/O power/O of/O the/O realm/O behind/O them/O ,/O and/O that/O they/O shall/O not/O have/O ./O 
I/O must/O play/O out/O this/O fool/O 's/O masquerade/O as/O if/O nothing/O is/O amiss/O ./O 
Remember/O why/O I/O came/O here/O ,/O my/O love/O ./O 
If/O I/O find/O proof/O that/O the/O Lannisters/O murdered/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O felt/O Catelyn/O tremble/O in/O his/O arms/O ./O 
Her/O scarred/O hands/O clung/O to/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O If/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O what/O then/O ,/O my/O love/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O most/O dangerous/O part/O ,/O Ned/PERSON knew/O ./O 
\/O ``/O All/O justice/O flows/O from/O the/O king/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O I/O know/O the/O truth/O ,/O I/O must/O go/O to/O Robert/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O pray/O that/O he/O is/O the/O man/O I/O think/O he/O is/O ,/O he/O finished/O silently/O ,/O and/O not/O the/O man/O I/O fear/O he/O has/O become/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
