-LSB-/O ``/O CATELYN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O eastern/O sky/O was/O rose/O and/O gold/O as/O the/O sun/O broke/O over/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Arryn/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON Stark/PERSON watched/O the/O light/O spread/O ,/O her/O hands/O resting/O on/O the/O delicate/O carved/O stone/O of/O the/O balustrade/O outside/O her/O window/O ./O 
Below/O her/O the/O world/O turned/O from/O black/O to/O indigo/O to/O green/O as/O dawn/O crept/O across/O fields/O and/O forests/O ./O 
Pale/O white/O mists/O rose/O off/O Alyssa/PERSON 's/O Tears/O ,/O where/O the/O ghost/O waters/O plunged/O over/O the/O shoulder/O of/O the/O mountain/O to/O begin/O their/O long/O tumble/O down/O the/O face/O of/O the/O Giant/O 's/O Lance/PERSON ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON could/O feel/O the/O faint/O touch/O of/O spray/O on/O her/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Alyssa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O seen/O her/O husband/O ,/O her/O brothers/O ,/O and/O all/O her/O children/O slain/O ,/O and/O yet/O in/O life/O she/O had/O never/O shed/O a/O tear/O ./O 
So/O in/O death/O ,/O the/O gods/O had/O decreed/O that/O she/O would/O know/O no/O rest/O until/O her/O weeping/O watered/O the/O black/O earth/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O where/O the/O men/O she/O had/O loved/O were/O buried/O ./O 
Alyssa/PERSON had/O been/O dead/O six/O thousand/O years/O now/O ,/O and/O still/O no/O drop/O of/O the/O torrent/O had/O ever/O reached/O the/O valley/O floor/O far/O below/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON wondered/O how/O large/O a/O waterfall/O her/O own/O tears/O would/O make/O when/O she/O died/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Tell/O me/O the/O rest/O of/O it/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Kingslayer/O is/O massing/O a/O host/O at/O Casterly/LOCATION Rock/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON answered/O from/O the/O room/O behind/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O brother/O writes/O that/O he/O has/O sent/O riders/O to/O the/O Rock/O ,/O demanding/O that/O Lord/O Tywin/PERSON proclaim/O his/O intent/O ,/O but/O he/O has/O had/O no/O answer/O ./O 
Edmure/PERSON has/O commanded/O Lord/O Vance/PERSON and/O Lord/ORGANIZATION Piper/ORGANIZATION to/O guard/O the/O pass/O below/O the/O Golden/O Tooth/O ./O 
He/O vows/O to/O you/O that/O he/O will/O yield/O no/O foot/O of/O Tully/LOCATION land/O without/O first/O watering/O it/O with/O Lannister/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON turned/O away/O from/O the/O sunrise/O ./O 
Its/O beauty/O did/O little/O to/O lighten/O her/O mood/O ;/O it/O seemed/O cruel/O for/O a/O day/O to/O dawn/O so/O fair/O and/O end/O so/O foul/O as/O this/O one/O promised/O to/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Edmure/O has/O sent/O riders/O and/O made/O vows/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O Edmure/PERSON is/O not/O the/O Lord/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
What/O of/O my/O lord/O father/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O message/O made/O no/O mention/O of/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tugged/O at/O his/O whiskers/O ./O 
They/O had/O grown/O in/O white/O as/O snow/O and/O bristly/O as/O a/O thornbush/O while/O he/O was/O recovering/O from/O his/O wounds/O ;/O he/O looked/O almost/O himself/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O father/O would/O not/O have/O given/O the/O defense/O of/O Riverrun/PERSON over/O to/O Edmure/O unless/O he/O was/O very/O sick/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O worried/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O should/O have/O been/O woken/O as/O soon/O as/O this/O bird/O arrived/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O lady/O sister/O thought/O it/O better/O to/O let/O you/O sleep/O ,/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON told/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O should/O have/O been/O woken/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O insisted/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O maester/O tells/O me/O your/O sister/O planned/O to/O speak/O with/O you/O after/O the/O combat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O she/O still/O plans/O to/O go/O through/O with/O this/O mummer/O 's/O farce/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON grimaced/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O dwarf/O has/O played/O her/O like/O a/O set/O of/O pipes/O ,/O and/O she/O is/O too/O deaf/O to/O hear/O the/O tune/O ./O 
Whatever/O happens/O this/O morning/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ,/O it/O is/O past/O time/O we/O took/O our/O leave/O ./O 
My/O place/O is/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION with/O my/O sons/O ./O 
If/O you/O are/O strong/O enough/O to/O travel/O ,/O I/O shall/O ask/O Lysa/PERSON for/O an/O escort/O to/O see/O us/O to/O Gulltown/LOCATION ./O 
We/O can/O take/O ship/O from/O there/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Another/O ship/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON looked/O a/O shade/O green/O ,/O yet/O he/O managed/O not/O to/O shudder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O old/O knight/O waited/O outside/O her/O door/O as/O Catelyn/LOCATION summoned/O the/O servants/O Lysa/PERSON had/O given/O her/O ./O 
If/O she/O spoke/O to/O her/O sister/O before/O the/O duel/O ,/O perhaps/O she/O could/O change/O her/O mind/O ,/O she/O thought/O as/O they/O dressed/O her/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON 's/O policies/O varied/O with/O her/O moods/O ,/O and/O her/O moods/O changed/O hourly/O ./O 
The/O shy/O girl/O ''/O ,/O ``/O she/O had/O known/O at/O Riverrun/LOCATION had/O grown/O into/O a/O woman/O who/O was/O by/O turns/O proud/O ,/O fearful/O ,/O cruel/O ,/O dreamy/O ,/O reckless/O ,/O timid/O ,/O stubborn/O ,/O vain/O ,/O and/O ,/O above/O all/O ,/O inconstant/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O that/O vile/O turnkey/O of/O hers/O had/O come/O crawling/O to/O tell/O them/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON wished/O to/O confess/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O urged/O Lysa/PERSON to/O have/O the/O dwarf/O brought/O to/O them/O privately/O ,/O but/O no/O ,/O nothing/O would/O do/O but/O that/O her/O sister/O must/O make/O a/O show/O of/O him/O before/O half/O the/O Vale/O ./O 
And/O now/O this/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lannister/O is/O my/O prisoner/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O told/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON as/O they/O descended/O the/O tower/O stairs/O and/O made/O their/O way/O through/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON 's/O cold/O white/O halls/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON wore/O plain/O grey/O wool/O with/O a/O silvered/O belt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O sister/O must/O be/O reminded/O of/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O At/O the/O doors/O to/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O apartments/O ,/O they/O met/O her/O uncle/O storming/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Going/O to/O join/O the/O fool/O 's/O festival/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Brynden/PERSON snapped/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O tell/O you/O to/O slap/O some/O sense/O into/O your/O sister/O ,/O if/O I/O thought/O it/O would/O do/O any/O good/O ,/O but/O you/O 'd/O only/O bruise/O your/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O bird/O from/O Riverrun/LOCATION ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON began/O ,/O \/O ``/O a/O letter/O from/O Edmure/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O know/O ,/O child/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O black/O fish/O that/O fastened/O his/O cloak/O was/O Brynden/PERSON 's/O only/O concession/O to/O ornament/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O to/O hear/O it/O from/O Maester/O Colemon/O ./O 
I/O asked/O your/O sister/O for/O leave/O to/O take/O a/O thousand/O seasoned/O men/O and/O ride/O for/O Riverrun/PERSON with/O all/O haste/O ./O 
Do/O you/O know/O what/O she/O told/O me/O ?/O 
The/O Vale/O can/O not/O spare/O a/O thousand/O swords/O ,/O nor/O even/O one/O ,/O Uncle/O ,/O she/O said/O ./O 
You/O are/O the/O Knight/O of/O the/O Gate/O ./O 
Your/O place/O is/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O gust/O of/O childish/O laughter/O drifted/O through/O the/O open/O doors/O behind/O him/O ,/O and/O her/O uncle/O glanced/O darkly/O over/O his/O shoulder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O ,/O I/O told/O her/O she/O could/O bloody/O well/O find/O herself/O a/O new/O Knight/O of/O the/O Gate/O ./O 
Black/O fish/O or/O no/O ,/O I/O am/O still/O a/O Tully/O ./O 
I/O shall/O leave/O for/O Riverrun/LOCATION by/O evenfall/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O could/O not/O pretend/O to/O surprise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Alone/O ?/O 
You/O know/O as/O well/O as/O I/O that/O you/O will/O never/O survive/O the/O high/O road/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON and/O I/O are/O returning/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Come/O with/O us/O ,/O Uncle/O ./O 
I/O will/O give/O you/O your/O thousand/O men/O ./O 
Riverrun/PERSON will/O not/O fight/O alone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Brynden/PERSON thought/O a/O moment/O ,/O then/O nodded/O a/O brusque/O agreement/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O long/O way/O home/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O more/O like/O to/O get/O there/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O wait/O for/O you/O below/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O went/O striding/O off/O ,/O his/O cloak/O swirling/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON exchanged/O a/O look/O with/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
They/O went/O through/O the/O doors/O to/O the/O high/O ,/O nervous/O sound/O of/O a/O child/O 's/O giggles/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O apartments/O opened/O over/O a/O small/O garden/O ,/O a/O circle/O of/O dirt/O and/O grass/O planted/O with/O blue/O flowers/O and/O ringed/O on/O all/O sides/O by/O tall/O white/O towers/O ./O 
The/O builders/O had/O intended/O it/O as/O a/O godswood/O ,/O but/O the/O Eyrie/O rested/O on/O the/O hard/O stone/O of/O the/O mountain/O ,/O and/O no/O matter/O how/O much/O soil/O was/O hauled/O up/O from/O the/O Vale/LOCATION ,/O they/O could/O not/O get/O a/O weirwood/O to/O take/O root/O here/O ./O 
So/O the/O Lords/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O planted/O grass/O and/O scattered/O statuary/O amidst/O low/O ,/O flowering/O shrubs/O ./O 
It/O was/O there/O the/O two/O champions/O would/O meet/O to/O place/O their/O lives/O ,/O and/O that/O of/O Tyrion/LOCATION Lannister/LOCATION ,/O into/O the/O hands/O of/O the/O gods/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O freshly/O scrubbed/O and/O garbed/O in/O cream/O velvet/O with/O a/O rope/O of/O sapphires/O and/O moonstones/O around/O her/O milk-white/O neck/O ,/O was/O holding/O court/O on/O the/O terrace/O overlooking/O the/O scene/O of/O the/O combat/O ,/O surrounded/O by/O her/O knights/O ,/O retainers/O ,/O and/O lords/O high/O and/O low/O ./O 
Most/O of/O them/O still/O hoped/O to/O wed/O her/O ,/O bed/O her/O ,/O and/O rule/O the/O Vale/O of/O Arryn/O by/O her/O side/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O From/O what/O Catelyn/PERSON had/O seen/O during/O her/O stay/O at/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O it/O was/O a/O vain/O hope/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O wooden/O platform/O had/O been/O built/O to/O elevate/O Robert/PERSON 's/O chair/O ;/O there/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O sat/O ,/O giggling/O and/O clapping/O his/O hands/O as/O a/O humpbacked/O puppeteer/O in/O blue-and-white/O motley/O made/O two/O wooden/O knights/O hack/O and/O slash/O at/O each/O other/O ./O 
Pitchers/O of/O thick/O cream/O and/O baskets/O of/O blackberries/O had/O been/O set/O out/O ,/O and/O the/O guests/O were/O sipping/O a/O sweet/O orange-scented/O wine/O from/O engraved/O silver/O cups/O ./O 
A/O fool/O 's/O festival/O ,/O Brynden/PERSON had/O called/O it/O ,/O and/O small/O wonder/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Across/O the/O terrace/O ,/O Lysa/PERSON laughed/O gaily/O at/O some/O jest/O of/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON 's/O ,/O and/O nibbled/O a/O blackberry/O from/O the/O point/O of/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON 's/O dagger/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O suitors/O who/O stood/O highest/O in/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O favor/O .../O today/O ,/O at/O least/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON would/O have/O been/O hard-pressed/O to/O say/O which/O man/O was/O more/O unsuitable/O ./O 
Eon/PERSON Hunter/PERSON was/O even/O older/O than/O Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON had/O been/O ,/O half-crippled/O by/O gout/O ,/O and/O cursed/O with/O three/O quarrelsome/O sons/O ,/O each/O more/O grasping/O than/O the/O last/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON was/O a/O different/O sort/O of/O folly/O ;/O lean/O and/O handsome/O ,/O heir/O to/O an/O ancient/O but/O impoverished/O house/O ,/O but/O vain/O ,/O reckless/O ,/O hot-tempered/O .../O and/O ,/O it/O was/O whispered/O ,/O notoriously/O uninterested/O in/O the/O intimate/O charms/O of/O women/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O Lysa/PERSON espied/O Catelyn/PERSON ,/O she/O welcomed/O her/O with/O a/O sisterly/O embrace/O and/O a/O moist/O kiss/O on/O the/O cheek/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O n't/O it/O a/O lovely/O morning/O ?/O 
The/O gods/O are/O smiling/O on/O us/O ./O 
Do/O try/O a/O cup/O of/O the/O wine/O ,/O sweet/O sister/O ./O 
Lord/O Hunter/PERSON was/O kind/O enough/O to/O send/O for/O it/O ,/O from/O his/O own/O cellars/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Thank/O you/O ,/O no/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON ,/O we/O must/O talk/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O After/O ,/O \/O ''/O her/O sister/O promised/O ,/O already/O beginning/O to/O turn/O away/O from/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON spoke/O more/O loudly/O than/O she/O 'd/O intended/O ./O 
Men/O were/O turning/O to/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON ,/O you/O can/O not/O mean/O to/O go/O ahead/O with/O this/O folly/O ./O 
Alive/O ,/O the/O Imp/O has/O value/O ./O 
Dead/O ,/O he/O is/O only/O food/O for/O crows/O ./O 
And/O if/O his/O champion/O should/O prevail/O here/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Small/O chance/O of/O that/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON assured/O her/O ,/O patting/O her/O shoulder/O with/O a/O liver/O -/O spotted/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O is/O a/O doughty/O fighter/O ./O 
He/O will/O make/O short/O work/O of/O the/O sellsword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Will/O he/O ,/O my/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O coolly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wonder/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O had/O seen/O Bronn/LOCATION fight/O on/O the/O high/O road/O ;/O it/O was/O no/O accident/O that/O he/O had/O survived/O the/O journey/O while/O other/O men/O had/O died/O ./O 
He/O moved/O like/O a/O panther/O ,/O and/O that/O ugly/O sword/O of/O his/O seemed/O a/O part/O of/O his/O arm/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O suitors/O were/O gathering/O around/O them/O like/O bees/O round/O a/O blossom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Women/O understand/O little/O of/O these/O things/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Morton/PERSON Waynwood/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O is/O a/O knight/O ,/O sweet/O lady/O ./O 
This/O other/O fellow/O ,/O well/O ,/O his/O sort/O are/O all/O cowards/O at/O heart/O ./O 
Useful/O enough/O in/O a/O battle/O ,/O with/O thousands/O of/O their/O fellows/O around/O them/O ,/O but/O stand/O them/O up/O alone/O and/O the/O manhood/O leaks/O right/O out/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Say/O you/O have/O the/O truth/O of/O it/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O with/O a/O courtesy/O that/O made/O her/O mouth/O ache/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O will/O we/O gain/O by/O the/O dwarfs/O death/O ?/O 
Do/O you/O imagine/O that/O Jaime/PERSON will/O care/O a/O fig/O that/O we/O gave/O his/O brother/O a/O trial/O before/O we/O flung/O him/O off/O a/O mountain/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Behead/O the/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON suggested/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O the/O Kingslayer/O receives/O the/O Imp/PERSON 's/O head/O ,/O it/O will/O be/O a/O warning/O to/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Lysa/PERSON gave/O an/O impatient/O shake/O of/O her/O waist-long/O auburn/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON wants/O to/O see/O him/O fly/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O as/O if/O that/O settled/O the/O matter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O the/O Imp/O has/O only/O himself/O to/O blame/O ./O 
It/O was/O he/O who/O demanded/O a/O trial/O by/O combat/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON had/O no/O honorable/O way/O to/O deny/O him/O ,/O even/O if/O she/O 'd/O wished/O to/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON intoned/O ponderously/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ignoring/O them/O all/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON turned/O all/O her/O force/O on/O her/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O remind/O you/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON is/O my/O prisoner/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O I/O remind/O you/O ,/O the/O dwarf/O murdered/O my/O lord/O husband/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Her/O voice/O rose/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O poisoned/O the/O Hand/O of/O the/O King/O and/O left/O my/O sweet/O baby/O fatherless/O ,/O and/O now/O I/O mean/O to/O see/O him/O pay/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Whirling/O ,/O her/O skirts/O swinging/O around/O her/O ,/O Lysa/PERSON stalked/O across/O the/O terrace/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON and/O Ser/PERSON Morton/PERSON and/O the/O other/O suitors/O excused/O themselves/O with/O cool/O nods/O and/O trailed/O after/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O he/O did/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON asked/O her/O quietly/O when/O they/O were/O alone/O again/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Murder/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON ,/O that/O is/O ?/O 
The/O Imp/O still/O denies/O it/O ,/O and/O most/O fiercely/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O believe/O the/O Lannisters/O murdered/O Lord/O Arryn/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON replied/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O whether/O it/O was/O Tyrion/O ,/O or/O Ser/O Jaime/O ,/O or/O the/O queen/O ,/O or/O all/O of/O them/O together/O ,/O I/O could/O not/O begin/O to/O say/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON had/O named/O Cersei/PERSON in/O the/O letter/O she/O had/O sent/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O but/O now/O she/O seemed/O certain/O that/O Tyrion/PERSON was/O the/O killer/O .../O perhaps/O because/O the/O dwarf/O was/O here/O ,/O while/O the/O queen/O was/O safe/O behind/O the/O walls/O of/O the/O Red/O Keep/O ,/O hundreds/O of/O leagues/O to/O the/O south/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON almost/O wished/O she/O had/O burned/O her/O sister/O 's/O letter/O before/O reading/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tugged/O at/O his/O whiskers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Poison/O ,/O well/O .../O that/O could/O be/O the/O dwarfs/O work/O ,/O true/O enough/O ./O 
Or/O Cersei/PERSON 's/O ./O 
It/O 's/O said/O poison/O is/O a/O woman/O 's/O weapon/O ,/O begging/O your/O pardons/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
The/O Kingslayer/O ,/O now/O I/O have/O no/O great/O liking/O for/O the/O man/O ,/O but/O he/O 's/O not/O the/O sort/O ./O 
Too/O fond/O of/O the/O sight/O of/O blood/O on/O that/O golden/O sword/O of/O his/O ./O 
Was/O it/O poison/O ,/O my/O lady/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Catelyn/O frowned/O ,/O vaguely/O uneasy/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O else/O could/O they/O make/O it/O look/O a/O natural/O death/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Behind/O her/O ,/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON shrieked/O with/O delight/O as/O one/O of/O the/O puppet/O knights/O sliced/O the/O other/O in/O half/O ,/O spilling/O a/O flood/O of/O red/O sawdust/O onto/O the/O terrace/O ./O 
She/O glanced/O at/O her/O nephew/O and/O sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O is/O utterly/O without/O discipline/O ./O 
He/O will/O never/O be/O strong/O enough/O to/O rule/O unless/O he/O is/O taken/O away/O from/O his/O mother/O for/O a/O time/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O His/O lord/O father/O agreed/O with/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O a/O voice/O at/O her/O elbow/O ./O 
She/O turned/O to/O behold/O Maester/PERSON Colemon/PERSON ,/O a/O cup/O of/O wine/O in/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O was/O planning/O to/O send/O the/O boy/O to/O Dragonstone/O for/O fostering/O ,/O you/O know/O .../O oh/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O speaking/O out/O of/O turn/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O apple/O of/O his/O throat/O bobbed/O anxiously/O beneath/O the/O loose/O maester/O 's/O chain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O fear/O I/O 've/O had/O too/O much/O of/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON 's/O excellent/O wine/O ./O 
The/O prospect/O of/O bloodshed/O has/O my/O nerves/O all/O a/O -/O fray/O .../O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O are/O mistaken/O ,/O Maester/O ,/O \/O ''/O Catelyn/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O was/O Casterly/O Rock/O ,/O not/O Dragonstone/O ,/O and/O those/O arrangements/O were/O made/O after/O the/O Hand/O 's/O death/O ,/O without/O my/O sister/O 's/O consent/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O maester/O 's/O head/O jerked/O so/O vigorously/O at/O the/O end/O of/O his/O absurdly/O long/O neck/O that/O he/O looked/O half/O a/O puppet/O himself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O No/O ,/O begging/O your/O forgiveness/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O Lord/O Jon/PERSON who/O -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O bell/O tolled/O loudly/O below/O them/O ./O 
High/O lords/O and/O serving/O girls/O alike/O broke/O off/O what/O they/O were/O doing/O and/O moved/O to/O the/O balustrade/O ./O 
Below/O ,/O two/O guardsmen/O in/O sky-blue/O cloaks/O led/O forth/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O ./O 
The/O Eyrie/O 's/O plump/O septon/O escorted/O him/O to/O the/O statue/O in/O the/O center/O of/O the/O garden/O ,/O a/O weeping/O woman/O carved/O in/O veined/O white/O marble/O ,/O no/O doubt/O meant/O to/O be/O Alyssa/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O bad/O little/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON said/O ,/O giggling/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O ,/O can/O I/O make/O him/O fly/O ?/O 
I/O want/O to/O see/O him/O fly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Later/O ,/O my/O sweet/O baby/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON promised/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Trial/O first/O ,/O \/O ''/O drawled/O Ser/PERSON Lyn/PERSON Corbray/PERSON ,/O \/O ``/O then/O execution/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O moment/O later/O the/O two/O champions/O appeared/O from/O opposite/O sides/O of/O the/O garden/O ./O 
The/O knight/O was/O attended/O by/O two/O young/O squires/O ,/O the/O sellsword/O by/O the/O Eyrie/O 's/O master-at-arms/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON was/O steel/O from/O head/O to/O heel/O ,/O encased/O in/O heavy/O plate/O armor/O over/O mail/O and/O padded/O surcoat/O ./O 
Large/O circular/O rondels/O ,/O enameled/O cream-and-blue/O in/O the/O moon-and-falcon/O sigil/O of/O House/ORGANIZATION Arryn/O ,/O protected/O the/O vulnerable/O juncture/O of/O arm/O and/O breast/O ./O 
A/O skirt/O of/O lobstered/O metal/O covered/O him/O from/O waist/O to/O midthigh/O ,/O while/O a/O solid/O gorget/O encircled/O his/O throat/O ./O 
Falcon/ORGANIZATION 's/O wings/O sprouted/O from/O the/O temples/O of/O his/O helm/O ,/O and/O his/O visor/O was/O a/O pointed/O metal/O beak/O with/O a/O narrow/O slit/O for/O vision/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON was/O so/O lightly/O armored/O he/O looked/O almost/O naked/O beside/O the/O knight/O ./O 
He/O wore/O only/O a/O shirt/O of/O black/O oiled/O ringmail/O over/O boiled/O leather/O ,/O a/O round/O steel/O halfhelm/O with/O a/O noseguard/O ,/O and/O a/O mail/O coif/O ./O 
High/O leather/O boots/O with/O steel/O shinguards/O gave/O some/O protection/O to/O his/O legs/O ,/O and/O discs/O of/O black/O iron/O were/O sewn/O into/O the/O fingers/O of/O his/O gloves/O ./O 
Yet/O Catelyn/PERSON noted/O that/O the/O sellsword/O stood/O half/O a/O hand/O taller/O than/O his/O foe/O ,/O with/O a/O longer/O reach/O .../O and/O Bronn/PERSON was/O fifteen/O years/O younger/O ,/O if/O she/O was/O any/O judge/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O knelt/O in/O the/O grass/O beneath/O the/O weeping/O woman/O ,/O facing/O each/O other/O ,/O with/O Lannister/O between/O them/O ./O 
The/O septon/O removed/O a/O faceted/O crystal/O sphere/O from/O the/O soft/O cloth/O bag/O at/O his/O waist/O ./O 
He/O lifted/O it/O high/O above/O his/O head/O ,/O and/O the/O light/O shattered/O ./O 
Rainbows/O danced/O across/O the/O Imp/PERSON 's/O face/O ./O 
In/O a/O high/O ,/O solemn/O ,/O singsong/O voice/O ,/O the/O septon/O asked/O the/O gods/O to/O look/O down/O and/O bear/O witness/O ,/O to/O find/O the/O truth/O in/O this/O man/O 's/O soul/O ,/O to/O grant/O him/O life/O and/O freedom/O if/O he/O was/O innocent/O ,/O death/O if/O he/O was/O guilty/O ./O 
His/O voice/O echoed/O off/O the/O surrounding/O towers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O the/O last/O echo/O had/O died/O away/O ,/O the/O septon/O lowered/O his/O crystal/O and/O made/O a/O hasty/O departure/O ./O 
Tyrion/O leaned/O over/O and/O whispered/O something/O in/O Bronn/LOCATION 's/O ear/O before/O the/O guardsmen/O led/O him/O away/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O rose/O laughing/O and/O brushed/O a/O blade/O of/O grass/O from/O his/O knee/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robert/PERSON Arryn/PERSON ,/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O Defender/O of/O the/O Vale/ORGANIZATION ,/O was/O fidgeting/O impatiently/O in/O his/O elevated/O chair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O are/O they/O going/O to/O fight/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O plaintively/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON was/O helped/O back/O to/O his/O feet/O by/O one/O of/O his/O squires/O ./O 
The/O other/O brought/O him/O a/O triangular/O shield/O almost/O four/O feet/O tall/O ,/O heavy/O oak/O dotted/O with/O iron/O studs/O ./O 
They/O strapped/O it/O to/O his/O left/O forearm/O ./O 
When/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O master-at-arms/O offered/O Bronn/LOCATION a/O similar/O shield/O ,/O the/O sellsword/O spat/O and/O waved/O it/O away/O ./O 
Three/O days/O growth/O of/O coarse/O black/O beard/O covered/O his/O jaw/O and/O cheeks/O ,/O but/O if/O he/O did/O not/O shave/O it/O was/O not/O for/O want/O of/O a/O razor/O ;/O the/O edge/O of/O his/O sword/O had/O the/O dangerous/O glimmer/O of/O steel/O that/O had/O been/O honed/O every/O day/O for/O hours/O ,/O until/O it/O was/O too/O sharp/O to/O touch/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O held/O out/O a/O gauntleted/O hand/O ,/O and/O his/O squire/O placed/O a/O handsome/O double-edged/O longsword/O in/O his/O grasp/O ./O 
The/O blade/O was/O engraved/O with/O a/O delicate/O silver/O tracery/O of/O a/O mountain/O sky/O ;/O its/O pommel/O was/O a/O falcon/O 's/O head/O ,/O its/O crossguard/O fashioned/O into/O the/O shape/O of/O wings/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O had/O that/O sword/O crafted/O for/O Jon/PERSON in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON told/O her/O guests/O proudly/O as/O they/O watched/O Ser/ORGANIZATION Vardis/ORGANIZATION try/O a/O practice/O cut/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O wore/O it/O whenever/O he/O sat/O the/O Iron/O Throne/O in/O King/O Robert/PERSON 's/O place/O ./O 
Is/O n't/O it/O a/O lovely/O thing/O ?/O 
I/O thought/O it/O only/O fitting/O that/O our/O champion/O avenge/O Jon/PERSON with/O his/O own/O blade/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O engraved/O silver/O blade/O was/O beautiful/O beyond/O a/O doubt/O ,/O but/O it/O seemed/O to/O Catelyn/LOCATION that/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON might/O have/O been/O more/O comfortable/O with/O his/O own/O sword/O ./O 
Yet/O she/O said/O nothing/O ;/O she/O was/O weary/O of/O futile/O arguments/O with/O her/O sister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Make/O them/O fight/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Robert/PERSON called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O faced/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O lifted/O his/O sword/O in/O salute/O ./O 
\/O ``/O For/O the/O Eyrie/O and/O the/O Vale/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Tyrion/O Lannister/O had/O been/O seated/O on/O a/O balcony/O across/O the/O garden/O ,/O flanked/O by/O his/O guards/O ./O 
It/O was/O to/O him/O that/O Bronn/PERSON turned/O with/O a/O cursory/O salute/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O await/O your/O command/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON said/O to/O her/O lord/O son/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fight/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O boy/O screamed/O ,/O his/O arms/O trembling/O as/O they/O clutched/O at/O his/O chair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O swiveled/O ,/O bringing/O up/O his/O heavy/O shield/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON turned/O to/O face/O him/O ./O 
Their/O swords/O rang/O together/O ,/O once/O ,/O twice/O ,/O a/O testing/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O backed/O off/O a/O step/O ./O 
The/O knight/O came/O after/O ,/O holding/O his/O shield/O before/O him/O ./O 
He/O tried/O a/O slash/O ,/O but/O Bronn/PERSON jerked/O back/O ,/O just/O out/O of/O reach/O ,/O and/O the/O silver/O blade/O cut/O only/O air/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON circled/O to/O his/O right/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON turned/O to/O follow/O ,/O keeping/O his/O shield/O between/O them/O ./O 
The/O knight/O pressed/O forward/O ,/O placing/O each/O foot/O carefully/O on/O the/O uneven/O ground/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O gave/O way/O ,/O a/O faint/O smile/O playing/O over/O his/O lips/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON attacked/O ,/O slashing/O ,/O but/O Bronn/PERSON leapt/O away/O from/O him/O ,/O hopping/O lightly/O over/O a/O low/O ,/O moss-covered/O stone/O ./O 
Now/O the/O sellsword/O circled/O left/O ,/O away/O from/O the/O shield/O ,/O toward/O the/O knight/O 's/O unprotected/O side/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON tried/O a/O hack/O at/O his/O legs/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O not/O have/O the/O reach/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON danced/O farther/O to/O his/O left/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON turned/O in/O place/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O man/O is/O craven/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON declared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Stand/O and/O fight/O ,/O coward/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Other/O voices/O echoed/O the/O sentiment/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/O looked/O to/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
Her/O master-at-arms/O gave/O a/O curt/O shake/O of/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O wants/O to/O make/O Ser/O Vardis/O chase/O him/O ./O 
The/O weight/O of/O armor/O and/O shield/O will/O tire/O even/O the/O strongest/O man/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O She/O had/O seen/O men/O practice/O at/O their/O swordplay/O near/O every/O day/O of/O her/O life/O ,/O had/O viewed/O half/O a/O hundred/O tourneys/O in/O her/O time/O ,/O but/O this/O was/O something/O different/O and/O deadlier/O :/O a/O dance/O where/O the/O smallest/O misstep/O meant/O death/O ./O 
And/O as/O she/O watched/O ,/O the/O memory/O of/O another/O duel/O in/O another/O time/O came/O back/O to/O Catelyn/O Stark/O ,/O as/O vivid/O as/O if/O it/O had/O been/O yesterday/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O met/O in/O the/O lower/O bailey/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
When/O Brandon/PERSON saw/O that/O Petyr/PERSON wore/O only/O helm/O and/O breastplate/O and/O mail/O ,/O he/O took/O off/O most/O of/O his/O armor/O ./O 
Petyr/PERSON had/O begged/O her/O for/O a/O favor/O he/O might/O wear/O ,/O but/O she/O had/O turned/O him/O away/O ./O 
Her/O lord/O father/O promised/O her/O to/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O and/O so/O it/O was/O to/O him/O that/O she/O gave/O her/O token/O ,/O a/O pale/O blue/O handscarf/O she/O had/O embroidered/O with/O the/O leaping/O trout/O of/O Riverrun/LOCATION ./O 
As/O she/O pressed/O it/O into/O his/O hand/O ,/O she/O pleaded/O with/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O is/O only/O a/O foolish/O boy/O ,/O but/O I/O have/O loved/O him/O like/O a/O brother/O ./O 
It/O would/O grieve/O me/O to/O see/O him/O die/O ./O 
\/O ''/O And/O her/O betrothed/O looked/O at/O her/O with/O the/O cool/O grey/O eyes/O of/O a/O Stark/O and/O promised/O to/O spare/O the/O boy/O who/O loved/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O fight/O was/O over/O almost/O as/O soon/O as/O it/O began/O ./O 
Brandon/PERSON was/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O and/O he/O drove/O Littlefinger/PERSON all/O the/O way/O across/O the/O bailey/O and/O down/O the/O water/O stair/O ,/O raining/O steel/O on/O him/O with/O every/O step/O ,/O until/O the/O boy/O was/O staggering/O and/O bleeding/O from/O a/O dozen/O wounds/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yield/O !/O 
\/O ''/O he/O called/O ,/O more/O than/O once/O ,/O but/O Petyr/PERSON would/O only/O shake/O his/O head/O and/O fight/O on/O ,/O grimly/O ./O 
When/O the/O river/O was/O lapping/O at/O their/O ankles/O ,/O Brandon/PERSON finally/O ended/O it/O ,/O with/O a/O brutal/O backhand/O cut/O that/O bit/O through/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Petyr/O 's/O rings/O and/O leather/O into/O the/O soft/O flesh/O below/O the/O ribs/O ,/O so/O deep/O that/O Catelyn/PERSON was/O certain/O that/O the/O wound/O was/O mortal/O ./O 
He/O looked/O at/O her/O as/O he/O fell/O and/O murmured/O \/O ``/O Cat/O \/O ''/O as/O the/O bright/O blood/O came/O flowing/O out/O between/O his/O mailed/O fingers/O ./O 
She/O thought/O she/O had/O forgotten/O that/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O That/O was/O the/O last/O time/O she/O had/O seen/O his/O face/O .../O until/O the/O day/O she/O was/O brought/O before/O him/O in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O fortnight/O passed/O before/O Littlefinger/PERSON was/O strong/O enough/O to/O leave/O Riverrun/PERSON ,/O but/O her/O lord/O father/O forbade/O her/O to/O visit/O him/O in/O the/O tower/O where/O he/O lay/O abed/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON helped/O their/O maester/O nurse/O him/O ;/O she/O had/O been/O softer/O and/O shyer/O in/O those/O days/O ./O 
Edmure/PERSON had/O called/O on/O him/O as/O well/O ,/O but/O Petyr/PERSON had/O sent/O him/O away/O ./O 
Her/O brother/O had/O acted/O as/O Brandon/PERSON 's/O squire/O at/O the/O duel/O ,/O and/O Littlefinger/PERSON would/O not/O forgive/O that/O ./O 
As/O soon/O as/O he/O was/O strong/O enough/O to/O be/O moved/O ,/O Lord/O Hoster/PERSON Tully/PERSON sent/O Petyr/PERSON Baelish/PERSON away/O in/O a/O closed/O litter/O ,/O to/O finish/O his/O healing/O on/O the/O Fingers/O ,/O upon/O the/O windswept/O jut/O of/O rock/O where/O he/O 'd/O been/O born/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O ringing/O clash/O of/O steel/O on/O steel/O jarred/O Catelyn/LOCATION back/O to/O the/O present/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON was/O coming/O hard/O at/O Bronn/LOCATION ,/O driving/O into/O him/O with/O shield/O and/O sword/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O scrambled/O backward/O ,/O checking/O each/O blow/O ,/O stepping/O lithely/O over/O rock/O and/O root/O ,/O his/O eyes/O never/O leaving/O his/O foe/O ./O 
He/O was/O quicker/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON saw/O ;/O the/O knight/O 's/O silvered/O sword/O never/O came/O near/O to/O touching/O him/O ,/O but/O his/O own/O ugly/O grey/O blade/O hacked/O a/O notch/O from/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O plate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O brief/O flurry/O of/O fighting/O ended/O as/O swiftly/O as/O it/O had/O begun/O when/O Bronn/PERSON sidestepped/O and/O slid/O behind/O the/O statue/O of/O the/O weeping/O woman/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON lunged/O at/O where/O he/O had/O been/O ,/O striking/O a/O spark/O off/O the/O pate/O marble/O of/O Alyssa/PERSON 's/O thigh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 're/O not/O fighting/O good/O ,/O Mother/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O complained/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O want/O them/O to/O fight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O will/O ,/O sweet/O baby/O ,/O \/O ''/O his/O mother/O soothed/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O sellsword/O ca/O n't/O run/O all/O day/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Some/O of/O the/O lords/O on/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O terrace/O were/O making/O wry/O jests/O as/O they/O refilled/O their/O wine/O cups/O ,/O but/O across/O the/O garden/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON 's/O mismatched/O eyes/O watched/O the/O champions/O dance/O as/O if/O there/O were/O nothing/O else/O in/O the/O world/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON came/O out/O from/O behind/O the/O statue/O hard/O and/O fast/O ,/O still/O moving/O left/O ,/O aiming/O a/O two-handed/O cut/O at/O the/O knight/O 's/O unshielded/O right/O side/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON blocked/O ,/O but/O clumsily/O ,/O and/O the/O sellsword/O 's/O blade/O flashed/O upward/O at/O his/O head/O ./O 
Metal/O rang/O ,/O and/O a/O falcon/O 's/O wing/O collapsed/O with/O a/O crunch/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON took/O a/O half/O step/O back/O to/O brace/O himself/O ,/O raised/O his/O shield/O ./O 
Oak/O chips/O flew/O as/O Bronn/PERSON 's/O sword/O hacked/O at/O the/O wooden/O wall/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O stepped/O left/O again/O ,/O away/O from/O the/O shield/O ,/O and/O caught/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON across/O the/O stomach/O ,/O the/O razor/O edge/O of/O his/O blade/O leaving/O a/O bright/O gash/O when/O it/O bit/O into/O the/O knight/O 's/O plate/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O drove/O forward/O off/O his/O back/O foot/O ,/O his/O own/O silver/O blade/O descending/O in/O a/O savage/O arc/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON slammed/O it/O aside/O and/O danced/O away/O ./O 
The/O knight/O crashed/O into/O the/O weeping/O woman/O ,/O rocking/O her/O on/O her/O plinth/O ./O 
Staggered/O ,/O he/O stepped/O backward/O ,/O his/O head/O turning/O this/O way/O and/O that/O as/O he/O searched/O for/O his/O foe/O ./O 
The/O slit/O visor/O of/O his/O helm/O narrowed/O his/O vision/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Behind/O you/O ,/O ser/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lord/O Hunter/PERSON shouted/O ,/O too/O late/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON brought/O his/O sword/O down/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O catching/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON in/O the/O elbow/O of/O his/O sword/O arm/O ./O 
The/O thin/O lobstered/O metal/O that/O protected/O the/O joint/O crunched/O ./O 
The/O knight/O grunted/O ,/O turning/O ,/O wrenching/O his/O weapon/O up/O ./O 
This/O time/O Bronn/PERSON stood/O ''/O ,/O ``/O his/O ground/O ./O 
The/O swords/O flew/O at/O each/O other/O ,/O and/O their/O steel/O song/O filled/O the/O garden/O and/O rang/O off/O the/O white/O towers/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Ser/O Vardis/O is/O hurt/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ,/O his/O voice/O grave/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Catelyn/PERSON did/O not/O need/O to/O be/O told/O ;/O she/O had/O eyes/O ,/O she/O could/O see/O the/O bright/O finger/O of/O blood/O running/O along/O the/O knight/O 's/O forearm/O ,/O the/O wetness/O inside/O the/O elbow/O joint/O ./O 
Every/O parry/O was/O a/O little/O slower/O and/O a/O little/O lower/O than/O the/O one/O before/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON turned/O his/O side/O to/O his/O foe/O ,/O trying/O to/O use/O his/O shield/O to/O block/O instead/O ,/O but/O Bronn/PERSON slid/O around/O him/O ,/O quick/O as/O a/O cat/O ./O 
The/O sellsword/O seemed/O to/O be/O getting/O stronger/O ./O 
His/O cuts/O were/O leaving/O their/O marks/O now/O ./O 
Deep/O shiny/O gashes/O gleamed/O all/O over/O the/O knight/O 's/O armor/O ,/O on/O his/O right/O thigh/O ,/O his/O beaked/O visor/O ,/O crossing/O on/O his/O breastplate/O ,/O a/O long/O one/O along/O the/O front/O of/O his/O gorget/O ./O 
The/O moon-and-falcon/O rondel/O over/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON 's/O right/O arm/O was/O sheared/O clean/O in/O half/O ,/O hanging/O by/O its/O strap/O ./O 
They/O could/O hear/O his/O labored/O breath/O ,/O rattling/O through/O the/O air/O holes/O in/O his/O visor/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Blind/PERSON with/O arrogance/O as/O they/O were/O ,/O even/O the/O knights/O and/O lords/O of/O the/O Vale/O could/O see/O what/O was/O happening/O below/O them/O ,/O yet/O her/O sister/O could/O not/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Enough/O ,/O Ser/O Vardis/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Lady/PERSON Lysa/PERSON called/O down/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Finish/O him/O now/O ,/O my/O baby/O is/O growing/O tired/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O it/O must/O be/O said/O of/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON that/O he/O was/O true/O to/O his/O lady/O 's/O command/O ,/O even/O to/O the/O last/O ./O 
One/O moment/O he/O was/O reeling/O backward/O ,/O half-crouched/O behind/O his/O scarred/O shield/O ;/O the/O next/O he/O charged/O ./O 
The/O sudden/O bull/O rush/O caught/O Bronn/LOCATION off/O balance/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON crashed/O into/O him/O and/O slammed/O the/O lip/O of/O his/O shield/O into/O the/O sellsword/O 's/O face/O ./O 
Almost/O ,/O almost/O ,/O Bronn/PERSON lost/O his/O feet/O .../O he/O staggered/O back/O ,/O tripped/O over/O a/O rock/O ,/O and/O caught/O hold/O of/O the/O weeping/O woman/O to/O keep/O his/O balance/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Throwing/O aside/O his/O shield/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON lurched/O after/O him/O ,/O using/O both/O hands/O to/O raise/O his/O sword/O ./O 
His/O right/O arm/O was/O blood/O from/O elbow/O to/O fingers/O now/O ,/O yet/O his/O last/O desperate/O blow/O would/O have/O opened/O Bronn/LOCATION from/O neck/O to/O navel/O .../O if/O the/O sellsword/O had/O stood/O to/O receive/O it/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O But/O Bronn/PERSON jerked/O back/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON Arryn/PERSON 's/O beautiful/O engraved/O silver/O sword/O glanced/O off/O the/O marble/O elbow/O of/O the/O weeping/O woman/O and/O snapped/O clean/O a/O third/O of/O the/O way/O up/O the/O blade/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON put/O his/O shoulder/O into/O the/O statue/O 's/O back/O ./O 
The/O weathered/O likeness/O of/O Alyssa/PERSON Arryn/PERSON tottered/O and/O fell/O with/O a/O great/O crash/O ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON went/O down/O beneath/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bronn/PERSON was/O on/O him/O in/O a/O heartbeat/O ,/O kicking/O what/O was/O left/O of/O his/O shattered/O rondel/O aside/O to/O expose/O the/O weak/O spot/O between/O arm/O and/O breastplate/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Vardis/PERSON was/O lying/O on/O his/O side/O ,/O pinned/O beneath/O the/O broken/O torso/O of/O the/O weeping/O woman/O ./O 
Catelyn/PERSON heard/O the/O knight/O groan/O as/O the/O sellsword/O lifted/O his/O blade/O with/O both/O hands/O and/O drove/O it/O down/O and/O in/O with/O all/O his/O weight/O behind/O it/O ,/O under/O the/O arm/O and/O through/O the/O ribs/O ./O 
Ser/O Vardis/PERSON Egen/PERSON shuddered/O and/O lay/O still/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Silence/O hung/O over/O the/O Eyrie/O ./O 
Bronn/PERSON yanked/O off/O his/O halfhelm/O and/O let/O it/O fall/O to/O the/O grass/O ./O 
His/O lip/O was/O smashed/O and/O bloody/O where/O the/O shield/O had/O caught/O him/O ,/O and/O his/O coal-black/O hair/O was/O soaked/O with/O sweat/O ./O 
He/O spit/O out/O a/O broken/O tooth/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Is/O it/O over/O ,/O Mother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/O asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O No/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON wanted/O to/O tell/O him/O ,/O it/O 's/O only/O now/O beginning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON said/O glumly/O ,/O her/O voice/O as/O cold/O and/O dead/O as/O the/O captain/O of/O her/O guard/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Can/O I/O make/O the/O little/O man/O fly/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Across/O the/O garden/O ,/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON got/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Not/O this/O little/O man/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O little/O man/O is/O going/O down/O in/O the/O turnip/O hoist/O ,/O thank/O you/O very/O much/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O presume/O -/O \/O ''/O Lysa/PERSON began/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O presume/O that/O House/ORGANIZATION Arryn/O remembers/O its/O own/O words/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Imp/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O High/O as/O Honor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O promised/O I/O could/O make/O him/O fly/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O Lord/O of/O the/O Eyrie/PERSON screamed/O at/O his/O mother/O ./O 
He/O began/O to/O shake/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lady/O Lysa/PERSON 's/O face/O was/O flushed/O with/O fury/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O gods/O have/O seen/O fit/O to/O proclaim/O him/O innocent/O ,/O child/O ./O 
We/O have/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O free/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O She/O lifted/O her/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Guards/O ./O 
Take/O my/O lord/O of/O Lannister/O and/O his/O .../O creature/O here/O out/O of/O my/O sight/O ./O 
Escort/O them/O to/O the/O Bloody/O Gate/O and/O set/O them/O free/O ./O 
See/O that/O they/O have/O horses/O and/O supplies/O sufficient/O to/O reach/O the/O Trident/O ,/O and/O make/O certain/O all/O their/O goods/O and/O weapons/O are/O returned/O to/O them/O ./O 
They/O shall/O need/O them/O on/O the/O high/O road/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O high/O road/O ,/O \/O ''/O Tyrion/PERSON Lannister/PERSON said/O ./O 
Lysa/PERSON allowed/O herself/O a/O faint/O ,/O satisfied/O smile/O ./O 
It/O was/O another/O sort/O of/O death/O sentence/O ,/O Catelyn/PERSON realized/O ./O 
Tyrion/O Lannister/O must/O know/O that/O as/O well/O ./O 
Yet/O the/O dwarf/O favored/O Lady/PERSON Arryn/PERSON with/O a/O mocking/O bow/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O command/O ,/O my/O lady/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O believe/O we/O know/O the/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
