-LSB-/O ``/O BRAN/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O light/O snow/O was/O falling/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O feel/O the/O flakes/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O melting/O as/O they/O touched/O his/O skin/O like/O the/O gentlest/O of/O rains/O ./O 
He/O sat/O straight/O atop/O his/O horse/O ,/O watching/O as/O the/O iron/O portcullis/O was/O winched/O upward/O ./O 
Try/O as/O he/O might/O to/O keep/O calm/O ,/O his/O heart/O was/O fluttering/O in/O his/O chest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O you/O ready/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O nodded/O ,/O trying/O not/O to/O let/O his/O fear/O show/O ./O 
He/O had/O not/O been/O outside/O Winterfell/LOCATION since/O his/O fall/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O determined/O to/O ride/O out/O as/O proud/O as/O any/O knight/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O 's/O ride/O ,/O then/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON put/O his/O heels/O into/O his/O big/O grey-and-white/O gelding/O ,/O and/O the/O horse/O walked/O under/O the/O portcullis/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Go/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O whispered/O to/O his/O own/O horse/O ./O 
He/O touched/O her/O neck/O lightly/O ,/O and/O the/O small/O chestnut/O filly/O started/O forward/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O named/O her/O Dancer/O ./O 
She/O was/O two/O years/O old/O ,/O and/O Joseth/PERSON said/O she/O was/O smarter/O than/O any/O horse/O had/O a/O right/O to/O be/O ./O 
They/O had/O trained/O her/O special/O ,/O to/O respond/O to/O rein/O and/O voice/O and/O touch/O ./O 
Up/O to/O now/O ,/O Bran/O had/O only/O ridden/O her/O around/O the/O yard/O ./O 
At/O first/O Joseth/PERSON or/O Hodor/O would/O lead/O her/O ,/O while/O Bran/O sat/O strapped/O to/O her/O back/O in/O the/O oversize/O saddle/O the/O Imp/O had/O drawn/O up/O for/O him/O ,/O but/O for/O the/O past/O fortnight/O he/O had/O been/O riding/O her/O on/O his/O own/O ,/O trotting/O her/O round/O and/O round/O ,/O and/O growing/O bolder/O with/O every/O circuit/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O passed/O beneath/O the/O gatehouse/O ,/O over/O the/O drawbridge/O ,/O through/O the/O outer/O walls/O ./O 
Summer/O and/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON came/O loping/O beside/O them/O ,/O sniffing/O at/O the/O wind/O ./O 
Close/O behind/O came/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O with/O his/O longbow/O and/O a/O quiver/O of/O broadheads/O ;/O he/O had/O a/O mind/O to/O take/O a/O deer/O ,/O he/O had/O told/O them/O ./O 
He/O was/O followed/O by/O four/O guardsmen/O in/O mailed/O shirts/O and/O coifs/O ,/O and/O Joseth/PERSON ,/O a/O stick-thin/O stableman/O whom/O Robb/PERSON had/O named/O master/O of/O horse/O while/O Hullen/PERSON was/O away/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON brought/O up/O the/O rear/O ,/O riding/O on/O a/O donkey/O ./O 
Bran/O would/O have/O liked/O it/O better/O if/O he/O and/O Robb/PERSON had/O gone/O off/O alone/O ,/O just/O the/O two/O of/O them/O ,/O but/O Hal/PERSON Mo/PERSON lien/PERSON would/O not/O hear/O of/O it/O ,/O and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON backed/O him/O ./O 
If/O Bran/O fell/O off/O his/O horse/O or/O injured/O himself/O ,/O the/O maester/O was/O determined/O to/O be/O with/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Beyond/O the/O castle/O lay/O the/O market/O square/O ,/O its/O wooden/O stalls/O deserted/O now/O ./O 
They/O rode/O down/O the/O muddy/O streets/O of/O the/O village/O ,/O past/O rows/O of/O small/O neat/O houses/O of/O log/O and/O undressed/O stone/O ./O 
Less/O than/O one/O in/O five/O were/O occupied/O ,/O thin/O tendrils/O of/O woodsmoke/O curling/O up/O from/O their/O chimneys/O ./O 
The/O rest/O would/O fill/O up/O one/O by/O one/O as/O it/O grew/O colder/O ./O 
When/O the/O snow/O fell/O and/O the/O ice/O winds/O howled/O down/O out/O of/O the/O north/O ,/O Old/O Nan/PERSON said/O ,/O farmers/O left/O their/O frozen/O fields/O and/O distant/O holdfasts/O ,/O loaded/O up/O their/O wagons/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O winter/O town/O came/O alive/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O never/O seen/O it/O happen/O ,/O but/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON said/O the/O day/O was/O looming/O closer/O ./O 
The/O end/O of/O the/O long/O summer/O was/O near/O at/O hand/O ./O 
Winter/O is/O coming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O few/O villagers/O eyed/O the/O direwolves/O anxiously/O as/O the/O riders/O went/O past/O ,/O and/O one/O man/O dropped/O the/O wood/O he/O was/O carrying/O as/O he/O shrank/O away/O in/O fear/O ,/O but/O most/O of/O the/O townfolk/O had/O grown/O used/O to/O the/O sight/O ./O 
They/O bent/O the/O knee/O when/O they/O saw/O the/O boys/O ,/O and/O Robb/PERSON greeted/O each/O of/O them/O with/O a/O lordly/O nod/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O With/O his/O legs/O unable/O to/O grip/O ,/O the/O swaying/O motion/O of/O the/O horse/O made/O Bran/O feel/O unsteady/O at/O first/O ,/O but/O the/O huge/O saddle/O with/O its/O thick/O horn/O and/O high/O back/O cradled/O him/O comfortingly/O ,/O and/O the/O straps/O ''/O ,/O ``/O around/O his/O chest/O and/O thighs/O would/O not/O allow/O him/O to/O fall/O ./O 
After/O a/O time/O the/O rhythm/O began/O to/O feel/O almost/O natural/O ./O 
His/O anxiety/O faded/O ,/O and/O a/O tremulous/O smile/O crept/O across/O his/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Two/O serving/O wenches/O stood/O beneath/O the/O sign/O of/O the/O Smoking/O Log/O ,/O the/O local/O alehouse/O ./O 
When/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON called/O out/O to/O them/O ,/O the/O younger/O girl/O turned/O red/O and/O covered/O her/O face/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON spurred/O his/O mount/O to/O move/O up/O beside/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Sweet/PERSON Kyra/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O with/O a/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O squirms/O like/O a/O weasel/O in/O bed/O ,/O but/O say/O a/O word/O to/O her/O on/O the/O street/O ,/O and/O she/O blushes/O pink/O as/O a/O maid/O ./O 
Did/O I/O ever/O tell/O you/O about/O the/O night/O that/O she/O and/O Bessa/PERSON -/O \/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Not/O where/O my/O brother/O can/O hear/O ,/O Theon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON warned/O him/O with/O a/O glance/O at/O Bran/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O looked/O away/O and/O pretended/O not/O to/O have/O heard/O ,/O but/O he/O could/O feel/O Greyjoy/PERSON 's/O eyes/O on/O him/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O he/O was/O smiling/O ./O 
He/O smiled/O a/O lot/O ,/O as/O if/O the/O world/O were/O a/O secret/O joke/O that/O only/O he/O was/O clever/O enough/O to/O understand/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON seemed/O to/O admire/O Theon/PERSON and/O enjoy/O his/O company/O ,/O but/O Bran/ORGANIZATION had/O never/O warmed/O to/O his/O father/O 's/O ward/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON rode/O closer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O doing/O well/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O go/O faster/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O replied/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O sent/O his/O gelding/O into/O a/O trot/O ./O 
The/O wolves/O raced/O after/O him/O ./O 
Bran/O snapped/O the/O reins/O sharply/O ,/O and/O Dancer/O picked/O up/O her/O pace/O ./O 
He/O heard/O a/O shout/O from/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O and/O the/O hoofbeats/O of/O the/O other/O horses/O behind/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O 's/O cloak/O billowed/O out/O ,/O rippling/O in/O the/O wind/O ,/O and/O the/O snow/O seemed/O to/O rush/O at/O his/O face/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON was/O well/O ahead/O ,/O glancing/O back/O over/O his/O shoulder/O from/O time/O to/O time/O to/O make/O sure/O Bran/O and/O the/O others/O were/O following/O ./O 
He/O snapped/O the/O reins/O again/O ./O 
Smooth/O as/O silk/O ,/O Dancer/O slid/O into/O a/O gallop/O ./O 
The/O distance/O closed/O ./O 
By/O the/O time/O he/O caught/O Robb/PERSON on/O the/O edge/O of/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O two/O miles/O beyond/O the/O winter/O town/O ,/O they/O had/O left/O the/O others/O well/O behind/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O can/O tide/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O shouted/O ,/O grinning/O ./O 
It/O felt/O almost/O as/O good/O as/O flying/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'd/O race/O you/O ,/O but/O I/O fear/O you/O 'd/O win/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON 's/O tone/O was/O light/O and/O joking/O ,/O yet/O Bran/O could/O tell/O that/O something/O was/O troubling/O his/O brother/O underneath/O the/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O race/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O looked/O around/O for/O the/O direwolves/O ./O 
Both/O had/O vanished/O into/O the/O wood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Did/O you/O hear/O Summer/O howling/O last/O night/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON was/O restless/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
His/O auburn/O hair/O had/O grown/O shaggy/O and/O unkempt/O ,/O and/O a/O reddish/O stubble/O covered/O his/O jaw/O ,/O making/O him/O look/O older/O than/O his/O fifteen/O years/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sometimes/O I/O think/O they/O know/O things/O .../O sense/O things/O .../O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON sighed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O know/O how/O much/O to/O tell/O you/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
I/O wish/O you/O were/O older/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O eight/O now/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Eight/O is/O n't/O so/O much/O younger/O than/O fifteen/O ,/O and/O I/O 'm/O the/O heir/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON ,/O after/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O So/O you/O are/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON sounded/O sad/O ,/O and/O even/O a/O little/O scared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O I/O need/O to/O tell/O you/O something/O ./O 
There/O was/O a/O bird/O last/O night/O ./O 
From/O King/O 's/O Landing/O ./O 
Maester/O Luwin/O woke/O me/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O felt/O a/O sudden/O dread/O ./O 
Dark/O wings/O ,/O dark/O words/O ,/O Old/O Nan/PERSON always/O said/O ,/O and/O of/O late/O the/O messenger/O ravens/O had/O been/O proving/O the/O truth/O of/O the/O proverb/O ./O 
When/O Robb/PERSON wrote/O to/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O the/O bird/O that/O came/O back/O brought/O word/O that/O Uncle/PERSON Benjen/PERSON was/O still/O missing/O ./O 
Then/O a/O message/O had/O arrived/O from/O the/O Eyrie/LOCATION ,/O from/O Mother/O ,/O but/O that/O had/O not/O been/O good/O news/O either/O ./O 
She/O did/O not/O say/O when/O she/O meant/O to/O return/O ,/O only/O that/O she/O had/O taken/O the/O Imp/PERSON as/O ''/O ,/O ``/O prisoner/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O sort/O of/O liked/O the/O little/O man/O ,/O yet/O the/O name/O Lannister/O sent/O cold/O fingers/O creeping/O up/O his/O spine/O ./O 
There/O was/O something/O about/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O something/O he/O ought/O to/O remember/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O tried/O to/O think/O what/O ,/O he/O felt/O dizzy/O and/O his/O stomach/O clenched/O hard/O as/O a/O stone/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON spent/O most/O of/O that/O day/O locked/O behind/O closed/O doors/O with/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ,/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O and/O Hallis/PERSON Mollen/PERSON ./O 
Afterward/O ,/O riders/O were/O sent/O out/O on/O fast/O horses/O ,/O carrying/O Robb/PERSON 's/O commands/O throughout/O the/O north/O ./O 
Bran/O heard/O talk/O of/O Moat/PERSON Cailin/PERSON ,/O the/O ancient/O stronghold/O the/O First/O Men/O had/O built/O at/O the/O top/O of/O the/O Neck/O ./O 
No/O one/O ever/O told/O him/O what/O was/O happening/O ,/O yet/O he/O knew/O it/O was/O not/O good/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O now/O another/O raven/O ,/O another/O message/O ./O 
Bran/O clung/O to/O hope/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Was/O the/O bird/O from/O Mother/O ?/O 
Is/O she/O coming/O home/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O message/O was/O from/O Alyn/PERSON in/O King/ORGANIZATION 's/O Landing/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON Cassel/PERSON is/O dead/O ./O 
And/O Wyl/O and/O Heward/PERSON as/O well/O ./O 
Murdered/O by/O the/O Kingslayer/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON lifted/O his/O face/O to/O the/O snow/O ,/O and/O the/O flakes/O melted/O on/O his/O cheeks/O ./O 
\/O ``/O May/O the/O gods/O give/O them/O rest/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O did/O not/O know/O what/O to/O say/O ./O 
He/O felt/O as/O if/O he/O 'd/O been/O punched/O ./O 
Jory/PERSON had/O been/O captain/O of/O the/O household/O guard/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION since/O before/O Bran/O was/O born/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O killed/O Jory/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O remembered/O all/O the/O times/O Jory/PERSON had/O chased/O him/O over/O the/O roofs/O ./O 
He/O could/O picture/O him/O striding/O across/O the/O yard/O in/O mail/O and/O plate/O ,/O or/O sitting/O at/O his/O accustomed/O place/O on/O the/O bench/O in/O the/O Great/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O joking/O as/O he/O ate/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Why/O would/O anyone/O kill/O Jory/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON shook/O his/O head/O numbly/O ,/O the/O pain/O plain/O in/O his/O eyes/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ,/O and/O .../O Bran/O ,/O that/O 's/O not/O the/O worst/O of/O it/O ./O 
Father/O was/O caught/O beneath/O a/O falling/O horse/O in/O the/O fight/O ./O 
Alyn/PERSON says/O his/O leg/O was/O shattered/O ,/O and/O .../O Maester/PERSON Pycelle/PERSON has/O given/O him/O the/O milk/O of/O the/O poppy/O ,/O but/O they/O are/O n't/O sure/O when/O .../O when/O he/O .../O \/O ''/O The/O sound/O of/O hoofbeats/O made/O him/O glance/O down/O the/O road/O ,/O to/O where/O Theon/PERSON and/O the/O others/O were/O coming/O up/O ./O 
\/O ``/O When/O he/O will/O wake/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON finished/O ./O 
He/O laid/O his/O hand/O on/O the/O pommel/O of/O his/O sword/O then/O ,/O and/O went/O on/O in/O the/O solemn/O voice/O of/O Robb/PERSON the/O Lord/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bran/O ,/O I/O promise/O you/O ,/O whatever/O might/O happen/O ,/O I/O will/O not/O let/O this/O be/O forgotten/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Something/O in/O his/O tone/O made/O Bran/O even/O more/O fearful/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O will/O you/O do/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O as/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON reined/O in/O beside/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Theon/PERSON thinks/O I/O should/O call/O the/O banners/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Blood/O for/O blood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O For/O once/O Greyjoy/PERSON did/O not/O smile/O ./O 
His/O lean/O ,/O dark/O face/O had/O a/O hungry/O look/O to/O it/O ,/O and/O black/O hair/O fell/O down/O across/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Only/O the/O lord/O can/O call/O the/O banners/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O as/O the/O snow/O drifted/O down/O around/O them/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O If/O your/O father/O dies/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Robb/PERSON will/O be/O Lord/O of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O wo/O n't/O die/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O screamed/O at/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON took/O his/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O wo/O n't/O die/O ,/O not/O Father/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O calmly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Still/O .../O the/O honor/O of/O the/O north/O is/O in/O my/O hands/O now/O ./O 
When/O our/O lord/O father/O took/O his/O leave/O of/O us/O ,/O he/O told/O me/O to/O be/O strong/O for/O you/O and/O for/O Rickon/PERSON ./O 
I/O 'm/O almost/O a/O man/O grown/O ,/O Bran/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O shivered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wish/O Mother/O was/O back/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O miserably/O ./O 
He/O looked/O around/O for/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ;/O his/O donkey/O was/O visible/O in/O the/O far/O distance/O ,/O trotting/O over/O a/O rise/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Does/O Maester/O Luwin/O say/O to/O call/O the/O banners/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O maester/O is/O timid/O as/O an/O old/O woman/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Theon/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Father/O always/O listened/O to/O his/O counsel/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O reminded/O his/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mother/O too/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O listen/O to/O him/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O listen/O to/O everyone/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O joy/O Bran/O had/O felt/O at/O the/O ride/O was/O gone/O ,/O melted/O away/O like/O the/O snowflakes/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
Not/O so/O long/O ago/O ,/O the/O thought/O of/O Robb/PERSON calling/O the/O banners/O and/O riding/O off/O to/O war/O would/O have/O filled/O him/O with/O excitement/O ,/O but/O now/O he/O felt/O only/O dread/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Can/O we/O go/O back/O now/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O cold/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON glanced/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O need/O to/O find/O the/O wolves/O ./O 
Can/O you/O stand/O to/O go/O a/O bit/O longer/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O can/O go/O as/O long/O as/O you/O can/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON had/O warned/O him/O to/O keep/O the/O ride/O short/O ,/O for/O fear/O of/O saddle/O sores/O ,/O but/O Bran/O would/O not/O admit/O to/O weakness/O in/O front/O of/O his/O brother/O ./O 
He/O was/O sick/O of/O the/O way/O everyone/O was/O always/O fussing/O over/O him/O and/O asking/O how/O he/O was/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O 's/O hunt/O down/O the/O hunters/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
Side/O by/O side/O ,/O they/O urged/O their/O mounts/O off/O the/O kingsroad/O and/O struck/O out/O into/O the/O wolfswood/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON dropped/O back/O and/O followed/O well/O behind/O them/O ,/O talking/O and/O joking/O with/O the/O guardsmen/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O nice/O under/O the/O trees/O ./O 
Bran/O kept/O Dancer/O to/O a/O walk/O ,/O holding/O the/O reins/O lightly/O and/O looking/O all/O around/O him/O as/O they/O went/O ./O 
He/O knew/O this/O wood/O ,/O but/O he/O had/O been/O so/O long/O confined/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON that/O he/O felt/O as/O though/O he/O were/O seeing/O it/O for/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
The/O smells/O filled/O his/O nostrils/O ;/O the/O sharp/O fresh/O tang/O of/O pine/O needles/O ,/O the/O earthy/O odor/O of/O wet/O rotting/O leaves/O ,/O the/O hints/O of/O animal/O musk/O and/O distant/O cooking/O fires/O ./O 
He/O caught/O a/O glimpse/O of/O a/O black/O squirrel/O moving/O through/O the/O snow-covered/O branches/O of/O an/O oak/O ,/O and/O paused/O to/O study/O the/O silvery/O web/O of/O an/O empress/O spider/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON and/O the/O others/O fell/O farther/O and/O farther/O behind/O ,/O until/O Bran/O could/O no/O longer/O hear/O their/O voices/O ./O 
From/O ahead/O came/O the/O faint/O sound/O of/O rushing/O waters/O ./O 
It/O grew/O louder/O until/O they/O reached/O the/O stream/O ./O 
Tears/O stung/O his/O eyes/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Bran/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O 's/O wrong/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O just/O remembering/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jory/PERSON brought/O us/O here/O once/O ,/O to/O fish/O for/O trout/O ./O 
You/O and/O me/O and/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
Do/O you/O remember/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O remember/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ,/O his/O voice/O quiet/O and/O sad/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O did/O n't/O catch/O anything/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O Jon/PERSON gave/O me/O his/O fish/O on/O the/O way/O back/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Will/O we/O ever/O see/O Jon/PERSON again/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O saw/O Uncle/PERSON Benjen/PERSON when/O the/O king/O came/O to/O visit/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON pointed/O out/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Jon/PERSON will/O visit/O too/O ,/O you/O 'll/O see/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O stream/O was/O running/O high/O and/O fast/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON dismounted/O and/O led/O his/O gelding/O across/O the/O ford/O ./O 
In/O the/O deepest/O part/O of/O the/O crossing/O ,/O the/O water/O came/O up/O to/O midthigh/O ./O 
He/O tied/O his/O horse/O to/O a/O tree/O on/O the/O far/O side/O ,/O and/O waded/O back/O across/O for/O Bran/O and/O Dancer/O ./O 
The/O current/O foamed/O around/O rock/O and/O root/O ,/O and/O Bran/O could/O feel/O the/O spray/O on/O his/O face/O as/O Robb/PERSON led/O him/O over/O ./O 
It/O made/O him/O smile/O ./O 
For/O a/O moment/O he/O felt/O strong/O again/O ,/O and/O whole/O ./O 
He/O looked/O up/O at/O the/O trees/O and/O dreamed/O of/O climbing/O them/O ,/O right/O up/O to/O the/O very/O top/O ,/O with/O the/O whole/O forest/O spread/O out/O beneath/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O were/O on/O the/O far/O side/O when/O they/O heard/O the/O howl/O ,/O a/O long/O rising/O wail/O that/O moved/O through/O the/O trees/O like/O a/O cold/O wind/O ./O 
Bran/O raised/O his/O head/O to/O listen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Summer/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
No/O sooner/O had/O he/O spoken/O than/O a/O second/O voice/O joined/O the/O first/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O 've/O made/O a/O kill/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O as/O he/O remounted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O best/O go/O and/O bring/O them/O back/O ./O 
Wait/O here/O ,/O Theon/PERSON and/O the/O others/O should/O be/O along/O shortly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O go/O with/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'll/O find/O them/O faster/O by/O myself/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON spurred/O his/O gelding/O and/O vanished/O into/O the/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Once/O he/O was/O gone/O ,/O the/O woods/O seemed/O to/O close/O in/O around/O Bran/O ./O 
The/O snow/O was/O falling/O more/O heavily/O now/O ./O 
Where/O it/O touched/O the/O ground/O it/O melted/O ,/O but/O all/O about/O him/O rock/O and/O root/O and/O branch/O wore/O a/O thin/O blanket/O of/O white/O ./O 
As/O he/O waited/O ,/O he/O was/O conscious/O of/O how/O uncomfortable/O he/O felt/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O feel/O his/O legs/O ,/O hanging/O useless/O in/O the/O stirrups/O ,/O but/O the/O strap/O around/O his/O chest/O was/O tight/O and/O chafing/O ,/O and/O the/O melting/O snow/O had/O soaked/O through/O his/O gloves/O to/O chill/O his/O hands/O ./O 
He/O wondered/O what/O was/O keeping/O Theon/PERSON and/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON and/O Joseth/PERSON and/O the/O rest/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O When/O he/O heard/O the/O rustle/O of/O leaves/O ,/O Bran/O used/O the/O reins/O to/O make/O Dancer/O turn/O ,/O expecting/O to/O see/O his/O friends/O ,/O but/O the/O ragged/O men/O who/O stepped/O out/O onto/O the/O bank/O of/O the/O stream/O were/O strangers/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Good/O day/O to/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O nervously/O ./O 
One/O look/O ,/O and/O Bran/O knew/O they/O were/O neither/O foresters/O nor/O farmers/O ./O 
He/O was/O suddenly/O conscious/O of/O how/O richly/O he/O was/O dressed/O ./O 
His/O surcoat/O was/O new/O ,/O dark/O grey/O wool/O with/O silver/O buttons/O ,/O and/O a/O heavy/O silver/O pin/O fastened/O his/O fur-trimmed/O cloak/O at/O the/O shoulders/O ./O 
His/O boots/O and/O gloves/O were/O lined/O with/O fur/O as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O All/O alone/O ,/O are/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O said/O the/O biggest/O of/O them/O ,/O a/O bald/O man/O with/O a/O raw/O windburnt/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Lost/O in/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O poor/O lad/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O lost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O did/O not/O like/O the/O way/O the/O strangers/O were/O looking/O at/O him/O ./O 
He/O counted/O four/O ,/O but/O when/O he/O turned/O his/O head/O ,/O he/O saw/O two/O others/O behind/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O My/O brother/O rode/O off/O just/O a/O moment/O ago/O ,/O and/O my/O guard/O will/O be/O here/O shortly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Your/O guard/O ,/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O a/O second/O man/O said/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON stubble/O covered/O his/O gaunt/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O what/O would/O they/O be/O guarding/O ,/O my/O little/O lord/O ?/O 
Is/O that/O a/O silver/O pin/O I/O see/O there/O on/O your/O cloak/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Pretty/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O a/O woman/O 's/O voice/O ./O 
She/O scarcely/O looked/O like/O a/O woman/O ;/O tall/O and/O lean/O ,/O with/O the/O same/O hard/O face/O as/O the/O others/O ,/O her/O hair/O hidden/O beneath/O a/O bowl-shaped/O halfhelm/O ./O 
The/O spear/O she/O held/O was/O eight/O feet/O of/O black/O oak/O ,/O tipped/O in/O rusted/O steel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Let/O 's/O have/O a/O look/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O big/O bald/O man/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O watched/O him/O anxiously/O ./O 
The/O man/O 's/O clothes/O were/O filthy/O ,/O fallen/O almost/O to/O pieces/O ,/O patched/O here/O with/O brown/O and/O here/O with/O blue/O and/O there/O with/O a/O dark/O green/O ,/O and/O faded/O everywhere/O to/O grey/O ,/O but/O once/O that/O cloak/O might/O have/O been/O black/O ./O 
The/O grey/O stubbly/O man/O wore/O black/O rags/O too/O ,/O he/O saw/O with/O a/O sudden/O start/O ./O 
Suddenly/O Bran/O remembered/O the/O oathbreaker/O his/O father/O had/O beheaded/O ,/O the/O day/O they/O had/O found/O the/O wolf/O pups/O ;/O that/O man/O had/O worn/O black/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O Father/PERSON said/O he/O had/O been/O a/O deserter/O from/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
No/O man/O is/O more/O dangerous/O ,/O he/O remembered/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON saying/O ./O 
The/O deserter/O knows/O his/O life/O is/O forfeit/O if/O he/O is/O taken/O ,/O so/O he/O will/O notflinch/O from/O any/O crime/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O vile/O or/O cruel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O pin/O ,/O lad/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O big/O man/O said/O ./O 
He/O held/O out/O his/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O 'll/O take/O the/O horse/O too/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O another/O of/O them/O ,/O a/O woman/O shorter/O than/O Robb/PERSON ,/O with/O a/O broad/O fiat/O face/O and/O lank/O yellow/O hair/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Get/O down/O ,/O and/O be/O quick/O about/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O A/O knife/O slid/O from/O her/O sleeve/O into/O her/O hand/O ,/O its/O edge/O jagged/O as/O a/O saw/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O blurted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O big/O man/O grabbed/O his/O reins/O before/O Bran/O could/O think/O to/O wheel/O Dancer/O around/O and/O gallop/O off/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O can/O ,/O lordling/O .../O and/O will/O ,/O if/O you/O know/O what/O 's/O good/O for/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Stiv/O ,/O look/O how/O he/O 's/O strapped/O on/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O tall/O woman/O pointed/O with/O her/O spear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Might/O be/O it/O 's/O the/O truth/O he/O 's/O telling/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Straps/O ,/O is/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Stiv/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O drew/O a/O dagger/O from/O a/O sheath/O at/O his/O belt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O ways/O to/O deal/O with/O straps/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O some/O kind/O of/O cripple/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O the/O short/O woman/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O flared/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'm/O Brandon/PERSON Stark/PERSON of/O Winterfell/LOCATION ,/O and/O you/O better/O let/O go/O of/O my/O horse/O ,/O or/O I/O 'll/O see/O you/O all/O dead/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O gaunt/O man/O with/O the/O grey/O stubbled/O face/O laughed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O 's/O a/O Stark/O ,/O true/O enough/O ./O 
Only/O a/O Stark/O would/O be/O fool/O enough/O to/O threaten/O where/O smarter/O men/O would/O beg/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Cut/O his/O little/O cock/O off/O and/O stuff/O it/O in/O his/O mouth/O ,/O \/O ''/O suggested/O the/O short/O woman/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O should/O shut/O him/O up/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 're/O as/O stupid/O as/O you/O are/O ugly/O ,/O Hali/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O tall/O woman/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O boy/O 's/O worth/O nothing/O dead/O ,/O but/O alive/O .../O gods/O be/O damned/O ,/O think/O what/O Mance/PERSON would/O give/O to/O have/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON 's/O own/O blood/O to/O hostage/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mance/O be/O damned/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O big/O man/O cursed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O want/O to/O go/O back/O there/O ,/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ?/O 
More/O fool/O you/O ./O 
Think/O the/O white/O walkers/O will/O care/O if/O you/O have/O a/O hostage/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O turned/O back/O to/O Bran/O and/O slashed/O at/O the/O strap/O around/O his/O thigh/O ./O 
The/O leather/O parted/O with/O a/O sigh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O stroke/O had/O been/O quick/O and/O careless/O ,/O biting/O deep/O ./O 
Looking/O down/O ,/O Bran/O glimpsed/O pale/O flesh/O where/O the/O wool/O of/O his/O leggings/O had/O parted/O ./O 
Then/O the/O blood/O began/O to/O flow/O ./O 
He/O watched/O the/O red/O stain/O spread/O ,/O feeling/O light-headed/O ,/O curiously/O apart/O ;/O there/O had/O been/O no/O pain/O ,/O not/O even/O a/O hint/O of/O feeling/O ./O 
The/O big/O man/O grunted/O in/O surprise/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Put/O down/O your/O steel/O now/O ,/O and/O I/O promise/O you/O shall/O have/O a/O quick/O and/O painless/O death/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON called/O out/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Bran/O looked/O up/O in/O desperate/O hope/O ,/O and/O there/O he/O was/O ./O 
The/O strength/O of/O the/O words/O were/O undercut/O by/O the/O way/O his/O voice/O cracked/O with/O strain/O ./O 
He/O was/O mounted/O ,/O the/O bloody/O carcass/O of/O an/O elk/O slung/O across/O the/O back/O of/O his/O horse/O ,/O his/O sword/O in/O a/O gloved/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O the/O man/O with/O the/O grey/O stubbly/O face/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O a/O fierce/O one/O ,/O he/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O mocked/O the/O short/O woman/O ./O 
Hali/PERSON ,/O they/O called/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O mean/O to/O fight/O us/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O n't/O be/O a/O fool/O ,/O lad/O ./O 
You/O 're/O one/O against/O six/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O tall/O woman/O ,/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O leveled/O her/O spear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Off/O the/O horse/O ,/O and/O throw/O down/O the/O sword/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O thank/O you/O kindly/O for/O the/O mount/O and/O for/O the/O venison/O ,/O and/O you/O and/O your/O brother/O can/O be/O on/O your/O way/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON whistled/O ./O 
They/O heard/O the/O faint/O sound/O of/O soft/O feet/O on/O wet/O leaves/O ./O 
The/O undergrowth/O parted/O ,/O low-hanging/O branches/O giving/O up/O their/O accumulation/O of/O snow/O ,/O and/O Grey/LOCATION Wind/LOCATION and/O Summer/O emerged/O from/O the/O green/O ./O 
Summer/O sniffed/O the/O air/O and/O growled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Wolves/O ,/O \/O ''/O gasped/O Hali/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Direwolves/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O said/O ./O 
Still/O half-grown/O ,/O they/O were/O as/O large/O as/O any/O wolf/O he/O had/O ever/O seen/O ,/O but/O the/O differences/O were/O easy/O to/O spot/O ,/O if/O you/O knew/O what/O to/O look/O for/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON and/O Farlen/PERSON the/O kennelmaster/O had/O taught/O him/O ./O 
A/O direwolf/O had/O a/O bigger/O head/O and/O longer/O legs/O in/O proportion/O to/O its/O body/O ,/O and/O its/O snout/O and/O jaw/O were/O markedly/O leaner/O and/O more/O pronounced/O ./O 
There/O was/O something/O ''/O ,/O ``/O gaunt/O and/O terrible/O about/O them/O as/O they/O stood/O there/O amid/O the/O gently/O falling/O snow/O ./O 
Fresh/O blood/O spotted/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON 's/O muzzle/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dogs/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O big/O bald/O man/O said/O contemptuously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Yet/O I/O 'm/O told/O there/O 's/O nothing/O like/O a/O wolfskin/O cloak/O to/O warm/O a/O man/O by/O night/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O made/O a/O sharp/O gesture/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Take/O them/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON shouted/O ,/O \/O ``/O Winterfell/O !/O 
\/O ''/O and/O kicked/O his/O horse/O ./O 
The/O gelding/O plunged/O down/O the/O bank/O as/O the/O ragged/O men/O closed/O ./O 
A/O man/O with/O an/O axe/O rushed/O in/O ,/O shouting/O and/O heedless/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON 's/O sword/O caught/O him/O full/O in/O the/O face/O with/O a/O sickening/O crunch/O and/O a/O spray/O of/O bright/O blood/O ./O 
The/O man/O with/O the/O gaunt/O stubbly/O face/O made/O a/O grab/O for/O the/O reins/O ,/O and/O for/O half/O a/O second/O he/O had/O them/O .../O and/O then/O Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON was/O on/O him/O ,/O bearing/O him/O down/O ./O 
He/O fell/O back/O into/O the/O stream/O with/O a/O splash/O and/O a/O shout/O ,/O flailing/O wildly/O with/O his/O knife/O as/O his/O head/O went/O under/O ./O 
The/O direwo/O If/O plunged/O in/O after/O him/O ,/O and/O the/O white/O water/O turned/O red/O where/O they/O had/O vanished/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON and/O Osha/ORGANIZATION matched/O blows/O in/O midstream/O ./O 
Her/O long/O spear/O was/O a/O steel-headed/O serpent/O ,/O flashing/O out/O at/O his/O chest/O ,/O once/O ,/O twice/O ,/O three/O times/O ,/O but/O Robb/PERSON parried/O every/O thrust/O with/O his/O longsword/O ,/O turning/O the/O point/O aside/O ./O 
On/O the/O fourth/O or/O fifth/O thrust/O ,/O the/O tall/O woman/O overextended/O herself/O and/O lost/O her/O balance/O ,/O just/O for/O a/O second/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON charged/O ,/O riding/O her/O down/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O A/O few/O feet/O away/O ,/O Summer/O darted/O in/O and/O snapped/O at/O Hali/LOCATION ./O 
The/O knife/O bit/O at/O his/O flank/O ./O 
Summer/O slid/O away/O ,/O snarling/O ,/O and/O came/O rushing/O in/O again/O ./O 
This/O time/O his/O jaws/O closed/O around/O her/O calf/O ./O 
Holding/O the/O knife/O with/O both/O hands/O ,/O the/O small/O woman/O stabbed/O down/O ,/O but/O the/O direwo/O If/O seemed/O to/O sense/O the/O blade/O coming/O ./O 
He/O pulled/O free/O for/O an/O instant/O ,/O his/O mouth/O full/O of/O leather/O and/O cloth/O and/O bloody/O flesh/O ./O 
When/O Hali/PERSON stumbled/O and/O fell/O ,/O he/O came/O at/O her/O again/O ,/O slamming/O her/O backward/O ,/O teeth/O tearing/O at/O her/O belly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sixth/O man/O ran/O from/O the/O carnage/O .../O but/O not/O far/O ./O 
As/O he/O went/O scrambling/O up/O the/O far/O side/O of/O the/O bank/O ,/O Grey/ORGANIZATION Wind/ORGANIZATION emerged/O from/O the/O stream/O ,/O dripping/O wet/O ./O 
He/O shook/O the/O water/O off/O and/O bounded/O after/O the/O running/O man/O ,/O hamstringing/O him/O with/O a/O single/O snap/O of/O his/O teeth/O ,/O and/O going/O for/O the/O throat/O as/O the/O screaming/O man/O slid/O back/O down/O toward/O the/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O then/O there/O was/O no/O one/O left/O but/O the/O big/O man/O ,/O Stiv/PERSON ./O 
He/O slashed/O at/O Bran/O 's/O chest/O strap/O ,/O grabbed/O his/O arm/O ,/O and/O yanked/O ./O 
Suddenly/O Bran/O was/O falling/O ./O 
He/O sprawled/O on/O the/O ground/O ,/O his/O legs/O tangled/O under/O him/O ,/O one/O foot/O in/O the/O stream/O ./O 
He/O could/O not/O feel/O the/O cold/O of/O the/O water/O ,/O but/O he/O felt/O the/O steel/O when/O Stiv/PERSON pressed/O his/O dagger/O to/O his/O throat/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Back/O away/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O warned/O ,/O \/O ``/O or/O I/O 'll/O open/O the/O boy/O 's/O windpipe/O ,/O I/O swear/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON reined/O his/O horse/O in/O ,/O breathing/O hard/O ./O 
The/O fury/O went/O out/O of/O his/O eyes/O ,/O and/O his/O sword/O arm/O dropped/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O In/O that/O moment/O Bran/O saw/O everything/O ./O 
Summer/O was/O savaging/O Hali/PERSON ,/O pulling/O glistening/O blue/O snakes/O from/O her/O belly/O ./O 
Her/O eyes/O were/O wide/O and/O staring/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O not/O tell/O whether/O she/O was/O alive/O or/O dead/O ./O 
The/O grey/O stubbly/O man/O and/O the/O one/O with/O the/O axe/O lay/O unmoving/O ,/O but/O Osha/ORGANIZATION was/O on/O her/O knees/O ,/O crawling/O toward/O her/O fallen/O spear/O ./O 
Grey/O Wind/O padded/O toward/O her/O ,/O dripping/O wet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Call/O him/O off/O !/O 
\/O ''/O the/O big/O man/O shouted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Call/O them/O both/O off/O ,/O or/O the/O cripple/O boy/O dies/O now/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Grey/O Wind/O ,/O Summer/O ,/O to/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O direwolves/O stopped/O ,/O turned/O their/O heads/O ./O 
Grey/PERSON Wind/PERSON loped/O back/O to/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
Summer/O stayed/O where/O he/O was/O ,/O his/O eyes/O on/O Bran/O and/O the/O man/O beside/O him/O ./O 
He/O growled/O ./O 
His/O muzzle/O was/O wet/O and/O red/O ,/O but/O his/O eyes/O burned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION used/O the/O butt/O end/O of/O her/O spear/O to/O lever/O herself/O back/O to/O her/O feet/O ./O 
Blood/O leaked/O from/O a/O wound/O on/O the/O upper/O arm/O where/O Robb/PERSON had/O cut/O her/O ./O 
Bran/O could/O see/O sweat/O trickling/O down/O the/O big/O man/O 's/O face/O ./O 
Stiv/PERSON was/O as/O scared/O as/O he/O was/O ,/O he/O realized/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Starks/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O the/O man/O muttered/O ,/O \/O ``/O bloody/O Starks/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O raised/O his/O voice/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O kill/O the/O wolves/O and/O get/O his/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Kill/O them/O yourself/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O replied/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'll/O not/O be/O getting/O near/O those/O monsters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O For/O a/O moment/O Stiv/PERSON was/O at/O a/O loss/O ./O 
His/O hand/O trembled/O ;/O Bran/PERSON felt/O a/O trickle/O of/O blood/O where/O the/O knife/O pressed/O against/O his/O neck/O ./O 
The/O stench/O of/O the/O man/O filled/O his/O nose/O ;/O he/O smelled/O of/O fear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O called/O out/O to/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O a/O name/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O Robb/PERSON Stark/PERSON ,/O the/O heir/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O This/O is/O your/O brother/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O want/O him/O alive/O ,/O you/O do/O what/O I/O say/O ./O 
Off/O the/O horse/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON hesitated/O a/O moment/O ./O 
Then/O ,/O slowly/O and/O deliberately/O ,/O he/O dismounted/O and/O stood/O with/O his/O sword/O in/O hand/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Now/O kill/O the/O wolves/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON did/O not/O move/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O do/O it/O ./O 
The/O wolves/O or/O the/O boy/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Bran/O screamed/O ./O 
If/O Robb/PERSON did/O as/O they/O asked/O ,/O Stiv/PERSON would/O kill/O them/O both/O anyway/O ,/O once/O the/O direwolves/O were/O dead/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O bald/O man/O took/O hold/O of/O his/O hair/O with/O his/O free/O hand/O and/O twisted/O it/O cruelly/O ,/O till/O Bran/O sobbed/O in/O pain/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O shut/O your/O mouth/O ,/O cripple/O ,/O you/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O twisted/O harder/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O hear/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O A/O low/O thrum/O came/O from/O the/O woods/O behind/O them/O ./O 
Stiv/PERSON gave/O a/O choked/O gasp/O as/O a/O half/O foot/O of/O razor-tipped/O broadhead/O suddenly/O exploded/O out/O of/O his/O chest/O ./O 
The/O arrow/O was/O bright/O red/O ,/O as/O if/O it/O had/O been/O painted/O in/O blood/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O dagger/O fell/O away/O from/O Bran/O 's/O throat/O ./O 
The/O big/O man/O swayed/O and/O collapsed/O ,/O facedown/O in/O the/O stream/O ./O 
The/O arrow/O broke/O beneath/O him/O ./O 
Bran/O watched/O his/O life/O go/O swirling/O off/O in/O the/O water/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION glanced/O around/O as/O Father/O 's/O guardsmen/O appeared/O from/O beneath/O the/O trees/O ,/O steel/O in/O hand/O ./O 
She/O threw/O down/O her/O spear/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Mercy/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O called/O to/O Robb/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O guardsmen/O had/O a/O strange/O ,/O pale/O look/O to/O their/O faces/O as/O they/O took/O in/O the/O scene/O of/O slaughter/O ./O 
They/O eyed/O the/O wolves/O uncertainly/O ,/O and/O when/O Summer/O returned/O to/O Hali/PERSON 's/O corpse/O to/O feed/O ,/O Joseth/PERSON dropped/O his/O knife/O and/O scrambled/O for/O the/O bush/O ,/O heaving/O ./O 
Even/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON seemed/O shocked/O as/O he/O stepped/O from/O behind/O a/O tree/O ,/O but/O only/O for/O an/O instant/O ./O 
Then/O he/O shook/O his/O head/O and/O waded/O across/O the/O stream/O to/O Bran/O 's/O side/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O hurt/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O cut/O my/O leg/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/PERSON said/O ,/O \/O ``/O but/O I/O could/O n't/O feel/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O As/O the/O maester/O knelt/O to/O examine/O the/O wound/O ,/O Bran/PERSON turned/O his/O head/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON stood/O beside/O a/O sentinel/O tree/O ,/O his/O bow/O in/O hand/O ./O 
He/O was/O smiling/O ./O 
Ever/O smiling/O ./O 
A/O half-dozen/O arrows/O were/O thrust/O ''/O ,/O ``/O into/O the/O soft/O ground/O at/O his/O feet/O ,/O but/O it/O had/O taken/O only/O one/O ./O 
\/O ``/O A/O dead/O enemy/O is/O a/O thing/O of/O beauty/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O announced/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON always/O said/O you/O were/O an/O ass/O ,/O Greyjoy/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O loudly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O ought/O to/O chain/O you/O up/O in/O the/O yard/O and/O let/O Bran/O take/O a/O few/O practice/O shots/O at/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O should/O be/O thanking/O me/O for/O saving/O your/O brother/O 's/O life/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O if/O you/O had/O missed/O the/O shot/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O if/O you/O 'd/O only/O wounded/O him/O ?/O 
What/O if/O you/O had/O made/O his/O hand/O jump/O ,/O or/O hit/O Bran/O instead/O ?/O 
For/O all/O you/O knew/O ,/O the/O man/O might/O have/O been/O wearing/O a/O breastplate/O ,/O all/O you/O could/O see/O was/O the/O back/O of/O his/O cloak/O ./O 
What/O would/O have/O happened/O to/O my/O brother/O then/O ?/O 
Did/O you/O ever/O think/O of/O that/O ,/O Greyjoy/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/O 's/O smile/O was/O gone/O ./O 
He/O gave/O a/O sullen/O shrug/O and/O began/O to/O pull/O his/O arrows/O from/O the/O ground/O ,/O one/O by/O one/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON glared/O at/O his/O guardsmen/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Where/O were/O you/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O demanded/O of/O them/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O sure/O you/O were/O close/O behind/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O men/O traded/O unhappy/O glances/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O were/O following/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Quent/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O youngest/O of/O them/O ,/O his/O beard/O a/O soft/O brown/O fuzz/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Only/O first/O we/O waited/O for/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON and/O his/O ass/O ,/O begging/O your/O pardons/O ,/O and/O then/O ,/O well/O ,/O as/O it/O were/O He/O glanced/O over/O at/O Theon/O and/O quickly/O looked/O away/O ,/O abashed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O spied/O a/O turkey/O ,/O \/O ''/O Theon/PERSON said/O ,/O annoyed/O by/O the/O question/O ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O was/O I/O to/O know/O that/O you/O 'd/O leave/O the/O boy/O alone/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON turned/O his/O head/O to/O look/O at/O Theon/PERSON once/O more/O ./O 
Bran/O had/O never/O seen/O him/O so/O angry/O ,/O yet/O he/O said/O nothing/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O knelt/O beside/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O badly/O is/O my/O brother/O wounded/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O more/O than/O a/O scratch/O ,/O \/O ''/O the/O maester/O said/O ./O 
He/O wet/O a/O cloth/O in/O the/O stream/O to/O clean/O the/O cut/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Two/O of/O them/O wear/O the/O black/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O Robb/PERSON as/O he/O worked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON glanced/O over/O at/O where/O Stiv/PERSON lay/O sprawled/O in/O the/O stream/O ,/O his/O ragged/O black/O cloak/O moving/O fitfully/O as/O the/O rushing/O waters/O tugged/O at/O it/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Deserters/O from/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O grimly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O must/O have/O been/O fools/O ,/O to/O come/O so/O close/O to/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Folly/O and/O desperation/O are/O ofttimes/O hard/O to/O tell/O apart/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Shall/O we/O bury/O them/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Quent/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O would/O not/O have/O buried/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Hack/O off/O their/O heads/O ,/O we/O 'll/O send/O them/O back/O to/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Leave/O the/O rest/O for/O the/O carrion/O crows/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O this/O one/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Quent/O jerked/O a/O thumb/O toward/O Osha/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON walked/O over/O to/O her/O ./O 
She/O was/O a/O head/O taller/O than/O he/O was/O ,/O but/O she/O dropped/O to/O her/O knees/O at/O his/O approach/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O me/O my/O life/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O of/O Stark/O ,/O and/O I/O am/O yours/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Mine/O ?/O 
What/O would/O I/O do/O with/O an/O oathbreaker/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O broke/O no/O oaths/O ./O 
Stiv/PERSON and/O Wallen/PERSON flew/O down/O off/O the/O Wall/O ,/O not/O me/O ./O 
The/O black/O crows/O got/O no/O place/O for/O women/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON sauntered/O closer/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Give/O her/O to/O the/O wolves/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O urged/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
The/O woman/O 's/O eyes/O went/O to/O what/O was/O left/O of/O Hali/PERSON ,/O and/O just/O as/O quickly/O away/O ./O 
She/O shuddered/O ./O 
Even/O the/O guardsmen/O looked/O queasy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O She/O 's/O a/O woman/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wildling/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bran/O told/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O said/O they/O should/O keep/O me/O alive/O so/O they/O could/O take/O me/O to/O Mance/PERSON Rayder/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O have/O a/O name/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Robb/PERSON asked/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Osha/ORGANIZATION ,/O as/O it/O please/O the/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O muttered/O sourly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Maester/PERSON Luwin/PERSON stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O might/O do/O well/O to/O question/O her/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Bran/O could/O see/O the/O relief/O on/O his/O brother/O 's/O face/O ./O 
\/O ``/O As/O you/O say/O ,/O Maester/O ./O 
Wayn/PERSON ,/O bind/O her/O hands/O ./O 
She/O 'll/O come/O back/O to/O Winterfell/PERSON with/O us/O .../O and/O live/O or/O die/O by/O the/O truths/O she/O gives/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
