-LSB-/O ``/O JON/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O breaking/O his/O fast/O on/O applecakes/O and/O blood/O sausage/O when/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON plopped/O himself/O down/O on/O the/O bench/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 've/O been/O summoned/O to/O the/O sept/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON said/O in/O an/O excited/O whisper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O passing/O me/O out/O of/O training/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O to/O be/O made/O a/O brother/O with/O the/O rest/O of/O you/O ./O 
Can/O you/O believe/O it/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O truly/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Truly/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O to/O assist/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON with/O the/O library/O and/O the/O birds/O ./O 
He/O needs/O someone/O who/O can/O read/O and/O write/O letters/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O 'll/O do/O well/O at/O that/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ,/O smiling/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON glanced/O about/O anxiously/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Is/O it/O time/O to/O go/O ?/O 
I/O should/O n't/O be/O late/O ,/O they/O might/O change/O their/O minds/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O was/O fairly/O bouncing/O as/O they/O crossed/O the/O weed-strewn/O courtyard/O ./O 
The/O day/O was/O warm/O and/O sunny/O ./O 
Rivulets/O of/O water/O trickled/O down/O the/O sides/O of/O the/O Wall/O ,/O so/O the/O ice/O seemed/O to/O sparkle/O and/O shine/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Inside/O the/O sept/O ,/O the/O great/O crystal/O caught/O the/O morning/O light/O as/O it/O streamed/O through/O the/O south/O -/O facing/O window/O and/O spread/O it/O in/O a/O rainbow/O on/O the/O altar/O ./O 
Pyp/PERSON 's/O mouth/O dropped/O open/O when/O he/O caught/O sight/O of/O Sam/PERSON ,/O and/O Toad/PERSON poked/O Grenn/PERSON in/O the/O ribs/O ,/O but/O no/O one/O dared/O say/O a/O word/O ./O 
Septon/PERSON Celladar/PERSON was/O swinging/O a/O censer/O ,/O filling/O the/O air/O with/O fragrant/O incense/O that/O reminded/O Jon/PERSON of/O Lady/O Stark/O 's/O little/O sept/O in/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
For/O once/O the/O septon/O seemed/O sober/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O high/O officers/O arrived/O in/O a/O body/O ;/O Maester/O Aemon/O leaning/O on/O Clydas/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON cold-eyed/O and/O grim/O ,/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON resplendent/O in/O a/O black/O wool/O doublet/O with/O silvered/O bearclaw/O fastenings/O ./O 
Behind/O them/O came/O the/O senior/O members/O of/O the/O three/O orders/O :/O red/O -/O faced/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON the/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON ,/O First/O Builder/O Othell/PERSON Yarwyck/PERSON ,/O and/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON ,/O who/O commanded/O the/O rangers/O in/O the/O absence/O of/O Benjen/O Stark/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Mormont/PERSON stood/O before/O the/O altar/O ,/O the/O rainbow/O shining/O on/O his/O broad/O bald/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O came/O to/O us/O outlaws/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O began/O ,/O \/O ``/O poachers/O ,/O rapers/O ,/O debtors/O ,/O killers/O ,/O and/O thieves/O ./O 
You/O came/O to/O us/O children/O ./O 
You/O came/O to/O us/O alone/O ,/O in/O chains/O ,/O with/O neither/O friends/O nor/O honor/O ./O 
You/O came/O to/O us/O rich/O ,/O and/O you/O came/O to/O us/O poor/O ./O 
Some/O of/O you/O bear/O the/O names/O of/O proud/O houses/O ./O 
Others/O have/O only/O bastards/O '/O names/O ,/O or/O no/O names/O at/O all/O ./O 
It/O makes/O no/O matter/O ./O 
All/O that/O is/O past/O now/O ./O 
On/O the/O Wall/O ,/O we/O are/O all/O one/O house/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O At/O evenfall/O ,/O as/O the/O sun/O sets/O and/O we/O face/O the/O gathering/O night/O ,/O you/O shall/O take/O your/O vows/O ./O 
From/O that/O moment/O ,/O you/O will/O be/O a/O Sworn/O Brother/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
Your/O crimes/O will/O be/O washed/O away/O ,/O your/O debts/O forgiven/O ./O 
So/O too/O you/O must/O wash/O away/O your/O former/O loyalties/O ,/O put/O aside/O your/O grudges/O ,/O forget/O old/O wrongs/O and/O old/O loves/O alike/O ./O 
Here/O you/O begin/O anew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O lives/O his/O life/O for/O the/O realm/O ./O 
Not/O for/O a/O king/O ,/O nor/O a/O lord/O ,/O nor/O the/O honor/O of/O this/O house/O or/O that/O house/O ,/O neither/O for/O gold/O nor/O glory/O nor/O a/O woman/O 's/O love/O ,/O but/O for/O the/O realm/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O people/O in/O it/O ./O 
A/O man/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O takes/O no/O wife/O and/O fathers/O no/O sons/O ./O 
Our/O wife/O is/O duty/O ./O 
Our/O mistress/O is/O honor/O ./O 
And/O you/O are/O the/O only/O sons/O we/O shall/O ever/O know/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O have/O learned/O the/O words/O of/O the/O vow/O ./O 
Think/O carefully/O before/O you/O say/O them/O ,/O for/O once/O you/O have/O taken/O the/O black/O ,/O there/O is/O no/O turning/O back/O ./O 
The/O penalty/O for/O desertion/O is/O death/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O Old/O Bear/O ''/O ,/O ``/O paused/O for/O a/O moment/O before/O he/O said/O ,/O \/O ``/O Are/O there/O any/O among/O you/O who/O wish/O to/O leave/O our/O company/O ?/O 
If/O so/O ,/O go/O now/O ,/O and/O no/O one/O shall/O think/O the/O less/O of/O you/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O No/O one/O moved/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Well/O and/O good/O ,/O \/O ''/O said/O Mormont/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O may/O take/O your/O vows/O here/O at/O evenfall/O ,/O before/O Septon/O Celladar/O and/O the/O first/O of/O your/O order/O ./O 
Do/O any/O of/O you/O keep/O to/O the/O old/O gods/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON stood/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O do/O ,/O my/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O expect/O you/O will/O want/O to/O say/O your/O words/O before/O a/O heart/O tree/O ,/O as/O your/O uncle/O did/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O gods/O of/O the/O sept/O had/O nothing/O to/O do/O with/O him/O ;/O the/O blood/O of/O the/O First/O Men/O flowed/O in/O the/O veins/O of/O the/O Starks/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O heard/O Grenn/PERSON whispering/O behind/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O There/O 's/O no/O godswood/O here/O ./O 
Is/O there/O ?/O 
I/O never/O saw/O a/O godswood/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O would/O n't/O see/O a/O herd/O of/O aurochs/O until/O they/O trampled/O you/O into/O the/O snow/O ,/O \/O ''/O Pyp/PERSON whispered/O back/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O would/O so/O ,/O \/O ''/O Grenn/PERSON insisted/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O 'd/O see/O them/O a/O long/O way/O off/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Mormont/O himself/O confirmed/O Grenn/PERSON 's/O doubts/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Castle/O Black/O has/O no/O need/O of/O a/O godswood/O ./O 
Beyond/O the/O Wall/O the/O haunted/O forest/O stands/O as/O it/O stood/O in/O the/O Dawn/O Age/O ,/O long/O before/O the/O Andals/O brought/O the/O Seven/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O 
You/O will/O find/O a/O grove/O of/O weirwoods/O half/O a/O league/O from/O this/O spot/O ,/O and/O mayhap/O your/O gods/O as/O well/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O My/O lord/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O voice/O made/O Jon/PERSON glance/O back/O in/O surprise/O ./O 
Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON was/O on/O his/O feet/O ./O 
The/O fat/O boy/O wiped/O his/O sweaty/O palms/O against/O his/O tunic/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Might/O I./O ./O 
./O 
might/O I/O go/O as/O well/O ?/O 
To/O say/O my/O words/O at/O this/O heart/O tree/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Does/O House/O Tarly/O keep/O the/O old/O gods/O too/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON replied/O in/O a/O thin/O ,/O nervous/O voice/O ./O 
The/O high/O officers/O frightened/O him/O ,/O Jon/PERSON knew/O ,/O the/O Old/O Bear/O most/O of/O all/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O was/O named/O in/O the/O light/O of/O the/O Seven/O at/O the/O sept/O on/O Horn/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION ,/O as/O my/O father/O was/O ,/O and/O his/O father/O ,/O and/O all/O the/O Tarlys/O for/O a/O thousand/O years/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O would/O you/O forsake/O the/O gods/O of/O your/O father/O and/O your/O House/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O wondered/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O is/O my/O House/ORGANIZATION now/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O Seven/O have/O never/O answered/O my/O prayers/O ./O 
Perhaps/O the/O old/O gods/O will/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O boy/O ,/O \/O ''/O Mormont/PERSON said/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON took/O his/O seat/O again/O ,/O as/O did/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O have/O placed/O each/O of/O you/O in/O an/O order/O ,/O as/O befits/O our/O need/O and/O your/O own/O strengths/O and/O skills/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON stepped/O forward/O and/O handed/O him/O a/O paper/O ./O 
The/O Lord/O Commander/O unrolled/O it/O and/O began/O to/O read/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Haider/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O builders/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O began/O ./O 
Haider/PERSON gave/O a/O stiff/O nod/O of/O approval/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Grenn/O ,/O to/O the/O rangers/O ./O 
Albett/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O builders/O ./O 
Pypar/O ,/O to/O the/O rangers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Pyp/O looked/O over/O at/O Jon/PERSON and/O wiggled/O his/O ears/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Samwell/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O stewards/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Sam/PERSON sagged/O with/O relief/O ,/O mopping/O at/O his/O brow/O with/O ,/O a/O scrap/O of/O silk/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Matthar/O ,/O to/O the/O rangers/O ./O 
Dareon/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O stewards/O ./O 
Todder/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O rangers/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON ,/O to/O the/O stewards/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O stewards/O ?/O 
For/O a/O moment/O Jon/PERSON could/O not/O believe/O what/O he/O had/O heard/O ./O 
Mormont/O must/O have/O read/O it/O wrong/O ./O 
He/O started/O to/O rise/O ,/O to/O open/O his/O mouth/O ,/O to/O tell/O them/O there/O had/O been/O a/O mistake/O .../O and/O then/O he/O saw/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON studying/O him/O ,/O eyes/O shiny/O as/O two/O flakes/O of/O obsidian/O ,/O and/O he/O knew/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Old/O Bear/O rolled/O up/O the/O paper/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Your/O firsts/O will/O instruct/O you/O in/O your/O duties/O ./O 
May/O all/O the/O gods/O preserve/O you/O ,/O brothers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O The/O Lord/O Commander/O favored/O them/O with/O a/O half/O bow/O ,/O and/O took/O his/O leave/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON went/O with/O him/O ,/O a/O thin/O smile/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O never/O seen/O the/O masterat-arms/O took/O quite/O so/O happy/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Rangers/O with/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Jaremy/PERSON Rykker/PERSON called/O when/O they/O were/O gone/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Pyp/O was/O staring/O at/O Jon/PERSON as/O he/O got/O slowly/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
His/O ears/O were/O red/O ./O 
Grenn/PERSON ,/O grinning/O broadly/O ,/O did/O not/O seem/O to/O realize/O that/O anything/O was/O amiss/O ./O 
Matt/PERSON and/O Toad/ORGANIZATION fell/O in/O beside/O them/O ,/O and/O they/O followed/O Ser/O Jaremy/O from/O the/O sept./O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Builders/O ,/O \/O ''/O announced/O lantern-jawed/O Othell/PERSON Yarwyck/PERSON ./O 
Haider/PERSON and/O Albert/PERSON trailed/O out/O after/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON looked/O around/O him/O in/O sick/O disbelief/O ./O 
Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON 's/O blind/O eyes/O were/O raised/O toward/O the/O light/O he/O could/O not/O see/O ./O 
The/O septon/O was/O arranging/O crystals/O on/O the/O altar/O ./O 
Only/O Sam/PERSON and/O Darcon/PERSON remained/O on/O the/O benches/O ;/O a/O fat/O boy/O ,/O a/O singer/O .../O and/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON rubbed/O his/O plump/O hands/O together/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Samwell/O ,/O you/O will/O assist/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON in/O the/O rookery/O and/O library/O ./O 
Chert/O is/O going/O to/O the/O kennels/O ,/O to/O help/O with/O the/O hounds/O ./O 
You/O shall/O have/O his/O cell/O ,/O so/O as/O to/O be/O close/O to/O the/O maester/O night/O and/O day/O ./O 
I/O trust/O you/O will/O take/O good/O care/O of/O him/O ./O 
He/O is/O very/O old/O and/O very/O precious/O to/O us/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Dareon/O ,/O I/O am/O told/O that/O you/O sang/O at/O many/O a/O high/O lord/O 's/O table/O and/O shared/O their/O meat/O and/O mead/O ./O 
We/O are/O sending/O you/O to/O Eastwatch/PERSON ./O 
It/O may/O be/O your/O palate/O will/O be/O some/O help/O to/O Cotter/PERSON Pyke/PERSON when/O merchant/O galleys/O come/O trading/O ./O 
We/O are/O paying/O too/O dear/O for/O salt/O beef/O and/O pickled/O fish/O ,/O and/O the/O quality/O of/O the/O olive/O oil/O we/O 're/O getting/O has/O been/O frightful/O ,/O Present/O yourself/O to/O Boreas/O when/O you/O arrive/O ,/O he/O will/O keep/O you/O busy/O between/O ships/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Marsh/PERSON turned/O his/O smile/O on/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Lord/O Commander/O Mormont/PERSON has/O requested/O you/O for/O his/O personal/O steward/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
You/O 'll/O sleep/O in/O a/O cell/O beneath/O his/O chambers/O ,/O in/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O tower/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O And/O what/O will/O my/O duties/O be/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON asked/O sharply/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Will/O I/O serve/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O 's/O meals/O ,/O help/O him/O fasten/O his/O clothes/O ,/O fetch/O hot/O water/O for/O his/O bath/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Certainly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Marsh/O frowned/O at/O Jon/PERSON 's/O tone/O ./O 
\/O ``/O And/O you/O will/O run/O his/O messages/O ,/O keep/O a/O fire/O burning/O in/O his/O chambers/O ,/O change/O his/O sheets/O and/O blankets/O daily/O ,/O and/O do/O all/O else/O that/O the/O Lord/O Commander/O might/O require/O of/O YOU/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O take/O me/O for/O a/O servant/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O No/O ,/O \/O ''/O Maester/PERSON Aemon/PERSON said/O ,/O from/O the/O back/O of/O the/O sept./O ./O 
Clydas/PERSON helped/O him/O stand/O ./O 
\/O ``/O We/O took/O you/O for/O a/O man/O of/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O .../O but/O perhaps/O we/O were/O wrong/O in/O that/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O It/O was/O all/O Jon/PERSON could/O do/O to/O stop/O himself/O from/O walking/O out/O ./O 
Was/O he/O supposed/O to/O churn/O butter/O and/O sew/O doublets/O like/O a/O girl/O for/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O days/O ?/O 
\/O ``/O May/O I/O go/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O stiffly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O As/O you/O wish/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON responded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Dareon/PERSON and/O Sam/PERSON left/O with/O him/O ./O 
They/O descended/O to/O the/O yard/O in/O silence/O ./O 
Outside/O ,/O Jon/PERSON looked/O up/O at/O the/O Wall/O shining/O in/O the/O sun/O ,/O the/O melting/O ice/O creeping/O down/O its/O side/O in/O a/O hundred/O thin/O fingers/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON 's/O rage/O was/O such/O that/O he/O would/O have/O smashed/O it/O all/O in/O an/O instant/O ,/O and/O the/O world/O be/O damned/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON said/O excitedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Wait/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O you/O see/O what/O they/O 're/O doing/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON turned/O on/O him/O in/O a/O fury/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O see/O Ser/PERSON Alliser/PERSON 's/O bloody/O hand/O ,/O that/O 's/O all/O I/O see/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O to/O shame/O me/O ,/O and/O he/O has/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Dareon/PERSON gave/O him/O a/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O stewards/O are/O fine/O for/O the/O likes/O of/O you/O and/O me/O ,/O Sam/PERSON ,/O but/O not/O for/O Lord/O Snow/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O 'm/O a/O better/O swordsman/O and/O a/O better/O rider/O than/O any/O of/O you/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON blazed/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O not/O fair/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fair/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Dareon/PERSON sneered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O girl/O was/O waiting/O for/O me/O ,/O naked/O as/O the/O day/O she/O was/O born/O ./O 
She/O pulled/O me/O through/O the/O window/O ,/O and/O you/O talk/O to/O me/O of/O fair/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O He/O walked/O off/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O There/O is/O no/O shame/O in/O being/O a/O steward/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O think/O I/O want/O to/O spend/O the/O rest/O of/O my/O life/O washing/O an/O old/O man/O 's/O smallclothes/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O old/O man/O is/O Lord/O Commander/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O be/O with/O him/O day/O and/O night/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O you/O 'll/O pour/O his/O wine/O and/O see/O that/O his/O bed/O linen/O is/O fresh/O ,/O but/O you/O 'll/O also/O take/O his/O letters/O ,/O attend/O him/O at/O meetings/O ,/O squire/O for/O him/O in/O battle/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O be/O as/O close/O to/O him/O as/O his/O shadow/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O know/O everything/O ,/O be/O a/O part/O of/O everything/O .../O and/O the/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON said/O Mormont/PERSON asked/O for/O you/O himself/O !/O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O When/O I/O was/O little/O ,/O my/O father/O used/O to/O insist/O that/O I/O attend/O him/O in/O the/O audience/O chamber/O whenever/O he/O held/O court/O ./O 
When/O he/O rode/O to/O Highgarden/LOCATION to/O bend/O his/O knee/O to/O Lord/O Tyrell/PERSON ,/O he/O made/O me/O come/O ./O 
Later/O ,/O though/O ,/O he/O started/O to/O take/O Dickon/PERSON and/O leave/O me/O at/O home/O ,/O and/O he/O no/O longer/O cared/O whether/O I/O sat/O through/O his/O audiences/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O Dickon/PERSON was/O there/O ./O 
He/O wanted/O his/O heir/O at/O his/O side/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O see/O ?/O 
To/O watch/O and/O listen/O and/O learn/O from/O all/O he/O did/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O wager/O that/O 's/O why/O Lord/O Mormont/PERSON requested/O you/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
What/O else/O could/O it/O be/O ?/O 
He/O wants/O to/O groom/O you/O for/O command/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON was/O taken/O aback/O ./O 
It/O was/O true/O ,/O Lord/O Eddard/PERSON had/O often/O made/O Robb/PERSON part/O of/O his/O councils/O back/O at/O Winterfell/LOCATION ./O 
Could/O Sam/PERSON be/O right/O ?/O 
Even/O a/O bastard/O could/O rise/O high/O in/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O they/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O never/O asked/O for/O this/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O stubbornly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O None/O of/O us/O are/O here/O for/O asking/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sam/PERSON reminded/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O And/O suddenly/O Jon/PERSON Snow/PERSON was/O ashamed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Craven/PERSON or/O not/O ,/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON had/O found/O the/O courage/O to/O accept/O his/O fate/O like/O a/O man/O ./O 
On/O the/O Wall/O ,/O a/O man/O gets/O only/O what/O he/O earns/O ,/O Benjen/PERSON Stark/PERSON had/O said/O the/O last/O night/O Jon/PERSON had/O seen/O him/O alive/O ./O 
You/O 're/O no/O ranger/O ,/O Jon/PERSON ,/O only/O a/O green/O boy/O with/O the/O smell/O of/O summer/O still/O on/O you/O ./O 
He/O 'd/O heard/O it/O said/O that/O bastards/O grow/O up/O faster/O than/O other/O children/O ;/O on/O the/O Wall/O ,/O you/O grew/O up/O or/O you/O died/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/O let/O out/O a/O deep/O sigh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O have/O the/O right/O of/O it/O ./O 
I/O was/O acting/O the/O boy/O .../O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Then/O you/O 'll/O stay/O and/O say/O your/O words/O with/O me/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O old/O gods/O will/O be/O expecting/O us/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O made/O himself/O smile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O set/O out/O late/O that/O afternoon/O ./O 
The/O Wall/O had/O no/O gates/O as/O such/O ,/O neither/O here/O at/O Castle/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION nor/O anywhere/O along/O its/O three/O hundred/O miles/O ./O 
They/O led/O their/O horses/O down/O a/O narrow/O tunnel/O cut/O through/O the/O ice/O ,/O cold/O dark/O walls/O pressing/O in/O around/O them/O as/O the/O passage/O twisted/O and/O turned/O ./O 
Three/O times/O their/O way/O was/O blocked/O by/O iron/O bars/O ,/O and/O they/O had/O to/O stop/O while/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON drew/O out/O his/O keys/O and/O unlocked/O the/O massive/O chains/O that/O secured/O them/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON could/O sense/O the/O vast/O weight/O pressing/O down/O on/O him/O as/O he/O waited/O behind/O the/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON ./O 
The/O air/O was/O colder/O than/O a/O tomb/O ,/O and/O more/O still/O ./O 
He/O felt/O a/O strange/O relief/O when/O they/O reemerged/O into/O the/O afternoon/O light/O on/O the/O north/O side/O of/O the/O Wall/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sam/PERSON blinked/O at/O the/O sudden/O glare/O and/O looked/O around/O apprehensively/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O wildlings/O .../O they/O would/O n't/O .../O they/O 'd/O never/O dare/O come/O this/O close/O to/O the/O Wall/O ./O 
Would/O they/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O They/O never/O have/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON climbed/O into/O his/O saddle/O ./O 
When/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON and/O their/O ranger/O escort/O had/O mounted/O ,/O Jon/PERSON put/O two/O fingers/O in/O his/O mouth/O and/O whistled/O ./O 
Ghost/O came/O loping/O out/O of/O the/O tunnel/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O Lord/O Steward/PERSON 's/O garron/O whickered/O and/O backed/O away/O from/O the/O direwolf/O \/O ``/O Do/O you/O mean/O to/O take/O that/O beast/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ,/O my/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
Ghost/O 's/O head/O lifted/O ./O 
He/O seemed/O to/O taste/O the/O air/O ./O 
In/O the/O blink/O of/O an/O eye/O he/O was/O off/O ,/O racing/O across/O the/O broad/O ,/O weedchoked/O field/O to/O vanish/O in/O the/O trees/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Once/O they/O had/O entered/O the/O forest/O ,/O they/O were/O in/O a/O different/O world/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O often/O hunted/O with/O his/O father/O and/O Jory/PERSON and/O his/O brother/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
He/O knew/O the/O wolfswood/O around/O Winterfell/LOCATION as/O well/O as/O any/O man/O ./O 
The/O haunted/O forest/O was/O much/O the/O same/O ,/O and/O yet/O the/O feel/O of/O it/O was/O very/O different/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Perhaps/O it/O was/O all/O in/O the/O knowing/O ./O 
They/O had/O ridden/O past/O the/O end/O of/O the/O world/O ;/O somehow/O that/O changed/O everything/O ./O 
Every/O shadow/O seemed/O darker/O ,/O every/O sound/O more/O ominous/O ./O 
The/O trees/O pressed/O close/O and/O shut/O out/O the/O light/O of/O the/O setting/O sun/O ./O 
A/O thin/O crust/O of/O snow/O cracked/O beneath/O the/O hooves/O of/O their/O horses/O ,/O with/O a/O sound/O like/O breaking/O bones/O ./O 
When/O the/O wind/O set/O the/O leaves/O to/O rustling/O ,/O it/O was/O like/O a/O chilly/O finger/O tracing/O a/O path/O up/O Jon/PERSON 's/O spine/O ./O 
The/O Wall/O was/O at/O their/O backs/O ,/O and/O only/O the/O gods/O knew/O what/O lay/O ahead/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O sun/O was/O sinking/O below/O the/O trees/O when/O they/O reached/O their/O destination/O ,/O a/O small/O clearing/O in/O the/O deep/O of/O the/O wood/O where/O nine/O weirwoods/O grew/O in/O a/O rough/O circle/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON drew/O in/O a/O breath/O ,/O and/O be/O saw/O Sam/PERSON Tarly/PERSON staring/O ./O 
Even/O in/O the/O wolfswood/O ,/O you/O never/O found/O more/O than/O two/O or/O three/O of/O the/O white/O trees/O growing/O together/O ;/O a/O grove/O of/O nine/O was/O unheard/O of/O ./O 
The/O forest/O floor/O was/O carpeted/O with/O fallen/O leaves/O ,/O bloodred/O on/O top/O ,/O black/O rot/O beneath/O ./O 
The/O wide/O smooth/O trunks/O were/O bone/O pale/O ,/O and/O nine/O faces/O stared/O inward/O ./O 
The/O dried/O sap/O that/O crusted/O in/O the/O eyes/O was/O red/O and/O hard/O as/O ruby/O ./O 
Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON commanded/O them/O to/O leave/O their/O horses/O outside/O the/O circle/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O a/O sacred/O place/O ,/O we/O will/O not/O defile/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O When/O they/O entered/O the/O grove/O ,/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON turned/O slowly/O looking/O at/O each/O face/O in/O turn/O ./O 
No/O two/O were/O quite/O alike/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O 're/O watching/O us/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O whispered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O old/O gods/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON knelt/O ,/O and/O Sam/PERSON knelt/O beside/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O said/O the/O words/O together/O ,/O as/O the/O last/O light/O faded/O in/O the/O west/O and/O grey/O day/O became/O black/O night/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Hear/O my/O words/O ,/O and/O bear/O witness/O to/O my/O vow/O ,/O \/O ''/O they/O recited/O ,/O their/O voices/O filling/O the/O twilit/O grove/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Night/O gathers/O ,/O and/O now/O my/O watch/O begins/O ./O 
It/O shall/O not/O end/O until/O my/O death/O ./O 
I/O shall/O take/O no/O wife/O ,/O hold/O no/O lands/O ,/O father/O no/O children/O ./O 
I/O shall/O wear/O no/O crowns/O and/O win/O no/O glory/O ./O 
I/O shall/O live/O and/O die/O at/O my/O post/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O sword/O in/O the/O darkness/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O watcher/O on/O the/O walls/O ./O 
I/O am/O the/O fire/O that/O burns/O against/O the/O cold/O ,/O the/O light/O that/O brings/O the/O dawn/O ,/O the/O horn/O that/O wakes/O the/O sleepers/O ,/O the/O shield/O that/O guards/O the/O realms/O of/O men/O ./O 
I/O pledge/O my/O life/O and/O honor/O to/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ,/O for/O this/O night/O and/O all/O the/O nights/O to/O come/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O woods/O fell/O silent/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O knelt/O as/O boys/O ,/O \/O ''/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON intoned/O solemnly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Rise/O now/O as/O men/O of/O the/O Night/O 's/O Watch/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON held/O out/O a/O hand/O to/O pull/O Sam/PERSON back/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
The/O rangers/O gathered/O round/O to/O offer/O smiles/O and/O congratulations/O ,/O all/O but/O the/O gnarled/O old/O forester/O Dywen/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Best/O we/O be/O starting/O back/O ,/O m/O `/O lord/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O ''/O ,/O ``/O said/O to/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Dark/O 's/O falling/O ,/O and/O there/O 's/O something/O in/O the/O smell/O o/O '/O the/O night/O that/O I/O mislike/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O And/O suddenly/O Ghost/O was/O back/O ,/O stalking/O softly/O between/O two/O weirwoods/O ./O 
White/O fur/O and/O red/O eyes/O ,/O Jon/PERSON realized/O ,/O disquieted/O ./O 
Like/O the/O trees/O .../O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O wolf/O had/O something/O in/O his/O jaws/O ./O 
Something/O black/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O 's/O he/O got/O there/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O asked/O Bowen/PERSON Marsh/PERSON ,/O frowning/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O To/O me/O ,/O Ghost/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON knelt/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bring/O it/O here/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O direwo/O If/O trotted/O to/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON heard/O Samwell/PERSON Tarly/PERSON 's/O sharp/O intake/O of/O breath/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Gods/O be/O good/O ,/O \/O ''/O Dywen/PERSON muttered/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O 's/O a/O hand/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O -RSB-/O 
