-LSB-/O ``/O ARYA/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON 's/O stitches/O were/O crooked/O again/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O frowned/O down/O at/O them/O with/O dismay/O and/O glanced/O over/O to/O where/O her/O sister/O Sansa/PERSON sat/O among/O the/O other/O girls/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON 's/O needlework/O was/O exquisite/O ./O 
Everyone/O said/O so/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Sansa/O 's/O work/O is/O as/O pretty/O as/O she/O is/O ,/O \/O ''/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON told/O their/O lady/O mother/O once/O ./O 
\/O ``/O She/O has/O such/O fine/O ,/O delicate/O hands/O ./O 
\/O ''/O When/O Lady/PERSON Catelyn/PERSON had/O asked/O about/O Arya/PERSON ,/O the/O septa/O had/O sniffed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON has/O the/O hands/O of/O a/O blacksmith/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON glanced/O furtively/O across/O the/O room/O ,/O worried/O that/O Septa/O Mordane/O might/O have/O read/O her/O thoughts/O ,/O but/O the/O septa/O was/O paying/O her/O no/O attention/O today/O ./O 
She/O was/O sitting/O with/O the/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON ,/O all/O smiles/O and/O admiration/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O often/O that/O the/O septa/O was/O privileged/O to/O instruct/O a/O royal/O princess/O in/O the/O womanly/O arts/O ,/O as/O she/O had/O said/O when/O the/O queen/O brought/O Myrcella/PERSON to/O join/O them/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON thought/O that/O Myrcella/PERSON 's/O stitches/O looked/O a/O little/O crooked/O too/O ,/O but/O you/O would/O never/O know/O it/O from/O the/O way/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON was/O cooing/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O studied/O her/O own/O work/O again/O ,/O looking/O for/O some/O way/O to/O salvage/O it/O ,/O then/O sighed/O and/O put/O down/O the/O needle/O ./O 
She/O looked/O glumly/O at/O her/O sister/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O chatting/O away/O happily/O as/O she/O worked/O ./O 
Beth/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON 's/O little/O girl/O ,/O was/O sitting/O by/O her/O feet/O ,/O listening/O to/O every/O word/O she/O said/O ,/O and/O Jeyne/PERSON Poole/PERSON was/O leaning/O over/O to/O whisper/O something/O in/O her/O ear/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O talking/O about/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON asked/O suddenly/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O startled/O look/O ,/O then/O giggled/O ./O 
Sansa/O looked/O abashed/O ./O 
Beth/PERSON blushed/O ./O 
No/O one/O answered/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Tell/O me/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jeyne/PERSON glanced/O over/O to/O make/O certain/O that/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON was/O not/O listening/O ./O 
Myrcella/PERSON said/O something/O then/O ,/O and/O the/O septa/O laughed/O along/O with/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O ladies/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O We/O were/O talking/O about/O the/O prince/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON said/O ,/O her/O voice/O soft/O as/O a/O kiss/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON knew/O which/O prince/O she/O meant/O :/O Joffrey/PERSON ,/O of/O course/O ./O 
The/O tall/O ,/O handsome/O one/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON got/O to/O sit/O with/O him/O at/O the/O feast/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O to/O sit/O with/O the/O little/O fat/O one/O ./O 
Naturally/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON likes/O your/O sister/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jeyne/PERSON whispered/O ,/O proud/O as/O if/O she/O had/O something/O to/O do/O with/O it/O ./O 
She/O was/O the/O daughter/O of/O WinterfeiPs/O steward/O and/O Sansa/PERSON 's/O dearest/O friend/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O told/O her/O she/O was/O very/O beautiful/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O going/O to/O marry/O her/O ,/O \/O ''/O little/O Beth/PERSON said/O dreamily/O ,/O hugging/O herself/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Then/O Sansa/O will/O be/O queen/O of/O all/O the/O realm/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Sansa/O had/O the/O grace/O to/O blush/O ./O 
She/O blushed/O prettily/O ./O 
She/O did/O everything/O prettily/O ,/O Arya/PERSON thought/O with/O dull/O resentment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Beth/PERSON ,/O you/O should/O n't/O make/O up/O stories/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/PERSON corrected/O the/O younger/O girl/O ,/O gently/O stroking/O her/O hair/O to/O take/O the/O harshness/O out/O of/O her/O words/O ./O 
She/O looked/O at/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O did/O you/O think/O of/O Prince/O Joff/PERSON ,/O sister/O ?/O 
He/O 's/O very/O gallant/O ,/O do/O n't/O you/O think/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Jon/PERSON says/O he/O looks/O like/O a/O girl/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O sighed/O as/O she/O stitched/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Poor/O Jon/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O gets/O jealous/O because/O he/O 's/O a/O bastard/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O He/O 's/O our/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON said/O ,/O much/O too/O loudly/O ./O 
Her/O voice/O cut/O through/O the/O afternoon/O quiet/O of/O the/O tower/O room/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON raised/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O bony/O face/O ,/O sharp/O eyes/O ,/O and/O a/O thin/O lipless/O mouth/O made/O for/O frowning/O ./O 
It/O was/O frowning/O now/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O talking/O about/O ,/O children/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Our/O half/O brother/O ,/O \/O ''/O Sansa/O corrected/O ,/O soft/O and/O precise/O ./O 
She/O smiled/O for/O the/O septa/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON and/O I/O were/O remarking/O on/O how/O pleased/O we/O were/O to/O have/O the/O princess/O with/O us/O today/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON nodded/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Indeed/O ./O 
A/O great/O honor/O for/O us/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON smiled/O uncertainly/O at/O the/O compliment/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O why/O are/O n't/O you/O at/O work/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O septa/O asked/O ./O 
She/O rose/O to/O her/O feet/O ,/O starched/O skirts/O rustling/O as/O she/O started/O across/O the/O room/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O see/O your/O stitches/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON wanted/O to/O scream/O ./O 
It/O was/O just/O like/O Sansa/O to/O go/O and/O attract/O the/O septa/O 's/O attention/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Here/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ,/O surrendering/O up/O her/O work/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O The/O septa/O examined/O the/O fabric/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O Arya/PERSON ,/O Arya/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O will/O not/O do/O ./O 
This/O will/O not/O do/O at/O all/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Everyone/O was/O looking/O at/O her/O ./O 
It/O was/O too/O much/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O too/O well/O bred/O to/O smile/O at/O her/O sister/O 's/O disgrace/O ,/O but/O Jeyne/PERSON was/O smirking/O on/O her/O behalf/O ./O 
Even/O Princess/O Myrcella/PERSON looked/O sorry/O for/O her/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON felt/O tears/O filling/O her/O eyes/O ./O 
She/O pushed/O herself/O out/O of/O her/O chair/O and/O bolted/O for/O the/O door/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON called/O after/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Arya/PERSON ,/O come/O back/O here/O !/O 
Do/O n't/O you/O take/O another/O step/O !/O 
Your/O lady/O mother/O will/O hear/O of/O this/O ./O 
In/O front/O of/O our/O royal/O princess/O too/O !/O 
You/O 'll/O shame/O us/O all/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON stopped/O at/O the/O door/O and/O turned/O back/O ,/O biting/O her/O lip/O ./O 
The/O tears/O were/O running/O down/O her/O cheeks/O now/O ./O 
She/O managed/O a/O stiff/O little/O bow/O to/O Myrcella/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O By/O your/O leave/O ,/O my/O lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Myrcella/PERSON blinked/O at/O her/O and/O looked/O to/O her/O ladies/O for/O guidance/O ./O 
But/O if/O she/O was/O uncertain/O ,/O Septa/PERSON Mordane/PERSON was/O not/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Just/O where/O do/O you/O think/O you/O are/O going/O ,/O Arya/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O septa/O demanded/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON glared/O at/O her/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O have/O to/O go/O shoe/O a/O horse/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O sweetly/O ,/O taking/O a/O brief/O satisfaction/O in/O the/O shock/O on/O the/O septa/O 's/O face/O ./O 
Then/O she/O whirled/O and/O made/O her/O exit/O ,/O running/O down/O the/O steps/O as/O fast/O as/O her/O feet/O would/O take/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O n't/O fair/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O everything/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON was/O two/O years/O older/O ;/O maybe/O by/O the/O time/O Arya/PERSON had/O been/O born/O ,/O there/O had/O been/O nothing/O left/O ./O 
Often/O it/O felt/O that/O way/O ./O 
Sansa/O could/O sew/O and/O dance/O and/O sing/O ./O 
She/O wrote/O poetry/O ./O 
She/O knew/O how/O to/O dress/O ./O 
She/O played/O the/O high/O harp/O and/O the/O bells/O ./O 
Worse/O ,/O she/O was/O beautiful/O ./O 
Sansa/PERSON had/O gotten/O their/O mother/O 's/O fine/O high/O cheekbones/O and/O the/O thick/O auburn/O hair/O of/O the/O Tullys/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON took/O after/O their/O lord/O father/O ./O 
Her/O hair/O was/O a/O lusterless/O brown/O ,/O and/O her/O face/O was/O long/O and/O solemn/O ./O 
Jeyne/PERSON used/O to/O call/O her/O Arya/PERSON Horseface/PERSON ,/O and/O neigh/O whenever/O she/O came/O near/O ./O 
It/O hurt/O that/O the/O one/O thing/O Arya/PERSON could/O do/O better/O than/O her/O sister/O was/O ride/O a/O horse/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O that/O and/O manage/O a/O household/O ./O 
Sansa/O had/O never/O had/O much/O of/O a/O head/O for/O figures/O ./O 
If/O she/O did/O marry/O Prince/PERSON Joff/PERSON ,/O Arya/PERSON hoped/O for/O his/O sake/O that/O he/O had/O a/O good/O steward/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Nymeria/O was/O waiting/O for/O her/O in/O the/O guardroom/O at/O the/O base/O of/O the/O stairs/O ./O 
She/O bounded/O to/O her/O feet/O as/O soon/O as/O she/O caught/O sight/O of/O Arya/PERSON ./O 
Arya/PERSON grinned/O ./O 
The/O wolf/O pup/O loved/O her/O ,/O even/O if/O no/O one/O else/O did/O ./O 
They/O went/O everywhere/O together/O ,/O and/O Nymeria/PERSON slept/O in/O her/O room/O ,/O at/O the/O foot/O of/O her/O bed/O ./O 
If/O Mother/PERSON had/O not/O forbidden/O it/O ,/O Arya/PERSON would/O gladly/O have/O taken/O the/O wolf/O with/O her/O to/O needlework/O ./O 
Let/O Septa/O Mordane/O complain/O about/O her/O stitches/O then/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Nymeria/PERSON nipped/O eagerly/O at/O her/O hand/O as/O Arya/PERSON untied/O her/O ./O 
She/O had/O yellow/O eyes/O ./O 
When/O they/O caught/O the/O sunlight/O ,/O they/O gleamed/O like/O two/O golden/O coins/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON had/O named/O her/O after/O the/O warrior/O queen/O of/O the/O Rhoyne/PERSON ,/O who/O had/O led/O her/O people/O across/O the/O narrow/O sea/O ./O 
That/O had/O been/O a/O great/O scandal/O too/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Sansa/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O had/O named/O her/O pup/O \/O ``/O Lady/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON made/O a/O face/O and/O hugged/O the/O wolfling/O tight/O ./O 
Nymeria/PERSON licked/O her/O ear/O ,/O and/O she/O giggled/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O By/O now/O Septa/ORGANIZATION Mordane/ORGANIZATION would/O certainly/O have/O sent/O word/O to/O her/O lady/O mother/O ./O 
If/O she/O went/O to/O her/O room/O ,/O they/O would/O find/O her/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON did/O not/O care/O to/O be/O found/O ./O 
She/O had/O a/O better/O notion/O ./O 
The/O boys/O were/O at/O practice/O in/O the/O yard/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O see/O Robb/PERSON put/O gallant/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON flat/O on/O his/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O whispered/O to/O Nymeria/LOCATION ./O 
She/O got/O up/O and/O ran/O ,/O the/O wolf/O coming/O hard/O at/O her/O heels/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O window/O in/O the/O covered/O bridge/O between/O the/O armory/O and/O the/O Great/O Keep/O where/O you/O had/O a/O view/O of/O the/O whole/O yard/O ./O 
That/O was/O where/O they/O headed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O They/O arrived/O ,/O flushed/O and/O breathless/O ,/O to/O find/O Jon/PERSON seated/O on/O the/O sill/O ,/O one/O leg/O drawn/O up/O languidly/O to/O his/O chin/O ./O 
He/O was/O watching/O the/O action/O ,/O so/O absorbed/O that/O he/O seemed/O unaware/O of/O her/O approach/O until/O his/O white/O wolf/O moved/O to/O meet/O them/O ./O 
Nymeria/O stalked/O closer/O on/O wary/O feet/O ./O 
Ghost/O ,/O already/O larger/O than/O his/O litter/O mates/O ,/O smelled/O her/O ,/O gave/O her/O ear/O a/O careful/O nip/O ,/O and/O settled/O back/O down/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON gave/O her/O a/O curious/O look/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Should/O n't/O you/O be/O working/O on/O your/O stitches/O ,/O little/O sister/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON made/O a/O face/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O wanted/O to/O see/O them/O fight/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O He/O smiled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O here/O ,/O then/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON climbed/O up/O on/O the/O window/O and/O sat/O beside/O him/O ,/O to/O a/O chorus/O of/O thuds/O and/O grunts/O from/O the/O yard/O below/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O To/O her/O disappointment/O ,/O it/O was/O the/O younger/O boys/O drilling/O ./O 
Bran/O was/O so/O heavily/O padded/O he/O looked/O as/O though/O he/O had/O belted/O on/O a/O featherbed/O ,/O and/O Prince/PERSON Tommen/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O plump/O to/O begin/O with/O ,/O seemed/O positively/O round/O ./O 
They/O were/O huffing/O and/O puffing/O and/O hitting/O at/O each/O other/O with/O padded/O wooden/O swords/O under/O the/O watchful/O eye/O of/O old/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON Cassel/PERSON ,/O the/O master-at-arms/O ,/O a/O great/O stout/O keg/O of/O a/O man/O with/O magnificent/O white/O cheek/O whiskers/O ./O 
A/O dozen/O spectators/O ,/O man/O and/O boy/O ,/O were/O calling/O out/O encouragement/O ,/O Robb/PERSON 's/O voice/O the/O loudest/O among/O them/O ./O 
She/O spotted/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON beside/O him/O ,/O his/O black/O doublet/O emblazoned/O with/O the/O golden/O kraken/O of/O his/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O look/O of/O wry/O contempt/O on/O his/O face/O ./O 
Both/O of/O the/O combatants/O were/O staggering/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON judged/O that/O they/O had/O been/O at/O it/O awhile/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O shade/O more/O exhausting/O than/O needlework/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON observed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O shade/O more/O fun/O than/O needlework/O ,/O \/O ''/O Arya/PERSON gave/O back/O at/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON grinned/O ,/O reached/O over/O ,/O and/O messed/O up/O her/O hair/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON flushed/O ./O 
They/O had/O always/O been/O close/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON had/O their/O father/O 's/O face/O ,/O as/O she/O did/O ./O 
They/O were/O the/O only/O ones/O ./O 
Robb/PERSON and/O Sansa/PERSON and/O Bran/O and/O even/O little/O Rickon/PERSON all/O took/O after/O the/O Tullys/O ,/O with/O easy/O smiles/O and/O fire/O in/O their/O hair/O ./O 
When/O Arya/PERSON had/O been/O little/O ,/O she/O had/O been/O afraid/O that/O meant/O that/O she/O was/O a/O bastard/O too/O ./O 
It/O been/O Jon/PERSON she/O had/O gone/O to/O in/O her/O fear/O ,/O and/O Jon/PERSON who/O had/O reassured/O her/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Why/O are/O n't/O you/O down/O in/O the/O yard/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON asked/O him/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O He/O gave/O her/O a/O half/O smile/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Bastards/O are/O not/O allowed/O to/O damage/O young/O princes/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Any/O bruises/O they/O take/O in/O the/O practice/O yard/O must/O come/O from/O trueborn/O swords/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Oh/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON felt/O abashed/O ./O 
She/O should/O have/O realized/O ./O 
For/O the/O second/O time/O today/O ,/O Arya/PERSON reflected/O that/O life/O was/O not/O fair/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O watched/O her/O little/O brother/O whack/O at/O Tommen/LOCATION ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O could/O do/O just/O as/O good/O as/O Bran/O ,/O \/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O He/O 's/O only/O seven/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O nine/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON looked/O her/O over/O with/O all/O his/O fourteen-year-old/O wisdom/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O too/O skinny/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O took/O her/O arm/O to/O feel/O her/O muscle/O ./O 
Then/O he/O sighed/O and/O shook/O his/O head/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O doubt/O you/O could/O even/O lift/O a/O longsword/O ,/O little/O sister/O ,/O never/O mind/O swing/O one/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON snatched/O back/O her/O arm/O and/O glared/O at/O him/O ./O 
Jon/PERSON messed/O up/O her/O hair/O again/O ./O 
They/O watched/O Bran/O and/O Tommen/O circle/O each/O other/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O see/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON ?/O 
\/O ''/O Jon/PERSON asked/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O She/O had/O n't/O ,/O not/O at/O first/O glance/O ,/O but/O when/O she/O looked/O again/O she/O found/O him/O to/O the/O back/O ,/O under/O the/O shade/O of/O the/O high/O stone/O wall/O ./O 
He/O was/O surrounded/O by/O men/O she/O did/O not/O recognize/O ,/O young/O squires/O in/O the/O livery/O of/O Lannister/LOCATION and/O Baratheon/LOCATION ,/O strangers/O all/O ./O 
There/O were/O a/O few/O older/O men/O among/O them/O ;/O knights/O ,/O she/O surmised/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Look/O at/O the/O arms/O on/O his/O surcoat/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON suggested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON looked/O ./O 
An/O ornate/O shield/O had/O been/O embroidered/O on/O the/O prince/O 's/O padded/O surcoat/O ./O 
No/O doubt/O the/O needlework/O was/O exquisite/O ./O 
The/O arms/O were/O divided/O down/O the/O middle/O ;/O on/O one/O side/O was/O the/O crowned/O stag/O of/O the/O royal/O House/ORGANIZATION ,/O on/O the/O other/O the/O lion/O of/O Lannister/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O Lannisters/O are/O proud/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON observed/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'd/O think/O the/O royal/O sigil/O would/O be/O sufficient/O ,/O but/O no/O ./O 
He/O makes/O his/O mother/O 's/O House/ORGANIZATION equal/O in/O honor/O to/O the/O king/O 's/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O The/O woman/O is/O important/O too/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Arya/PERSON protested/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON chuckled/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Perhaps/O you/O should/O do/O the/O same/O thing/O ,/O little/O sister/O ./O 
Wed/O Tully/O to/O Stark/O in/O your/O arms/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O A/O wolf/O with/O a/O fish/O in/O its/O mouth/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O It/O made/O her/O laugh/O ./O 
\/O ``/O That/O would/O look/O silly/O ./O 
Besides/O ,/O if/O a/O girl/O ca/O n't/O fight/O ,/O why/O should/O she/O have/O a/O coat/O of/O arms/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Girls/O get/O the/O arms/O but/O not/O the/O swords/O ./O 
Bastards/O get/O the/O swords/O but/O not/O the/O arms/O ./O 
I/O did/O not/O make/O the/O rules/O ,/O little/O sister/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O There/O was/O a/O shout/O from/O the/O courtyard/O below/O ./O 
Prince/O Tommen/PERSON was/O rolling/O in/O the/O dust/O ,/O trying/O to/O get/O up/O and/O failing/O ./O 
All/O the/O padding/O made/O him/O look/O like/O a/O turtle/O on/O its/O back/O ./O 
Bran/O was/O standing/O over/O him/O with/O upraised/O wooden/O sword/O ,/O ready/O to/O whack/O him/O again/O once/O he/O regained/O his/O feet/O ./O 
The/O men/O began/O to/O laugh/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Enough/O !/O 
\/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON called/O out/O ./O 
He/O gave/O the/O prince/O a/O hand/O and/O yanked/O him/O back/O to/O his/O feet/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Well/O fought/O ./O 
Lew/PERSON ,/O Donnis/PERSON ,/O help/O them/O out/O of/O their/O armor/O ./O 
\/O ''/O He/O looked/O around/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Prince/PERSON Joffrey/PERSON ,/O Robb/PERSON ,/O will/O you/O go/O another/O round/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON ,/O already/O sweaty/O from/O a/O previous/O bout/O ,/O moved/O forward/O eagerly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Gladly/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON moved/O into/O the/O sunlight/O in/O response/O to/O Rodrik/PERSON 's/O summons/O ./O 
His/O hair/O shone/O like/O spun/O gold/O ./O 
He/O looked/O bored/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O a/O game/O for/O children/O ,/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON gave/O a/O sudden/O bark/O of/O laughter/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O are/O children/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O derisively/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Robb/PERSON may/O be/O a/O child/O ,/O \/O ''/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O am/O a/O prince/O ./O 
And/O I/O grow/O tired/O of/O swatting/O at/O Starks/PERSON with/O a/O play/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O You/O got/O more/O swats/O than/O you/O gave/O ,/O Joff/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Are/O you/O afraid/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Prince/O Joffrey/PERSON looked/O at/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O terrified/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 're/O so/O much/O older/O ./O 
\/O ''/O Some/O of/O the/O Lannister/O men/O laughed/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON looked/O down/O on/O the/O scene/O with/O a/O frown/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON is/O truly/O a/O little/O shit/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O told/O Arya/PERSON ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tugged/O thoughtfully/O at/O his/O white/O whiskers/O ./O 
\/O ``/O What/O are/O you/O suggesting/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O he/O asked/O the/O prince/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Live/O steel/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Done/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON shot/O back/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O 'll/O be/O sorry/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O master-at-arms/O put/O a/O hand/O on/O Robb/PERSON 's/O shoulder/O to/O quiet/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Live/O steel/O is/O too/O dangerous/O ./O 
I/O will/O permit/O you/O tourney/O swords/O ,/O with/O blunted/O edges/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON said/O nothing/O ,/O but/O a/O man/O strange/O to/O Arya/PERSON ,/O a/O tall/O knight/O with/O black/O hair/O and/O burn/O scars/O on/O his/O face/O ,/O pushed/O forward/O in/O front/O of/O the/O prince/O ./O 
\/O ``/O This/O is/O your/O prince/O ./O 
Who/O are/O you/O to/O tell/O him/O he/O may/O not/O have/O an/O edge/O on/O his/O sword/O ,/O ser/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Master-at-arms/O of/O Winterfell/O ,/O Clegane/PERSON ,/O and/O you/O would/O do/O well/O not/O to/O forget/O it/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Are/O you/O training/O women/O here/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O the/O burned/O man/O wanted/O to/O know/O ./O 
He/O was/O muscled/O like/O a/O bull/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O am/O training/O knights/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O pointedly/O ./O 
\/O ``/O They/O will/O have/O steel/O when/O they/O are/O ready/O ./O 
When/O they/O are/O of/O an/O age/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O The/O burned/O man/O looked/O at/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O How/O old/O are/O you/O ,/O boy/O ?/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Fourteen/O ,/O \/O ''/O Robb/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ''/O \/O ``/O I/O killed/O a/O man/O at/O twelve/O ./O 
You/O can/O be/O sure/O it/O was/O not/O with/O a/O blunt/O sword/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON could/O see/O Robb/PERSON bristle/O ./O 
His/O pride/O was/O wounded/O ./O 
He/O turned/O on/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON ./O 
\/O ``/O Let/O me/O do/O it/O ./O 
I/O can/O beat/O him/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Beat/O him/O with/O a/O tourney/O blade/O ,/O then/O ,/O \/O ''/O Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON said/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/PERSON shrugged/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O and/O see/O me/O when/O you/O 're/O older/O ,/O Stark/O ./O 
If/O you/O 're/O not/O too/O old/O ./O 
\/O ''/O There/O was/O laughter/O from/O the/O Lannister/O men/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Robb/PERSON 's/O curses/O rang/O through/O the/O yard/O ./O 
Arya/PERSON covered/O her/O mouth/O in/O shock/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON Greyjoy/PERSON seized/O Robb/PERSON 's/O arm/O to/O keep/O him/O away/O from/O the/O prince/O ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON tugged/O at/O his/O whiskers/O in/O dismay/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Joffrey/O feigned/O a/O yawn/O and/O turned/O to/O his/O younger/O brother/O ./O 
\/O ``/O Come/O ,/O Tommen/PERSON ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O hour/O of/O play/O is/O done/O ./O 
Leave/O the/O children/O to/O their/O frolics/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O That/O brought/O more/O laughter/O from/O the/O Lannisters/O ,/O more/O curses/O from/O Robb/PERSON ./O 
Ser/PERSON Rodrik/PERSON '/O s/O face/O was/O beet-red/O with/O fury/O under/O the/O white/O of/O his/O whiskers/O ./O 
Theon/PERSON kept/O Robb/PERSON locked/O in/O an/O iron/O grip/O until/O the/O princes/O and/O their/O party/O were/O safely/O away/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Jon/PERSON watched/O them/O leave/O ,/O and/O Arya/PERSON watched/O Jon/PERSON ./O 
His/O face/O had/O grown/O as/O still/O as/O the/O pool/O at/O the/O heart/O of/O the/O godswood/O ./O 
Finally/O he/O climbed/O down/O off/O the/O window/O ./O 
\/O ``/O The/O show/O is/O done/O ,/O \/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O bent/O to/O scratch/O Ghost/O behind/O the/O ears/O ./O 
The/O white/O wolf/O rose/O and/O rubbed/O against/O him/O ./O 
\/O ``/O You/O had/O best/O run/O back/O to/O your/O room/O ,/O little/O sister/O ./O 
Septa/O Mordane/O will/O surely/O be/O lurking/O ./O 
The/O longer/O you/O hide/O ,/O the/O sterner/O the/O penance/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O be/O sewing/O all/O through/O winter/O ./O 
When/O the/O spring/O thaw/O comes/O ,/O they/O will/O find/O your/O body/O with/O a/O needle/O still/O locked/O tight/O between/O your/O frozen/O fingers/O ./O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ``/O Arya/PERSON did/O n't/O think/O it/O was/O funny/O ./O 
\/O ``/O I/O hate/O needlework/O !/O 
\/O ''/O she/O said/O with/O passion/O ./O 
\/O ``/O It/O 's/O not/O fair/O !/O 
\/O ''/O ''/O ,/O ''/O \/O ``/O Nothing/O is/O fair/O ,/O \/O ''/O Jon/PERSON said/O ./O 
He/O messed/O up/O her/O hair/O again/O and/O walked/O away/O from/O her/O ,/O Ghost/O moving/O silently/O beside/O him/O ./O 
Nymeria/PERSON started/O to/O follow/O too/O ,/O then/O stopped/O and/O came/O back/O when/O she/O saw/O that/O Arya/PERSON was/O not/O coming/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O Reluctantly/O she/O turned/O in/O the/O other/O direction/O ./O ''/O 
,/O ``/O It/O was/O worse/O than/O Jon/PERSON had/O thought/O ./O 
It/O was/O n't/O Septa/O Mordane/O waiting/O in/O her/O room/O ./O 
It/O was/O Septa/O Mordane/PERSON and/O her/O mother/O ./O ''/O -RSB-/O 
